Went out to dinner
the other night.
Check came at the end
of the meal, as it always does.
Never liked the "check
at the end of the meal" system,
because money's
a very different thing
before and after you eat.
Before you eat,
money has no value.
You don't care about money
when you're hungry.
You sit down in a restaurant
and you're like the ruler
of an empire--
More drinks!
Appetizers!
Quickly, quickly.
It will be the greatest meal
of our lives.
Then after the meal, you know,
you got the pants open,
you got the napkins destroyed,
cigarette butt
in the mashed potatoes.
Then the check comes
at that moment.
People are always upset,
you know.
They're mystified by the check.
They're...
"What is this?
How could this be?"
They start passing it
around the table.
"Does this look right to you?
"We're not hungry now.
Why are we buying
all this food?"
Well, I think Superman
probably has
a very good sense of humor.
I never heard him say
anything really funny.
But it's common sense.
He's got super strength,
super speed.
I'm sure he's got super humor.
You'd think that, but...
either you're born with
a sense of humor or you're not.
It's not gonna change.
Even if you go from
the red sun of Krypton
all the way
to the yellow sun
of the Earth...
Ehh...
Why?
Why would that one area
of his mind
not be affected
by the yellow sun of the Earth?
I don't know.
But he ain't funny.
Hi. I know, I know.
I'm sorry I'm late.
No problem.
Whew.
I dropped a grape.
Pardon?
I dropped a grape
in the kitchen,
and it disappeared.
I couldn't find it.
I was literally
on my knees for 10 minutes
looking for
this stupid grape.
I have no idea
where it went.
[SNIFFS]
Were you crying? I mean,
it's just a grape.
You'll find it.
No. I'm just getting over
an allergy attack.
This guy I'm going out with--
Robert.
Yes. Thank you.
He has two cats,
and I'm allergic to them.
You know, I finally meet
a normal man,
and I can't even go
into his apartment, you know?
And of course my apartment
is The Actors' Studio,
so we can't go there.
It's really causing
a lot of problems, you know?
He won't even go away
for the weekend
because of these cats.
Guys with cats...
I don't know.
I've been thinking
about asking this girl
I'm seeing--
Vanessa?
Vanessa. Thank you.
I've been thinking
about asking her
to go away
for a couple days.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
I'd have to advise against that.
What do you know this woman,
a month?
You're gonna be with her
for 72 hours.
That's a dating decathlon.
Hey, why don't you
take her
to that place in Vermont
I was telling you about?
You know,
that really charming place
with separate faucets
for the hot and cold.
She'll love it.
That's exquisite.
Listen, if it's not
too much trouble,
could you pass me
that paper over there?
Just the business
section is good.
You'd better
find that grape
before it mutates
into another
life form.
[CHUCKLES]
There was once
a mutant grape
that terrorized
an entire town
in the Texas panhandle.
They brought in the Army.
Nobody could stop it.
Apparently,
it had a pit of steel.
Up again.
This is incredible.
I'm-- I'm getting it.
You're getting what?
A stock.
What stock?
Did you ever meet
my friend, Simons?
Maybe.
He know this guy, Wilkenson.
He made a fortune
in the stock market.
Now he's got some new thing,
you know, it's supposed
to be a big merger.
I wasn't even supposed
to say anything.
You guys should think
about doing this too.
How high is it
supposed to go?
I don't know, but Simons said
that if I wanted
to get involved,
that Wilkenson would tell me
the exact right minute to sell.
You want to do it?
Boy, I don't know.
I'd do it, but I don't
have any money.
What kind of
company is it?
It's called Centrax.
They've got
some new kind of new technique
for televising
opera.
Televising opera?
Some sort of electronic thingy.
Well, how much
are you gonna invest?
Five thousand.
Ten. Ten thousand.
Boy.
Come on.
Wilkenson's got millions
invested in this stock.
It's gone up three points
since I've been watching it.
What if I lose it?
Come on.
Go for 2500.
We'll do it together.
Come on, come on.
We're in it
together.
All right, 2500.
That's it.
Yeah, can I take
your order?
I will check
to the raiser.
My bet? All right.
I'll open with...
a tuna sandwich.
Tuna?
Oh, the dolphin thing?
They're dying
in the nets.
You know, the whole
concept of lunch
is based on tuna.
But, Jerry,
can't you incorporate
one unselfish act
in your daily routine?
Hey, when I'm driving,
I let people in
ahead of me
all the time.
I'm always waving
everybody in.
Go ahead, go ahead,
go ahead.
All right, all right,
I'll have the chicken salad.
Um, and I'm gonna have
an English muffin
with margarine
on the side
and a cup of coffee.
Okay,
what about you?
I'll have the tuna.
I have to say,
those people talking behind us
really ruined that movie for me.
Why didn't you do something?
What do you want me to do?
I gave the guy the half turn...
Then I gave him the full turn
with the eye roll...
I mean, beyond that,
I'm risking a punch
in the mouth.
Excuse me,
do you have these in the puffs?
No puffs,
just flakes.
Have you thought any more
about that trip?
Yeah, I've been
thinking about it.
You know, my friend told me
about this great place
in Vermont.
I don't know.
I just worry about
trips like this.
It's a lot
of pressure.
It's great.
It speeds up the intimacy level.
It's like putting
the relationship
in a time compressor.
Where we would be
six months from now,
we accomplish in three days.
Oh... so you want
to move our relationship
into phase two.
Exactly.
I love phase two.
Extra toothbrushes,
increased phone call frequency,
walking around naked.
You know,
the presents get a lot better
in phase two.
Really?
Can we go fishing
up there?
Yeah, we can fish.
What, blues, carp...marlin?
They have marlin in Vermont?
Oh, big fighting marlin.
Jerry, the stock
is the same
as when you checked it
earlier.
There are no changes
after the market
closes.
The stock
is still down.
I know,
but this is a different paper.
I thought maybe they have
different...sources.
[IMITATES CAR ENGINE]
Is that my paper?
Bad news, my friend.
What? What news?
Centrax.
Oh, come on, it's down again?
Two and a half points.
Oh, I can't
believe it.
Let me see that.
That's four and a half points
in three days.
That's almost half my money.
Hey, I told you.
Yeah, you told me.
It's all manipulated
with junk bonds.
You can't win.
H...
There's one thing
I don't understand.
Why does it please you?
George Costanza, please.
I'm just telling you
to get rid of that stock now!
George, what's going on?
Sell it!
Just say, "I'm selling."
Well, where is the guy?
Nothing?
Almost half my money
is gone.
Well, call me
right back.
Nobody can reach Wilkenson.
He hasn't been home
or in his office
in the past three days.
You know, I can't believe
you put your money
in that Centrax.
You could have invested
in my roll-out tie dispenser.
The roll-out tie dispenser...
What was that one?
Okay, you're in a restaurant.
You've got a very big meeting
coming up.
Okay.
Oh, man,
you've got mustard on your tie.
Oh, no.
You just...ksh,
tear it off,
and...vvvvt, you've got
a new one right here, huh?
And then...you're gone.
You're gone, all right.
Hey, where are you going?
You gonna take a trip?
The-- With the map...
Yeah, I'm going to Vermont
with Vanessa
for a few days.
Hey, can I use your place?
I've got a bunch of friends
coming over this weekend.
What friends?
Well,
it's just some people I met
at a rock concert.
Do you mind
if they use your bed?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Because they're
really good people, Jerry.
I'm telling you, you know,
they're anarchists.
They're-- They're--
They're huge.
Yeah.
George, what?
You're kidding.
Well, what's wrong?
So, what are we
gonna do?
Great. All right,
I'll speak to you later.
Wilkenson, the guy
who's supposed
to tell us
when to sell
the stock,
he's in the hospital.
JERRY:
You don't know what's wrong with him?
GEORGE: All Simons
was able to find out
is that he's
in the hospital.
Okay, fine.
Has Simons been in touch
with him?
Of course he's been
in touch with him.
He left two messages.
He...just hasn't heard
back yet, that's all.
Well, this is it. I'm selling.
All right, just-- Just give it
a little more time.
I never should have
gotten involved in this.
I'm a nervous wreck.
I'm not cut out for investing.
All right, that's it.
I'm gonna go down there.
Where?
To the hospital.
The hospital?
I'm gonna find out
what's going on, all right?
Are you nuts?
You don't even know the guy.
So what?
I'll start talking to him,
you know, casual.
I'll work my way around to it.
What if he's in an iron lung
or something?
What are you gonna do?
How you feeling, Mr. Wilkenson?
[IMITATES STEAM HISSING]
By the way,
what's happening with Centrax?
Maybe he's there resting.
Who goes to a hospital to rest?
What are you, a doctor?
Okay, fine, fine.
When are you going down there?
Today,
I'm going today.
Just don't do
anything
until you hear
from me.
All right.
Boy,
I have to get to a bathroom.
May I help you?
Yeah, I picked up
this shirt here yesterday.
It's completely shrunk.
There's absolutely no way
I can wear it.
When did you bring it in?
What's the difference?
Look at it. Do you see
the size of this shirt?
You got a receipt?
I can't find the receipt.
You should get
the receipt.
Look, forget about
the receipt, all right?
Even if I had the receipt,
look at it, it's a hand puppet.
What am I gonna do with this?
Yes, but how do I know
we did the shirt?
What do you think?
This is a little scam I have?
I take this tiny shirt
all over the city,
conning dry cleaners
out of money?
In fact, forget the money.
I don't even want the money.
I just once would like
to hear a dry cleaner admit
that something was their fault.
That's what I want.
I want an admission of guilt.
Maybe you asked
for it to be washed.
No, dry-cleaned.
Let me explain to you
something, okay?
With certain types
of fabrics,
different chemicals
can react, causing--
You shrunk it.
You know you shrunk it.
Just tell me
you shrunk it.
I shrunk it.
I think the only reason
we go to the dry cleaner
is so I can say
to the dry cleaner,
"Well...it's ruined,"
and of course,
the dry cleaner can respond,
"It's not our fault.
We're not responsible.
We just ruin the clothes.
That ends our legal obligation."
See, the whole problem
with dry cleaning
is that we all believe
that this is actually possible.
Right?
They're cleaning our clothes,
but they're not getting
anything wet.
It's all dry.
I know there's got to be
some liquids back there,
some fluids that they're using.
There's no such thing
as dry cleaning.
When you get something
on your shirt--
Ever get something on your shirt
and try and get it off
like that?
That's dry cleaning.
I don't think
that's what they're doing
back there.
They don't have 80 guys going,
"Come on, hurry up.
There's a lot of shirts today."
[ELAINE SNEEZES]
JERRY:
Bless you.
Thank you.
What evidence is there
that cats are so smart
anyway, huh?
What do they do?
Because they're clean?
I'm sorry.
My uncle Pete showers
four times a day,
and he can't count to 10,
so don't give me hygiene.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know,
I can't think of any solution...
Unless, of course,
they should meet
with some unfortunate accident.
What do you think
a hit man would charge
to rub out a couple of cats?
Well,
it couldn't be too expensive.
Thirteen, 14 bucks a cat?
What do you think, Jerry?
You want to make 28 bucks?
I'm no cat killer.
How about...
we go over there
right now,
and we shave them?
I'd really like to go, Elaine,
but...George is coming back
from the hospital,
I've got to wait for him.
But otherwise,
I would definitely go.
He actually went
to the hospital?
Yeah.
Oh, man, he's nuts.
Yeah, he's nuts.
You want to bump off
a couple of cats.
I know, I know. It's down again.
How much you down
altogether?
I don't know, $1500.
Wow.
You don't have to say "wow."
I know it's "wow."
And there's that smile again.
What is that?
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
JERRY:
It's George.
Yeah.
Oh...
Oh, look at this one
by the bus stop.
Jerry, come here.
Take a look at this.
I really don't
need to look.
What a body.
Yeah, that's for me.
Yeah, and you're just
what she's looking for too,
a stranger leering
through a pair of binoculars
10 floors up.
I'm gonna go down there
and try and talk to her, huh?
[SNAPS FINGERS]
What?
What? Did you go down there?
Did he tell you
what's going to happen?
How long were you there?
Fifteen seconds.
You told him you knew Simons.
Yeah, I mentioned Simons.
Next thing I know,
I'm in the parking lot!
Perhaps they had
some sort of a falling out.
I'll tell you one thing--
I don't know what he's got,
but for a sick guy,
he's very strong.
Well, that's it.
Look, I'm going to Vermont.
I don't want to think
about this.
I'm selling.
Didn't work, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Not quite.
What are you gonna do
about the stock?
I'm keeping it.
I'm going down with the ship.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
So I know this guy.
I'm getting
all my sneakers
at a discount now.
I know.
You mentioned it.
Oh, yeah, right.
JERRY'S VOICE:
Oh, God, get me out of here. What a mistake.
What made me think
this would work?
And I've still got another day.
I've got nothing left to say.
Wait, wait, I've got one.
That's a nice watch.
Yeah.
Do you wind it?
No, it's got
a little battery.
Well, that's good.
Well, the drive home
should be a delight.
I'm speeding the whole way.
Let them throw me in jail.
I don't care.
That's the manager.
Do you want me to see
if we can get another room?
No, it's okay.
So I guess you don't find
the separate faucets
for the hot and the cold...
charming?
Not especially.
Well, what do you want to do
this afternoon?
What can we do? It's raining.
We could play "Sorry."
We could play
"Steal the old man's bundle."
Maybe I can get
an extension cord
and hang myself.
What kind of perfume
is that you're wearing?
Oh, you've never
heard of it.
No, what...
what kind is it?
I can't tell you.
Yeah, that's real normal.
Excuse me, sir.
Could I have a look
at that business section?
The stock?
Thank you.
I thought
you got out of that.
I did. I'm just curious.
It's been almost a week.
I want to check it out.
Six points?
It's up six points.
I told you not to sell.
You did not tell me not to sell.
I said the market fluctuates.
Remember?
Look, Vanessa,
of course the market fluctuates.
Everybody knows that.
I just got fluctuated
out of $4000.
That's probably why we're...
What?
Forget it.
No, that's probably why...
That's probably why
we're staying here,
because you lost money
on the stock.
So what am I looking at here?
Twenty-nine hours to go?
Well, at least
I've got plenty of time
to find out the name
of that perfume.
[LAUGHING]
James...he kills me, kills me.
Have something else.
Come on, have a little dessert.
I'm good, thanks.
Elaine, get something.
It's all taken care of.
I'm kind of full.
So don't finish it!
She's full.
So, big daddy, I'm just curious.
How much did you clear
on your little transaction
there,
all told?
I don't like to discuss figures.
How much?
I don't know, 8,000.
It's a Hyundai.
Get out of here.
I told you not to sell.
Simons made money.
Wilkenson cleaned up.
So Wilkenson
is out of the hospital now?
No.
You'd be surprised.
You don't recover that quickly
from a nose job.
[SNEEZES]
Oh, God.
Is that still
from those cats?
No...
I've just got a cold.
So, what ever happened
with that?
I gave him an ultimatum.
He chose the cats?
They're very clean animals.
I've got to say,
that's pretty bad,
losing out to a cat.
Almost as bad
as losing out to a perfume.
[CHUCKLES]
[ELAINE LAUGHS]
Told you those trips
are relationship-killers.
Too bad you can't get
your buddy Superman
to fly around
the earth
at super speed
and reverse time.
Get all the money back,
could have avoided
the whole trip
to Vermont...
Superman can go back in time?
We went over that.
Psst...
Wilkenson's got a bite
on a new one...
The Tramco Corporation.
Out of...Springfield, I think.
They're about to introduce
some sort of a robot butcher.
A robot butcher?
Shh...
You want to get in...
very little time.
[MOUTHS WORDS]
Ahem.
Sweetheart...
No, no, no, no, no,
that ought to cover it.
Just a second.
Just let me...peek.
Good.
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on...
I'm not an investor.
People always tell me,
"You should have your money
working for you."
I've decided I'll do the work,
I'm gonna let the money relax.
You know what I mean?
Because you send your money
out there
working for you,
a lot of times, it gets fired.
You go back there,
"What happened?
I had my money, it was here,
it was working for me."
"Yeah, I remember your money.
"Showing up late,
taking time off...
We had to let him go."