Do you know what this is all
about? Why we're here?
To be out. This is out.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
And out is one of
the single most
enjoyable experiences of life.
Do you know how people talk
about "We should go out"?
This is what
they're talking about.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
This whole thing.
We're all out now.
No one is home.
Not one person here is home.
We're all out. There are people
trying to find us.
They don't know where we are.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Did you re--? I can't find him.
Where did he go?
"He didn't tell me
where he was going.
He must have gone out."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
You wanna go out.
You get ready, you pick out
the clothes, right?
You take the shower,
get all ready,
get the cash,
get your friends,
the car, the spot,
the reservation.
Then you stand around.
What do you do? You go,
"We gotta be getting back."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Once you're out,
you wanna get back.
You wanna go to sleep,
you wanna get up,
you wanna go out again
tomorrow, right?
Wherever you are in life,
it's my feeling,
you've gotta go.
JERRY:
See that? To me, that button's in the worst possible spot.
The second button literally
makes or breaks the shirt.
Look at it.
It's too high.
It's in no man's land.
You look like you live
with your mother.
Are you through?
You do, of course,
try on when you buy.
Yes, it was purple.
I liked it.
I don't actually recall
considering the buttons.
Oh, you don't recall.
Er, n-no,
not at this time.
Well, senator,
I'd just like to know
what you knew
and when you knew it.
Mr. Seinfeld,
Mr. Costanza.
Are you sure
this is decaf?
Where's
the orange indicator?
It's missing.
I have to do it in my head.
Decaf left,
regular right.
It's very challenging work.
Can you relax?
It's a cup of coffee.
Claire's
a professional waitress.
Trust me, George.
No one has any interest
in seeing you on caffeine.
How come you're not doing
the second show tomorrow?
Well, there's this, uh, woman
who might be coming in.
Wait a second.
What coming in?
What woman is coming in?
I told you about Laura,
the girl I met in Michigan.
No, you didn't.
I thought I told you
about her.
Yeah. She teaches
political science,
I met her the night
I did the show in Lansing.
Huh.
There's no milk in here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why's there no milk?
What is she--? What is she like?
Oh, she's really great.
She's got, like,
a real warmth about her.
And she's really bright
and really pretty and...
And the conversation,
though, I mean, it was...
You know, talking with her,
it was like talking with you,
but, you know,
obviously much better.
So, you know,
wh-what happened?
Well, nothing happened,
you know.
But it was great.
Oh, nothing happened,
but it was...
This is great!
Yeah. Yeah.
So, you know she called
and said she wants to go out
with you tomorrow night?
God bless.
You devil, you.
Yeah. Well, not exactly.
I mean, she said--
You know, she called
this morning and said
she had to come in
for a seminar,
and maybe we'd get together.
[WHISTLES]
So, you know...
Oh, oh, oh.
"Had to"?
Y-yeah.
"Had to come in"?
Yeah, but--
"And maybe we'll get together"?
"Had to" and "maybe"?
Yeah.
No,
no.
No, I hate to
tell you this.
You're not gonna see
this woman.
What? Are you serious?
Why--? Why did she call?
What do I know? Maybe, you know,
she wanted to be polite.
To be polite?
You are insane.
All right. All right.
I didn't want to
tell you this.
Wanna know why she called?
Yes.
You're a backup.
You're a second line,
a "just in case,"
a B plan,
a contingency.
Oh, I get it.
This is about the button.
Claire. Claire,
you're a woman, right?
What gave it away,
George?
I'd like to
ask you--
Ask you
to analyze
a hypothetical phone call,
you know, from
a female point of view.
Oh, come on, now.
What are you
asking her?
Now, how's she
gonna know?
Please. Now,
a woman calls me, right?
Mm-hmm.
She says she has to...
No.
come to New York
on business--
You are beautiful.
And--
And maybe...
she'll see me
when she gets in.
Does this woman intend
to spend time with me?
I'd have to say, uh...no.
So why did
she call?
Be polite.
To be polite. I rest my case.
Good, good.
Did you have fun?
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Now, come with me. I gotta go
get my stuff out of the dryer.
I'm not gonna
watch you do laundry.
Oh, come on.
Be a "come-with" guy.
Come on.
I'm tired.
Don't worry. I gave him
a little caffeine.
He'll perk up.
Right. I knew
I felt something.
I can't--
Boom.
Jerry...
I have to tell you
something.
This is the dullest moment
I've ever experienced.
Oh, look at this guy.
Look at-- He's got
everything.
He's got detergents,
sprays, fabric softener.
This is not
his first load.
I need a break,
Jerry.
You know, I gotta
get out of the city.
I feel so cramped--
And you didn't hear
how she sounded.
What?
Laura.
I can't believe--
We already discussed this.
Yeah, but how could you
be so sure?
Because it's
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
signals, Jerry.
It's signals.
Don't you--?
All right.
Did she even ask you
what you were doing
tomorrow night,
if you were busy?
No.
She calls you today,
she doesn't make a plan
for tomorrow?
What is that?
It's Saturday night.
Yeah.
What is that? It's ridiculous.
You don't even know
what hotel she's staying at.
You can't call her.
That's a signal,
Jerry.
That's a signal.
[FINGERS SNAP]
Signal.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm right?
Of course
I'm right.
Mm-hmm.
This is insane.
You know, I don't even know
where she's staying.
She's-- She's not gonna
call me.
It's unbelievable.
[SOFTLY]
I know, I know. It's tough.
Listen, your stuff
has to be done by now.
Why don't you just see
if it's dry? Just--
No, no, no.
Don't interrupt the cycle.
The machine is working.
It knows what it's doing.
Just let it finish.
You're gonna
overdry it.
You can't overdry.
Why not?
Same reason
you can't overwet.
You see, once something
is wet, it's wet.
Same thing with death.
Like, once you die,
you're dead. Right?
Let's say you drop dead
and I shoot you.
You not gonna die again.
You're already dead.
You can't "overdie,"
you can't overdry.
Any questions?
How could she not tell me
where she was staying?
Look at that.
They're done.
Dry!
Laundry day is
the only exciting day
in the life of clothes.
It is.
No, think about it.
The washing machine
is the nightclub of clothes.
You know, it's dark,
there's bubbles happening,
they're all kind of
dancing around in there.
A shirt grabs the underwear.
"Come on, babe. Let's go."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
You come by, you open up
the lid, and they all:
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Socks are the most amazing
article of clothing.
They hate their lives.
They're in the shoes with
stinky feet, the boring drawers.
The dryer is their only chance
to escape and they all know it.
They do escape from the dryer.
They plan it in the hamper
the night before.
"Tomorrow, the dryer,
I'm going."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"You wait here."
The dryer door swings open,
the sock is waiting
up against the side wall.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
He hopes you don't see him,
then he goes down the road.
♪ Duh-du-duh
Duh-duh duh-duh ♪
They get buttons
sewn on their face,
join a puppet show.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
So they're showing me
on television
the detergents are
getting out bloodstains.
Is this a violent image
to anybody? Bloodstains?
I mean, come on.
You got a T-shirt
with bloodstains all over it,
maybe laundry isn't
your biggest problem right now.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
You ought to get the harpoon
out of your chest first.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
["CHARGE" RIFF PLAYS ON TV]
[CROWD NOISES ON TV]
[RINGING]
[LOWERS VOLUME]
If you know what happened
in the Met game,
don't say anything,
I taped it. Hello.
Yeah. No, I'm sorry.
You have the wrong number.
Yeah. No--
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah.
You up?
Yeah. Yeah.
People do move.
Have you ever seen
the big trucks
out on the street?
Yeah, no problem.
Boy, the Mets blew it
tonight, huh?
Oh, what are you doing?
Kessler, it's a tape.
I taped the game.
It's 1:00 in the morning.
I avoided human contact
all night to watch this.
Hey, I'm sorry. I...
You know, I-I thought
you knew. I...
You got any meat?
Meat?
I-I don't know.
Go...hunt.
Well, what happened
in the game, anyway?
What happened?
Well, they stunk!
That's what happened.
You know I almost wound up
going to that game?
Yeah, you almost went
to the game.
You haven't been out of
the building in 10 years.
Yeah.
Well...?
You...?
I...
Oh.
You done
with this?
No.
[GROANS]
When you're done, let me know.
Yeah, yeah.
You can have it
tomorrow.
I thought I wasn't allowed
to be in here this weekend.
No, it's okay now.
That girl's not coming.
I-- I misread
the whole thing.
Hmm.
You want me to talk to her?
I don't think so.
No, I can be
very persuasive.
You know that I was
almost a lawyer?
That close, huh?
You better believe it.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Laura.
Oh, give me it.
Let me talk.
No. What's up?
Well, let me talk to her.
Believe me,
I'm always up
at this hour.
How are you? Great.
Sure.
What time does
the plane get in?
I'll get my friend George
to take me.
Now slide!
Out. Do you
believe that?
No, it's just
my neighbor.
Um...
Yeah, I got it. 10:15.
No, don't be silly.
Go ahead and ask.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, great.
No, no.
It's no trouble at all.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Great. Bye.
I don't believe it.
That-- That was her.
She wants to stay here.
If my father
was moving this,
he'd have to have a cigarette
in his mouth the whole way.
"Have you got your end?"
[COUGHS]
"Your end's got to
come down first.
"Easy, now.
Drop it down.
Your end's gotta come down."
You know, I can't believe
you're bringing in an extra bed
for a woman that wants
to sleep with you.
Why don't you bring in
an extra guy too?
Look, it's a very
awkward situation.
I don't wanna be
presumptuous.
All right. All right.
One more time.
What was the exact phrasing
of the request?
All right. She said she couldn't
find a decent hotel room.
A decent hotel room.
Yeah, a decent hotel room.
Would it be
terribly inconvenient
if she stayed at my place?
You can't be serious.
This is New York City.
There must be 11 million
decent hotel rooms.
What do you need, a--?
A flag?
This is
the signal, Jerry.
This is the signal.
Thank you, Mr. Signal.
Where were you
yesterday?
I think I was affected
by the caffeine.
Ho, ho.
All right. Good dog.
Good dog. All right.
Hey, he really likes you,
George.
Well, that's flattering.
Ah, he's getting
a drink of water.
Is this
for that girl?
Yeah.
Why even give her
an option?
This is a person I like.
It's not how to score
on spring break.
All right. Can we go?
I'm double-parked.
I'm gonna get
a ticket.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, wait a second.
I-- I forgot to clean
the bathroom.
So what?
That's good.
Now how could that
be good?
Because filth
is good.
What do you think, rock stars
have sponges and ammonia
lying around
the bathroom?
You think they have a woman
coming over, "I gotta tidy up"?
In these matters, you never do
what your instincts tell you.
Always, always
do the opposite.
This is how you operate?
Psh. Yeah, I wish.
Let me just wipe the sink.
It'll--
Why even give her an option for?
Just give me a second.
It's unbelievable.
Yeah.
How's the real estate
business?
It's, uh, not bad.
It's coming along.
Why, did you
need something?
You handle any of
that commercial
whhhhhh...real estate,
that...sshhhooo?
Well, I might be
getting into that.
You keep me posted.
I'm aware of you.
All right, let's go.
Let's go. Oh!
You're on-stage
in 25 minutes.
The dating world
is not a fun world.
It's a pressure world.
It's a world of tension,
it's a world of pain.
And if a woman comes over
to my house,
I gotta get that bathroom ready
because she needs things.
Women need equipment.
I don't know what they need.
I know I don't have it,
I know that.
You-- You know
what they need?
Women seem to need
a lot of cotton balls.
This is one-- Always been one of
the most amazing things to me.
I have no cotton balls.
We're all human beings.
What is the story?
I've never had one,
I never bought one,
I never needed one.
I've never been in a situation
where I thought to myself,
"I could use a cotton ball
right now."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"I could certainly
get out of this mess."
Women need them.
And they don't need one or two.
They need thousands of them.
They need bags.
They're like
peat moss bags.
Have you ever seen
these giant bags?
They're huge...
and two days later, they're out.
They're gone.
The bag is empty.
Where are the cotton balls,
ladies?
What are you
doing with them?
The only time
I ever see them
is in the bottom of
your little wastebasket.
There's two or three
that look like
they've been through
some horrible experience.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Tortured, interrogated,
I don't know
what happened to them.
I once went out
with a girl,
she left a little Ziploc Baggie
of cotton balls at my house.
I didn't know what to do.
I put them on the kitchen floor
like little tumbleweeds.
I thought maybe
the cockroaches would see it,
figure, "This is a dead town.
Let's move on."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
The dating world is a world
of pressure. Let's face it,
a date is a job interview
that lasts all night.
The only difference between
a date and job interview is
not many job interviews
is there a chance
you'll end up naked
at the end of it.
You know, "Well, Bill,
"the boss thinks
you're the man for the position
"Why don't you strip down
and meet
some of the people
you'll be working with?"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Wouldn't it be great
if you could ask a woman
what she's thinking?
Psh. What a world
that would be
if you could just ask a woman
what she's thinking.
You know, instead...
I'm like a detective.
I gotta pick up clues.
The whole thing's
a murder investigation.
All right, listen, listen.
Don't get worked up.
because you're gonna know
the whole story
the minute she steps off
the plane..
Really, how?
Because it's all
in the greeting.
All right. If she puts
the bags down
before she greets you,
that's a good sign.
Right.
You know, anything in--
In the lip area is good.
Lip area.
You know, a hug,
definitely good.
Hug is definitely good.
Sure.
Although, what if it's
one of those hugs
where the shoulders
are touching,
the hips are
8 feet apart?
Those are brutal.
I hate that.
You know how they do that?
Also, a shake is bad.
Shake is bad. But what if
it's the two-hander?
The hand on the bottom,
the hand on the top.
The warm look
in the eyes.
Hand sandwich. Right.
Right.
Well, that's open
to interpretation
because so much depends
on the layering
and the quality of
the wetness in the eyes--
Guess who.
Hey, hey. He--
BOTH:
Hey!
Hey.
Hey. It's good to see you.
Hi.
This is my friend George.
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
How are you?
This is Laura.
Sure, Laura, sure.
I can't believe you're here.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, wow.
Wow.
[CHUCKLES]
The bags. Let's get the bags.
Oh, yeah, sure, the bags.
Here, Laura. I'm sorry.
Oh, thank you.
Boy, that was
an interesting greeting.
Did you notice that,
George?
Yes, the "surprise blindfold"
greeting.
That wasn't in the manual.
So...
what do you think?
Whoa.
Wow.
This place isn't so bad.
Yeah, it kind of motivates me
to work on the road.
So make yourself
at home.
[SIGHS]
So, uh...
can I get you anything?
Uh...
Bread, water...
salad dressing?
Actually, um,
do you have any wine?
Uh, yeah,
I think I do.
Oh, do you mind
if I turn this down?
Uh, no. Yeah, go--
Go right ahead. Yeah.
Jerry, I was wondering
would it be possible,
and if it's not, fine,
for me to stay here
tomorrow night too?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
Yeah, why don't you stay?
Yeah. Um...
What is your schedule
for tomorrow?
Are you doing
anything?
Oh. No, I'd love
to do something.
I have my seminar
in the morning,
but after that
I'm wide open.
Really? What would you
like to do?
Well...
[LAUGHS]
Now, I know this sounds
touristy,
but I'd love to go
on one of those
five-hour boat rides
around Manhattan.
Yeah, we could do that.
[POURS WINE]
Why not? Why not?
[GIGGLES]
I'm just-- I'm really glad
you're here.
[RINGING]
[DING]
Hello.
Yes.
Yes, she is.
Hold on.
Um, it's for you.
Oh.
Uh... Hello?
Oh, hi.
No, no. It was great,
right on time.
No, I-I'm gonna stay here
tomorrow.
Yes. Yes, it's fine.
[LAUGHS]
No, we're going on a boat ride.
[SIGHS]
Don't be silly.
I'm not gonna have
this conversation.
Look, I'll call you
tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
[SIGHS]
Never get engaged.
You're engaged?
You know, you really
have no idea
what it's like until
you actually do it.
I'm on this emotional
roller coaster.
You're engaged?
You know, I can't believe it
myself sometimes.
You-- You have to start
thinking in terms of "we."
It's a very
stressful situation.
You're engaged.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's a great guy.
You'd really
like him.
I can't wait
to get on that boat.
Me too.
I swear, I have
absolutely no idea
what women are thinking.
I don't get it, okay?
I-I-I admit, I'm not
getting the signals.
I am not getting it.
Women, they're so subtle.
Their little--
Everything they do
is subtle.
[LAUGHTER]
Men are not subtle.
We are obvious.
Women know what men want,
men know what men want.
What do we want?
We want women.
That's it.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS, CLAPS]
It's the only thing we know
for sure. It really is.
We want women.
How do we get them?
Oh, we don't know about that.
We don't know.
The next step after that,
we have no idea.
This is why you see
men honking car horns,
yelling from
construction sites.
These are the best ideas
we've had so far.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
The car horn honk.
Is that the beauty?
Have you seen men
doing this?
What is this?
The man is in the car.
The woman walks by
the front of the car.
He honks the--
[IMITATES HORN]
This man is
out of ideas.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
How does the--?
[IMITATES HORN]
"I don't think
she likes me."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
The amazing thing is that
we still get women,
don't we?
Men-- I mean,
men are with women.
You see men with women.
How are men getting women?
Many people wonder.
Let me tell you a little bit
about our organization.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Wherever women are,
we have a man working on
the situation right now.
Now, he may not be
our best man...
Okay, we have a lot of
areas to cover,
but someone from our staff
is on the scene.
That's why I think
men get frustrated
when we see women
reading articles
like "Where to Meet Men."
We're here.
We are everywhere.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
We're honking our horns
to serve you better.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
[♪]