So, I move into the center lane.
Now, I get ahead of this woman
who felt, for some reason,
I guess, that she thought
that I'd cut her off.
So she pulls up
alongside of me,
gives me...the finger.
It seems like
such an arbitrary,
ridiculous thing
to just pick a finger,
and you show it to the person.
It's a finger.
What does it mean?
Someone shows me
one of their fingers,
and I'm supposed to feel bad.
Is that the way
it's supposed to work?
I mean...you could just
give someone the toe, really,
couldn't you?
I would feel worse
if I got the toe
than if I got the finger,
because it's not easy
to give someone the toe.
You got to get the shoe off,
the sock off,
and drive, get it up in the...
Look at that toe, buddy.
I mean, that's really insulting,
to get the toe, isn't it?
JERRY: That it?
I've got the Q-Tips,
I've got the mini-umbrella,
something boring
to read on the plane.
That's it. Done!
That is the single greatest
packing performance
I have ever seen.
I am...
the master packer.
Yeah, right.
You're the master packer.
What you must understand,
Elaine...
packing's no different
than leading men
into battle.
You've got to know
the strengths and weaknesses
of every soldier
in that platoon...
from a collapsible toothbrush
to a pair of ordinary
black socks.
Excuse me, master packer?
Yes?
Just give me your keys.
All right, sir.
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
George?
Yeah.
Okay, so, now,
is there anything else
I need to know
about this place?
Uh, yeah.
The hot water takes
a little while to come on,
so the best thing to do
is to turn it on,
do all your shopping,
and come back,
and take a shower.
Okay. This is quite a place.
There's more.
The refrigerator.
Deduct a minimum
of two days
off all
expiration dates.
No meat, no leftovers,
no butter,
and I cannot
overstate this--
no soft cheeses
of any kind.
Is that clear?
I'll eat out.
And one more thing,
Benes.
Regarding
sexual activity...
strictly prohibited,
but if you absolutely must,
do us all a big favor--
do it in the tub.
You ready?
Yeah. One second.
Hey, Elaine.
Hi.
You coming
to the airport with us?
No, I'm staying here
for the weekend.
I'm getting a break
from my roommate.
Oh, the actress/waitress.
No. The waitress/actress.
She just got some part
in some dinner theater
production
of A Chorus Line.
So, now, all day long,
she's walking around
the apartment singing,
♪ God, I hope
I get it ♪
♪ I hope I get it ♪
She's going to get it,
right in the...
Why don't you
just kick her out?
She's on the lease.
George, you have got to find
another place for me.
Well, a little rough
finding something good
in your price range...
Hey, but you, my friend,
may be in luck.
I'm not looking.
No, no, no.
This one's different.
This one's a beauty.
What's it like?
I haven't seen it yet,
but it's a two-bedroom.
It's on, uh,
the West 83rd,
about a half-block
from the park.
How much?
Twice what you're paying here,
but it's a great building.
It's two bedrooms.
Two bedrooms?
Why do I need
two bedrooms?
I've got
enough trouble
maintaining activity
in one.
I saw that.
You ought to at least
take a look at it.
Really? Why?
Because then
I could move in here.
Ah...
Ah.
I know what
you're saying now.
It's time you got
out of here anyway.
Yeah, tell him, but quickly.
I'm double-parked here.
Jerry, this place
is falling apart.
You have no hot water,
you can't have
soft cheese.
And let's not forget
the radiator.
The steam has been on here
for 10 years.
No human
can turn this off.
Jerry, come on.
You're doing okay now.
You should at least
take a look at this place.
You shouldn't
have to live like this.
Like this?
You just said
you wanted to live here.
Well, for me,
it's a step up.
It's like moving from
Iceland to Finland.
Jerry, what do you--?
Do you want to see
the place or not?
I can't think about it now.
Come on, I'm going
to Minneapolis.
I got four shows this weekend.
[GRUNTS]
Elaine?
[SIGHS]
ELAINE: Jerry?
Jer-- Oh, hi.
Welcome back.
How were the shows?
Great. I had fun.
Where's the TV?
Where's the VCR?
What?
They were stolen.
Stolen?
When?
A couple
of hours ago.
The police are coming
right over.
Stolen?
Someone left the door open.
Oh, yeah, uh...
You left the door open?
Uh... Yeah, well, you know,
I was cooking,
and I, you know, I came in
to get the spatula.
I left the door open...
because I was going to bring
the spatula right back.
Wait, you left
the lock open,
or the door open?
The door.
The door?
You left the door open?
Yeah, well, I was going
to bring the spatula right back.
Yeah, and?
Well, I got caught up
watching a soap opera.
Bold and the Beautiful.
So the door was wide open.
Wide open!
Excuse me.
And where were you?
I was
at Bloomingdale's,
waiting for the shower
to heat up.
Look, Jerry,
I'm sorry. I'm--
You have insurance,
right, buddy?
No.
How can you not have insurance?
Because...
I spent my money
on the Clapco D-29.
It's the most impenetrable lock
on the market today.
It has only one design flaw.
The door...
must be closed!
Jerry, I'm going
to find your stuff.
I'm going to solve it.
I'm on the case, buddy.
I'm on the case.
Yeah, don't investigate.
Don't pay me back.
It was an accident.
I made a mistake.
These things happen.
I'm human.
In your way.
OFFICER:
Let's see, that's one TV,
stereo, one leather jacket,
a VCR, and a computer.
Is that about it?
The answering
machine.
Answering machine.
Boy, I hate the idea
of somebody out there
returning my calls.
What do you mean?
It's a joke.
I see.
Well, Mr. Seinfeld, uh,
we'll look into it,
and we'll let you know,
if we, you know,
if we find anything.
Do you ever
find anything?
No.
Well, thanks anyway.
You bet.
I didn't get
that joke either.
The crook has the machine.
The messages aren't for him,
he's the crook.
Why would he answer--?
How did you get in here?
I walked in.
Your lobby door is broken again.
Again?
I don't know how
you put up with this.
Yeah.
Tell him, George.
You would still
want to move in here?
Yes.
You don't
understand.
I'm living
with Ethel Merman
without the talent.
Is that, uh...
other apartment
still available?
I got ripped off
for about the...
18th time.
Now, the first couple of times
you go through it,
it's very upsetting,
and your first reaction,
or one of your friends will say,
"Call the police.
You really should
call the police."
So you think to yourself,
you know, you watch TV,
you think, "Yeah,
I'm calling the police--
"Stakeouts, manhunts...
I'm going to see
some real action."
Right? You think that.
So, the police come over
to your house,
they fill out the report.
They give you...
your copy.
Now, unless they give the crook
his copy,
I don't really think we're going
to crack this case, do you?
It's not like Batman,
where there's three crooks
in the city
and everybody pretty much
knows who they are.
Very few crooks
even go to the trouble
to come up with a theme
for their careers anymore.
It makes them
a lot tougher to spot.
"Did you lose a Sony?
"It could be the Penguin.
"I think we can round him up.
"He's dressed like a penguin.
We can find him.
He's a penguin."
Oh... Oh.
Well... Come on.
This is an apartment.
This is a home.
This is a place
to live.
[GASPS]
A fireplace!
Are you kidding me?
Does this work?
I didn't know
there was a fireplace.
A fireplace!
That's incredible.
How do you get
all that wood in here?
They deliver it.
They deliver wood?
Yeah.
What do you tip
a wood guy?
I didn't know
there was a fireplace.
ELAINE:
Look! Look at-- Look at this.
There's a garden.
A garden?
I can't believe
there's a garden.
Would I have to get a gardener?
Yeah, you can get a gardener.
You tip him?
You can.
You don't tip
a gardener.
You can tip
You don't need
a gardener.
Jerry, you can
barbecue back here.
They deliver the coal?
Sure.
It's probably
the same guy
who delivers the wood.
Oh, then I got to
tip him.
Oh, man, this place
is incredible.
Look at
all this great light.
I don't have any plants.
I have plants.
[SNORTS]
Jerry, look at this closet.
Look at this. I'm walking in it.
It's a walk-in.
Can you believe it?
I'm nuts about this.
What do you think?
I like that.
What do you think,
George?
It's your decision.
I'm taking it.
Oh!
I'm taking the place.
I'm going to take it.
This is going to be
my new place.
I'm living here.
I'm moving.
You're moving?
That means I'm moving.
Oh! Gee!
Is that incredible?
Congratulations.
What about the couch?
You like the couch?
Tell you what I'm gonna do.
What?
You're moving in.
You're a good friend.
I wanna start you off
on the right foot.
Give me...
$150.
In fact, get it
out of here right now.
Take it out the door.
I don't even want to see it.
A hundred and fifty dollars?
For what? For this couch?
Yeah.
For this couch?
Okay, you tell me.
What is it worth?
Okay, uh...
[BLOWING THROUGH PURSED LIPS]
I tell you what...
I could go as high
as, uh...
I don't know.
Maybe...twenty dollars?
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
All right.
Forget it.
I'm gonna take it with me, then.
I'm just gonna pack up
the cushions right now.
Okay, okay, you win.
Forty dollars.
You wanna get
the other end,
because I wanna
get it in the hall.
Fifty dollars, okay?
Fifty dollars?
Is that all right?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you very much.
Hey, what's going on?
I just bought
Jerry's couch for $50.
So did you bring the lease?
Well, all right.
Gee, three years.
That kind of seems
like a long time.
Oh, Jerry, Jerry, Jerry, Jerry,
Listen, if you are
feeling uncomfortable
about this at all,
at all,
do not feel like
you have to take it.
Why?
If you're having
second thoughts,
if you didn't want it,
don't worry about it,
because, uh, you know, I--
I could take it, you know?
You could take it?
You want it?
No, I don't want it.
I want it if you don't want it.
So you...do want it.
No, I want it
if you don't want it.
You just said you wanted it.
No, I'm saying
if a situation arose
in which you didn't want it,
I might take it.
So take it.
How can I take it?
It's your apartment.
How can I want it now
if you want it?
Excuse me. I don't mean
to cause any trouble here,
but, George, if you take it,
can I take your place?
Yes, but I am not taking it.
I am not taking it.
Well, one of you better
damn well take it.
Well, what do you want
to do here?
I don't know.
Do you want to flip a coin?
Who flips?
You flip, I'll call.
Okay. Fine.
All right. All right.
This is
the official flip.
All right.
No crying, no guilt.
Winner takes all, and that's it.
Agreed?
I'm good.
I don't know
who to root for.
George's place
has carpeting.
Shh, shh.
All right.
Now, you call it
in the air.
No catching.
No, no.
All right, flip it.
Heads!
[COIN CLANGS]
Tails.
No, it hit the table.
It hit the table.
So what?
Interference.
You can't count that.
Come on.
Are you crazy?
The coin cannot
touch anything.
It affects it.
You didn't call
"no interference."
You don't have
to call that.
That's a rule!
I don't believe this.
Oh! Oh! All right. Fine, Jerry.
You win. Take it.
Just take it.
I don't want
to win it like this.
Elaine,
what do you think?
I better not.
Jesus.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'll choose you for it.
Straight choose, three takes it.
No disputes. That's it.
You got to win three.
Okay.
Okay. I'll choose you.
What do you want?
Odds.
I want evens.
Good.
You got odds.
You got evens.
Right.
Ready.
For the apartment.
BOTH: Once, twice,
three, shoot!
Mine.
BOTH: Once, twice,
three, shoot!
Mine!
BOTH: Once, twice,
three, shoot!
Mine!
BOTH: Once, twice, three,
Shoot!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I'm just gonna...wash.
GEORGE [YELLING]:
Why did I put out two? Why did I put out two?
[BANGING DOOR]
Jerry?
I think I'm onto something.
I think I found your stuff.
You know the Englishman
who lives down the hall?
Yeah.
The last couple of days,
he's been acting very strange.
I think he's avoiding me.
Hard to imagine.
Yeah, and get this--
I just got off the elevator
with him,
and I tested him.
I tested him.
Like I-- This is what
I said to him,
like I was like this, I went,
"Oh, by the way, I know
about the stuff."
You know, very casual...
Right.
so he's gonna take me
into his confidence.
So, what did he say?
"What stuff?"
Oh.
Case closed.
Oh, no, no.
You don't understand.
You see, he swallowed.
See, the guy, he swallowed.
Oh, he was nervous
about something.
Now, I'm gonna go over there.
I'm gonna borrow some tea.
You know, if I don't get back
in five minutes,
maybe you better call
the police.
Okay.
Starting...now!
Yeah!
One of the problems in life
is that when you're a kid,
you have a certain way
of working out disagreements...
and those laws do not work
in the adult world.
One of the main ways
that kids resolve any dispute
is by calling it.
One of them'll say,
"I got the front seat."
"I wanted the front seat."
"I called it."
And the other kid knows
he's got nothing to say.
"He called it. What can I do?"
If there was a kid court of law,
it holds up.
"Your Honor, my client did ask
for the front seat."
And the judge would go,
"Did he call it?"
"Well, no, he didn't call it--"
Bang. "He has to call it.
Case closed.
Objection overruled."
I love the mirror
in that bathroom.
I don't know what
in the hell it is.
I look terrific
in that mirror.
I don't know if it's the tile
or the lighting.
I feel like Robert Wagner
in there.
It's a good mirror.
So, what are you getting?
I don't know. What can you eat?
You can't have anything anymore.
Look at this. Look at this.
Eggs, out.
Coffee, out.
French fries, out.
B.L.T., out.
I go to visit
my grandparents.
They're eating
big brisket sandwiches.
I'm sitting there with a carrot.
They're closing in on 100.
I'm saying to them,
"How can you eat that stuff?"
I'm so sick about
losing that choose.
You don't know. I--
All right. Forget it.
Forget it.
I'm not taking the place.
What?
How can I live there?
Why not?
Look at you. You're
still thinking about it.
I'll never feel comfortable.
Oh, please. Get outta here.
How can I ever
have you over?
You'll sit there moping.
I won't mope.
You're
already moping.
Would you take the place?
No. Impossible.
It's your apartment.
You found the place.
You won the choose.
All right. Forget it.
It's over.
I'm not moving.
Well, me neither.
Definitely?
Definitely.
All right.
Then just get rid of it.
You won't have any problem.
No, it's not a problem.
I can get rid
of the apartment
this afternoon.
What apartment?
Oh, it's a great place.
It's a two-bedroom, West 83rd,
about a half block
from the park.
What's the rent?
I hate housewarmings.
I don't know
what we're doing here.
This is ridiculous.
She wanted to thank us
for the apartment.
I can't believe
I lost the deposit
on that U-Haul,
and I threw out my couch.
If only the coin
hadn't hit the table.
The table is interference.
You know it.
It is not.
It is too.
My roommate starts
rehearsal tonight on Carousel.
Hi.
Oh, hi, Carol.
I just wanted
to introduce you
to my husband.
This is Larry.
This is George,
Elaine and Jerry.
These are the guys
who got us the apartment.
You don't know
how grateful I am.
If there's anything
I can ever do to repay you--
I mean, we're just
so thrilled with this place.
It's a dream.
LARRY: I'm running
in the park now.
I've lost weight.
We're barbecuing
every night,
and the rent
is unbelievable.
We're really glad
for you.
Couldn't be happier.
It's wonderful.
Oh, Diane.
Diane, come here.
This is my new
next-door neighbor, Diane.
Hi.
These are the guys
who turned this place down.
Can you believe it?
Diane gave me
the greatest back rub today.
She's a masseuse.
How could you guys
have turned this place down?
It's such
a great location,
and it's so close
to the park.
Yeah, we're aware
of the proximity to the park.
It's--
Well, it was nice
to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
[SIGHS]
How late are
the stores open?
I'm thinking of maybe
buying a new TV
and smashing it
over my head.
So I get a call from Gilmore
this morning, and get this--
They're restructuring
the organization in Atlanta,
and I gotta be there
on the first of the month.
Really? What are you gonna do
about the apartment?
Well, what can I do?
I'll give it up.
[IN UNISON]
What's the rent?
[♪]