So I'm on a line
at the supermarket.
Two women in front of me.
One of them,
her total was $8.00.
The other, $3.00.
They both, of course,
choose to pay
by the use of the...
MAN: Check.
Check.
Now...
The fact is,
if it is a woman in front of you
that's writing out the check,
you'll not be waiting long.
I have noticed that women
are very fast with checks,
you know, because they write out
so many checks.
The keys, they can never find
in their purse.
They don't know where that is.
But the checkbook--
They got that.
They never fumble
for the checkbook.
They've got-- The checkbook
comes out of a holster.
Who do I make it out to?
[♪]
There's my I.D.
There's something about a check
that, to a man,
is not masculine.
I don't know exactly what it is.
I think, to a man,
a check is like a note
from your mother that says,
"I don't have any money,
"but if you'll contact
these people,
"I'm sure
they'll stick up for me.
"If you could just trust me
this one time.
"I don't have any money,
but I have these.
"I wrote on these.
Is this of any value at all?"
What's that one?
Cocoon 2: The Return.
I guess they didn't like it
up there.
Maybe they came back
for Chinese food.
You know Maureen Stapleton--
she gets a craving,
she's probably screaming
at those aliens,
"I gotta have a lo mein."
Okay, what are
we doing here?
I have seen everything.
Oh, yeah?
I don't believe
you've seen this.
Oh, lovely.
Yeah.
What do you think
their parents think?
So, what's your son
doing now, Dr. Stevens?
Oh, he's
a public fornicator.
Yes, he's a fine boy.
You know what?
This would be a funny gift
for Pamela's birthday.
Pamela. Do I know her?
Yeah, you met her
when we were going out.
Oh, yeah, right.
You have no idea who
I'm talking about, do you?
No.
Blonde hair. Remember?
Glasses.
Have you totally blocked out
the entire time
we were a couple?
Riverside Drive.
Right.
In fact...
No. Never mind.
Well, what is it?
Well, a bunch of people
are getting together
tomorrow night at some bar
for her birthday,
but...
You don't wanna go to that.
No. Okay.
Wait a second.
We could work out
a little deal here.
What little deal?
I will go to that...
You go with me
to a little family wedding
I have on Saturday.
A wedding?
Have you lost it, man?
My parents are coming
in for this.
They're coming in?
Yeah, tomorrow.
Hey, did your father
ever get that hair weave?
No, no.
Still doing
the big sweep across.
Why does he do that?
Doesn't think anyone can tell.
So, come on.
Do we have a deal?
A wedding?
There's a lot of people to mock.
All right. What the hell.
Great.
When you're dead, you're dead.
That's it.
You're not going anywhere.
ELAINE:
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Was I supposed
to bring something?
You could've.
I met her one time.
It is not necessary.
Then what did you
say that for? Hi!
Hi, Pamela.
You remember Jerry?
Hi.
Yes, we met.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Everybody, this is
Jerry and Elaine.
Hi.
JERRY: Hi.
I didn't bring
anything.
I put you two
right here.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what-- you know.
I didn't hear.
Nobody's told me anything...
[PIANO PLAYING]
How big a tip
you think it would take
to get him to stop?
I'm in for five.
I'll supply the hat.
JERRY: Uh-oh,
what do we have here?
Why don't you relax
and take your jacket off?
Oh, I can't.
I have a tendency to get chilly.
How masculine.
Plus, I'm wearing short sleeves.
I don't want to expose
my tattoos.
She's unbelievable.
Hey, this guy says
he knows Bricker.
Oh, you know Bricker.
From where?
What's going on here?
Gotta be a boyfriend.
She's too good to be alone.
What's the difference?
I can't maneuver anyway,
with Elaine next to me.
How do you know Pamela?
Friend of a friend.
And you?
We went to law school together.
ELAINE: Oh, Jerry.
Oh, no. Not now.
I had this dream
last night,
and you were in it.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I've gotta get out of this.
You were you,
but you weren't you.
No kidding.
Yeah.
Why is this happening?
Please make her stop.
I think--
I think we were in my house
where I grew up,
and you were
standing there.
You were
looking out the window.
This is brutal.
And then you turned around
and you had these wooden teeth.
[MAN LAUGHS]
How do you like that?
Can I turn now?
Is this over?
No, I can't, I can't.
I'm stuck.
Jerry,
are you listening to me?
Yes. I heard you.
Elaine, what's the name
of that jewelry store
you took me to
that time?
Thank you, Pamela.
So you're a lawyer?
Sagman, Bennett, Robbins,
Oppenheim, and Taff.
Of course, they handled
my tattoo-removal lawsuit.
Oh, that was you.
Imagine, spelling "mom"
with two O's.
That's very funny.
What do you do?
Comedian.
Really?
Well, that explains it.
Sagman, Bennett, Robbins,
Oppenheim, and Taff.
You ready?
We gotta run.
WOMAN:
Happy birthday.
Goodbye, everyone.
PAMELA:
Thanks for coming.
Bye.
I can't believe it.
I've got nothing.
I don't even know her name.
Sagman, Bennett, Robbins,
Oppenheim, and Taff.
Oppen...
Sagman... Bennett, Robbins...
Ro...
JERRY: That wasn't
so bad, really.
You know, um...
You could use a little work
on your manners.
Why, what did I do?
Well, I just don't appreciate
these little courtesy responses,
like I'm selling you
aluminum siding.
I was listening.
No, you couldn't wait
to get back
to your little... conversation.
No. You were talking about
the, um, the dream you had
where you were, um--
you had wooden teeth.
No! No! You had wooden teeth.
You had wooden teeth.
I didn't have wooden teeth.
You did.
All right, so I had
wooden teeth. So what?
So-- so nothing. Nothing.
Apparently, Plato,
who came up with the concept
of the platonic relationship,
was pretty excited about it.
He named it after himself.
He said,
"Yeah, I got this new thing--
"platonic.
"My idea, my name,
calling it after myself.
"What I do is,
I go out with the girls,
"I talk with them,
don't do anything,
"and go right home.
"What do you think?
I think it's going to be big."
I bet you there were
other guys in history
that tried to get relationships
named after them,
but it didn't work.
You know, I bet you there were
guys that tried to do it,
just went,
"Hi, my name's Rico. Uh...
"Would you like to go to bed
immediately?
Hey, it's
a Riconic relationship."
Hey.
Ah, there he is.
This is what I like. See?
You come home,
your parents are in your bed.
You know, Jerry,
we don't have to do this.
What are you talking about?
It's fine.
I love having you here.
Tomorrow,
we'll go to a hotel.
Ma, will you stop?
No, why should we take over
your apartment?
I don't care.
I'm sleeping next door.
Your friend, Kramer,
doesn't mind?
No. He's making a bouillabaisse.
So, Dad, let me
ask you a question.
How many people work
at these big law offices?
Depends on the firm.
If you called up
and described someone,
do you think they would know
who it was?
What's the matter?
You need a lawyer?
No, I met someone at this party,
and I know where she works,
but I don't know her name.
So why don't you ask someone
who was at the party?
No, the only one I could ask
is Elaine.
I can't ask her.
Why not?
Because it's complicated.
There's some tension there.
He used to go with her.
Which one is she?
From Maryland.
She brought you
the chocolates you didn't like.
Oh, yeah. Very alert.
Warm person.
Oh, yeah, she's great.
So how come
nothing materialized there?
Well, it's a tough thing
to talk about.
Uh...
I don't know.
I know what it was.
You don't know what it was.
So what was it?
Well, we fight a lot
for some reason.
Oh, well.
And there was a little problem
with the physical chemistry.
Well, I think
she's a very attractive girl.
Oh, she is.
She absolutely is.
I can see if there was
a weight problem...
No, it's not that.
It wasn't all one-sided.
You know,
you can't be so particular.
Nobody's perfect.
I know, I know.
MORTY:
You know, Jerry,
it's a good thing
I wasn't so particular.
Idiot.
So who are you looking for,
Sophia Loren?
That's got nothing
to do with it.
How about
Loni Anderson?
Where do you get
Why, what's wrong
with Loni Anderson?
I like Elaine
more than Loni Anderson.
What are you two talking about?
Look, Elaine
just wasn't the one.
And this other one's
the one?
I don't know. Maybe.
So ask Elaine there
for the number.
I can't.
She'll get upset.
I never talk about
other women with her,
especially this one tonight.
How could you still see her
if you're not interested?
We're friends.
You don't sound like
you're friends to me.
If you were friends,
you'd ask her
for the number.
Do you know where
this other one works?
Oh, yeah.
So, go up
to the office.
Up to her office?
Go to the building.
She goes out to lunch,
doesn't she?
I guess.
So you stand
in the lobby
by the elevator
and wait for her
to come down for lunch.
You mean, stake out the lobby?
Morty, that's ridiculous.
Just ask Elaine
for the number.
He doesn't wanna ask
Elaine for the number.
So you got him
standing by the elevator
like a dope.
What happens
when he sees her?
He pretends
he bumped into her.
You know what?
This is not that bad an idea.
What does
she look like?
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
What actress
does she remind you of?
Loni Anderson.
Loni Anderson?
What, there's something wrong
with Loni Anderson?
Hey, listen.
Thanks again for running
over here. I appreciate it.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I was showing a condo
on 48th street.
Besides, you think
I want to miss this?
I'm a little nervous.
Yeah. Me too.
If I see her, what do I say
I'm doing in the building?
You came to see me.
I work in the building.
What do you do?
I'm an architect.
You're an architect?
I'm not?
I don't see architecture
coming from you.
I suppose
you could be an architect.
I never said
that I was the architect.
Just something else.
All right.
She's not even gonna ask.
If we see her,
which is remote.
Well, what do you want me
to say, I just wandered in here?
We're having lunch
with a friend.
He works in the building.
What is his name?
Burt Har...
binson.
Burt Harbinson.
Right.
It sounds made up.
No good?
All right. Um...
Art...
Core.
Art Core.
Velay.
Corevelay?
Yeah, right.
Well, what does he do?
He's an importer.
Just imports? No exports?
He's an importer-exporter, okay?
Did Elaine
ever call you back?
No, I guess
she's still mad.
I don't understand.
You never talk to her
about other women?
Never.
JERRY: Wait a second.
That's her, on the right.
I forgot who I am.
Who am I?
You're you.
We're having lunch
with Art Corevelay.
Vandelay.
Corevelay.
Let me be the architect.
I can do it. I can do it.
Hey, hey, uh...
Pamela's birthday party.
Didn't I see you there?
Jerry.
Sure. Hi.
Uh, this is George.
I'm sorry.
Vanessa.
Nice to meet you.
Ah, Sagman, Bennett, Robbins,
Oppenheim, and Taff.
That's right.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Ah.
Ah...
We're meeting
a friend of ours for lunch,
works in the building.
Yeah, Art Vandelay.
VANESSA:
Oh, really?
Which company?
I don't know...
Company? No.
He's an importer.
Importer.
And exporter.
He's an importer-exporter.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm a--
I'm an architect.
Really?
Well, what do you design?
Uh, railroads.
I thought engineers do that.
They can.
I'm sorry you had to leave
so early the other night.
Oh, me too.
My cousin had to go
back to Boston.
Oh, that guy
was your cousin.
Yeah...
And that woman was your--
Friend.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'll just get a paper.
So, um...
do you date immature men?
Almost exclusively.
[HELEN HUMMING]
I have no letters.
[CONTINUES HUMMING]
Ma, will you go already?
What are you doing?
Wait, I just
wanna see something.
You can't look in there.
We're playing.
Hi.
Good evening,
Mr. Kramer.
Hey, Morty.
Salad dressing?
Look.
"Quo," is that a word?
Maybe.
Will you challenge it?
Ma, you can't look up words
in the dictionary.
Dad, she's cheating.
"Quo"? That's not a word.
You're such a stickler.
Well, put something down.
You're taking 20 minutes
on this.
[SIGHS]
So is Uncle Mac and Artie--
they're all coming over here
before the wedding?
They'll be here at 2:00.
Oh, Elaine called.
She said she'd be here at 2:30,
and she says,
"Hope your meeting went well
with Art Vandelay."
She said what?
Just what I said. Here.
She knows.
Oh, I am such a jackass.
She knows what?
She knows
the whole stupid thing--
Vanessa and the elevator.
No, no, no.
That won't do.
He may have the Z.
So how did she
find out?
Because Vanessa
probably told Pamela...
and Pamela
probably told Elaine.
So, uh, what are you,
afraid of her?
Yes. Yes, I am.
What else did she say
on the phone?
Whatever I wrote down.
Yeah, but what was
the tone in her voice?
How did she sound?
Who am I, Rich Little?
Well, she can't be
too mad.
She's still coming
to the wedding.
Yeah, but now I'm nervous.
Oh, stop it.
"Quone"?
Thirty, 31...
No, I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to challenge that.
KRAMER: No, no. You don't
have to challenge.
That's a word.
That's a definite word.
I am challenging it.
Quone-- to quone something.
Uh-huh.
I'm not playing
with you anymore.
Quone's not a word.
No good. Sorry.
There it is.
Get it off.
Why did you make me
put that down?
No. We need
a medical dictionary.
Like a patient gets difficult,
you quone him.
CAROL: You wanna get
some funny material?
You ought to come down
to where I work.
There's a sitcom.
You must have
quite a time down there.
We got plenty of time.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm just waiting
for someone.
Watch what you say
to this guy.
He'll put it
in his next act.
Yeah, yeah.
Jerry, did I tell you
that I'm writing a book,
an autobiography?
Yeah, Uncle Mac,
you mentioned it.
It's based
on all my experiences.
That's perfect.
Could you excuse me one second?
Oh, sure.
I'm sorry.
How do you do?
Jerry Seinfeld.
Elaine Bennes.
[CHUCKLES]
Um, do you wanna do this now
or you wanna wait
till we get in the car?
Oh, no. Let's do it now.
All right.
The whole elevator business--
let me just explain.
Okay.
Jerry, are you going with us?
No, I'm gonna
take my car.
That's why I brought the wagon.
Why the hell
did I bring the wagon?
Anyway, you know
why I didn't ask you?
I mean, I felt so uncomfortable,
and you were so annoyed
in the cab.
Well, Jerry, I never saw you
flirt with anyone before.
It was quite the spectacle.
Jerry, we'll
see you there.
Bye, Elaine.
Oh, bye. Good to see you.
Oh, we didn't meet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Elaine...
This is my cousin
Artie "Leveen." Levine.
CAROL: Artie!
Artie! Come on.
Yeah, Levine.
And I'm Jerry
Cougar Mellencamp.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Anyway, I admit
it was a fairly
ridiculous thing to do,
but I mean,
obviously, we have
a little problem here.
Yeah, obviously.
I mean,
if we're gonna be friends,
we gotta be able to talk
about other people.
Couldn't agree more.
Good.
Great.
Great?
Where do you get great?
It's great to talk about...
other people.
Guys.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Well, anybody specific?
No.
A general guy.
Oh, really?
Elaine Marie Bennes.
What? No, it's not a big deal.
No, that's great.
That's terrific.
No, we just met.
Doesn't matter.
What's the young man's name?
I would like to meet him.
Mm...
I don't think so.
Well, what does he do?
Is he an artisan,
a craftsman,
a laborer of some sort?
Wall Street.
Ah, high finance.
Bulls, bears,
people from Connecticut.
And he happens to be
pretty good-looking.
All right, sir.
And he's hilarious.
Now, that's not fair.
So where did you meet this guy?
I staked out his health club.
Uh-huh.
When you're on a stakeout,
do you find it's better
to stand up against the wall
or kind of crouch down
behind a big plant?
You know, I think that...
even if you've had
a relationship with someone,
or let's say
especially if you've had
a relationship with someone,
and you try and become friends
afterwards,
it's very difficult.
Isn't this?
It's hard
because you know each other
so well, you know?
You know
all each other's tricks.
It's like two magicians
trying to entertain each other,
you know?
The one goes, "Look, a rabbit."
The other one goes, "So?"
I believe that's your card.
Look, why don't we just
saw each other in half
and call it a night, okay?
[♪]