I'm on the street the other day,
make a pay phone call,
go overtime on the call,
hang up the phone, walk away.
You've had this happen?
[MURMURED ASSENT FROM CROWD]
Phone rings.
It's the phone company.
They want more money.
Don't you love this?
And you've got them
right where you want them
for the first time in your life.
You're on the street.
There's nothing they can do.
I like to let it ring
a few times, you know,
let her sweat a little
over there,
and then just pick it up.
"Yeah, hello, operator?
"Oh, I've got the money.
[LAUGHTER]
"I've got the money right here.
"Do you hear that?
[TAPPING]
"That's a quarter.
Yeah, you want that, don't you?"
[♪]
No, they just have to get
more cops on the force.
It's as simple
as that.
Cops. I don't even
care about cops.
I want to see
garbage men.
It's much more important.
All I want to see
are garbage trucks,
garbage cans,
and garbage men.
You're never
gonna stop crime.
We should at least
be clean.
I tell what they should do.
They should combine
the two jobs.
Make it one job,
cop/garbage man.
I always see cops
walking around
with nothing to do.
Grab a broom.
Start sweeping.
You sweep, sweep,
sweep, sweep.
Catch a criminal,
get right back to sweeping.
You should run
for mayor.
Ah, nobody listens.
Where is someone?
I'm starving.
This is him
right here.
Is there
a table ready? How many?
How many?
Is Tatiana coming?
Well, I don't know.
I have to call her,
tell her where we are.
I'm very lucky she's even
considering seeing me at all.
Really? I thought
things were going okay.
They were.
It's...kind of complicated.
Well, what is it?
How many?
All right, uh...
Four. Seinfeld.
Four.
That'll be 5, 10 minutes.
What do you
want to do?
Let's go someplace else.
I am too hungry.
We might as well stay here.
We haven't got much time
to make the movie.
Okay. I'm gonna call Tatiana.
There's the phone.
Tatiana...
Excuse me. Are you
gonna be very long?
MAITRE D': Lasbrook, four!
So did I do
a terrible thing?
You mean
lying to your uncle?
I couldn't have
dinner with him.
Plan Nine
From Outer Space.
One night only. The big screen.
My hands are tied.
You know,
it's a public phone.
You're not supposed
to just chitchat.
Jerry, get menus
so when we sit down,
we'll be able to order
right away.
Can't look
at a menu now.
I gotta be at the table.
He knows I'm waiting.
He sees me. He just
doesn't want to look.
Everything's
gotta be just so
all the time with you,
doesn't it?
Hey, I offered you those
cookies in my house.
Health cookies.
I hate those little
dust-board fructose things.
I just can't believe
the way people are.
What is it
with humanity?
What kind of a world
do we live in?
What?
There's a woman over there
looks really familiar.
Dark hair, striped shirt.
I've never
seen her before.
I know this woman.
This is gonna
drive me crazy.
Excuse me.
Ooh, I'm sorry.
Did you see that?
Those people-- Look,
they're getting a table.
Well, maybe they were
here from before.
No, no, no,
they weren't here before.
Excuse me, are you
gonna be much longer?
I have to make
a very important call.
Jerry, find out
what's going on.
Excuse me.
Didn't those people
just come in?
I believe we were
ahead of them.
What's your name?
Seinfeld.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
No, no. They were here before.
Uh, Kackige! Two!
You ever notice
how happy people are
when they finally get a table?
They feel so special
because they've been chosen.
It's enough to make you sick.
Boy, you are really hungry.
[WHISTLES]
Hey!
If anything happens here,
can I count on you?
What?
If we decide to go at it.
Yeah, I want to get
into a rumble.
I have to get in touch
with Tatiana.
Look at his
little outfit.
It's all so
coordinated.
The little socks
match the little shirt.
I really hate this guy.
Oh, I'm gonna faint.
George...
Who is that woman
in the stripes?
I don't know her.
She looks so familiar.
You know, it's not fair
that people are seated
first come, first serve.
It should be based
on who's hungriest.
I feel like
just walking over there
and taking some food
off of somebody's plate.
I'll tell you what.
There's 50 bucks in it for you
if you do it.
What do you mean?
You walk over
to that table,
you pick up an egg roll,
you don't say anything...
you eat it,
say, "Thank you very much,"
wipe your mouth, walk away,
I give you 50 bucks.
What are they
gonna do?
They won't do anything.
In fact...
you'll be giving them
a story to tell
for the rest
of their lives.
50 bucks?
You'll give me 50 bucks?
50 bucks.
That table over there.
The three couples.
Okay, I don't want
to go over there
and do it
and then come back here
and find out there was
some little loophole,
like I didn't put
mustard on it or something.
No. No tricks.
Should I do it, George?
For 50 bucks?
I'd put my face
in their soup and blow.
All right.
Here, hold this.
I'm doing it.
[QUIETLY]
I know this sounds crazy,
but the two men
who are standing behind me
are gonna give me 50 bucks
if I stand here
and eat one of your egg rolls.
I'll give you 25
if you let me do it.
What?
What is she
talking about?
What'd she say?
What did she say?
Will someone tell me
what she said?
What did she say?
What happened?
Did you see that?
What were you
telling them?
I offered them 25.
They had no idea why.
George, the phone's free.
Hallelujah.
Excuse me.
I-I was waiting here.
What, I didn't see you.
I've been standing here
for the last 10 minutes.
I won't be long.
Um, that's not
the point.
The point is I was here first.
Well, if you were here first,
you'd be holding the phone.
You know, we're living
in a society!
We're supposed to act
in a civilized way!
Does she care?
No.
Does anyone ever display
the slightest sensitivity
over the problems
of a fellow individual?
No. No.
A resounding no.
Hey. Sorry
I took so long.
Oh, that's okay. Really,
don't worry about it.
How do people fast?
Did Gandhi
get this crazy?
I'm gonna go walk around
and see what dishes
look good.
I told my uncle I had
a stomachache tonight.
You think he bought that?
Yeah, he...
probably
bought it.
So, what happened
with Tatiana?
I shouldn't even tell you.
Come on.
Well, after dinner last week,
she invites me
back to her apartment.
I'm with you.
Well, it's this little place
with this little bathroom,
and it's, like, right there,
you know?
It's not even down a little hall
or off in an alcove,
you understand?
There's no...buffer zone.
So...
we start to fool around,
and it's the first time,
and it's early in the going,
and I begin to perceive
this impending...
intestinal requirement...
whose needs are going to surpass
by great lengths
anything in the sexual realm.
So I know I'm gonna
have to stop,
and as this is happening,
I'm thinking even if I can
somehow manage to momentarily...
extricate myself
from the proceedings
and relieve
this unstoppable force,
I know that that bathroom
is not gonna provide me
with the privacy
that I know I'm going to need...
This could only
happen to you.
So, uh...
I finally stop and say, um...
"Tatiana, I hope you don't
take this the wrong way,
but I think it would be best
if I left."
You said this
to her...after?
No.
During.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Wow. So?
So I'm dressing,
and she's staring up at me,
struggling to compute this
unprecedented turn of events.
I don't know what to say
to reassure this woman,
and worst of all,
I don't have the time to say it.
The only excuse
she might possibly have accepted
is if I told her
I am in reality Batman,
and I'm very sorry,
I just saw the Bat signal.
It took me three days
of phone calls
to get her to agree
to see me again.
Now she's waiting
for me to call,
and she's still
on the phone.
I hate this place.
I don't know why
we came here.
I am never coming
back here again.
Who is that woman?
Remember when you first went out
to eat with your parents?
Remember?
It was such a treat to go.
And they serve you
this different food
that you never saw before,
and they put it in front of you,
and it was such a delicious
and exciting adventure.
And now I just feel
like a big, sweaty hog
waiting for them
to fill up the trough.
Oh.
She's off.
Jerry,
talk to that guy again.
What am I gonna say?
Tell him we want
to catch a movie
and that we're late.
Hey.
What stinks in here?
Mr. Cohen, haven't seen you
for a couple of weeks.
Well, I've been looking
for a better place.
[LAUGHS]
Better place.
Want a--?
Want a table?
No, just bring me a plate,
and I'll eat here.
Bring him a plate.
He'll eat here!
Come on. I'll give you a table.
Excuse me.
We've been waiting here.
Now, I know we were ahead
of that guy. He just came in.
Oh, no. Mr. Cohen always here.
He's always here.
What does that mean?
Oh, Mr. Cohen very nice man.
He live on Park Avenue.
Where am I?
Is this a dream?
What in God's name
is going on here?
She's not there.
She left.
She must have waited and left
because those people
wouldn't get off the phone.
Did you leave a message?
Yeah, I told her to call me here
and to tell anyone that answers
the phone
to ask for a balding stocky man
with glasses.
I better tell them
I'm expecting a call.
Uh, Jerry,
here comes that woman.
Where do I know her?
Hi, Jerry.
Hey!
How are you doing?
How is everything?
Good, good, good.
What's going on?
Oh, working hard. And you?
Oh, you know,
working around.
Same stuff.
Doing...
whatever.
Well, you haven't been
around in a while.
I know.
I know. Well...
You know.
You should come by.
Definitely.
I plan to.
I'm not just
saying that.
Hi. I'm Elaine.
Oh, Lorraine Catalano.
I'm sorry.
Lorraine,
this is Elaine.
[SIGHS]
Well, it was nice
seeing you, Jerry...
and nice meeting you.
Oh, nice to meet you too,
Lorraine.
Oh, my God, Lorraine.
That's Lorraine
from my uncle's office.
I am in big,
big trouble.
The one you broke
the plans with tonight?
Yeah, she works in his office.
Now she's gonna
see him tomorrow
and tell him she saw me here
tonight.
He's gonna tell his wife.
His wife's gonna
call my mother...
Oh, this is bad.
You don't know.
The chain reaction
of calls
this is gonna set off.
New York,
Long Island, Florida.
It's like
the Bermuda Triangle.
Unfortunately,
nobody ever disappears.
My uncle to my aunt,
my aunt to my mother,
my mother to my uncle...
And my uncle
to my cousin,
my cousin to my sister,
my sister to me...
You should've just had dinner
with your uncle tonight
and gotten it over with.
It's just a movie.
Just a movie?
You don't understand.
This isn't Plans 1-8
From Outer Space.
This is Plan 9.
This is the one
that worked,
the worst movie ever made.
I'm really
looking forward to it.
Hey. I got news
for you.
If we're making
this movie,
we gotta get a table
immediately.
All right. Look it. Let's stop
fooling around.
Let's just slip him some money.
In a Chinese restaurant?
Do they take money?
Everyone takes money.
I went out with a guy
who did it all the time.
You just slip them 20 bucks.
Twenty bucks?
Isn't that excessive?
Well, what do you wanna
give him, change?
It's more
than the meal.
Oh, come on.
We'll divide it up
three ways.
All right.
Seven, seven...
six.
I'm not gonna
eat that much.
I'm counting
your shrimps.
Okay,
who's gonna do it?
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
I'm not good at these things.
I get flustered.
Once I tried
to bribe an usher
at the roller derby.
I almost got arrested.
I guess it's you, Jer.
Me? What about you?
Oh, I can't do that.
It's a guy thing.
The women's movement
just can't seem
to make any progress
in the world of bribery,
can they?
Give me the money.
[COUGHS]
How's it going?
Very busy.
Boy, we are
really anxious
to sit down.
Very good specials
tonight.
If there's anything
you can do
to get us a table,
we'd really
appreciate it.
Oh, what is your name?
No, no.
I want to eat now.
Yes,
whole sea bass dinner tonight,
very fresh.
Here. Take this.
I'm starving.
Take it.
Uh...Dennison, four!
Your table is ready.
No, no, no.
I want that table!
I want that table.
Oh, come on. Did you see that?
What was that?
He took the money.
He didn't give us
a table.
You lost the 20.
Well...
How could he do that?
You didn't make it clear.
Make it clear?
What a sorry exhibition
that was.
All right,
let me get
the money back.
Excuse me.
I realize this is
extremely embarrassing.
My friend here apparently
made a mistake.
Your name?
Seinfeld.
Yes, Seinfeld, four.
No, no, no.
Do you see the girl
with the long hair?
Oh, yes, yes.
Very beautiful girl.
Very beautiful.
Your girlfriend?
Well, actually, we did date
for a while, but...
that's really
not relevant here.
Relationships are difficult.
It is very hard
to stay together.
All right, listen.
All right.
How much longer
is it gonna be?
Oh...
Be about five, 10 minutes.
GEORGE: So?
There seems to be
a bit of a discrepancy.
So when are
we gonna eat?
Five, 10 minutes.
Oh.
We should've
left earlier.
I told you.
I don't see any way
we can eat
and make this movie.
Oh, well, I have to eat.
Let's order it to go.
We'll eat it in the cab.
Eat it in the cab?
Chinese food in a cab?
We'll eat it
in the movie.
Where do you think
you're going?
Do you think that they have
big picnic tables there?
Well, what do you
suggest?
I say we leave now,
we go to Sky Burger,
and we scarf 'em down.
I'm not going
to Sky Burger.
Besides,
it's in the
opposite direction.
Let's just eat popcorn
or something.
Cartwright?
I can't have popcorn for dinner.
MAITRE D':
Cartwright!
I have to eat!
Well, they have
hot dogs there.
Oh, movie hot dogs.
I'd rather lick the food
off the floor.
I can't go anyway.
I have to wait here
for Tatiana's call.
Let me just check.
Excuse me.
I'm expecting a call.
Costanza.
Yes. I just got a call.
I yell...Cartwright!
Cartwright!
Just like that.
Nobody came up. I hang up.
Well, was it
for Costanza or...
Yes, yes, that's it.
Nobody answered.
Was it a woman?
Yes, yes.
I tell her you not here.
She said curse word. I hang up.
She called.
He yelled, "Cartwright."
I missed her.
Who's Cartwright?
I'm Cartwright.
You're not Cartwright.
Of course I'm not Cartwright!
Look, why don't you two
just go to the movies
by yourself.
I'm not in the mood.
Well, me either.
I'm going to Sky Burger.
So you're not going?
You don't need us.
I can't go
to a bad movie
by myself.
What, am I gonna make
sarcastic remarks
to strangers?
I guess I'll just go
to my uncle's.
Should we tell him
we're leaving?
Oh, what for?
Let's just get out of here.
Seinfeld, four!
Hunger will make people
do amazing things.
I mean, the proof of that
is cannibalism.
Cannibalism. What...?
What do they say?
I mean, they're eating,
you know?
"This is good. Who is this?
I like this person."
You know, I mean...
I would think the hardest thing
about being a cannibal
is trying to get
some really deep sleep.
You know what I mean?
I would think you'd be like...
"What is it? Who is that?
Who's there?
"Who's there? Is somebody there?
"What do you want?
What do you want?
"You look hungry.
Are you hungry?
Get out of here."
[♪]