I hate clothes, okay?
I hate buying them,
I hate picking them
out of my closet.
I can't stand every day
trying to come up
with little outfits for myself.
I think, eventually,
fashion won't even exist.
It won't.
I think, eventually,
we'll all be wearing
the same thing.
Because any time
I see a movie or a TV show
where there's people
from the future
or another planet,
they're all
wearing the same thing.
Somehow, they decided,
"This is going
to be our outfit.
"One-piece silver jump suit,
V-stripe and boots.
That's it."
We should come up
with an outfit for Earth.
An Earth outfit.
We should vote on it,
candidates propose
different outfits,
no speeches.
They walk out, twirl, walk off.
We just sit
in the audience and go,
That was nice.
I could wear that."
I think
I've seen enough.
Well, I might have
something in the back.
The back? They never find
anything in the back.
If they had anything good,
they'd put it out in the front.
Why don't they open up
an entire store for the back?
Call it "Just Back."
All back.
No front.
You walk in the front,
you're immediately in the back.
Look, Elaine. Tie carwash.
Oh, I just read that.
That's terrific.
Her father wrote that.
Alton Benes is your father?
Yeah, uh-huh.
I always felt he deserved
a wider audience.
I'm not so sure he wants one.
Oh...
Hey, don't forget Sunday, okay?
You and George are coming,
right? Hotel Westbury, 8:00.
Yeah, I guess I'm coming.
I mean...
What? What, you don't
want to go now?
No, I'll go. I'm going.
No, Jerry you have to.
I need a buffer.
You know, I haven't seen
my father in a while...
I'm worried I won't
be able to talk to him.
He's such a great writer.
Frankly, I prefer
the company of nitwits.
So that's why
we're not together anymore.
Pfft. Aah! Aah!
What is this?
This is beautiful.
These jackets
never fit me right.
Try it on.
Mm. Wow.
This is soft suede.
This may be
the most perfect jacket
I have ever put on.
How much is it?
[GASP]
Oh...my God.
Bad?
Very bad?
You have no idea.
I have some idea.
No idea.
I've got a ballpark.
There is no park,
and the team has relocated.
Let me see that.
That is high.
Oh, man, that is
a beautiful jacket, though.
What's with the pink lining
with the candy stripes?
I don't know,
it's just a lining,
you can always
have it changed.
Should I get it?
I hate these moments.
I'm hearing the dual voices now,
you know.
"What about the money?"
"What's money?"
It looks
wonderful on you.
[CROWD CHEERING ON TV]
[SHUTS OFF TV]
Hey.
New jacket.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
Is it me?
That's definitely you.
Really?
That's more you
than you've ever been.
Hey, what is with
the pink lining?
I don't know.
It's got a pink lining.
So, what did
you pay for this?
I paid what it costs.
How much?
What's the difference?
What, you're not
gonna tell me?
I'd rather not say it out loud.
It's embarrassing.
Over 300?
Yes, but let's just
stop it right there.
It's over 400?
I'm really not
answering anymore.
Is it over 400?
Would you...?
Whoa, Nelson.
I know. I know.
What are you going to do
with the leather one?
I don't know.
Are you going
to wear it?
I don't know, maybe.
You're not going
to wear this.
Do you want it?
Uh, yeah, okay, I'll take it.
I like that jacket.
Okay. Take it.
Hey...
good karma for you.
Oh, baby.
♪ Master of the house
Doling out the charm ♪
♪ Ready with the handshake
And an open palm ♪
♪ Tells a saucy tale
Loves to make a stir ♪
What is that song?
Everyone appreciates
a bon-- ♪
It's from "Les Misérables."
I went to see it last week.
I can't get it out of my head.
I just keep singing it
over and over.
It just comes out.
I have no control over it.
I'm singing it
on elevators, buses,
singing it
in front of clients.
It's taking over my life.
You know,
Schumann went mad from that.
Artie Schumann
from Camp Hatchapee?
No, you idiot.
What are you, Bud Abbott?
What are you calling me
an idiot for?
You don't know
Robert Schumann, the composer?
Oh, Schumann. Of course.
He went crazy from one note.
Couldn't get it out of his head.
I think it was an A.
He kept repeating it
over and over again.
He had to be institutionalized.
Really?
Well, what if it doesn't stop?
Oh, that I really
needed to hear.
That helps a lot.
All right, just say something.
Just start talking.
Change the subject.
Let's just go, all right?
I can't believe we're having
dinner with Alton Benes.
I know exactly
what's gonna happen tonight.
I'm gonna try and act
like I'm not impressed.
He's gonna see through it.
Yeah, he'll be
looking at us
like he's backstage
at a puppet show.
Let me just get
my jacket.
♪ Master of the house
Keeper of the inn-- ♪
[SIGHS]
This is huge.
When did this happen?
Wednesday.
This jacket has completely
changed my life.
When I leave
the house in this,
it's with
a whole different confidence.
Like, tonight I might have been
a little nervous,
but inside this jacket,
I am composed, grounded,
secure that I can meet
any social challenge.
Can I say
one thing to you?
And I say this with
an unblemished record
of staunch heterosexuality.
Absolutely.
It's fabulous.
I know.
And I'll tell you
something else.
I'm not even gonna
ask you.
I want to know,
but I'm not gonna ask.
You'll tell me
when you feel comfortable.
So, what was it, 400?
Four hundred?
Five hundred?
Did you pay 500 for this?
Over 6?
Can't be 7.
Don't tell me you paid
$700 for this jacket.
Did you pay $700?
Is that what
you're saying to me?
You are sick!
Is that what you paid
for this jacket?
Over 700?
What did you pay
for this jacket?
I won't say anything.
I want to know what
you paid for this jacket.
Oh, my God!
A thousand dollars?
You paid a thousand dollars
for this jacket.
All right, fine,
I'm walking out of here
right now
thinking you paid
a thousand dollars
for this jacket,
unless you
tell me different.
Hah-hah! Oh!
All right,
I'll tell you what,
if you don't say anything
in the next five seconds,
I'll know
it was over a thousand.
Hey. Hey, will you
do me a solid?
Well, what kind of solid?
Sit in the car two minutes
while it's double-parked.
I gotta pick up some birds.
Birds?
Yeah, a friend of mine,
he's a magician,
he's going away and asked me
to take care of his doves.
So take a cab.
They won't take
a cage full of birds.
I can't, I'm on my way out.
There's no way I can do it.
George, do me a solid.
Two minutes.
Well, I'm going with him.
I'd like to.
I've never done
a solid before.
All right. I'll... Yeah.
All right, have a good one.
Two minutes.
Believe me,
I know his two minutes.
By his conception of time,
his life will last
over 2000 years.
♪ Master of the house
Quick to catch your eye ♪
♪ Never wants a passerby
To pass him by... ♪
Schumann.
Where are they?
Maybe he didn't show up.
What, you don't want
to do this?
I don't think there's ever been
an appointment in my life
where I wanted
the other guy to show up.
Wait a second.
Is that him?
Yeah. I think it is.
Where's Elaine?
I'm nervous.
Excuse me,
Mr. Benes.
Yeah?
I'm Jerry,
Elaine's friend.
This is George.
It's a great thrill
to meet you, sir.
[COUGHING]
Sit down.
Want a drink?
Sure.
What will you have?
I'll have a cranberry juice
with two limes.
And, uh, I'll have
a club soda with no ice.
I'll have another scotch
with plenty of ice.
You like ice.
Huh?
I said, do you like ice?
Like it?
Don't you find that
you get more without it?
Where's Elaine?
Well, we thought she was
meeting you earlier.
She's usually
pretty punctual.
Don't you find that, George?
Yeah. Yeah, she's, uh...
She's punctual.
And, uh...
She's been late sometimes.
Yeah, yeah.
Sometimes she's on time,
and...sometimes she's late.
I guess...
today, she's late.
It appears that way.
Yup.
Looks like rain.
I know, I know.
That's what they said.
Who said?
Uh, the weather guy,
Dr. Waldo.
I don't need anybody
to tell me it's going to rain.
Oh, no. Of course not. I--
All I have to do
is stick my head out the window.
Which one's supposed to be
the funny guy?
Oh, he's the comedian.
I-- I'm just
a regular person.
Nah, nah.
He's just being modest.
We had a funny guy
with us in Korea.
A tail gunner.
They blew his brains out
all over the Pacific.
There's nothing funny
about that.
Would you excuse me
a minute?
I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Ahem.
I just wanted to tell you
that I really enjoyed Fair Game.
I thought it was just brilliant.
Drivel.
Yeah, well, maybe some parts.
What parts?
The, uh...
drivel parts.
Oh, my gosh.
I just realized
I have to make a phone call.
I can't believe...
Would you--? I'll...
I'll be right back.
Thank you
for leaving me alone with him.
That was brutal.
I can't go back out there.
Well, let's just leave.
Elaine will kill me.
Where is she?
She's got to be
here soon.
How could she leave us
alone with this lunatic?
10 more minutes,
and that's it.
I'm leaving.
I have to tell you,
this guy scares me.
The waiter was trembling.
If she doesn't show up,
we can't possibly
have dinner with him alone.
How are we gonna
get out of it?
We'll say we're frightened
and we have to go home.
Yeah. That's good.
He'd clunk our heads
together like Moe.
I don't know.
Just...start scratching.
Tell him you have the crabs.
He was in the military.
He'll understand that.
All fathers are intimidating.
They're intimidating
because they are fathers.
Once a man has children,
for the rest of his life,
his attitude is,
"The hell with the world.
"I can make my own people.
"I'll eat whatever I want,
"I'll wear whatever I want,
and I'll create whoever I want."
Who'd you call?
My...uh, uncle is, um...
having an operation.
I just wanted
to see how he was.
What kind of an operation?
Bone marrow.
Mr. Benes?
Yeah?
Message for you.
From Elaine.
She got tied up.
She'll be here in 30 minutes.
ALTON:
Yeah, they should have
taken care of Castro
when they had the chance,
Like we did
in Guatemala in '53.
Well, Guatemala...
Sure. Guatemala.
All right.
You boys
get yourselves together.
We'll head up
to the restaurant.
I'll leave a note
for Elaine.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Come on. Let's go.
What about Elaine?
Hell with Elaine.
She'll be furious.
We're dying here!
That's her. She's here.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Where is Dad?
[IMITATING ALTON]
He's in the bathroom.
Where have you been?
Kramer. That Kramer.
I'm just about to leave.
He calls me up.
He begs me to sit in his car
for two minutes
so he can pick up
these...birds.
Oh, you didn't?
Well, he said he'd drive me here
right after.
So I am sitting in his car
for 20 minutes!
He doesn't come down.
I am freezing.
Then a cop comes by.
Tells me to get out of the car.
He's a city marshal.
He's towing the car away.
Kramer owes thousands
of dollars in back tickets.
He was going to tow it
with me in the car.
So they tow the car.
Now I am standing outside,
and I am freezing,
but I cannot leave
because I gotta tell him
what happened to the car.
So finally, he--
Finally, he comes down
with this giant cage
filled with doves.
He said he was getting
special instructions,
that each dove
has a different diet.
So we're wandering around,
trying to get a cab,
when two of these doves fly out.
Now we're running down
the street after these doves.
I almost got hit by a bus.
Whew.
So how's everything
going over here?
Great.
Couldn't be better.
Good.
Because Dad can make some people
a little uncomfortable.
Oh, no.
Get out of here.
Man, Kramer.
I could kill him.
You know better than
to get involved with Kramer.
He said he'd give me a lift.
Ah, the lift.
Like the lure
of the siren's song.
Never what it seems to be,
yet who among us
can resist?
Where do you come up
with this stuff?
Well, look who's here.
Oh, hi, Dad.
Hello, dear.
Who's the lipstick for?
No one.
How's your mother?
Fine.
How about you?
Are you working?
Yeah. I'm reading manuscripts
for Pendant Publishing.
I told you 10 times.
Pendant? Those bastards.
Well, all right, boys.
We're going to
that Pakistani restaurant
on 46th Street.
You're not afraid
of a little spice, are you?
♪ Master of the house
Doling out the charm ♪
♪ Ready with the handshake
And an open-- ♪
Pipe down, chorus boy.
Ooh, it's snowing.
It's beautiful.
Snow?
Snow, that can't be good
for suede, can it?
I wouldn't think so.
What should I do?
We're taking a cab,
aren't we?
Cab?
It's only five blocks.
Why don't you
turn it inside out?
Inside out. Great.
Wait a minute.
What the hell do you call this?
I turned my jacket inside out.
Well, you look like
a damn fool.
Well, it's a new suede jacket.
It might get ruined.
You're not walking
down the street
with me and my daughter
dressed like that.
That's for damn sure.
It's, uh...
It's only a few blocks.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Elaine?
Yeah.
Come on up.
Hey.
I got to feed the birds.
So?
You got any
of those Mini Ritzes?
I can't believe that I do.
What, are you going out?
Yeah.
Hey, where's your new jacket?
What?
Oh, what did you do to it?
I was out in the snow
last night.
Don't you know
what that does to suede?
I have an idea.
We can make the 9:30
at Cinema Three.
Okay.
[COLDLY]
Hello.
Listen, thanks again
for coming last night.
Dad said he had a great time.
Is he's still in town?
No, he's driving
back to Maryland tonight.
So, uh, what are you going to do
with that one now?
I don't know.
Well.
I didn't want
to tell you this,
but usually
he hates everyone.
Really?
You going to throw this out?
Well, I can't wear it.
Yeah, he liked you, though.
Said you reminded him
of somebody he knew in Korea.
Well, if you're
just gonna throw it out,
you know, I could take it.
Yeah. Go ahead. Take it.
Dad thinks George is gay.
Oh, because of all the singing?
No. He pretty much thinks
everyone is gay.
Hey. See, I like it like this.
[GASPS]
Isn't that...?
Oh! Oh!
Is this from the snow
last night?
You know
what you should have done?
You should have
turned it inside out.
I'll try and remember that.
Boy, it's too bad
you gave me this one too.
Yeah. Too bad.
Yeah, well...
I'm going to have to do
something about this lining.
♪ Master of the house
Turning on the charm ♪
♪ Ready with a handshake
And an open palm ♪
I had a leather jacket
that got ruined.
Now, why does moisture
ruin leather?
I don't get this.
Aren't cows
outside most of the time?
I don't understand this.
When it's raining,
do cows go up to the farmhouse,
"Let us in.
We're all wearing leather!
"Open the door.
We're going to ruin
the whole outfit here!"
"Is it suede?"
"I am suede.
The whole thing is suede.
I can't have this cleaned.
It's all I've got."
[♪]