You know, I tell you,
I gotta say
that I'm enjoying adulthood
for a lot of reasons,
and I'll tell you
reason number one.
As an adult,
if I want a cookie,
I have a cookie, okay?
I have three cookies
or four cookies,
or 11 cookies if I want.
Many times,
I will intentionally ruin
my entire appetite.
Just ruin it...
and then I call my mother up
right after
to tell her that I did it.
Hello, Mom? Yeah, I just
ruined my entire appetite.
Cookies.
So what if you ruin it?
See, because as an adult,
we understand
even if you ruin an appetite,
there's another appetite
coming right behind it.
There's no danger
in running out of appetites.
I've got millions of them.
I ruin them whenever I want.
[SCI-FI TELEVISION PROGRAM
PLAYING]
Look, Sigmond,
look at the sky!
The planet's on fire.
It is just as you prophesied--
The planets of our solar system
incinerating
like flaming globes, Sigmond,
like flaming globes!
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
Sigmond...
[CHUCKLES]
[♪]
Thank you.
What do you got,
a cucumber?
Yeah. So what?
You're bringing in
an outside cucumber?
They refuse to put cucumber
in the salad. I need cucumber.
What have I done?
I can't read this.
"Fullman...
Hurtel...vom"?
I got up last night,
I wrote this down
I thought I had
this great bit.
Wait a second.
"Fax me some halibut."
Is that funny?
Is that a joke?
Let me see that.
"Don't mess
with Johnny."
Johnny? Johnny who?
Johnny Carson?
Did I insult Johnny
on The Tonight Show?
Did you mess
with Johnny, Jerry?
Let me see that.
Hey, where's Kramer?
I don't know.
That's like asking
"Where's Waldo?"
I think I'm having
a heart attack.
I don't think that's it.
I'm not kidding.
What does that mean?
I think what
he's trying to say
is that he's having
a heart attack.
Oh, he's having
Tightness.
Come on.
Shortness
of breath.
Oh, this is
ridiculous.
Radiating waves of pain.
I know what
this is.
You saw that show
on PBS last night,
Coronary Country.
I saw it in
the TV Guide.
I called him
told him
make sure
and not watch it.
There was nothing else on.
Have some water--
Oh, the left arm!
Left arm.
He saw that show
on anorexia last year,
ate like an animal
for two weeks.
Why can't I have a heart attack?
I'm allowed!
So what do you want?
You want me to take you
to the hospital?
Manhattan Memorial.
Less of a line.
I'll call an ambulance.
Is everything
all right?
We'll just take a check.
You made a mistake on the--
George!
[SIRENS WAILING]
PATIENT: Aah...
Are you okay?
Ooh!
I'm George.
George Costanza.
I never been in a hospital
a day in my life...
except when I had
my tonsils out.
You know, they never gave me
any ice cream.
I always felt that if they--
Shut up!
Well, what do you think?
"Salami, salami,
bologna." Definitely.
Salami, salami, bologna?
Oh, your friend's fine.
He didn't have
a heart attack.
I'll be in
in a few minutes.
What a surprise.
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
You need anything?
You want me to go out
and get you a Superman comic?
No. No, thanks.
You know, I was wondering.
You know that Blackhawks jacket
you have?
Oh, sure, my Blackhawks jacket.
I love my Blackhawks jacket.
Well, You know, I was thinking,
if things don't exactly...
work out.
Well, it wouldn't fit you. The
sleeves are too short.
No, I tried it on. It fits good.
I didn't think about what I was
gonna do with all the... things.
Well, you know...
Well...
Well, okay.
Oh, and do you think
it would be all right
if called Susan Davis?
Susan Davis? Hey, wait a second!
Well, it's not like
we'll be bumping into you.
I don't know.
You and Susan Davis?
You know, if...
your future
was a little more certain...
Okay.
Go ahead, call her.
Get married. Have babies.
Have a great life.
What do I care?
I'm finished.
It's all over for me.
In fact...
let's end it right now.
Jerry... kill me.
Kill me now. I'm begging you.
Let's- let's just
get it over with. Be a pal.
Just take the pillow
and put it over my face.
Well, uh...
What, kind of like this?
What- What are you--
Jerry! Jerry!
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
Jerry!
[COUGHING]
Elaine, what are
you doing here?
Jerk off.
There's nothing
wrong with him.
I saw the doctor.
He's fine.
Hi, George.
How you feeling?
Is anybody getting
your apartment?
I tell you, if I ever
get out of here,
I'm gonna change my life.
I'm going to do
a whole Zen thing.
Take up yoga.
Meditate.
I'll eat right.
Calm down.
Lose my anger.
Hey! Is anybody
listening!
Hello.
Mr. Costanza...
Uh, yeah,
you know, doc,
I gotta tell you,
I feel a lot better.
Well, we looked at your EKGs,
ran some tests,
did a complete workup.
Oh, God. Mommy!
Well, you simply haven't
had a heart attack.
I haven't?
I'm okay?
I'm okay? Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
Doctor, I don't know how
to thank you.
Hey, that was
really fun, George.
Can we go home now?
No, actually, we'd like
to keep him here overnight
for observation
just to be safe.
Oh, sure, sure. Anything.
Can you believe it?
There's nothing wrong with me.
Well, I wouldn't go
that far.
What? Oh, my God. What?
Is it meningitis? Scoliosis?
Lupus! Is it Lupus?
Have you ever had
your tonsils taken out?
My tonsils?
Yeah, when I was a kid.
Well, they've grown back.
Your adenoids
are swollen too.
Really?
Oh, whose tonsils
grow back?
Oh, it happens.
Yeah, if you've been
exposed to gamma rays.
I still have my tonsils.
Everyone in my family
has their tonsils.
In fact, we were
forbidden to socialize
with anybody
who didn't have their tonsils.
That's interesting.
Because no one in my family
has their tonsils.
and we were forbidden
to socialize
with tonsil people.
[LAUGHS]
Well, it's like the Capulets
and the Montagues.
Excuse me.
Anyway, I strongly recommend
they come out.
What, you mean with a knife?
Yes, with a knife.
You know, snip, snip.
[CHUCKLES]
Anyway, you'd be
completely under,
you wouldn't feel a thing,
and when you wake up,
you can have some ice cream.
Yeah, that's what they told me
the last time.
Think about it.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I just have to ask that doctor
one more... question.
Women go after doctors
like men go after models.
They want someone
with knowledge of the body.
We just want the body.
Hey.
Boy! They got
a great cafeteria downstairs.
Hot food, sandwiches,
a salad bar.
It's like Sizzler
opened up a hospital.
So how did you have
a heart attack?
I mean, you're a young man.
What were you doing?
They gonna do a zipper job?
Oh, they love to do zipper jobs.
Kramer...
The really bad thing
about the heart
is the sex thing.
See, you got to be careful
about sex now.
You get that heart pumping--
[PANTS]
Suddenly, boom!
Next thing you know, you got
a hose coming out of your chest
attached to a piece of luggage.
Kramer, George didn't
have a heart attack.
No? That's good.
I have to have
my tonsils taken out.
Oh, man, no!
George, we gotta get you
out of here.
Get out right now.
They'll kill you in here.
It's routine surgery.
Oh yeah?
My friend, Bob Saccomanno,
he came in here
for a hernia operation.
Oh, yeah, routine surgery.
Now he's sitting around
in a chair by the window
going...
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
"My name is Bob!"
George, whatever you do,
don't let them cut you.
Don't let them cut you.
Well, what
should I do, Kramer?
Well, for one thing,
don't listen to him.
I'll tell you what you do.
You go to Tor Eckman.
Tor! Tor,
he'll fix you right up.
He's a- he's an herbalist,
a healer, George.
He's not just gonna fix
the tonsils and the adenoids.
He is gonna change
the whole way you function.
Body and mind.
Eckman? I thought
he was doing time.
No, no, he's out. He got out.
See, the medical
establishment...
see, they tried to frame him.
It's all politics,
but he's a rebel.
A rebel?
Mm-hmm.
No, Johnny Yuma
was a rebel.
Eckman is a nut.
George, you want to
take care of your tonsils,
you do it in a hospital
with a doctor.
He's holistic.
George, he's holistic.
Holistic?
Yeah.
That sounds right.
George, you need
a medical doctor.
Let me ask you
something.
How much do you think
it would cost
to have tonsils
and adenoids removed
in a hospital?
Well, an overnight
stay in a hospital,
minor surgery...
I don't know.
Four grand.
Uh-huh.
How much does
the healer charge?
First visit? 38 bucks.
Oh yeah. Holistic.
That's what I need.
That's the answer.
So how do you like the way
I talked you
into coming down here?
Don't flatter yourself,
my friend.
I'm here strictly for material,
and I have a feeling
this is a potential gold mine.
I still think
you're nuts, though.
All I know is I've been
going to doctors all my life.
What's it gotten me?
I'm 33 years old,
I haven't outgrown
the problems of puberty,
I'm already facing
the problems of old age.
I completely skipped
healthy adulthood.
I went from having orgasms
immediately,
to taking forever.
You can do your taxes
in the time it takes me
to have an orgasm.
I've never had a normal...
medium orgasm.
I never had
a really good pickle.
Besides, what's it
gonna cost me, 38 bucks?
Would you not put
your foot on that, please?
Sorry.
[CHIMES CYMBALS]
What month were you born?
April.
You should have been
born in August.
Your parents would have been
well advised to wait.
Really?
Do you use hot water
in the shower?
Yes.
Stop using it.
Okay.
I'm off hot water.
Kramer tells me
that you are interested
in an alternative to surgery.
Yes. Yes, I am.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
I think
we can help you.
See, unfortunately,
the medical establishment
is a business
like any other business,
and business needs customers,
and they want to sell you
their most expensive item,
which is
unnecessary surgery.
Can I use hot water
on my face?
No. You know,
I am not a businessman.
I am a holistic healer.
It's a calling,
it's a gift.
You see,
it's in the best interest
of the medical profession
that you remain sick.
See that insures
good business.
You're not a patient,
you're a customer.
And you're not a doctor,
but you play one in real life.
What about shaving?
You're eating
too much dairy.
May I?
I guess so.
[EXHALES]
Uhn... Uhn...
Uhn?
Ah, you see?
You are in disharmony.
The throat is the gateway
to the lung.
Tonsillitis, adenoiditis is,
in Chinese medical terms,
an invasion of heat and wind.
There's some hot air
blowing in here.
You know,
I lived with the Eskimos
many years ago,
and they used to plunge
their faces into the snow.
Can it be lukewarm?
Too much dairy?
You really think I'm
eating too much dairy?
The tongue...
Yes, the tongue,
or in medical terms, the glossa.
It's a muscular organ.
It consists of
two parts, the body-- Uh-huh.
and the root.
Uh-huh.
You see, it's covered
by this mucous membrane--
Uh-huh.
and these raised little projections here--
are the papillae.
Ah...
It's what gives it
its furred appearance.
Ah...
Very tactile.
Uh-huh.
[CHUCKLING]
Your tea
is ready now.
This will solve
your so-called tonsil problem.
It's a special concoction.
It contains cramp bark--
I love cramp bark.
Plus cleavers.
Cleaver? I once had
cleaver as a kid.
I was able
to lift a car!
And some couch grass.
Couch grass and cramp bark?
You know, I think
that's what killed Curly.
Go ahead, drink it, George.
Excuse me, Tor.
May I ask you
a question?
You have intuitive
abilities.
You're in touch
with a lot of cosmic
kind of things.
I have this note
I can't read.
I was wondering if...
[LAUGHS]
Oh, yes!
Yes!
Mm-hmm.
"Cleveland 117,
San Antonio 109."
Go ahead, George, drink it.
[SLURPS]
Hey, that's not too bad.
I'm an eggplant!
I'm a minstrel man!
I didn't take
your Chuckles, man!
I had five Chuckles.
I ate the green one
and the yellow one,
and the red one is missing!
I don't even like Chuckles!
Maybe he doesn't like them.
That's possible.
My face! My face!
Get me to the hospital!
I want that Chuckle back,
you hear me?
You want me
to get you a Chuckle?
Pull over!
Pull over?
Did you say pull over?
You want
a piece of me?
You're gonna fight?
No! I'm a mutant!
Hey!
Let me drive!
Come on, man,
pull over!
All right, I'm gonna
mess you up, man!
Really, gentlemen, please.
Oh, my heart! My heart!
Where are you going?
Are you crazy?
I'm going
to kick his ass!
Hey, you have keys?
Hey, you can't leave!
This is an ambulance!
This is an emergency!
[PARAMEDICS SHOUTING]
If you hear about
one more Chuckle,
I'm gonna kill you!
All this over a Chuckle.
What's a Chuckle?
It's a jelly candy.
It comes in five flavors.
You see, taste buds
run on grooves
along surfaces.
Can you let go of my tongue now?
What?
Let go of my tongue.
Oh, sorry.
Well, I should, uh, get going.
Mm-hm.
What are you doing?
Well, I was going
to kiss you good night.
A kiss? With the tongue?
The glossa with the bumps
and the papillae?
Hmm... I don't think so.
[SIRENS WAILING]
JERRY: You can't just
leave him out there!
I told him I was
gonna mess him up!
Well, can you
call him an ambulance?
I told him I didn't
take his Chuckle!
I don't eat that gooey crap!
Hey, watch the road.
Watch the road, man!
Hey, man, you want
some of what he got?
JERRY AND KRAMER: Watch out!
[TIRES SCREECHING,
CARS CRASHING]
How you doing?
Can't talk?
Hey, how did you get
the plastic one?
I like that.
So how's life without tonsils?
What? What's that?
So how much is this thing
gonna cost you now,
like, five, 6000?
Well, live and learn.
At least we lived.
Kramer went to Eckman.
He feels all better already.
What? What
are you doing?
Oh, poor George. Aw...
I'm sorry.
I can't stay long.
I don't want
to run into Dr. Tongue.
Here, I brought
you something.
See?
Oh, please, come on.
It's nothing--
JERRY: Hey,
check out the TV.
The planet's on fire!
It is just as you prophesied.
The planets of our solar system
incinerating
like flaming globes, Sigmond,
like flaming globes!
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
That's it! That's it!
Flaming globes of Sigmond!
That's my note!
That's what I thought
was so funny!
It's not funny.
There's nothing funny
about that.
PATIENT: Shut up!
Ow!
I have a friend
who's a hypochondriac.
He always thinks he's sick,
never is.
Then you have another
type of person,
always thinks they're well
no matter how bad
they really are.
You know this type of person?
Very annoying.
"Feel great!
"Like being on a respirator.
"Intravenous,
heart/lung machine,
I never felt better in my life."
Medical science
is making advances every day
to control health problems.
In fact, it's probably
only a matter of time
before a heart attack, you know,
becomes like a headache.
We'll just see people on TV
going,
"I had a heart attack this big,
"but I gave myself
one of these--
"Clear! Boom--
and it's gone!"
[♪]