I have to tell you
that I did get some
very exciting news recently.
And I don't know if I should
really tell you
exactly what it is,
because it's really not
a definite thing yet.
MAN: Come on!
WOMAN: Come on!
[CHEERS, CLAPS]
Well, I will tell you
what I do know so far.
According to the information
that I have
in the envelope that I received,
it seems...
that I may have already won
some very valuable prizes.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well...
Thank you.
That's very nice to hear that.
But in all honesty...
I have to say,
I didn't even know
I was in this thing.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
But according to the readout,
it looks like I am among
the top people
that they are considering.
You know, that's what annoys me
about sweepstakes companies.
They tease you with that,
"You may have already won."
I'd like once for a sweepstakes
company to have some guts.
Come out with the truth. Just
tell people the truth one time.
Send out envelopes,
"You have definitely lost."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
You turn it over,
giant printing,
"Not even close."
You open it up, there's this
whole letter of explanation:
"Even we cannot believe
how badly you've done
in this contest."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
To the right.
Boy, that took a while.
Don't get up.
I'd like to help,
but...my neck.
So...how long has it been
in the basement?
Since my grandfather
died.
I was supposed
to send it
down to my parents
in Florida,
but they didn't
want it.
They said get rid of it,
but I felt funny.
And then I sort of
forgot about it.
And it's been sitting
down there
for three years
until he saw it.
[DRUMMING]
Hm.
All right, so just
take what you want,
and let's get it
out of here.
What's in it?
Grandpa clothes.
I can't wear them.
Uh, you...
You want these?
Knee socks. You don't wear
knee socks.
No. Go ahead.
[CACKLES]
Look at this place.
I can't wait
to get it cleaned.
Hey, I'll know somebody
who'll do it.
She's good, she's honest.
No, Elaine's got this writer
friend from Finland. Rava.
Her boyfriend goes
to Columbia grad school.
And he's supposed to do it.
Well, students can't clean.
It's anathema.
They don't like it.
How long you been waiting
to squeeze that
into a conversation?
Now, this, I like.
Huh?
Wait a second.
I can't believe this.
Let me see this.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me just see it for a second!
No. Come on, come on.
Oh, my God.
It's exactly the same.
JERRY: What?
[LAUGHS]
When I was 10 years old,
my parents had
this very same statue
on the mantel
of our apartment.
Exactly.
And...
one day I grabbed it,
I was using it
as a microphone.
I was singing
"MacArthur Park." And...
I got to the part about,
"I'll never have
the recipe again"
and it slipped out my hand,
and it broke.
My parents looked at me like
I smashed the Ten Commandments.
To this day,
they bring it up.
It was the single most damaging
experience of my life.
Aside from seeing
my father naked.
No, give it back.
Come on, I saw it first.
Kramer, I have to have
the statue.
I got dibs.
What? No dibs.
I need the statue.
Give it!
Spread out.
Spread out!
You numbskulls.
Geez.
Why don't you just settle it
like mature adults?
Potato man.
No, no, no.
No potato man.
Inka-dink.
Okay.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Start with me.
Yeah. Good, good.
Inka dink-a
Bottle of ink-a
Cork fell out
And you stink...
Not because you're dirty
Not because you're clean
Just because you kissed a girl
Behind the magazine...
[LAUGHS]
No, no.
And...
Wait a minute.
You...
No, no.
Are...
No.
It.
What? What are you doing?
No, no.
Oh. Oh, okay.
All right.
He's out,
I get it.
No, no, no,
no, no.
I'm it. I win.
No. No.
He's it. He wins.
It is good.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Do over. Start with him.
No, no, no.
Come on, Kramer.
Now, you got the socks.
All right, you can have it.
D--!
Okay. I'm gonna take
the suit...
and...
shoes...
and the hat.
All right. Let's go.
Hey,
I look like Joe Friday
in Dragnet.
♪ Dum-dee-dum-dum ♪
I can't believe
I won at inka-dink.
[GIGGLES]
JERRY:
Come on, let's go.
Yeah.
Aren't you gonna
take it?
No, no. I don't wanna
carry it around.
I'll pick it up
later.
What about
your stuff?
Uh, oh, uh,
okay.
Yyyyah!
[CRASH]
[SMASH]
All right,
let's go.
Hey. You know,
you owe me one.
What?
The inka-dink.
You were it.
It's bad?
It very bad.
If they don't let you
be my editor on this book,
I go to another publisher.
It's that simple.
You told them that?
Of course.
[GASPS]
Oh, this is so fantastic.
I don't know how
to thank you.
So where's this
boyfriend of yours?
I can't wait much longer,
I got a flight.
Uh, he's probably caught
in traffic.
Or maybe he's dead.
So, what do you write,
children's books?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
That's Ray.
Ah, greetings.
Greetings
and salutations.
I beg your forgiveness.
My tardiness was unavoidable.
Rava, my love.
Elaine, dear friend.
And you must be Jerry,
lord of the manor.
Ah, my liege.
A pleasure
to serve you.
All right.
Well, we have to
get back to work.
[CHORTLES]
I gotta get to the airport.
Your palace shall sparkle
like the stars in heaven
upon your safe arrival, sire.
The, uh, toilet brush
is under the sink.
I don't really feel
that comfortable
with a maid either,
because there's that guilt
when you have someone
cleaning your house.
You're sitting there
on the sofa,
they go by
with the vacuum cleaner.
"I'm really sorry about this.
I don't know why I left
that stuff over there."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
And that's why
I could never be a maid,
because I would have
that attitude.
I'd find them,
wherever they are in the house.
"Oh, I suppose
you couldn't do this.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"No, don't get up.
Let me clean up your filth.
"No, you couldn't dust.
Oh. Oh, this is too tough,
isn't it?"
He really did
an amazing job. Look.
He uncoagulated the top
of the dishwashing liquid.
He cleaned out the bottom
of the little egg cups.
Come here,
look at this.
He cleaned in
the little one-inch area
between the refrigerator
and the counter.
How'd he
get in there?
He must be
like Rubber Man.
There's no Rubber Man.
Why did I think
there was a Rubber Man?
There's Elastic Man,
Plastic Man.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
To Rava's house.
I gotta pick up
her manuscript.
Oh, wait,
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Elaine...
he Windexed
the little peephole.
So the meeting with Lippman
is all set.
He's the
editor in chief.
I think because
of your request.
Demand.
They're gonna promote me
to editor.
Darn tooting.
There's Ray, late as usual.
Well.
This is an unexpected surprise.
And delight.
The once and future
king of comedy, Jerry the first,
gracing our humble abode.
Rava, we are in the presence
of royalty.
Hey, Ray, listen.
You really did a tremendous job
cleaning that apartment.
Oh, but I didn't just clean
your apartment.
It was a ritual,
a ceremony.
A celebration of life.
Shouldn't you be
out on a ledge somewhere?
[KETTLE WHISTLES]
[LAUGHING]
He's funny.
The water's boiling.
Are we all having tea?
Yes.
Yes. Jerry?
Jerry.
What?
RAVA:
Ray, would you give me a hand, please?
[SIGHS]
Yeah, I'm coming.
I think that's the statue
from my house.
That looks like the statue
What statue?
I had a statue.
You have a statue?
I never saw a statue.
My grandfather gave me a statue.
Since when?
What's the difference?
That's the one.
He ripped me off.
This guy ripped me off.
Do you take sugar?
Um, no.
No.
I can't believe it.
This guy ripped me off.
Do you realize
what you're saying?
Yes. This guy
ripped me off.
He stole that statue
right out of my house.
Lemon?
Um, sure.
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Pretty sure.
99% sure.
99% sure?
Ah, sweet elixir,
its fragrant nectar
a soothing balm for the soul.
[TIMER CHIMES]
Those are the pastries.
Ray, take care of that.
I'm gonna get Elaine
the manuscript.
The pastries.
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe it just looks the same.
Maybe it's a coincidence.
Coincidence?
This guy's in my apartment,
and then,
just by coincidence,
he has the exact same statue
in his apartment?
I never saw any statue.
I had a statue.
What should I do?
I'll call Kramer.
He can check my house.
Oh, Jerry.
Don't blow this for me.
Don't worry.
Kramer.
[WHISPERS]
It's Jerry. Jerry.
From next door.
Never mind where I am.
Yes, Jerry Seinfeld.
Ma, I told you
just dip the bread
in the batter
and put it in the pan.
Okay.
Bye. My mother.
She forgot how to make
French toast.
You know how mothers are.
My mother left us
when I was 6 years old.
All seven of us.
We never heard from her again.
I hope she's rotting
in an alley somewhere.
My mom's down in Florida.
She's got
one of those condos.
Hot down there in the summer.
You ever been down there?
I love these pastries.
You know,
in Scandinavian mythology,
the pastries
were the food of the gods.
Listen, I just
remembered, I'm, uh...
getting a facial.
Oh, I'll see you tomorrow
morning.
How about dinner?
No, I don't eat dinner.
Dinner's for suckers.
Uh-huh. Yeah, okay.
Thanks anyway. Bye.
Nope.
Cop says it's my word
against his.
There's nothing
they can do.
Let's go get him.
Yeah, right.
We can't let him
get away with this.
You realize how crazy
he had to be to do this?
He knew I was gonna know it's
missing and that he took it.
And of all things to take.
I left my watch, tape recorder,
stereo. He's crazy.
You wanna go get him?
Then if he's crazy,
you should just forget it.
Forget it?
I already called my parents.
I told them to expect
the surprise of a lifetime.
My mother's making
her roasted potatoes.
George, do you realize
that Rava has asked me
to edit her book?
Who is this Rava?
I say we get him.
Let me just call him.
No!
I'll call him.
Hello, Ray?
Hi, Ray. This is Rava's friend,
Elaine's friend, Jerry.
Yeah, the king of comedy,
right.
Listen, you know that statue
on your mantel
the one with the blue lady--?
Would you shut up?!
Yeah. Oh, you don't want to talk
about it over the phone.
You don't want Rava to hear.
Yeah, I understand.
You know the coffee shop
near my house, Monk's?
All right, tomorrow, 1:00.
Great. Okay, bye.
All right, look.
Look, look, look.
Let's say he stole it.
Oh, he stole it.
You-- You can't do anything
about it.
The cops won't do anything.
What, are you gonna
go fight him?
Why don't you
just forget it.
No.
Thought you said 1:00.
Relax. He's late.
He's always late.
It's part of his m.o.
Remember, don't take
any crap.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be right here.
That's comforting.
Shh. He's coming.
Ray.
Oh. Jerry.
I can't believe you asked me
about that statue.
You know how much trouble
you could've gotten me into?
Well, I--
Rava was standing
right next me.
I never told her
where I got the statue.
I wonder why.
Well, just give it back
and I won't
say anything.
Give it back?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
What's he talking about?
I'm talking about the statue.
Yeah, me too.
Give it back to whom?
Me.
Him.
You?
Yeah, me.
I'm not getting this.
You already got it.
Ray, I had a statue
in my house.
You were in my house.
And then I saw it
in your house.
What are you saying?
What am I saying?
Take a wild guess.
Are you saying
I stole your statue?
What a mind.
Well, I--
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
For your information,
I got that statue in a pawnshop.
Pawnshop?
A pawnshop?
Yes, in Chinatown,
with the money
I earned cleaning apartments.
Cleaning them out.
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah.
Look, Ray, you were
the only person in my house.
What's behind this?
It's Rava, isn't it?
Again with the Rava.
You want her.
No, she's a little
too cheery for me.
She's from Finland,
for crying out loud.
Finland!
Do you understand?
I know Finland.
They're neutral.
So, what, is it me?
Do I rub you the wrong way?
No, actually, I find you
quite charming.
A bit verbose at times.
"I find you so charming."
You wuss.
Did you call me
a wuss?
What did you say?
I said, "luss."
I'm at a luss.
I'd love to take you to
the pawnshop where I got it.
That's not necessary.
You know, maybe it's not
that bad an idea.
And I would love to.
Nothing would please me more.
But unfortunately, the guy
retired and moved to Singapore.
Singapore? Do you hear this?
If you really want,
maybe I can contact
the guy in Singapore.
Have him make a Photostat
of the receipt
and send it over.
Oh, that's it.
That's it! I can't take it.
I can't take it anymore!
You stole the statue!
You're a thief! You're a liar!
JERRY: George.
RAY: Who is this?
I'm the judge and the jury, pal.
And the verdict is, guilty!
What is going on here?
Guilty!
Your friend is crazy.
Oh, I'm crazy!
George, George.
I've gotta get going.
I have a class.
Oh, a class, huh? A class.
At Columbia?
Let me tell you something, pal.
I called the registrar's office.
I checked you out.
They have no record
of a Ray Thomas
at that school, you liar!
That is because I am registered
under my full legal name,
Raymond Thomas Wochinski.
Ray Thomas is
my professional name.
You mean "alias."
You are starting
to make me angry.
Well...
that was bound to happen.
I hope you think about
what you've done here today.
And if you wanna call
and apologize,
you know where
to reach me.
Hey, Ray.
Yes?
How did you get the goop
out of the top
of the dishwashing liquid?
It was like
a brand-new nozzle.
Nervous?
Why should I be?
Yeah. Right.
Your notes
were very insightful.
The book is great.
Did you go out
last night?
No, we made love on the floor
like two animals.
Ray is insatiable.
[COUGHS WEAKLY]
They all are.
Was Jerry?
I can't remember.
You know, Ray is very upset
over these accusations.
I'm staying out of this one.
This is between them.
I am not getting involved.
[ELEVATOR CHIMES]
So you think he stole it?
You have to admit,
the circumstantial evidence.
I admit nothing.
Will you put that cigarette out,
please?
I mean, he was
in the apartment,
and then it's gone,
and it's in your apartment.
Maybe you think
we're in cahoots. No, no.
But it's quite
a coincidence.
Yes, that's all,
Big coincidence.
Not a big coincidence.
A coincidence.
No, that's
a big coincidence.
That's what
a coincidence is.
There are no small coincidences
and big coincidences.
No. There are degrees
of coincidences.
No. There are only coincidences.
Ask anyone.
Are there big coincidences
and small coincidences
or just coincidences?
Well? Well?
[ELEVATOR CHIMES]
Will you put
that cigarette
out?
Maybe I put it out on your face.
It's just like Ray said.
You and Jerry,
you're jealous of our love.
You're trying
to destroy us.
Shouldn't you be
out on a ledge somewhere?
Ma, will you stop?
It's just a statue.
How is it my fault?
It was stolen.
I didn't even
touch it this time.
Okay, fine.
I don't see why this should
affect the potatoes.
Okay!
Goodbye.
She doesn't react
to disappointment very well.
Unlike me.
I'm not happy about this.
Why don't we just
throw a Molotov cocktail
through their window.
There's just no justice.
This experience has changed me.
It's made me more cynical,
more bitter, more jaded.
Really?
Sure. Why not?
How do you think
I feel?
Instead of editing
the first novel
of a major young
writing talent,
I am proofreading
a food-allergy cookbook.
Can't you talk to your boss?
I did.
He loves Rava.
Worse, he loves Ray.
And he doesn't think
you're funny at all.
I'm not happy about this.
Well, perhaps we can take
comfort in the knowledge
that in the next world,
Ray will be the recipient
of a much larger and more harsh
brand of justice.
Yeah, he'll have my parents.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
KRAMER:
Police. Open up!
Police?
Freeze, mama!
Hey, hey--
Shut up!
Spread them.
I said,
spread them!
You're in big
trouble, son.
Burglary,
grand larceny
possession
of stolen goods.
And murder!
Murder?
Shut up! Keep them spread.
You just make love
to that wall, pervert.
Hey, I think you have me
confused with somebody else.
Is your name Ray?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're the punk
I'm looking for!
Hey. Hey, are you
a cop?
Yeah, I'm a cop. I'm a good cop.
I'm a damn good cop!
And today's your lucky day,
junior.
Because I'm gonna let you off
with just a warning.
Any more of this criminal
activity,
and you'll be sorry.
You got me?
Got you? I don't know
what you're talking about.
Good, good.
Let's keep it that way.
All right, all right.
What's the big hubbub, bub?
[SIGHS]
[ELAINE AND JERRY GASP]
Kramer, I can't believe it.
Oh, you're my hero!
Yeah.
Kramer, what did you do?
Well, let's put it this way:
I didn't take him
to People's Court.
I feel like a huge weight has
been lifted off my shoulders.
I-- I-- I feel happy!
Kramer, I don't know
how to thank you.
Well, I'll think
of something.
Gah!
People are going to steal
from you. You can't stop them.
But everybody has their own
little personal security things.
Things that they think
will foil the crooks, you know.
In your own mind, right? You go
to the beach, go in the water.
Put your wallet in the sneaker.
Who's gonna know?
What criminal mind
could penetrate
this fortress of security?
"I tied a bow.
They can't get through that."
"I put the wallet down
by the toe of the sneaker.
"They never look there.
They check the heel,
they move on."
[♪]