Whenever I see the news,
and they're hauling in
some criminal terrorist
psycho maniac mass murderer guy,
you notice he's always
covering up his face
with the newspaper,
with the jacket, with the hat?
What is he worried about?
I mean,
what is this man's reputation
that he has to worry
about this kind of exposure
damaging his good name?
I mean, what is he,
up for a big job promotion
down at the office or something?
Afraid the boss
will catch this on TV
and go,
"Isn't that Johnson from Sales?
"He's up in that clock tower
"picking people off one by one.
"I don't know
if that's the kind of man
"we want heading up
that new branch office.
"he should be
in Bill Collection.
I think he's got aptitude."
[CHUCKLES]
She was great.
You don't want to know.
Hey, remind me to tell you
what we did in Lake George, huh?
Get this.
I got it all on video.
That's it. This is it.
I'm done. Through.
It's over.
I'm gone. Finished. Over.
I will never work for you again.
Look at you.
You think you're
an important man?
Is that what you think?
You are a laughingstock.
You are a joke.
These people
are laughing at you.
You're nothing.
You have no brains,
no ability, nothing.
I quit!
Hey.
Boy, I have really
had it with Newman.
He wakes me up
again last night
at 3:00 in the morning
to tell me he's going
up onto the roof
to kill himself.
Well, what did you say?
I said, "Jump."
He's been threatening
to do this for years.
I said, "If you're going
to kill yourself,
"do it already
and stop
bothering me."
At least I'd respect the guy
for accomplishing something.
What's his problem?
No job, no women.
He called the right guy.
I mean, what am I supposed
to tell him?
How much there is
for him to live for?
Why should I lie to him?
All right, I'm leaving.
I'm going to the laundry.
Why don't you use the machines
down in the basement?
Fluff and fold,
the only way to live.
I drop it off, I pick it up.
It's a delight.
How about if I
put a few things--
Wait a second.
I don't want to do that--
No, you're going over there--
No, I don't want
to mix in everything.
My guys don't know your guys.
You can't just lock them all
in the same machine together.
They'll start a riot.
Have you ever met my guys?
No, I can't say as I have.
Well...
All right, put them on top.
On top.
Oh, beautiful.
This stuff on top
is my friend's.
could I get it done
in a separate machine?
I'll have to charge you
for another machine.
Whatever it costs.
In fact, I would prefer it
if the machines are not even
touching each other,
because something could,
you know, jump across.
Guess what?
How did you know
I was here?
Kramer. Guess what?
I don't know.
I quit my job.
Get out of here.
I couldn't take it
anymore.
You can have this
on Monday.
What happened? Levitan?
I go in to use
his private bathroom,
everybody uses it,
and then I get a memo--
a memo--
telling me to use
the men's room in the hall.
I mean, we share it
with Pace Electronics.
It's disgusting.
You and your toilets.
I snapped.
It was the last straw.
So what are you
going to do now?
Are you going to look
for something else
in real estate?
Nobody's hiring now.
The market's terrible.
So what are you
going to do?
I like sports.
I could do something in sports.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
In what capacity?
You know,
like the general manager
of a baseball team.
Yeah, well,
that can be tough to get.
Well, it doesn't even have to be
the general manager.
Maybe I could be, like,
an announcer,
like a color man.
You know, how I always make
those interesting comments
during the game?
Yeah, yeah,
you make good comments.
So what about that?
Well, you know,
they tend to give those jobs
to ex-ballplayers
and people that are, you know,
in broadcasting.
Well, that's really not fair.
I know.
Well, okay, okay.
What else do you like?
Movies. I like to watch movies.
Yeah, yeah.
Do they pay people
to watch movies?
Projectionists.
That's true.
But you got to know
how to work the projector.
Right.
And it's probably a union thing.
Those unions.
Okay, sports...
movies...
What about a talk show host?
Talk show host, that's good.
I think I'd be good at that.
I talk to people all the time.
Someone told me they thought
I'd be a good talk show host.
Really?
Yeah, a couple of people.
How do you get that, though?
Where do you start?
Well, that's where
it gets tricky.
You can't just
walk into a building and say,
"I want to be a talk show host."
I wouldn't think so.
It's all politics.
All right, okay,
sports, movies,
talk show hosts.
What else?
This could have been
a huge mistake.
Yeah, well, it doesn't sound
like you completely
thought this through.
Guess not.
What should I do?
Maybe you can just go back.
Go back?
Yeah.
Pretend like it never happened.
You mean just walk
into the staff meeting
on Monday morning
like it never happened?
Sure. You're
an emotional person.
People don't
take you seriously.
Just go back.
Pretend the whole thing
never happened.
Never happened.
I was blowing off
a little steam. So what?
So what? You're entitled.
I'm emotional.
That's right, you're emotional.
Never happened.
To me, the most annoying thing
about the couple of times
I did work in an office
is that when you go in
in the morning,
you say hi to everyone,
and then for some reason,
throughout the day,
you have to continue
to greet these people
all day,
every time you see them.
You walk in,
"Morning, Bill. Morning, Bob.
How you doing? Fine."
10 minutes later,
you see them in the hall.
"How you doing?"
Every time you pass,
you got to come up
with another little greeting.
You know, you start
racking your brains.
You know,
you do the little eyebrow.
You know, "Hey."
Start coming up
with nicknames for them.
"Jimbo."
How you doing?
What are you doing here?
What? I work here.
I thought you quit.
What quit?
Who quit?
Bill, how was your weekend?
Oh, excellent weekend.
What about your weekend?
Fine weekend.
Yeah, good weekend.
Went up to the Cape.
Took the kids sailing.
Lisa was a little scared
at first,
but that kids gonna be
a good sailor some day.
Oh, she'll be a fine sailor.
Ava, what happened to you
Friday afternoon?
Oh, I got tied up.
I'll bet you did.
[GUFFAWS]
I want
to remind everyone
that the 10th
anniversary party
for Rick Barr Properties
is gonna be Wednesday afternoon
at 4:00
in Lasky's Bar
on Madison and 48th.
I want all of you to be there.
This really means a lot to me.
Is that Costanza over there?
What are you doing here?
What?
Am I crazy or didn't you quit?
When?
Friday.
Oh, what? What? That?
Are you kidding?
I didn't quit.
Why? You took that
seriously?
Oh, boy.
You mean "laughingstock,"
all that stuff...?
Come on,
will you stop it?
"No brains, no ability."
Teasing.
Okay, I want you out of here.
I don't know where
you're getting this from.
I...
You're serious,
aren't you?
Oh, you see,
you just... you don't know
my sense of humor.
I mean, Dan,
don't I joke around
all the time?
I wouldn't say
all the time.
You can't win.
You can't beat me.
That's why I'm here,
and you're there.
Because I'm a winner.
I'll always be a winner,
and you'll always be a loser.
"I'll always be a winner,
and you'll always be a loser."
This is what he said to me.
Well, so that's that.
No, that's not that.
That's not that?
No.
Well, if that's not that,
what is that?
I got some plans.
I got plans.
What kind of plans?
What's the difference?
You don't want
to tell me?
I'm going to slip him a mickey.
What, in his drink?
Are you out of your mind?
What are you,
Peter Lorre?
You don't understand.
He's got this big party
coming up.
He's been looking forward
to this for months.
This is going to destroy
the whole thing.
What if you destroy him?
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't worry.
It's perfectly safe.
I researched it.
He'll get a little woozy.
He might keel over.
Well, what does that do?
Big deal.
This is what they would do
in the movies.
It's the beautiful thing.
It's like a movie.
I'm going to slip him a mickey.
You've really gone mental.
Where are you going to get
this mickey?
I can't believe
I'm saying "mickey."
I got a source.
You got a mickey source?
And Elaine
is going to keep him busy.
Elaine?
How did you rope her into this?
I told her what a sexist he is,
how he cheats on his wife.
She knew that.
But she didn't know
he doesn't recycle.
What is the point
of all this?
Revenge.
Oh, the best revenge
is living well.
There's no chance of that.
[WHISTLING]
Did you get
your laundry?
Yeah.
What's with you?
He jumped.
What?
Yeah, Newman jumped.
Did he call last night?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
What did you say?
I said, "Wave to me
when you pass my window."
Whew.
Did he wave?
No. He jumped
from the second floor.
Mr. Papanickolas saw him
from across the street.
He's lying out there faking.
See, he's trying
to get back at me.
Oh, my God.
What?
What's the matter?
Oh, on Thursday
when I came home,
I had $1,500 on me.
For some reason,
I decided to I hide it
in my laundry bag,
and then I completely
forgot about it,
and then I took
the laundry in
on Friday.
Oh, come on, let's go.
Where? Where?
To the Laundromat.
I never saw it.
Okay, come on,
give the guy his money.
What are you doing?
Hey.
You see that sign
up there?
Oh, I see,
so you put up a sign
so you can do
whatever you want.
You are not a part
of society.
Yeah, that's right,
because this place
is my country,
and I'm the president,
and that's my constitution.
I'm not responsible.
So anybody
leaves anything here,
you could just take it.
You have a license
to steal.
You are like
the James Bond
of laundry.
You ever hear of a bank?
Come on, let's go.
No, no, you can't let him
get away with this.
[JAZZ PIANO PLAYING SOFTLY]
ELAINE:
Which one is he?
That's him over there.
The one that looks
like a blowfish.
Oh, yeah, I see him.
Yeah.
Hey, thanks
for doing this.
Why pass up
the opportunity
to go to prison?
This is by far
the most exciting thing
I've ever done.
Yeah, it is
kind of cool.
It's the first time
in my life
I've ever gotten back
at someone.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
This is the kind of thing
they do in the movies.
That's exactly
what I told Jerry.
Really?
Yes.
God, I've never
felt so alive.
Maybe we should call this off.
Come on.
What's the big deal?
We're just going to
put a little concrete
in the washing machine.
And what's going to happen?
Well, it'll mix up
with the water,
and then by the end
of the cycle,
it'll be a solid block.
If only you could put your mind
to something worthwhile.
You're like Lex Luthor.
You keep him busy.
Oh!
You go over there...
Yeah.
You start flirting
with him,
and I'll come by,
and while you're
keeping him busy,
I'll slip it in his drink.
Wouldn't it be easier
just to punch him
in the mouth?
Come on.
They're terrible.
They got no infield.
Oops! Excuse me.
Yeah.
I'm gonna
get some food.
You want some?
Nah.
Hi.
[MOCK-SNEEZES]
God bless you.
Oh...
thank you.
Thank you very much.
[HONKS LOUDLY]
Really, I mean that.
I am not
one of those people
who gives insincere
thank yous.
No, sir. No, sir.
When I thank somebody,
I really thank them.
So, thank...
you!
You're welcome.
People don't say
"God bless you"
as much
as they used to.
Have you noticed that?
No.
So, I'm going
to a nudist colony
next week.
Nudist colony?
Really?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I love nudist colonies.
They help me unwind.
Blah.
I've never been
to a nudist colony.
Oh, really?
Oh, you should go.
They're great.
Of course,
when it's over,
it's hard to get used
to all this clothing,
so a lot of times
I'll just lock the door
to my office
and I'll just
sit there naked.
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
I usually work naked
a couple of hours a day.
[WHISPERING]
Glenda,
can I ask you
a favor?
Could I have this seat?
[LOUDLY]
What do you have to sit here for?
There are plenty
of other seats.
I can't explain.
It's very important
that I sit here.
What are you
doing here anyway?
I thought
you were fired.
Okay, okay.
Fine.
I cook naked.
I clean...
I clean naked.
I drive naked.
Naked, naked, naked.
Who are you?
Oh, you don't want
to know, mister.
I'm trouble.
Big trouble.
What about the gentle cycle?
You ever use that?
Do you think it's effeminate
for a man to put clothes
in a gentle cycle?
What about
fine fabrics?
How do you deal
with that kind
of temperament?
What about stone-washing?
You ever witness one of those?
That must be something.
What, do they just
pummel the jeans
with rocks?
I didn't realize
it was a full box.
I'm going to
count to three.
If you don't
give up the chair,
the wig is coming off.
I don't wear a wig.
One...
No, no, no, no,
no, no.
I'm sorry.
I don't really
have a phone.
In fact, I don't really
have an apartment.
I kind of sleep around.
I just like to have
a few drinks
and then just
let the guy do
whatever he wants.
Uh, would you close
your eyes a second?
I want to tell you
a secret about my bra.
[LAUGHING]
Hello, Rick.
Hey, look who's here.
That's right,
Ricky-boy.
It's me.
You know something, Costanza?
I'm a very lucky man.
I've always been lucky.
Things just to seem to fall
right in my lap.
Boom!
You wouldn't believe it
if I told you.
Oh...
In fact, uh...
I'm glad you're here,
you know?
Maybe I've been
a little rough on you.
Oh...
Why should we let petty
personal differences
get in the way
of business?
I, uh...
I want you to come back,
and, uh...
you can use my bathroom
any time you want.
You want me
to come back?
Yeah.
Hey, how about
a toast, huh?
Everybody, a toast!
Rick, um...
Everyone,
I want to propose a toast
to 10 great years
at Rick Barr Properties...
Uh, Rick...
and all the people
in this room
that made that possible.
Rick...
I'd also like
to welcome back
into the fold, our...
our little, shrimpy friend,
George Costanza,
who,
although he really didn't
have a very good year--
how you blew that McConnel deal,
I'll never know,
but what the hell, huh?
we've always enjoyed
his antics
around the office.
Anything you want
to add to this?
Drink up!
I like history. The Civil War.
Maybe I could be a professor
or something.
Well, to teach something,
you really have to know
a lot about it.
I think
you need a degree.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, don't...
What?
Oh, my God,
the money!
The $1,500!
Where'd you find it?
It was in my laundry.
In your laundry?
The whole time?
I told you not
to mix in our guys.
What did we figure
the damage
on that machine
would be?
It was about 1,200 bucks.
Kramer!
That's Newman.
I'm on the roof!
Well? What are you waiting for?
Elaine, come on,
take a walk with me
down to the Laundromat.
I got to pay this guy
the money.
I like horses.
Maybe I could be a stable boy.
KRAMER: You want
to shoot some pool
tonight?
I can't.
I'm going to a movie!
Nah, it's probably
a union thing.
People like the idea of revenge.
Have you ever
heard the expression,
"The best revenge
is living well"?
I've said this.
In other words,
it means, supposedly,
the best way
to get back at someone
is just by being
happy and successful
in your own life.
Sounds nice.
Doesn't really work
on that Charles Bronson
kind of life.
You know what I mean?
Those movies
where his whole family
just gets wiped out
by some street scum.
You know,
maybe you could go up to him,
"Charlie, forget the .357.
"What you need
is a custom-made suit
"and a convertible.
"New carpeting, French doors,
a divan.
That'll show those punks."