I was watching women
in the department store
the other day trying on clothes,
and I noticed that they do it
differently from men.
Women don't try on the clothes,
they get behind the clothes,
you see?
They take a dress off the rack,
and they hold it up
against themselves.
They can tell something
from this.
They stick one leg way out.
Because they need to know
if someday I'm one-legged
at a 45-degree angle,
what am I going to wear?
You never see a man do that.
You never see a guy
take a suit off the rack,
put his head in the neck and go,
"What do you think
about this suit?
"I think I'll get it.
Yeah, looks fine.
"Put some shoes
by the bottom of the pants.
"I wanna make sure.
"Yeah, perfect.
Now, what if I'm walking?
Move the shoes, move the shoes,
move the shoes, move the shoes."
[CHANGING TELEVISION CHANNELS]
What are you doing?
All right.
All right!
What's the matter
with that?
What about that one?
Robert Vaughn,
The Helsinki Formula?
He was good in
Man From U.N.C.L.E.
Guess whose birthday
is coming up soon?
I know. I know.
I'm having my root canal
the same week.
Oh, right. I hope you got
a good oral surgeon,
because that can be
very serious.
Hey, look it,
naked people.
No, I don't wanna see
the naked people.
Been a while?
I have a vague
recollection
of doing something
with someone,
but it was a long,
long time ago.
I think my last time
was in Rochester.
My hair was a lot shorter.
I remember
that it's a good thing...
and someday,
I hope to do it again.
What?
What was that look?
What look?
The look you just gave me.
I gave a look?
Yes.
What kind of a look?
I know that look.
So what was it?
Why should I tell you?
Well, you're the big
look expert.
I want to see how smart you are.
Trust me. I know the look.
So?
What?
What about the look?
I don't know.
You got something on your mind?
No.
Things pop into your head.
You?
Things occur to me
from time to time.
Yeah. Me too.
Well, you can't expect
to just forget
the past completely.
Well, no, of course not.
I mean, it's something we did.
Probably about...
what, 25 times.
37.
Yeah, we pretty much know
what we're doing in there.
We know the terrain.
No big surprises.
Nope.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Well, it's something
to consider.
Yeah.
I mean, let's say...
what if... we did?
What if?
Is that like the end
of the world or something?
Certainly not.
Why shouldn't we be able
to do that once in a while
if we want to?
I know!
I mean, really,
what is the big deal?
We go in there.
We're in there
for a while,
then we come back
out here.
That's not complicated.
It's almost stupid if we didn't.
It's moronic.
Absurd!
Of course...
I guess maybe some little
problems could arise.
There are always a few.
I mean, if anything happened,
and we couldn't be friends
the way we are now,
that would really be bad.
Devastating.
Because this...
is very good.
And that would be good.
That would be good too.
The idea is to combine
the this...
and the that,
but this cannot
be disturbed.
Yeah, we just want
to take this...
and... add that.
But of course,
we'd have to figure out a way
to avoid the things
that cause the little problems.
Maybe some rules or something.
Huh.
For example...
Now, I call you
whenever I'm inclined
and vice versa...
Right.
but if we did that,
we might feel...
a certain obligation to call.
Well, why should that be?
Oh! I have an idea.
I have an idea.
No calls the day after that.
Beautiful.
Let's make it a rule.
All right, sir.
Now, here's another
little rule.
Yeah?
When we see each other now,
we retire
to our separate quarters,
but sometimes when people
get involved with that,
they feel pressure...
to sleep over,
when that...
is not really sleep.
Sleep is separate from that,
and I don't see why sleep
got all tied up
and connected...
with that.
Okay, okay, rule number two--
spending the night is optional.
Well, now
we're getting somewhere.
Good.
What about the kiss goodnight?
Tough one.
Your call.
It's bourgeois.
Fine.
Well...
You ready?
Ready.
So you think
you can handle this?
Definitely.
[BANG]
Hey.
Get the paper?
Not yet.
No paper.
I haven't been out yet.
Well, what's taking you so long?
So... oh!
Oh, yeah.
What's the deal
with Aquaman?
Could he go on the land,
or was he just restricted
to water?
No, I think I saw him on land
a couple times.
So how's
the job situation going?
Still looking.
Pretty bad out there.
What about you?
Nothing much.
I slept with Elaine last night.
Oxygen. I need some oxygen.
This is major.
I thought you'd like that.
Oh, this is huge!
I know.
All right, okay.
Let's go. Details.
Nah, I can't give details.
You what?
I can't give details.
No details?
I'm not in the mood.
You ask me here to have lunch,
tell me you slept with Elaine,
and then say you're not
in the mood for details.
Now, you listen to me.
I want details,
and I want them right now.
I don't have a job,
I have no place to go.
You're not in the mood?
Well, you get in the mood!
All right. Okay.
Well, we were in my apartment,
we're watching TV.
Where were you sitting?
On the couch.
Next to each other?
No, separate.
Time?
Around 11:00.
Okay, go ahead.
So she's flipping around the TV,
and she gets
to the naked station.
Oh... See, that's why
I don't have cable in my house,
because of that naked station.
If I had that in my house,
I would never turn it off.
I wouldn't sleep,
I wouldn't eat.
Eventually firemen would have
to break through the door.
They'd find me sitting there
in my pajamas
with drool coming down my face.
All right, all right,
so you're watching
the naked station.
And then...
somehow we started talking about
what if we had sex.
Boy, these are really
bad details.
It pains me to say this,
but I may be getting too mature
for details.
Oh, I hate to hear this.
Any kind of growth
really irritates me.
Well, I'll tell you, though,
it was really passionate.
Better than before?
She must have taken some kind of
seminar or something.
This is all too much.
So, what are you feeling,
what's going on?
Are you, like,
a couple again now?
Not exactly.
Not exactly?
What does that mean?
Well... we've tried
to arrange a situation
where we'll be able to do this
once in a while
and still be friends.
[LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY]
What?
Where are you living?
Are you here?
Are you on this planet?
It's impossible.
It can't be done.
Thousands of years,
people have been trying
to have their cake
and eat it too.
So all of a sudden,
the two of you are gonna
come along and do it.
Where do you get the ego?
No one can do it.
It can't be done.
I think we've
worked out a system.
Oh, you know what you're like?
You're like a pathetic gambler.
One of these losers in Las Vegas
who keeps thinking
he's gonna come up with a way
to win at blackjack.
No, this is very advanced.
We've designed a set of rules...
that we can maintain
the friendship
by avoiding
all the relationship pitfalls.
Sure.
All right, tell me the rules.
Okay.
No calls the next day.
So you have the sex,
the next day
you don't have to call.
That's pretty good.
Go ahead.
You ready for the second one?
I have to tell you,
I'm very impressed
with the first one.
Spending the night...
optional.
No. No, you see? You got greedy.
No, that's the rule.
It's optional.
I know less about women...
than anyone in the world,
but the one thing I do know
is that they are not happy
if you don't spend the night.
It could be a hot, sweaty room
with no air conditioning,
and all they have
is a little army cot this wide.
You're not going anywhere.
I think you're wrong.
I hope I am.
Is this yours
or the roommate's?
The roommate's.
Would she mind?
She keeps track
of everything.
Yes, well, that's too bad,
because I'm taking it.
Thanks.
Well...
guess I'll get going.
Oh.
Well, I've got that root canal
tomorrow morning.
It'd be easier if I go home.
Fine. Go ahead.
I don't understand.
Is there a problem?
I'm-I'm getting the impression
there's a problem.
Just go.
I'm having surgery tomorrow!
Oh, surgery.
You're going to the dentist!
But you said!
It could be very serious!
Okay. So, fine. Go!
What happened to the rules?
Remember?
Sleeping over was optional.
Yeah, it's my house,
it's my option.
It has nothing to do
with whose house it is.
Oh, of course it does!
Hi.
Hi, Jerry.
Such a great
improv class tonight.
Oh, really?
I did this improv...
where I pretended
I was working
in one of those booths,
you know,
in an amusement park
where you shoot the water
in the clown's mouth,
and you blow up
the balloon?
Uh, Tina, could you excuse us
for just one second?
Oh, yeah.
I'll excuse you.
What are you doing?
I can't go if you're mad.
I'm not mad.
You still seem a little mad.
No, no, Jerry, I'm fine.
Really, it's okay.
So you're okay
with everything?
Definitely. Are you?
Definitely.
Well... good night.
Good ni--
What are you doing?
What?
The rules.
Hey, who took my cake?
What about jewelry?
That's a nice birthday gift.
No, no, I have to be
very careful here.
I don't want to send
the wrong message,
especially after
the other night.
Maybe I'll get her some jewelry.
No, no, you can't get her
anything better than me.
Whatever I spend,
you have to spend half.
What am I supposed to get her,
Bazooka?
You don't understand.
I'm in a very delicate position.
Whatever I give her, she's gonna
be bringing in experts
from all over the country
to interpret
the meaning behind it.
What does she need?
Maybe there's something
that she needs.
I think I heard her say
something about a bench.
A bench?
What kind of a bench?
I don't know.
She mentioned a bench.
What, like at a bus stop?
I don't know.
Like a park bench?
I have no idea.
Who puts a bench in the house?
Forget the bench!
I got it.
You want to get her
something nice?
What about
a music box?
Nah, too relationship-y.
She opens it up, she hears
that "Lara's Theme," I'm dead.
Okay, what about a nice frame
with a picture
of another guy in it?
The frame says "I care for you,
but if you want to get serious,
perhaps you'd be interested
in someone like this."
Nice-looking fella.
What about candle holders?
Too romantic.
Lingerie?
Too sexual.
Waffle maker?
Too domestic.
Bust of Nelson Rockefeller?
Too... gubernatorial.
Let's work on the card.
I had to buy a gift for someone.
The hardest part, to me,
is that card.
That card is the killer.
I never know
what it's supposed to say,
and it's getting so tough
because the relationships
are becoming so complicated,
greeting card companies
now put out cards
that are blank on the inside.
Nothing. No message.
I mean, it's like
the card company says,
"We give up. You think
of something," you know?
"For 75 cents,
I don't want to get involved."
Maybe you won't like it.
Oh, how could I
not like it?
Of course I'll like it.
You could not like it.
Just the fact
that you remembered
means everything.
Of course I remembered.
You reminded me every day
for two months.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, the card.
Cash?
What do you think?
You got me cash?
Well, this way,
I figure you could go out
and get yourself
whatever you want.
No good?
Who are you, my uncle?
Hey, come on, that's $182 there.
I don't think that's
anything to sneeze at.
Let me see the card.
"To a wonderful girl,
a great pal, and more?"
Hey.
Oh, Elaine,
I'm glad you're here.
Stay-- stay
right here.
I'm gonna be
right back. Stay.
Pal? You think I'm your pal?
I said, "And more."
I am not your pal.
What's wrong with pal?
Why is everybody so down on pal?
Here.
Oh, what is this?
You got me something?
Yeah. Yeah. Open it.
Oh, Kramer!
Oh! The bench!
You got me the bench
that I wanted!
That's pretty good, huh?
Great.
Remember when we were standing
there, and she mentioned it?
I made a mental note of it.
Well, goodie for you.
Oh, yeah. See,
I'm very sensitive about that.
I mean, someone's birthday
comes up,
I keep my ears open.
So, what did you get her?
182 bucks.
Cash?
You gotta be kidding.
What kind of gift is that?
That's like something
her uncle would give her.
Think where man's glory
most begins and ends,
and say my glory was
I had such a friend.
Yeats.
Oh, Kramer...
Yeah...
Could you
excuse us, please?
Well, what?
We're talking.
Oh, the relationship.
You know, we never
had one fight
before this deal.
I know.
Never.
Ever.
We got along
beautifully.
Like clams.
It was wonderful.
A pleasure.
So I think we should just
forget the whole deal
and go back
to being friends.
I can't do it.
You what?
I can't do that.
You mean, it's...
No this?
No that?
No this or that.
Oh, boy.
Hmm.
What do you want?
This, that,
and the other.
Oh, sure, of course.
You're entitled.
Who doesn't want this,
that, and the other?
You.
Well...
Oh, those birthdays.
I told you,
they're relationship killers.
If a relationship is having
any problems whatsoever,
a birthday will always
bring it out.
I never should've made up
those rules.
What is it about sex
that just disrupts everything?
Is it the touching,
is it the nudity?
It can't be the nudity.
I never got into these
terrible kind of fights
and misunderstandings
when I was changing
before gym class.
You know what this means?
I can't see her anymore, either.
Why?
It's breakup by association.
Besides, she's mad at me anyway
because of my birthday present.
What? What did you wind up
giving her?
$91.
Sorry about that.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, if I do call her,
there's no joking around
anymore.
This is pretty much it.
So maybe this should be it.
It could be it.
She seems like an it.
She's as it as you get.
Imagine bumping into her
on the street in five years
with a husband?
And she tells me
that he's a sculptor,
they live in Vermont.
[SNORTS]
We'd have to kill him.
We'd get caught.
I'd get the chair.
I'd go to prison
as your accomplice.
Have to wear
that really heavy denim.
Go to the cafeteria line,
with the guy who slops those
mashed potatoes onto your plate.
Go to the bathroom
in front of hundreds of people.
Plus, you know what else.
You better call her.
Hey.
You got the paper yet?
Yeah.
Well, where is it?
Hey, are you done
with that?
No.
Well, you're not
reading it now.
All right,
you can take it,
but I want it back.
Oh, yeah.
So, uh, what are you guys
gonna do today?
Oh, this and...
that.
And the other.
Boy, I really liked
the two of you much better
when you weren't a couple.
Why is commitment
such a big problem for a man?
I think that for some reason,
when a man is driving
down that freeway of life,
the woman's he's involved with
is like an exit,
but he doesn't want to get out.
He wants to keep driving,
and the woman is like, "Look,
gas, food, lodging.
"That's our exit.
"That's everything we need
to be happy.
Get out of here now!"
But the man is focusing
on the sign underneath
that says,
"Next exit-- 27 miles,"
and he thinks, "I can make it."