I'm always in traffic
with the lane expert.
You know this type of person?
Constantly re-evaluating
their lane choice.
Never quite sure.
"Is this the best lane for me
for my life?"
They're always
a little bit ahead of you.
"Can I get in over there?"
"Could I get ahead of you?
Could I get in there?"
"Yeah, come on over here, pal.
We're zooming over here.
This is the secret lane.
Nobody knows about it."
The ultimate--
I think the ultimate
psychological test of traffic
is the total dead stop.
Not even rolling,
and you look out the window,
you can see gum clearly.
But we know that in the future,
traffic will get
even worse than that.
I mean, what will happen?
Will it start moving backwards,
I wonder?
Is that possible?
That someday, we'll be going,
"Boy, this is some
really bad traffic now, boy.
"This... is really bad.
"I'm going to try and get off
and get back on,
going the other way."
[HORNS HONKING]
She can't kill me,
right?
No, of course not.
People break up all the time.
Every day.
It just
didn't work out.
What can I do?
I wanted to love her.
I tried to love her.
I couldn't.
You tried.
I'd be looking
at her face,
I'd go, "Come on.
Love her, love her."
Did you tell her
you loved her?
Oh, I had no choice.
She squeezed it
out of me.
She'd tell me
she loved me, all right?
So, at first,
I'd just look at her.
I'd go, "Oh, really?"
Or "boy, that's--
that's something,"
but eventually,
you have to come back
with, "well, I love you."
You can only hold out
for so long.
You're a human being.
I didn't ask even her out.
She asked me out first.
She called me up.
What was I supposed to do,
say no?
I can't.
You're too nice a guy.
I am.
I'm a nice guy.
And then
she seduced me.
We're in my apartment,
I'm sitting on the couch,
she's on the chair.
I get up to go
to the bathroom,
I come back,
she's on the couch!
What am I supposed to do,
not do anything?
I couldn't do that.
That would have
insulted her.
You're flesh and blood.
I had nothing to do
with any of this.
[SIGHING]
I met all her friends.
I didn't want to meet them.
I kept trying to avoid it.
I knew it would only
get me in deeper,
but they were everywhere.
The kept popping up
all over the place.
"This is Nancy. This is Susan.
This is Amy.
"This is my cousin.
This is my brother.
This is my father."
I'm in quicksand here.
I told you
when I met her.
My back is killing me.
You gotta go
to my chiropractor.
He's the best.
Oh, everybody's guy
is the best.
I'm gonna make
an appointment for you.
We'll go together.
Please.
They don't do anything.
Look, do I have to
break up with her in person?
Can't I do it
over the phone?
I have no stomach
for these things.
You should just do it
like a Band-aid...
one motion-- right off!
Hi!
Hi.
What are you doing?
I'm letting you in.
Oh, no, I don't want
to sit in back.
I'll be left out
of the conversation.
No, you won't.
Yes, I will, George.
I'll have to stick my chin
on top of the seat.
[WHINING]
Okay.
Why can't you sit in the middle?
Please.
It doesn't look good--
boy, boy, girl.
Ah, I think you're afraid
to sit next to a man.
You're a little
homophobic, aren't you?
Is it that obvious?
Hello, Jerry.
Hello.
Did you get a haircut?
Nope. Shower.
So, where
are we eating?
ELAINE: Tell me if you think
this is strange.
There's this guy
who lives in my building
who I was introduced to
a couple years ago by a friend.
He's a, uh, teacher
or something.
Anyway, after we met, whenever
we'd run into each other
In the street, or in the lobby,
or whatever,
we would stop
and we would chat a little bit.
Nothing much, you know,
pleasantries.
He's a nice guy,
he's got a family.
Then after a while,
I noticed
there was no more stopping,
just sort of saying hello
and continuing on our way.
And then
the verbal hellos stopped,
and we just went into
these little sort of nods
of recognition.
So fine.
I figure that's where
this relationship
is finally going to settle--
polite nodding.
Then one day, he doesn't nod.
Hmm.
Like I don't exist.
He went from nods to nothing.
♪ You know I'd go
From nods to nothing ♪
And now there's
this intense animosity
whenever we pass.
I mean, it's like
we really hate each other.
It's based on nothing.
A relationship
is an organism.
You created this thing,
and then you starved it,
so it turned
against you.
Same thing happened
in The Blob.
I think you absolutely
have to say something
to this guy.
Confront him.
Really?
Yes!
Would you do that?
If I was
a different person.
JERRY: Hello?
Hello. Is Glen there?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is this 805-555-3234?
Yes, I know
I have the wrong number,
but I just want to know
if I dialed wrong or--
Why do people do that?
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Come on up.
Oh, it's you again.
See, now,
if you had answered me,
I wouldn't have
had to do this.
Now, that's two
long distance calls
I've made to you.
Why can't you--?
Why? Why do they
just hang up like that?
Thank you very much.
Taste this.
No, I just had a sandwich.
No, taste it.
Taste it.
I don't want
cantaloupe.
You never had
cantaloupe like this.
I only eat cantaloupe
at certain times--
But, Jerry, this
is great cantaloupe.
All right!
There. Huh?
It's very good.
It's good, huh?
It's good.
I got it at Joe's.
Uh-huh.
49 cents a pound.
Mm.
That's practically half
of what you're paying
at the supermarket.
I don't know why
you don't go to Joe's.
It's too far.
[TV PLAYING]
It's three blocks
further.
You can use
my shopping cart.
I'm not pulling
a shopping cart.
Should I wear a kerchief,
put stockings on,
and roll 'em down
below my knee?
See, the other thing is,
if you don't like anything,
he takes it right back.
I don't return fruit.
Fruit's a gamble.
I know that going in.
♪ Ye-di-di-di-di-di-di... ♪
[GEORGE HUMMING]
I'm out of there!
I did it! It's over!
You did it?
What happened?
I told her, in the kitchen,
which was risky,
because it's near
all the knives.
I started
with the word "listen."
Uh-huh.
I said, "Listen, Marlene..."
Next thing I know,
I'm in the middle of it,
and there's this voice
inside of me going,
"You're doing it--
you're doing it!"
And then she started to cry,
and I weakened a little bit.
I almost relented,
but the voice, Jerry, the voice
said, "Keep going.
Keep going. You're almost out."
It's-- it's like
I was making a prison break.
You know,
and I'm heading for the wall,
and I trip
and I twist my ankle,
and they throw
that light on you, you know?
Somehow,
I get through the crying,
and I keep running.
[SIGHS]
Then the cursing started.
She's firing from guard towers.
"Son of a--" Bang!
"Son of a--" Boom!
I get to the top of the wall,
the front door,
I open it up, I'm one foot away,
I take one last look
around the penitentiary,
and I jump!
See?
Never as bad as you imagine.
I like
that Marlene.
What's her number?
Uh... yeah.
No, I-- I don't think so.
[LIPS SMACKING]
Could you stop that smacking?
George, I want you
to taste this cantaloupe.
Oh, no, thank you.
It's the best cantaloupe
I ever had.
No, really. No. No, thanks.
Jerry, tell him
how good this cantaloupe is.
Very good cantaloupe.
Du...oh!
So that's it?
Yeah.
You're out.
Except for one small problem.
I, um...
I-- I left some books
in her apartment.
So? Go get them.
Oh, no, no.
I can't go back there.
Jerry, it's so awkward,
and, you know,
it could be dangerous--
sexually.
Something could happen.
I'd be right back
where I started from.
So forget about the books.
Did you read them?
Well, yeah.
What do you need 'em for?
I don't know. They're books.
What is this obsession
people have with books?
They put them in their houses
like they're trophies.
What do you need it for
after you read it?
They're my books.
So you want me to get the books,
is that it?
MARLENE:
So it must have been
95 degrees that night,
and everyone's just standing
around the pool,
with little drinks
in their hands.
I was wearing my old jeans
and t-shirt.
I don't know.
I was just in
one of those moods,
so I said to myself,
"Marlene, just do it,"
and I jumped in.
And as I'm getting out,
I feel all these eyes on me.
So, I look up
and everyone
is just staring at me.
So what did you do?
Well, nothing.
It's no skin off my hide
if people like to look.
I just didn't see
what the big attraction was.
Well, I have a general idea
what it was.
I could take a guess.
Hey, you know, Jerry,
just because George and I
don't see each other anymore,
it doesn't mean
we shouldn't stay friends.
No.
Good enough.
I'm really glad
we got that settled.
Great.
JERRY: I don't know
how this happened.
Jerry,
it's not my fault.
No, no,
it's not your fault.
"Books, books,
I need my books."
Have you re-read those books
yet, by the way?
You know
the great thing?
When you read Moby Dick
the second time,
Ahab and the whale
become good friends.
You know,
it's not like
Marlene's a bad person
or anything,
but, my God!
I mean, we've had, like,
three lunches and a movie,
and she never
stops calling.
And it's those
meaningless, purposeless
blather calls.
She never asks
if I'm busy or anything.
I just pick up the phone,
and she's in the middle
of a sentence.
It's... it's standard.
Has she left you
one of those messages
Which uses up
the whole machine?
Oh, and you know,
sometimes she'll go,
"Hello, Jerry?"
And I'll go,
[MONOTONOUSLY]
"Oh, hi, Marlene."
And then it's, "Jerry...
I don't know sometimes."
"I don't know sometimes."
What about trying
to get off the phone?
Oh!
You can't!
It's impossible.
There's no break
in the conversation
where you can go,
"all right, then..."
You know, it just
goes on and on and on
without a break
in the wall.
I mean, I've got
to put a stop this.
Do it like a Band-aid.
One motion-- right off!
She is sexy, though,
don't you think?
Yeah.
Yeah, she is.
Mr. Costanza?
Yeah?
The doctor will see you.
Yeah. "Doctor."
I'm gonna have to wait
in that little room
all by myself,
aren't I?
I better take this.
I hate the little room.
Oh, hello, "doctor."
The waiting room,
I hate when they make you
wait in the room.
It says "waiting room."
There's no chance
of not waiting.
Since they call it
"the waiting room,"
they're gonna use it.
They've got it.
It's all set up for you to wait.
And you sit there, you know,
and you got
your little magazine.
You pretend you're reading it,
but you're really
looking at the other people.
You know
you're thinking about them.
Things like,
"I wonder what he's got."
"As soon as she goes,
I'm getting her magazine."
And then they finally call you,
and it's a very exciting moment.
They finally call you,
and you stand up,
and you kind of look around
at the other people in the room,
"Well...
I guess I've been chosen.
I'll see you all later."
You know, and so you think
you're going to see the doctor,
but you're not, are you? No.
You're going into
the next waiting room--
the littler waiting room.
But if they are, you know,
doing some sort of medical thing
to you,
You want to be
in the smallest room
that they have.
You don't want to be
in the largest room
that they have,
you know what I mean?
You ever see
these operating theaters
with, like, stadium seating?
You don't want them
doing anything to you
that makes other doctors go,
"I have to see this."
"Are you kidding?
"Are they gonna really
do that to him?
"Are there seats? Can we get in?
Do they scalp tickets
to these things?
"I got two
for the Winslow tumor.
I got two."
So, how was it?
I was in there
for two minutes.
He didn't do anything.
Touch this, feel that--
75 bucks.
Well, it's a first visit.
It's 75 bucks.
What, am I seeing Sinatra
in there?
Am I being entertained?
I don't understand this.
I'm only paying half.
You can't do that.
Why not?
He's a doctor.
You got to pay what he says.
Oh, no, no, no.
I pay what I say.
You feeling weird?
No.
I'm fine.
Nothing
really happened.
Yeah.
I know.
We just kissed a little.
People kiss.
Yeah.
Well...
Night.
Good night.
Hey.
I got it.
This time I got it.
All right.
Hips! See?
It's all in the hips.
All right.
Come through
with the hips first.
Whoosh!
That is out there.
Definitely.
Joe's?
No. Supermarket.
Well, is it good?
It's, uh, it's okay.
Well, let me taste it.
Oh. See? That stinks.
You can't eat that.
You should take that back.
I'm not taking it back.
All right. I'll take it back.
I'm going by there.
I don't care
about it.
Jerry, you should care.
Cantaloupe like this
should be taken
out of circulation.
All right. Take it back.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
No. No...
Leave a message.
I'll call you back.
MARLENE: Jerry, have you ever
taken a bath in the dark?
I'm not talking into the soap
right now.
Call me back.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
Who was that?
Marlene.
Mar--
Oh... Oh.
Marlene.
I took her home
one night
and we kind of started up
a little bit in the car.
I thought you were
trying to get rid of her.
I was, but she's got me,
like, hypnotized or something.
Does George know?
No. He'd go nuts.
Yeah, no kidding.
I feel terrible.
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, I've seen her
a couple of times since then,
and I know
I can't go any further,
but I-- I--
she's got this psychosexual
hold over me.
I just want her.
I can't breathe.
It's like a drug.
[SIGHING]
Psychosexual.
I don't know how
I'm gonna tell him.
Man, I don't
understand people.
I mean, why would George want
to deprive you of pleasure?
Is it just me?
It's partially you, yeah.
You're his friend.
I mean, better that she should
sleep with someone else?
Some jerk that
he doesn't know?
Well, he can't kill me,
right?
You're a human being.
I mean, and she called me.
I never called her.
She started it!
You're flesh and blood.
I'm a nice guy!
Yeah.
Hi.
Ah, my little
airplane lamp.
Mm.
You have the slowest elevator
in the entire city.
That's hard to get used to
when you're in so many
other fast ones.
Well, the apartment elevators
are always slower than offices
because you don't have
to be home on time.
Unless you're married
to a dictator.
Yeah.
Because they'd be
very demanding people.
That's right.
Exactly.
So, I imagine,
at some point,
somebody's gonna offer me
some cantaloupe?
No. No good.
Well, you know
what they say.
Lucky in love,
unlucky with fruit.
Well, I'm taking
this back.
So, I had
what you might call
a little encounter
this morning.
Really? That guy
who stopped saying hello?
Yeah.
You talk to him?
Yeah, I spotted him
getting his mail,
and, at first, I was
just going to walk on by.
But then I thought,
"No, no, no, no.
Do not be afraid of this man."
Right.
So I walked up behind him
and tapped him on the shoulder,
and said, "Hi. Remember me?"
And he furrows his brow,
as if he's really
trying to figure it out.
So I said to him,
I said, "You little phony.
You know exactly who I am."
You said "you little phony"?
I did.
I most certainly did.
And he said, he goes, "Oh, yeah,
you're Jeanette's friend.
We did meet once."
And I said, "Well, how do you go
from that
to ignoring a person
when they walk by?"
This is amazing.
And he says-- he says,
"Look, I just didn't want to say
hello anymore, all right?"
And I said, "Fine! Fine!
"I didn't want to say hello
anymore either,
but I wanted you to know
that I'm aware of it."
You are
the queen of confrontation.
You're my new hero.
In fact,
you've inspired me.
I'm going to call George
about something right now.
Oh...
This cantaloupe stinks.
I don't care.
You're kidding?
No. I don't care.
You mean that?
Absolutely.
You don't care?
No.
How could you not care?
I don't know, but I don't.
I'm actually
almost happy to hear it.
I thought you'd be upset.
Well, I guess I should be,
but I'm not.
Am I a bad person?
Did I do something terrible?
You're a fine person.
You're a humanitarian.
She's very sexy.
That voice, that voice.
She's driving me crazy.
I know. I know.
So I can see her tonight
and you don't care?
See her tonight,
see her tomorrow. Go.
Knock yourself out.
She's too crazy
for me.
All right, as long
as you're okay.
Because I can't stop
thinking about her.
I'm okay. I'm fine.
I'm wonderful.
I never felt better
in my whole life.
Good.
And I'll tell you what.
You don't have
to pay me back the $35
I gave the chiropractor
for the rest of your bill.
You paid that crook?
I had to.
He didn't do anything!
Jerry, it's a scam!
Who told you to do that?
It was embarrassing to me.
Oh, I trying to make a point.
Why don't you make a point
with your own doctor?
Yeah, but J--
[HACKING]
What's wrong?
I think I swallowed a fly.
Oh, God.
I swallowed a fly!
What do I do? What can happen?
So, you want to come up
for a few minutes?
I'm sorry, Jerry.
I just don't think
this is gonna work.
Really?
I thought--
I know.
I'm sorry.
Gee... I just
didn't expect it
from the way
you've been acting.
Are you sure you want
to talk about this?
Because I sure don't.
Of course I want
to talk about it.
Well, okay.
I guess things
changed for me
on Tuesday night.
Tuesday night?
What happened
I saw your act.
My act?
What does that
have to do with anything?
Well, to be honest,
it just didn't make it for me.
It's just so much fluff.
I can't believe this.
So what are you saying?
You didn't like my act?
So that's it?
I can't be with someone
if I don't respect what they do.
You're a cashier.
Look, Jerry,
it wasn't my kind of humor.
You can't go by the audience
that night.
It was late.
They were terrible.
I heard the material.
I have other stuff.
You should come see me
on the weekend.
Women need to like the job
of the guy they're with.
If they don't like the job,
they don't like the guy.
Men know this.
Which is why we make up
the phony, bogus names
for the jobs that we have.
"Right now,
"I'm the regional
management supervisor.
I'm in development,
research, consulting."
Men, on the other hand,
if they are physically attracted
to a woman,
are not that concerned
with her job, are we?
Men don't really care.
Men will just go,
"Really? Slaughterhouse?
Is that where you work?
"That sounds interesting.
"So, what,
you got a big cleaver there?
"You just
lopping their heads off?
"That sounds great.
"Listen,
why don't you shower up,
and we'll get some burgers
and catch a movie?"
[♪]