It's very hard to find the store
that you want in a mall.
They have the directory,
but the problem with it is
even if you figure out
where you are
and where you wanna go,
you still don't really know,
sometimes, which way to walk,
because it's an upright map.
If you had, like,
suction-cup feet,
then you could just, thp,
walk right up on it.
Then you could tell.
You could just be on it, going,
"All right, I'm here.
"I wanna go to the Gap.
That's down there.
All right.
Now, I'll just walk that way."
Thp, thp, thp, thp, thp.
But people would know you.
They would see you
walking down the mall,
going, "Thp, thp, thp, thp."
They go, "That's one of
those suction-cup guys.
"I heard about that guy.
He's never lost."
GEORGE:
One left. What a joke.
KRAMER:
You can have this one.
GEORGE: No,
that's not enough BTUs
for my living room.
This was a complete
waste of time.
ELAINE:
Hey, I didn't get one either.
JERRY:
Why do I always have the feeling
everybody's doing something
better than me
on Saturday afternoons?
This is what people do.
No, they don't.
They're out
on some big picnic.
They're cooking burgers,
making out on blankets.
Not at some mall in Jersey,
watching their friends
trying to find
the world's cheapest
air conditioner.
GEORGE:
You should see what
my father used to go through
before he bought a new car.
He'd go from state to state.
He was away for weeks at a time.
It's like he was running
for president,
and he was going through
the primaries.
We'd get phone calls from motels
in New Hampshire.
So we took a little ride.
What's the big deal?
Well, at least
you accomplished something.
You got fish.
Oh, big accomplishment.
Heh, fish.
What do they do?
What do you do?
KRAMER:
Hey, this way.
Jerry, what time
do you have?
I have 5:00.
Always late.
You're not late.
I told them
to meet me in front of
my building at 6:15.
Who?
My parents.
It's their anniversary.
I'm taking them out to dinner
and a show tonight.
Oh.
Think we'll hit traffic?
Of course we'll hit traffic.
It's rush hour.
Isn't it going
the other way?
There's no other way
in New York.
Everybody goes every way
all the time.
Yeah, but it's Saturday.
You got the picnic
and burger traffic.
There's picnic traffic?
Well, as my grandfather
used to say,
"Sometimes even
a picnic's no picnic."
I always get myself
in this position.
Can't be on time.
Gotta rush.
What's the matter?
Huh? Uh...
[MUTTERS]
I have to go
to the bathroom.
Why do they hide the bathrooms
in these malls?
Do you want me
to help you with that?
No, I got it.
Hup, cha.
What do you think,
Georgie boy?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Did I need that
pointed out for me?
What is that
gonna do for me?
How does that help me,
to see her?
I'm trying
to live my life.
Don't show me that.
Well, if you like her,
go and talk to her.
Oh, yeah, women love to get
approached in parking garages.
I'll just go up and say,
"Hi, how you doing?
"Would you like a glass
of white wine?
You'd get within
15 feet of that woman,
she'd have her finger
on the mace button.
Oh, now,
that was a guy.
That was
a guy?
Where's the car?
Well, I--
I thought it was here.
You don't know
where we parked?
Oh...
Ha ha heh ho,
this is great.
Look, I thought
it was green 22.
I remember orange.
I thought it was orange.
I didn't
pay attention.
Oh, this is
just what I need.
All right, I'm sure
it's right around here.
Yeah, yeah.
It looks familiar.
I remember
the elevator.
There's elevators
all over!
Everything looks
the same.
We're like rats
in some experiment.
It's over there.
I-I know where it is.
It's black,
right?
Well,
it's dark brown.
In a parking lot,
you write it down.
How hard is that?
There it is.
Ah.
No, no.
That's a Toyota.
[SIGHS]
Hey...
I thought
it was...
Hey, didn't we come in
over there?
I thought we came in
over there.
How long
can fish live
in one of these
plastic bags?
I don't know.
Maybe two hours.
You better find
this car.
Let's try
this way.
I really have to go
to the bathroom.
Why don't you just go
behind one of these cars?
Why?
There's nobody around.
I'll wait.
You know,
you hold it in like that,
you can cause a lot of damage
to your bladder.
That's what happens
to truck drivers.
Oh, they hold it in
all the time,
and eventually it starts
to come out involuntarily.
All right.
Jerry, are you aware
that adult diapers
are a $600,000,000 a year
industry?
Maybe I should just go
anytime I get the urge,
like you,
wherever I am.
There's too much urinary freedom
in this society.
I'm proud to hold it in.
It builds character.
[GASPS]
Is that it?
JERRY:
No.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Hey!
Watch it!
Maniac.
Oh, gee.
You sure you don't want me
to help you with that?
I'm gonna put it down
behind that car.
You worried somebody's
gonna pee on it?
KRAMER: It's purple 23.
Remember that.
Oh, I got it.
[SCOFFS]
That I'm supposed to
remember.
Where the car is,
that's insignificant.
I think
they're laboring.
Look at this place.
It's huge!
All right, all right.
Let me say this to you--
If I am not in front
of my building at 6:15
when my parents
get there,
they're gonna put me on
an aggravation installment plan
that will compound with interest
for decades.
Parents never forget
a foul-up.
I once left my jacket
on a bus when I was 14.
I was flying to Chicago
last week on a plane,
"Make sure you hang onto
your jacket."
There's no way you can
get in touch with them?
Yeah, I'll call them
on their car phone.
Huh, what do you think
it would take
for his parents
to get a car phone?
Hypnosis
by aliens.
Where the hell
is this car, Kramer?
We need
a system.
Well, it's gotta
be here.
Wh--? Why are they using
so many colors?
The numbers go up to 40.
Maybe it's not
on this level.
What?
There's four
different levels.
Maybe we're on
the wrong level.
How long was
the escalator ride up?
I-- It felt like
a couple of levels.
You should always bring
a pad and a pen.
I can't carry a pen.
I'm afraid
I'll puncture my scrotum.
I got a pen.
Where is the bathroom
in this mall?
With 600 stores,
I didn't see one bathroom.
What is this?
Like, a joke?
Don't they consult
with urologists
when they build
one of these places?
What's with you?
My ear itches.
WOMAN:
Hey, don't you dare
talk to me like that,
you hear me?
I told you
I don't care.
Ow!
You'll have to wait.
Hey, hey, is that
really necessary?
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Well, I think hitting
a defenseless child
is my business.
You're ugly.
What?
You are.
That's what you think.
That's what I know.
[ENGINE STARTS]
I found it!
ELAINE:
He's got it.
No, no, no.
All right, that's it.
From now on, no more
calling out "I found it"
unless we're sitting
in it, okay?
Jerry,
look at my fish.
His eyes look
a little cloudy.
See?
Oh, those are
your eyes.
Oh, they are gonna be
furious.
Who's got the tickets?
I do.
I thought
you knew this mall.
You said you'd
been here before.
Ah, it was easy
last time.
Okay, my fish are dying
right in front of me.
We've gotta
get someone
to drive us around
the parking lot
to help us
look for the car.
No one's gonna
do that.
Excuse me. Hi.
Um, we can't seem
to find our car.
I was wondering if
it would be possible,
if you're not
in a hurry,
to drive us around the garage
for five minutes
so we can look.
Sorry.
Just five minutes.
Can't do it.
We're not skinheads.
Excuse me.
I can't seem
to find my car.
Do you think
you could drive me--?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, that's funny?
Is that funny?
Hey, well, tell me
if you think this is funny.
These fish
are dying!
In an hour,
they'll be belly up.
Excuse me.
[SARCASTICALLY]
Hey, sorry to have
disturbed you.
Terribly sorry.
But the fish
will be dead...
you do know that.
They can't live in plastic.
That's not me talking.
That's science!
It's amazing how shopping
makes me have to go.
How does my bladder know
I'm in a department store?
Why don't you just go?
No, I can't.
Don't you get tired
of following rules?
You think
I'm too cautious?
But why
be uncomfortable
if you don't
have to?
It's organic.
Organic.
So is Buddy Hackett.
Buddy Hackett?
He's a comedian.
I know.
All right.
Hey, you can
go over here.
I can manage.
George?
Okay, let's go.
But...
Come on.
Kramer.
JERRY:
I'm telling you,
I've had this condition
since I was 11 years old.
I've been in and out
of hospitals my whole life.
I have no control
over it.
Doctors have told me
that when I feel it,
the best thing to do
is just release it.
Otherwise...
I could die.
Do you hear what
I'm saying to you?
I'm telling you
that if I don't go,
I could die.
Die!
Is it worth
dying for?
That's up to you.
Oh, so you don't care if I die?
What I care about
is the sanitary condition
of the parking facility.
Why would I do it
unless I was in mortal danger?
I know it's against the law.
I don't know.
Because I could get
"uromysitisis" poisoning
and die. That's why.
You think I enjoy
living like this?
The shame,
the humiliation?
You know, I've been issued
a public urination pass
by the city
because of my condition.
Unfortunately,
my little brother ran
out of the house
with it this morning.
Him and his friends are probably
peeing all over the place.
Jerry!
Unbelievable.
I'm never gonna get
outta here.
A guy goes to pee
and never comes back.
It's like
a science fiction story.
Maybe he went
to one of the other levels.
I'm gonna go look for him.
Oh, now
you're gonna go?
I'll be back
in five minutes.
If you go now, I know
what's gonna happen.
We'll find the car,
Jerry will show up,
and we'll never
find you.
I'll be right back.
What's
the difference?
We'll all be
ead eventually.
Does that bother you?
Yeah, it bothers me.
Doesn't it bother you?
Not at all.
You see, now,
that bothers me even more
than dying bothers me,
because it's people
like you
who live to be 120
because you're
not bothered by it.
How can it
not bother you?
Well, I once saw
this thing on TV
with people who
are terminally ill.
Every one
of them believed
that the secret of life
is just to live
every moment.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Meanwhile,
I'm here with you
in a parking garage
in Jersey.
That's a nice jacket.
Where'd you get that?
Some guy left it over
at my mother's house.
First of all,
you don't even know
technically that I went.
That's for starters.
I could've been pouring
a bottle of water out there.
I know what you did.
Oh, really? Do you?
Well, it just so happens
that I did pour water out.
I had a bottle
of very tepid water,
and I poured it out,
and I could see how
you made a mistake,
because pouring water out
sounds very much like
a person urinating...
And you know,
when you think about it,
It's-- it's really
quite an amusing case
of mistaken identity.
That's all it is.
And now he's gone.
I'm sure he's looking
for the car.
Five minutes, that's all.
I just want to find him.
I can't do it.
But why--
why can't you do it?
I can't.
No, see, that's
not a reason-- you can't.
You just
don't want to.
That's right.
But why
don't you want to?
I don't know.
Wouldn't you get
any satisfaction
out of helping someone out?
No, I wouldn't.
[ENGINE STARTS]
All right.
All right. I, uh...
I want to apologize.
Uh, I was frightened.
I said crazy things.
I obviously offended you.
I insulted your intelligence.
The "uromysitysis,"
the water bottle...
I made all that up,
and now I'm gonna
tell you the truth.
Today my parents
are celebrating...
their 50th--
Well, I'm jumping ahead here--
their 47th wedding anniversary,
and we made plans
to spend the evening together.
They're meeting me
in front of my building
at 6:15.
What I haven't told you,
or anyone else, for that matter,
is that my father's been
in a Red Chinese prison
for the past 14 years.
I mean, the guy
had a fat fetish.
The inspector never dated
a woman under 250 pounds.
Really.
And what did he do
with all that fat?
Does he just jump up
and down on it,
or does he gouge you
like Killer Kowalski?
Who's Killer Kowalski?
Oh, he was a wrestler.
You know, he would get down
on his knees,
and he would grab a hold
of someone's stomach,
and just squeeze till they gave.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, I have to go
to the bathroom.
Why don't you just go?
What, here?
You and Jerry. It's--
Okay.
All right, I'm gonna
go down this row.
What did I do?
I didn't do anything.
Kramer. Kramer!
What, don't you
believe me?
It's their 47th anniversary.
You know, this is gonna
kill them.
You're aware of that?
Kill them on the biggest night
of their life.
Your folks have
an anniversary today too?
Is your father
also in a Red Chinese prison?
Red Chinese prison?
George!
Jerry!
You know when you're
walking with someone
and you assume that they know
where the car is,
and you're fine until
you see them do this move.
Once they do this:
When they look back
from where they came from--
No, you're in bad shape.
Now, nobody that knows where
they're going does that.
Pilots on planes
don't open the cockpit door
and go:
Slam.
Well, what happened was
my father was staying
at the home
of one of Red China's
great military leaders,
General Chang,
who, by the way,
came up
with the recipe
for General Chang's chicken.
Chicken.
You know, the one
with the red pepper
and the orange peel?
Szechwan Gardens.
Sure. I eat it
all the time. Very spicy.
Apparently, General Chang's
a very flamboyant man.
Complete failure
as a general,
but a hell of a cook.
Look at this.
Will you look
at this?
He doesn't have enough
with the Mercedes.
He has to have
two spaces.
I tell you, you know
what I'd like to do?
I'd like to spit on it.
I would like
to see that.
Should I--
Should I do it?
Teach him a lesson
he'll never forget.
Who does he think he is?
Someone's gotta stop him.
It's against the law
isn't it?
Well, it certainly should be.
Okay.
[ALARM ACTIVATOR BEEPS]
This is some machine.
Leave it
to the Germans.
[SNORTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Let me ask you something.
What do they get for a tune-up
on this?
Jerry!
Elaine!
Where have you been?
I was arrested for urinating.
Me too.
You what?
I have "uromysitysis."
It's very serious,
you know.
Jerry,
look at my fish.
Is he...
No, but he's not looking good.
Ugh.
Please.
We can't find our car.
Please drive us
around the parking lot
to find our car.
My fish are dying.
Sorry. Can't do it.
I can see not caring
what happens to us.
We're human.
But what about the fish?
The fish.
Sorry.
Oh, that's right, go.
Go home to your dumbbells.
Go work on your pecs
and your lats.
We're all really impressed.
Yeah, that's right.
You heard me.
You got a problem
with that?
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
Elaine, shut up.
Don't worry.
I'm packing heat.
Hey, hey, hey. Where's Kramer?
I don't know.
I thought
he was with you.
Oh, see. See, I knew
this was gonna happen.
Look at the time. All right.
That's it.
All right. Did we look
over there?
Have we checked that side?
We came in
over there.
We didn't come in over there.
Where's Kramer?
Oh, look at these cars.
They all look
exactly alike.
ELAINE: Oh...
[COUGHING]
The fumes.
I can't breathe.
I'm having trouble breathing.
Hey, George,
there she is again.
What are you doing?
You're killing me.
Ask her to drive us around.
There's your opening.
That is an opening.
Uh, excuse me.
I'm really, uh...
Uh, see, what happened--
My friend forgot
where he parked, and--
Sure, I'll drive you around.
You will?
Sure.
GEORGE:
Thank you.
Thank you. We're late...
and my parents
are waiting for me
in front of my building,
and we're stuck here.
Well, I wouldn't wanna
get lost in here.
It smells like a toilet.
People are such animals.
You're telling me.
Filthy pigs.
GEORGE:
It's a brown Ford.
This has happened to me too.
It's very frustrating.
Oh...
I asked several people.
They wouldn't even answer me.
I'm happy to do it.
I'm Michele.
Hi, Michele.
I'm George.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
MICHELE: Get out!
But I didn't mean
anything by it.
I don't even know
L. Ron Hubbard.
I-- I didn't know
you were with that group.
What about my fish?
Boy, those scientologists.
They can be pretty sensitive.
I'll say.
What is it?
[GASPS]
The car!
[LAUGHING]
[SHOUTING WITH JOY]
ELAINE: I can't believe it!
Kramer.
Kramer's not here.
I knew it. I knew it.
I knew this
would happen.
Kramer!
ELAINE: Kramer!
Hey, look.
Boy, I had a hell of a time
finding that air conditioner.
You know, I looked everywhere.
I completely forgot
where I hid it.
Know where it was?
Purple 23.
Right. Purple 23.
I could have used you.
Sometimes it's good
to write those things down.
Oh, boy.
What time is it?
Seven forty-five.
Oh.
Well, at least there'll be
no traffic, huh?
Right.
Oh, boy.
What time's that play start?
Eight o'clock.
Oh, that could be a problem.
Where's
your little bag of...
Oh.
All right.
Let's giddy-up-up.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[CLICKING]
[ENGINE CONTINUES SPUTTERING]
See, the problem
with the mall garage
is that everything
looks the same.
They try to differentiate it.
They put up different colors,
different numbers,
different letters.
What they need to do
is name the levels like
"Your mother's a whore."
You know what I mean?
You would remember that.
You would go, "I know,
I'm parked
at My Father's
an Abusive Alcoholic."
I know where I'm parked.