It seems the way they've
designed the car alarm
is so that the car
will behave
as if it was a nervous,
hysterical person.
Anyone goes near it,
anyone disturbs it...
[MIMICS SIREN WAILING]
Lights flashing on and off,
acting all crazy.
Not everyone wants to draw
that much attention
to themselves.
Wouldn't it be nice if you could
have a car alarm that
was a little more subtle?
Maybe just, you know,
somebody tries to break in,
and it goes...
[CLEARS THROAT]
[LAUGHTER]
"Excuse me?"
I would like a car alarm
like that.
Do you believe this?
Car was parked
right out front.
Was the alarm on?
I don't know.
I guess it was on.
I don't know
my alarm sound.
I'm not tuned into it
like it's my son.
I don't understand.
How do these thieves
start the car?
They cross the wires
or something.
Cross the wires?
I can't even make
a pot of spaghetti.
Hey.
They stole my car.
Who did?
They did.
What? Is there more
than just one?
What should I do?
Call the police?
What are they gonna do?
You know, I'd better call
the car-phone company,
cancel my service.
Maybe you should
call your car phone.
Yeah.
He's probably driving
it right now.
Wait a minute.
Call the car phone.
See what happens.
Are you serious?
Yeah, go ahead. Call.
I don't even know
if I remember the number.
What do I say
if he picks up?
MAN: Hello.
Hello.
Is this 555-8383?
I have no idea.
Can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
Did you steal my car?
Yes, I did.
You did?
I did.
But that's my car.
I didn't know it was yours.
What are you
gonna do with it?
I don't know.
Drive around.
Then can I have it back?
Mmmm...
No, I'm gonna keep it.
Let me talk to him.
Give it, give it, give it.
Hello.
Yeah, who's this?
Kramer.
Hello, Kramer.
Listen, there's a pair of gloves
in the glove compartment.
Wait, hold it.
De, de, de-dee ♪
Brown ones?
Yeah.
Listen, could you
mail those to me?
Or bring them by my building.
It's 129 West 81st Street.
129. Okay.
All right, thanks a lot.
Here's Jerry.
Gloves.
Hello.
Jerry.
Yeah. Let me ask you
a question.
How do you cross those wires?
I didn't cross any wires.
The keys were in it.
Sid left the keys
in the car.
All right, I gotta go.
Drive carefully.
Hey, Jerry, when's the last
time you had a tune-up?
Because I can't find
the owner's--
Sid left the keys
in the car.
Who's Sid?
He's this guy
in the neighborhood.
Parks cars on the block.
What do you mean?
He moves them
from one side to the other,
so you don't
get ticketed.
You pay him for that?
Yeah. Like 50 bucks
a month.
How many people
does he do that for?
The whole block,
40, 50 cars.
He only works
three hours a day.
He makes a fortune.
He's been doing that
for years, right, Jerry?
Could anybody do that?
Hey, Sid,
what happened?
I'm sorry, Jerry.
Maybe I'm getting too old
for this stuff.
You left the keys
in the car?
Well, you know.
They're making that
Woody Allen movie on the block
and all those people
and trucks everywhere
and when I saw him, I must've
got a little distracted.
You know I'm in that movie.
You're what?
Yeah, I'm an extra.
How'd you get that?
Well, I was just watching
them film yesterday,
and some guy just asked me.
Right out of the clear blue sky?
Clear blue sky.
Why didn't they ask me?
I got a quality.
Hey, Jerry,
you got insurance, right?
Yeah, but no car.
I'll have to rent one.
I'm going to visit my sister
in Virginia next Wednesday
for a week,
so I can't park it.
This Wednesday?
No, next Wednesday.
Week after this Wednesday.
But the Wednesday two days
from now
is the next Wednesday.
If I meant this Wednesday,
I would've said,
"this Wednesday."
It's the week
after this Wednesday.
Sid, who's gonna move the cars
while you're away?
Whoever wants to move them.
What do I care who moves them?
They can move themselves
if they want.
Maybe I could move them
until you get back.
What's a young man like you
want to move cars for?
You don't work?
I'm in a transition phase
right now.
Well, if you want
to move the cars, move the cars.
Just don't forget to take
the keys out. That's all
All right.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Yeah, the defroster's
the one on the bottom.
Just slide it all the way over.
You're welcome.
I'm in awe of
his intellect.
When he talks,
it sounds like
he's reading from
one of his novels.
Owen March.
I never heard of him.
Well, he's not
a baseball player.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, so it sounds like it's
going pretty good.
Yeah. Well, there is
one little problem.
What's that?
He's 66 years old.
WOMAN: Next, please.
Go. Go. She-- Go. Come on.
Can I help you?
Name, please.
Uh, Seinfeld. I made
a reservation for a midsize,
and she's a small.
I'm kidding around,
of course.
Yes.
Okay,
let's see here.
Sixty-six years old?
Yeah, well, he's
in perfect health.
He works out. He's vibrant.
You'd really like him.
Why do people always
say that?
I hate everybody.
Why would I like him?
So, what do you think?
Could you go out
with a 66-year-old woman?
Well, I'll tell you, she would
have to be really vibrant.
So vibrant
she'd be spinning.
I'm sorry.
We have no midsize
available at the moment.
I don't understand.
I made a reservation.
Do you have my
reservation?
Yes, we do. Unfortunately,
we ran out of cars.
But the reservation
keeps the car here.
That's why you have
the reservation.
I know why we have
reservations.
I don't think you do.
If you did,
I'd have a car.
See, you know how to take
the reservation.
You just don't know
how to hold the reservation.
And that's really
the most important part
of the reservation,
the holding.
Anybody can
just take them.
Let me speak
with my supervisor.
Well, here we go.
The supervisor.
Know what she's saying
over there?
What?
"Hey, Marge, see
those two people?
"They think I'm talking to you.
"So you pretend like
you're talking to me.
Okay, now you start
talking."
"You mean like this? So it
looks like I'm saying something,
but I'm not really
saying anything at all?"
"Okay. Now you say something
else, and they won't yell at me,
because they thought
I was checking with you."
"Okay, I think. I think that's
enough. See you later."
I'm sorry. My supervisor says
there's nothing we can do.
Yeah, it looked like you were in
a real conversation over there.
But we do have a compact
if you would like that.
Fine.
All right.
Well, we have a blue Ford
Escort for you, Mr. Seinfeld.
Would you like insurance?
Yeah, you better give me
the insurance,
because I am gonna beat
the hell out of this thing.
Please fill this out.
So, what do you think?
Do you think I'm making
a big mistake?
Hey, if you enjoy being with
him, that's what's important.
I love being with him.
I mean,
I like being with him.
It's okay
being with him.
I just don't enjoy
Well, that's
what's important.
I'm meeting him for lunch
at Chadway's, around the corner.
Do I have to break up
with him face to face,
or can I just do
it over the phone?
How many times have
you been out?
Seven.
Face to face.
Seven dates
is a face-to-face breakup?
If it was six,
I could've let you go.
But seven, I'm afraid,
is over the limit.
Unless, of course,
there was no sex.
[HORNS HONKING,
CAR ALARMS WAILING OUTSIDE]
Hmm.
How's the pasta
over there?
Hey-- Whoa! Whoa!
What is going on
out there?
I need, like,
a bucket of water.
I got a car overheating.
I got an alarm
that won't go off.
I'm pressing one.
I'm pressing two. Nothing.
What do I do?
Help me. Help me.
[KEYS JANGLE]
Hey you know
they were supposed
to do my scene today.
Today?
Yeah.
You know they told me
that they wanted me
to walk down the block carrying
this bag of groceries.
So I start to walk, and I trip.
And the grocery bag goes flying
and Woody--
Woody starts laughing.
He was laughing?
Oh, yeah. He was
drinking something.
It started to come
out of his nose.
So then what?
I got a line
in the movie!
Get out!
That's great.
Ha-ha!
You got a line
in a Woody Allen movie?
Pretty good, huh?
You're in
the movie?
Is he in the scene?
Oh yeah, yeah.
It's me and him.
I might have a whole new
career on my hands, huh?
You mean
"a career."
So was
Mia Farrow there?
I didn't see him.
What's your line?
Well, okay, I'm there
with Woody, you know.
I'm at this bar,
and, uh, I'm sit--
You know it's Woody Allen.
Did I mention that?
We got it.
And I'm sitting there
with Woody,
and I say--
I turn to him and I go,
"Boy, these pretzels
are making me thirsty."
Is that how you're
gonna say it?
No, no. I'm working on it.
Do it like this.
"These pretzels are
making me thirsty"
No.
"These pretzels are
making me thirsty."
No, no. See, that's no good.
See, you don't know
how to act.
"These pretzels...
are making me thirsty!"
Oh, that was no good?
I didn't
say anything.
All right, I'm gonna go
break up with Owen.
What was wrong
with that?
I had a different
interpretation.
Do you know anything
about this pretzel guy?
Maybe he's been in the bar
a really long time
and he's really depressed
because he has no job,
and no woman
and he's parking cars
for a living!
All right! All right!
Shut up! Shut up!
I hear you!
I'm coming down!
These pretzels are
making me thirsty!
Yeah!
[HONKING, WAILING
CONTINUE OUTSIDE]
[LOUD KNOCKING]
Oh, my God.
Call an
ambulance.
Boy,
he took it hard.
ELAINE: We were walking
down the block
right by your house, and I was
about to break up with him,
and then all of a sudden,
he started to twitch.
Yes, I need an ambulance at 129
West 81st Street, Apartment 5A.
Tell them to hurry.
Hurry!
It's an ambulance.
I don't know,
but he's unconscious.
These pretzels
are making me thirsty!
Kramer.
What happened
here?
I don't know.
What should we do?
We called an ambulance.
Does anyone know first aid?
Do something
with the extremities.
What extremities?
What's an extremity?
You raise the feet,
get blood to the head.
You raise the head,
get blood to the feet.
Okay, what about
a cold compress?
They always do that.
I don't have
a washcloth.
Use a paper towel.
You can't put a paper
towel on his head.
What about
a big sponge?
How you gonna hold it on?
Use a belt.
No, no, no.
That'll--
It'll drip
all over him.
Should we
walk him around?
I've seen
them do that.
No, that's for
a drug overdose.
Maybe that's
what he's got.
No, I just had
lunch with him.
He didn't leave
the table.
Well, he could've dropped acid
when you weren't looking.
He is not
a drug addict.
Hey, maybe
he's diabetic.
He might just need
a cookie or something.
A cookie!
Can you give him a cookie?
How's he gonna chew it?
We'll move his teeth.
It happened to my uncle.
The sugar
revived him.
Careful, you're getting
crumbs all over him.
I've got him chewing,
but I don't think
he's gonna swallow.
Let's put a few cookies in a
blender and he could drink it.
Cookies don't liquefy.
Yes they do. You can
liquefy a cookie.
I'll get
the blender.
I don't have
a blender.
You've got a blender.
I'd know
if I had a blender.
Where is
the ambulance?!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[THUD,
GLASS SHATTERS]
Hello, yes. I called
for an ambulance
like 35 minutes ago.
I can't believe
what's going on out here.
This is an emergency.
What's taking so long?
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
Wait a second.
Maybe that's them.
Hello.
MAN: Paramedics.
Come on up.
Okay, they're here.
He seems
to be breathing.
You know,
I got to tell you,
he's a pretty
good-looking guy.
I know.
Those eyebrows could
use a trimming.
You ever mention
that to him?
Almost.
I mean, because,
come on,
they're running wild there.
It's not an easy
thing to bring up.
Yeah, that's true.
You should see his bathrobe,
man. It's all silk.
Yeah. Does he
wear slippers?
I bet he
wears slippers.
He does.
How'd you know that?
I could tell.
What happened?
What took you so long?
We got here 20 minutes ago,
but we couldn't move.
The whole intersection
is gridlocked.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Finally we make the turn,
and this guy who was running
around triple-parking cars
slammed into us
with a blue Escort.
Blue Escort?
That's my rent-a-car!
GEORGE: Oh, man.
What happened
to the car?
I'm sorry. You don't know
what's going on out there!
Who's he?
This guy I'm seeing.
GEORGE: What happened?
We don't know.
Who put cookies
in his mouth?
Cookies?
You're not supposed
to do that.
JERRY:
So how'd you
hit the car?
I was moving it
across the street.
I looked up and I saw
Woody Allen.
I got all distracted.
It's not even my car.
It's a rental.
What are you doing
out there?
You're holding up
the production of the movie.
We can't shoot, and Woody,
he's really mad at you.
Woody mentioned me?
What did he say?
He said, "Who's the moron who's
got the street all screwed up?"
Should I apologize to Woody?
All right,
I'll tell you what.
Next time I talk to him,
maybe I'll bring it up.
I'll feel him out.
What do you think first aid
was like hundreds of years ago?
You know, I mean,
they had no medicine, no drugs
no technology, no equipment.
Basically,
they were there first.
That was it. That was the whole
first aid. They sit with you.
That's all they could do.
"Can you help me?"
"No, we can't help you,
but we were the first ones here.
"Did you see our truck?
'First aid.' That's our motto.
[LAUGHTER]
We show up before anybody."
You didn't
tell me
you didn't know
how to drive.
Should've mentioned that.
Well, I know how to drive.
Then how did all those cars
get damaged?
Why are people calling me up,
screaming on the phone?
Most of them
canceled out on me.
Can I get anybody anything?
Moving cars from one side
of the street to the other
don't take no more sense
than putting on a pair of pants.
My question to you is:
Who's putting your pants on?
I put my pants on, Sid.
I don't believe you.
You can put your pants on,
you can move those cars.
I don't want to get into
a big dispute about the pants.
Who's gonna send money
to my sister in Virginia?
Her little boy
needs surgery on his foot.
Now he gonna be walking around
with a limp,
because you can't park
a few cars.
Maybe I could call
my father.
Hey, you seen
the paper yet?
Interestingly enough, no,
inasmuch as
it is my paper.
Look there.
There's an article
about that writer.
"Owen March, prominent author
and essayist,
"suffered a stroke
yesterday
in the Upper West Side
apartment of a friend."
That's the guy that was here.
You're the friend.
Thanks. "The extent
of the damage would've been
far less severe had paramedics
been able to reach him sooner."
Oh, Lord.
"The commotion also
delayed production
"of a Woody Allen movie
that was shooting up the block.
"A spokeswoman
for the legendary filmmaker
"said that Mr. Allen
was extremely agitated
"and wondered if his days
of shooting movies in New York
were over."
Five seconds.
Jerry, I was five seconds away
from breaking up with him.
Five seconds! The next
words out of my mouth were,
"Owen, it's over."
Can he communicate?
Yeah. Well, he nods.
And I think
he understands me.
He seems to enjoy it
when I read to him.
Phew.
All right, she's free.
Hi, I called before.
My car got smashed.
So, listen,
what should I do?
I mean, if I break up
with him now,
it'll look like I'm abandoning
him because of his condition.
I'll be ostracized
from the community.
What community?
There's a community?
Of course there's
a community.
All these years, I'm living
in a community, I had no idea.
Sir, the estimate on the damage
to your car is 2866 dollars.
Ooh, well, I got the insurance
and everything, so--
Yes. In your report, you said
you were not the driver
at the time of the accident.
That is right.
It was somebody else.
All right, well, sir,
you're only covered
for when you're
driving the car.
Mm-hm. What's that?
You're not covered
for other drivers.
Other drivers?
Mm-hm.
Your whole business is based
on other drivers.
It's a rented car.
That's who's driving it.
Other drivers.
Doesn't my credit card
cover me or something?
Not that
particular one.
I got a hundred cards.
Here, here. Pick a card.
Take any card you want.
Go ahead. Whichever one.
I don't care.
Really, sir, if you had read
the rental agreement--
Did you see the size
of that document?
It's like the Declaration
of Independence.
Who's gonna read that?
Mr. Seinfeld,
as it stands right now,
you are not covered
for that damage
and there is absolutely nothing
that can be done about that.
These pretzels
are making me thirsty.
Ahhh. It's good,
isn't it?
Yankee bean.
Why "Yankee" bean, huh?
Don't they have beans
in the South?
I mean, if you order Yankee bean
in the South, are they offended?
Huh?
[LAUGHS]
♪ Yankee bean
Yankee bean ♪
♪ I like my Yankee ♪
♪ Bean ♪
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Owen...
I think we have to talk.
I mean, uh, I have to talk.
It would be nice if we could,
but, you know, whatever.
Um...
Don't get me wrong.
I like coming here
and feeding you
and cleaning a little,
and paying your bills.
I mean, that's good stuff.
Good stuff.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I have a wonderful time
when I'm with you. Wonderful!
But at this point in my life,
I'm not really sure
that I'm ready to make
a commitment to one person.
I'm just not really sure
that we have enough in common.
I mean, for example:
I like running in the park,
bicycling,
roller-skating,
tennis and, uh, skiing.
And, um, well,
I'm gonna be brutally
honest with you now.
It's a bitch to get here.
It's two subways.
I have to transfer at 42nd
Street to take the double-R.
Anyway, I mean, this doesn't
mean we can't be friends.
These pretzels
are making me thirsty.
Can you die
from an odor?
I mean, like, if you were locked
in a vomitorium for two weeks
could you actually die
from the odor?
An overdose of odor.
Good question.
Do I smell?
No, no, no. I was just down
at the 42nd Street subway today.
It is disgusting.
Guess who I bumped
into? Owen.
Ah.
He's all right?
Yeah, he's almost
fully recovered.
Told me he was just
using me for sex.
Let me get that.
No, no, no.
I got it.
Please.
Come on. Let me.
I smashed your car.
It cost you
over 2000 dollars.
Yeah, a cup of coffee
should cover it.
Oh, man.
What are you
doing here?
I got fired
from the movie.
Get out of here. What?
What?
Well, you know, they were
gonna shoot it today.
We rehearsed it twice, and
then Woody yells, "Action."
I turn to him
and I say,
[IN UNISON]
"These pretzels are
making me thirsty."
Right.
Then I took
a swig of beer
and I slammed the glass
down on the bar,
and it shattered.
Ohhh.
Well, one of the pieces
must've hit Woody,
and he started crying.
And he yells out,
"I'm bleeding," and he runs off.
Anyway, this woman, she came up
to me, and she says,
"You're fired."
Boy, I really
nailed that scene.
Oh, wait a--
Oh. Oh, for crying
out loud.
[♪]
The best part of a relationship
is when you're sick.
And the best part of being sick
is when you're
in a relationship.
But if I was to get married,
you know those vows,
"for richer or for poorer,
for better or for worse."
All I need is the sickness.
That is the most important one.
"Do you take this man
in sickness?"
That's the only time
I need somebody there.
The rest of the time, go out,
have a ball.
Do whatever you want.
But if I get the sniffles,
you better be there.
[♪]