Does it seem to you
that the ventriloquist dummy
has a very active
sexual-social life?
He's always talking about dates
and women that he knows
and bringing them back
to the suitcase at night.
There's always a sawdust joke
in there somewhere, you know.
He says kinky things
because he's made out of wood
and he can spin his head around.
We're somehow
expected to believe,
Because the face is so animated,
that they think
we're not noticing
that the feet
are just swinging there.
Dummy feet
never look really right,
do they?
They're just
kind of dangling there.
They're always kind of askew,
you know?
And you always just see
a little ankle,
those little, thin,
fabric ankles that they have,
you know.
You think, "I don't think
this thing is real."
Are you kidding me?
Let me speak
with the head librarian.
Because it's absurd!
An overdue book from 1971?
This is a joke, right?
What, are you
from a radio station?
Okay, you got me.
I fell for it.
All right. Okay.
I can be down there
in, like, a half-hour.
Bye.
What's the problem?
This you're not
going to believe.
The New York
Public Library...
Uh-huh.
says that I took out
Tropic of Cancer in 1971
and never returned it.
Do you know
how much that comes to?
That's a nickel a day
for 20 years.
It's going to be $50,000.
It doesn't work
like that.
If it's a dime a day,
it could be 100,000.
It's not going to be
anything.
I returned the book.
I remember it
very vividly,
because I was
with Sherry Becker.
Mm-hmm.
She wore
this orange dress.
It was the first time
I ever saw her
in a dress like that.
I'd known her since ninth grade,
and she was developing this body
in secret,
under these loose clothes,
for, like, two years,
and then one day...
this orange dress.
It's burned in my memory.
Ooh. Memory burn, huh?
I wonder
whatever happened to her.
How did they find you?
Oh, computers.
They're cracking down now
on overdue books.
The whole thing's
completely ridiculous.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
That's George.
Wait'll he finds out
we're going
to the library
He'll be thrilled.
Uh-huh.
You know, I never got
a library card.
I'm coming down.
It's all a bunch
of cheapskates
in there anyway.
People sitting around,
reading the newspaper
attached to those
huge wooden sticks.
Trying to save a quarter.
Ooh.
I got to go
to the library.
You want to go?
Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
The Dewey Decimal System.
What a scam that was.
Boy, this Dewey guy
really cleaned up
on that deal.
Where's George?
Shh!
Look.
Trying to save
a quarter.
I kind of like
those sticks.
I'd like to get them
in my house.
This woman's
completely ignoring me.
Look at her.
This is a lonely woman
looking for companionship.
A spinster.
Maybe a virgin.
Maybe she got hurt
a long time ago.
She's a schoolgirl.
There was a boy.
It didn't work out,
so now she needs
a little tenderness.
She needs
a little understanding.
Needs a little Kramer.
Then she'll need
a little shot
of penicillin.
Yes?
Yeah, I called before.
I got this notice
in the mail.
Oh, Tropic of Cancer.
Henry Miller.
Uh, this case
has been turned over
to our Library Investigations
officer,
Mr. Bookman.
Bookman?
The library investigator's name
is actually Bookman?
Come on.
It's true.
That's amazing.
That's like an ice cream man
named Cone.
Well, Lieutenant Bookman's
been working here for 25 years,
so I think he's heard
all the jokes.
Can I speak
with this Bookman?
Just a second.
Jerry...
What?
I think I saw him.
I think it's him.
Who?
Did you see
the homeless guy
on the library steps
screaming obscenities
and doing some sort
of calisthenics routine?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
I think that's Mr. Heyman.
The gym teacher
from our high school.
Shh!
Heyman? Are you sure?
He's older.
Completely covered
in filth.
No whistle,
but I think it's him.
George got him fired.
He squealed on him.
Ooh. Tattletale.
I didn't tattle.
Shh!
All right.
Well, what did this guy do?
What happened?
There was an incident.
I'd rather not
discuss it.
Oh, come on. You can tell me.
Some other time.
What, tonight?
You know, I never figured you
for a squealer.
Oh, he sang
like a canary.
Mr. Bookman's not here.
Not here? Why was I told
to come down here?
He'll be out all afternoon
on a case.
He's out on a case?
He actually goes out cases?
Well, what am I
supposed to do now?
I'll have Mr. Bookman
get in touch with you.
All right. Thanks.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go see
if it's Heyman.
It's not him.
Hey, I'll, uh...
I'll see you boys later, huh?
So, uh, what's a guy
got to do around here
to get a library card?
Where's Karen?
She went
to pick up lunch.
Well,
she didn't ask me what I wanted.
She must have forgot.
How could she forget?
I've been ordering lunch here
every day
for three and a half years.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Because I'm getting, like,
a really weird vibe.
Is Lippman getting rid of me?
It's okay. You can tell me.
I won't say anything.
I don't know anything.
Aha!
You don't know anything.
You see?
"I don't know anything" means
that there's something to know.
If you really
didn't know anything,
you would have said,
"You're crazy."
Oh, hi, Mr. Lippman.
Elaine.
Um, I was wondering
if you got a chance
to look at that
biography of Columbus
that I gave you.
Yes, I did.
Marie, this water
is still too cold.
Oh, yeah.
It's freezing!
Hurts your teeth.
I'm telling you,
something is going on.
He never likes
anything I recommend,
and then
that lunch thing.
So they forgot
to get your lunch.
Big deal.
What do you know?
You've never worked
in an office.
See, you've worked
in an office, George.
You understand.
Jerry thinks
I'm overreacting,
but you understand.
Lunch.
I don't understand lunch.
I don't know anything
about lunch.
Just because
I got the guy fired
doesn't mean I turned him
into a bum, does it?
What did he do?
He purposely
mispronounced my name.
Instead of saying "Costanza",
he'd say, "Can't-stand-ya!
Can't-stand-ya!"
Remember he made me smell
my own gym socks once?
I remember, he made you wear
a jock on your head
for a whole class,
and the straps
were hanging down.
Okay, okay.
You never even
had him for gym.
I had him for hygiene.
Remember his teeth?
It was like
from an exhumed corpse.
Like little baked beans.
Ew.
Yuck.
Come on, tell me
what happened.
Well, okay.
As I said,
the guy had it in for me.
He actually failed me in gym.
Me.
And those
spastic Schnitzer twins.
Can't-stand-ya!
Yes, Mr. Heyman?
Your underwear
was sticking out
of your shorts
during gym class.
Oh, well,
I guess that's because
I wear boxer shorts.
Boxer shorts, huh?
What brand?
I'm not really sure. I--
Yeah, well,
let's take a look!
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[SCREAMS]
He gave me a wedgie.
And he got fired the next day.
Why do they call it
a wedgie?
Because the underwear
is pulled up from the back
until it...
wedges in.
They also have an atomic wedgie.
Now, the goal there
is to actually get the waistband
on top of the head.
It's very rare.
Boys are sick.
Well, what do girls do?
We just tease someone
till they develop
an eating disorder.
I got to go back to the library
and talk to him.
I got to find out
if I ruined his life.
Hey, Babaloo,
you better get home.
You know, this guy Bookman
from the library,
he's waiting for you.
What's amazing to me
about the library,
is that here's a place
where you can go in,
you take out any book you want,
and they just give it to you
and say, "Bring it back
when you're done."
Reminds you of, like,
this pathetic friend
everybody had
when they were a little kid
that would let you borrow
any of his stuff
if you would just be his friend,
you know?
That's what the library is.
It's a government-funded
pathetic friend,
and that's why everybody
kind of bullies the library.
I'll bring it back on time,
I'll bring it back late.
Oh, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
You gonna charge me,
a nickel?
Well, I'm glad
you're here.
We'll get this straightened out.
Would you like a cup of tea?
You got any coffee?
Coffee?
Yeah, coffee.
No, I don't drink coffee.
You don't drink coffee?
How about instant coffee?
No, I don't have--
You don't have
any instant coffee?
Well, I don't--
Who doesn't have instant coffee?
I don't.
You buy a jar
of Folger's crystals,
you put it in the cupboard,
you forget about it,
and later on, when you need it,
it's there.
It lasts forever.
It's freeze-dried crystals.
Freeze-dried crystals.
Really.
I'll have to remember that.
You took this book out
in 1971.
Yes, and I returned it
Yeah, '71.
That was my first year
on the job.
Bad year for libraries.
Bad year for America.
Hippies burning library cards.
Abbie Hoffman telling everybody
to steal books.
I don't judge a man
by the length of his hair
or the kind of music
he listens to.
Rock was never my bag.
But you put on a pair of shoes
when you walk into the New York
Public Library, fella.
Look, Mr. Bookman...
I returned that book.
I remember it very specifically.
You're a comedian.
You make people laugh.
I try.
You think this is all
a big joke, don't you?
No, I don't.
I saw you on TV once.
I remembered your name
from my list.
I looked it up.
Sure enough,
it checked out.
You think because
you're a celebrity
that somehow the law
doesn't apply to you?
That you're
above the law?
Certainly not.
Well, let me tell you something,
funny boy.
You know that little stamp,
the one that says
"New York Public Library"?
Well, that may not mean
anything to you,
but that means
a lot to me.
One whole hell of a lot.
Sure, go ahead,
laugh if you want to.
I've seen your type before.
Flashy, making the scene,
flaunting convention.
Yeah, I know
what you're thinking.
"Why's this guy
making such a big stink
about old library books?"
Well, let me give you
a hint, junior.
Maybe we can live
without libraries,
people like you and me.
Maybe.
Sure, we're too old
to change the world,
but what about that kid,
sitting down,
opening a book right now
in a branch of the local library
and finding drawings
of pee-pees and wee-wees...
in The Cat in the Hat
and The Five
Chinese Brothers?
Doesn't he deserve better?
Look, if you think
this is about
overdue fines
and missing books,
you'd better think again.
This is about that kid's right
to read a book
without getting his mind warped,
or maybe that turns you on,
Seinfeld.
Maybe that's how
you get your kicks,
you and your
good-time buddies.
Well, I got a flash for you,
joy-boy.
Party time is over.
You got seven days,
Seinfeld.
That is one week.
What's wrong?
It's Bookman,
the library cop.
So? I didn't do
anything wrong.
I'm supposed
to be at work.
I could get fired.
I never should have
come here.
Ooh. Why don't you leave?
I can't.
There's no way I'm paying that!
I returned that book in 1971!
I have a witness--
Sherry Becker!
She wore an orange dress!
She gave me
a piece of Blackjack Gum!
I said, "Licorice gum.
What are they gonna
think of next?"
I remember it!
Becker... Becker...
Kevin went to a public school.
He's the 14-year-old.
We were going to send Marsha
to a private school,
because in some ways,
they don't...
learn enough, I think.
So, Sherry, what do you remember
about that day at the library?
I remember it
like it was yesterday.
It was a Friday afternoon.
I wore a purple dress.
Purple?
You sure it wasn't orange?
Positive.
And I was chewing Dentyne.
Oh, I always chewed Dentyne.
Remember, Jerry? Dentyne?
No Blackjack?
Ugh! Licorice gum?
Never.
What else?
We were, uh,
reading passages to each other
from that Henry Miller book
you had.
Tropic of Cancer.
No! Tropic of Capricorn.
Tropic of Capricorn?
Remember?
"What holds the world together,
"as I have learned
"from bitter experience,
is sexual intercourse."
Wait a second, wait a second.
You're right.
I had both of them.
We read
from Tropic of Capricorn.
I was all set to return
Tropic of Cancer,
and then...
George, here's the book.
Oh, man!
Don't let anybody see it.
Don't let anything
happen to it.
Jerry, it's me, George.
Don't worry.
I'll return it tomorrow,
no problem.
All right. See you later.
I'm late
for Heyman's hygiene.
Where are you going?
It was nice
seeing you again.
I just remembered
something.
I've got to go.
It was George!
Read another poem.
"Pressed chest,
fleshed out west,
"might be the savior,
or a garden pest."
Wow. That is great poetry.
You should be published.
It's great.
Well, the library's
kind of a cool place
when it's closed.
Oh, yeah.
You don't have to be quiet.
Listen to the echo.
Hello!
Hello.
Mr. Bookman.
I remember
when the librarian
was a much older woman,
kindly, discreet,
unattractive.
We didn't know anything
about her private life.
We didn't want to know anything
She didn't have
a private life.
While you're thinking
about that,
think about this.
The library closes at 5:00,
no exceptions.
This is your
final warning.
Got that, kewpie doll?
Lippman wants to see me
in his office.
"See me." That can't be good.
Maybe you're
getting a raise.
Maybe I'm getting a wedgie.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
What?
It's George.
George is on his way up!
Wait till I tell him
about the book!
[WHIMPERING]
Are you okay?
[MOANS]
What? What?
It's, uh...
Oh...
It's Marion's poetry.
I can't take it!
Oh, Kramer.
[SOBBING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Remember that biography
I recommended?
My boss hated it!
I'm right here.
Oh. Sorry.
Remember
that Columbus book?
Columbus. Eurotrash.
Well, it's definitely him.
Him? Him who?
Him who? Heyman him.
Heyman?
The gym teacher?
You found him?
Oh, I found him.
He was sitting on the steps
to the library.
I sat down next to him.
He smelled
like the locker room
after that game
against Erasmus.
That was double overtime.
I said, "Mr. Heyman,
"it's me, George Costanza,
"J.F.K.,
'71."
He doesn't move,
so I said, uh...
"Can't-stand-ya.
Can't-stand-ya."
He turns and smiles.
Little baked bean teeth.
I get up to run away,
but something
was holding me back.
It was Heyman.
He had my underwear.
There I was,
on the steps
of the 42nd Street Library,
a grown man...
getting a wedgie.
At least
it wasn't atomic.
It was.
So, Georgie-boy,
guess what happened
to Tropic of Cancer?
How should I know?
Because I gave it to you.
Me?
Yeah. Think. Don't you remember?
You kept begging me to see it,
then finally I agreed.
You were supposed
to return it.
I met you in the gym locker room
and gave it to you.
The locker room.
George, here's the book.
Oh, man!
Don't let anybody
see it.
Don't let anything
happen to it.
Jerry, it's me, George.
Don't worry.
I'll return it tomorrow.
No problem.
All right.
I'll see you
after school.
I'm late
for Heyman's hygiene.
Oh.
[LAUGHING MENACINGLY]
Can't-stand-ya!
Yes, Mr. Heyman?
Your underwear
was sticking
out of your shorts
during gym class.
Well, I guess
that's because
I wear boxer shorts.
Boxer shorts, huh?
What brand?
Well, I'm not really sure. I--
Yeah? Well,
let's take a look!
[LAUGHS]
[SCREAMS]
[HEYMAN LAUGHING]
Anyway,
I hope there's
no hard feelings.
Hard feelings?
What do you know
about hard feelings?
You ever have a man die
in your arms?
Ever kill somebody?
What is your problem?
What's my problem?
Punks like you.
That's my problem,
and you'd better not
screw up again, Seinfeld,
because if you do,
I'll be all over you
like a pit bull on a poodle.
That is one tough monkey.
So, you were saying?
Oh.
So I took
your suggestion,
and I gave my boss
Marion's poems,
the ones
that affected Kramer
so much.
Oh, beautiful.
Did he like them?
No, he didn't.
Was he out there?
No, he's gone.
Wonder what happened to him.
I guess we'll never know.
[MUMBLING]
Can't-stand-ya!
[GIGGLING MADLY]
Any day that you had gym
was a weird school day.
You know what I mean?
Because it, like,
started off kind of normal.
You'd have, like, English,
geometry, social studies,
and then suddenly,
you're like
in Lord of the Flies
for 40 minutes, you know?
You're hanging from a rope.
You have hardly any clothes on.
Teachers are yelling at you,
"Where's your jockstrap?"
You know, and kids
are throwing dodge balls at you.
You're trying to survive.
Then it's history, science,
language.
There's something off
in the whole flow of that day.
[♪]