I have never seen an old person
in a new bathing suit.
In my life.
I don't know where they get
their bathing suits,
but my father has bathing suits
from other centuries,
and my parents live in Florida,
and if you go down there,
and you forget
your bathing suit,
then they want you to wear
one of theirs.
You know how that gets?
You need trunks, son?
I've got trunks for you.
You can wear my trunks.
Fathers don't wear
bathing suits,
they wear trunks.
It's kind of the same thing
a tree would wear
if it went swimming.
So I get in the water
in this thing,
and it's, like,
floating around me somewhere.
Have you ever
put on a bathing suit
that you don't even know
exactly where you are
inside the bathing suit?
You bump into somebody you know,
"No, I'm parasailing.
I'm waiting
for the boat to come back."
They were supposed
to be here at 7:30.
Call the airlines again.
What happened
to the scotch tape?
Who takes
the scotch tape?
Nobody returns anything
around here.
Oh, I think that's them.
Know what I'll do next time?
I'll hide it
so nobody can find it.
[KNOCK]
Hi!
Welcome.
How are you?
Welcome to Florida!
Hi, Mr. Seinfeld.
Hey, there's the old man.
How you doing?
So, what took you so long?
We waited 35 minutes
in the rent-a-car place.
I don't know why
you had to rent a car.
We would have
picked you up.
What's the difference?
Well, you could have
used our car.
I don't want to use your car.
What's wrong
with our car?
Nothing, it's a fine car,
what if you want to use it?
We don't use it.
What are you talking about?
We use it.
If you were using it,
we wouldn't use it.
So what would you do?
You would hitch?
How much is a rent-a-car?
I don't know, 25 bucks a day.
What?
Oh, you're crazy.
Plus the insurance.
Oh, I didn't get the insurance.
How could you
not get the insurance?
We'll pay for the car.
You're not paying for it.
Morty.
God, it's so hot in here.
Why don't you put on
the air conditioning?
You don't need
the air conditioner.
So, do you have
your speech all ready?
It's not a speech,
do I have to make a speech?
Of course, they're giving
a testimonial for your father.
You could do
your comic routines.
That'll go over real well
with that crowd.
Ooh, you have a lake.
The lake isn't real.
The lake is real.
Are you kidding?
They built the lake.
But it's real.
It's water.
Where are you
going with those?
I'm gonna put
Elaine's stuff in here.
Oh, don't sleep in there.
You can sleep in the bedroom.
Oh, I can't take
your bedroom.
I'm up at 6:00 in the morning.
I can't kick you
out of your bed.
We don't even sleep.
Ma.
But that's a sofa bed.
You'll be uncomfortable.
What about you?
Why should I be comfortable?
What about him?
Don't worry.
He's comfortable.
I'll sleep standing up.
I'll be fine.
Will you stop?
Yeah, I'll just
stay in here.
[WHISPERING]
Jerry.
Jerry, you don't have to stay
on the couch on my account.
The two of you
could be together.
Nah, that's not
such a good idea.
But I thought
that you--
Not now.
She's right inside.
What happened?
I don't know.
We decided we don't really work
as a couple.
What does that mean?
Well...
What are you whispering?
Shh! Nothing, nothing.
Elaine.
What about her?
You know, look at, uh,
the sun-dried tomatoes.
Where were they five years ago?
It just goes to show you,
you never know what--
what, uh, you know,
could happen...
to a vegetable.
It could just take right off
at any time.
We've tried
all kinds of arrangements,
but we can't seem to be friends
when we sleep together.
Why do you need more friends?
You've got plenty of friends.
He's an idealist.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking, that's the point.
I like looking.
He likes looking.
So look.
But how long
can you look?
I'm going for the record.
You know, your father
wouldn't say so,
but he's
really glad you came.
Oh, come on.
This is a big thing for him.
Outgoing president
of the condo association.
[KNOCKING]
Ah-hah!
So they
arrived safely.
You remember Jack and Doris?
Nice to see you.
This is Elaine.
Hi. Nice to meet you. Hello.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
Hey, Jerry...
You came all the way
down here for this?
And scuba diving.
Scuba diving?
Who's going scuba diving?
We're going scuba diving.
We'll be back in time.
What do you have to
go scuba diving for.
For fun.
For fun?
Jack, have
some sponge cake.
No, thanks. No.
Jack is emceeing? tomorrow.
He's in charge
of the whole thing.
So, Jerry,
your mother tells me
you're going to do
one of your little
comedy skits tomorrow.
I don't think so.
No?
Listen, Morty,
do you want
to settle up
from last night?
All right, I owe you $19.45.
What did you have?
You had the minute steak.
Yeah.
Did you have
a Coke or what?
I did not have a Coke.
Somebody had a Coke.
I had a Coke.
And I had the scampi.
So, that's, uh, 17.10,
and the tax and the tip.
All right,
make it 20 bucks.
It's 19.45, Morty.
19.45.
See, you know
your father.
You gotta get it
right to the penny,
but that's why he was
such a good president.
What kind of pen is that?
This pen?
Yeah.
Oh, this is
an astronaut pen.
It writes upside down.
They use this in space.
Oh, that's
the astronaut pen.
I heard about that.
Where did you get it?
It was a gift.
A lot of times
I write in bed,
and I have to turn
and lean on my elbow
to make the pen work.
Take the pen.
Oh, no.
Go ahead.
I couldn't.
Come on, take the pen!
I can't take it.
Do me a favor!
I'm not comfortable.
Take the pen!
I cannot take it.
Take the pen?
Are you sure?
I'm Positive.
Take the pen.
Okay, thank you
very much.
Thank you. Gee, boy.
Jack, what are you doing?
Stop it.
Jack, we should go.
It was nice meeting you.
Mm, nice to meet you.
Thanks again.
Come on!
She's adorable.
What did you take his pen for?
What? He gave it to me.
You didn't have to take it.
Oh, my God, she's gotta make
a big deal out of everything.
He offered it to me.
Because you made
such a big fuss about it.
Well, I liked it.
Should I have said I didn't?
You shouldn't have
said anything.
What do you
expect him to do?
He could have said,
"Thank you, I like it too,"
and put it in his pocket.
He loves that pen.
Aw, come on.
He talks about it all the time.
Every time he takes it out,
he goes on and on about
how it writes upside down,
how the astronauts use it.
If he likes it so much, then
he never should have offered it.
He didn't think you'd accept.
Well, he was wrong.
I know his wife.
She has some mouth on her.
She'll tell everyone
in the condo now
that you made him
give you the pen.
They're talking
about it right now.
So you want me to return it?
Yes.
DAD: He's not going
to return that pen.
That's ridiculous.
I don't want the pen now!
Jack can afford
to give away a pen
with all his money, believe me.
He gives me a check for 19.45.
He didn't have a Coke.
Ho-ho-ho!
Here, let me see it.
Hey, it writes upside down.
[KNOCKING]
Come in.
You okay in here?
Why is it so hot in here?
How can they sleep like this?
It's only for three days.
Today's over,
then we have tomorrow.
We leave on Sunday.
It's one day, really.
Oh. What is with this bar?
It's right in my back.
It's killing me.
Oh, do you want
to switch?
I'm sleeping in the love seat
I've got my feet up in the air
like I'm in a space capsule.
I am never going to fall asleep.
Oh, no don't say that.
You'll jinx me.
How can they not put
the air conditioning on?
They're nuts with temperature.
Oh, this bar
is right on my back.
It's making a dent.
How about that guy
writing a check for 19.45?
I'm sweating here.
I'm in bed, sweating.
It's one day.
Half a day, really.
I mean,
you subtract showers and meals,
it's like 20 minutes.
It'll go by like that.
Stay on 95 South
to Biscayne Boulevard.
Then you make a left turn.
Put your blinker on immediately.
There's an abutment there.
Then you're going to merge over
very quickly,
but stay on Biscayne.
Don't get off Biscayne.
Do you understand me?
Stay on Biscayne.
You're going
underwater?
Yes, generally, that's where
scuba diving is done.
What do you have to go
underwater for?
What's down there
that's so special?
What's so special up here?
Oh.
What's the matter?
Oh, my back.
Well, what happened?
That-- that bed.
The bar was right in my back.
I told you
to let us sleep in there.
Then you would be
hunched over.
Oh, I don't even know
if I can go scuba diving.
You can't go?
So stay home.
You can go.
Without you?
That's the whole reason
you came down here.
Don't go.
You sure?
Maybe you should
see a doctor.
We'll stay in a hotel tonight.
MOM: No, we'll stay
in there.
Why don't you get a new sofa?
Nobody uses it.
I'm buying you a new sofa.
Oh, Jerry, don't talk crazy.
Mrs. Seinfeld, please,
I am begging you...
put the air conditioner on.
You're hot?
I've lost six pounds.
I don't even know
to to work it.
I keep telling her
it's like an oven in here.
Is everybody up?
Hi. How are you?
Hello, Jerry.
Evelyn,
this is Elaine.
Hi, Evelyn.
Jerry, you got thin.
Too thin?
Oh, stop worrying so much
about how you look.
So where's the new pen?
What?
The pen,
the one Jack Clompers gave you.
How did you know that?
Blanche told me.
Blanche?
That's some good pen.
Writes upside down.
The astronauts use them.
What did Blanche say?
I don't know,
she said Jerry
wanted the pen.
I never really wanted the pen.
He gave him the pen.
Morty.
Why? You don't
like the pen?
No, no, I...
If you don't like it,
give it back to him.
Is that what she said?
Who?
Blanche.
What are you
talking about?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Oh, hello, Gussy.
What?
Jerry wouldn't do that.
Jack gave it to him.
All he said
was he liked it.
I mean, nobody put
a gun to his head.
You're giving him
back that pen.
Somebody, please,
the air conditioner.
Oh, my God,
I forget all about it.
All I said was,
"I like the pen."
How the hell
do you work this thing?
Maybe you shouldn't go tonight.
Oh, no, no,
I want to go.
But your back hurts.
Maybe a couple
of muscle relaxers
would help.
Oh. Oh, okay.
You can turn down
the air conditioning
if you want.
No, I'm fine.
You're not too cold?
No.
Don't be alarmed.
Oh, my God!
What the hell
happened to you?
I'm okay.
My capillaries burst.
Your capillaries?
Do you know
what you look like?
How are you doing?
Having a good time.
Is it my imagination
or is it freezing in here?
What happened to your eyes?
Well, I started
to go under--
With the instructor?
Yeah, and I got
about 10 feet down
and I felt this tremendous
pressure on my mask,
like my eyeballs were being
sucked out of their sockets.
I told you.
Excuse me.
Doris would like to borrow
your red pocketbook
to go with her shoes.
The shoes
have to match the pocketbook.
What's she doing, yoga?
My back hurts.
Morty, better hurry up.
Get ready.
We've got
plenty of time.
What happened to you?
I got in a fist fight
with one of
the ladies at the pool.
It's from scuba diving.
What's there
to see underwater?
Uh, listen, Mr. Clompers,
it was really a nice gesture
of you to give me the pen,
but I don't really need it.
You what?
No, I mean,
it's a terrific pen,
but I think you should keep it.
Well, I mean--
Take it.
All right.
You know, Jack,
you've got nerve,
taking that kid's pen.
Whose pen?
His pen.
This happens to be my pen.
Oh, you didn't give it to him?
What are you talking about?
He practically begged me for it.
Where do you come up
with this crap?
Listen, do you think
I take everything
everybody offers me?
You offered me
sponge cake yesterday.
Did I take it?
You said you didn't want it.
Of course,
I wanted it.
I love sponge cake!
DAD: Then who the hell
said you couldn't have it?
What do I care whether
you have a piece of sponge cake.
I saw your face last week
when I took the scotch tape!
Oh-ho!
So you got the scotch tape!
I've been looking
all over for it.
Don't worry about it,
I'll give it back.
I don't want it!
You know, Jack,
do me a favor, will you?
Take the pen and the scotch tape
and get the hell out of here!
Listen, do you think
I give a damn?
Aah!
The nerve of that guy,
taking back that pen.
Well, that's it for them.
What is going on
in this community?
Are you people aware
of what's happening?
What is driving you
to this behavior?
Is it the humidity,
is it the Muzak,
is it the white shoes?
I have no use
for either one of them.
I don't want even want
them there tonight.
Isn't he supposed to be
the emcee?
Yeah, he's supposed
to be the emcee.
Well, this should be
a very interesting evening.
Uh, what about
those muscle relaxers?
Say "astronaut."
Say what?
You took too many
of those pills.
"Astronaut"?
Say it!
ALL: Astronaut!
Astro--
Good. Okay.
What about last year,
when I took him
to the hospital every day.
Did he ever say
thank you?
Oh, God.
Uncle Leo.
Hello!
Morty, are you nervous?
What nervous?
What's with the sunglasses?
Who are you, Van Johnson?
Ah, I've got
a black eye.
Hello.
Oh, uh, Elaine,
this is my Aunt Stella.
[IMITATING BRANDO]
Stella!
Her back hurts.
Um, we saw you on
The Tonight Show last week.
I thought Johnny
was very rude to you.
He didn't even let you talk.
No, no.
You need some new material.
I've heard you do
that dog routine
three times already.
Stella!
You should get
your cousin Jeffrey
to write some material for you.
What are you talking--
Jeffrey works for
the Parks Department.
Read the letters
he's written.
He's funnier
than the whole bunch of you.
UNCLE LEO:
Oh, here's Jack.
We should sit down.
This better be good.
I'm missing
Golden Girls for this.
[FAKE LAUGH]
I hate her like poison.
MAN:
Hey, Jack, let's get started.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you know,
every year,
Phase Two
of the Pines of Mark Gables
honors the previous year's
president.
and this year,
we are honoring Morty Seinfeld.
CROWD: Morty!
A man who slept
more hours on the job
than Ronald Reagan.
Slept on the job?
Being president of the condo
is not easy.
It requires hard work,
dedication, and commitment,
and, unfortunately,
he possesses
none of these qualities.
He's joking.
His administration
did excel in one department,
the hiring of incompetents.
That's what you say.
But we do owe him
a debt of gratitude,
because by not fixing
the crack in the sidewalk,
it put Mrs. Ziven
out of commission
for a few weeks.
Tell them about
when you took my son's pen back.
Tell them about that.
Dad!
He gave my son a pen
and then he takes it back.
Tell them about that!
I took it back?
He gave it to me!
Come on, that's enough.
Sit down.
I'm not finished.
Give me that microphone.
Give it to me!
Morty, give me that back!
Where's the pen?
Ow!
You broke my dental plate.
Doris, he broke
my dental plate!
You son-of-a-bitch.
I'm gonna sue you.
Jerry, do your act.
I can't.
Nobody's even listening.
They're all going to leave.
Oh, God.
How you folks
doing tonight?
MAN: Who are you?
Hey, have you ever noticed
how they give you always
give you the peanuts
on the planes?
WOMAN: Not my Harry.
He flies first class.
Who would've thought
that the number one thing
everybody wants on a plane
is a peanut.
MAN: I'd rather have
a bottle of scotch!
Do the dog routine.
All I said was
I liked the pen!
Stella!
DOCTOR:
You could aggravate it.
I wouldn't go anywhere
for at least five days.
Five days?
You want me to stay here
for five more days?
There must be some mistake.
I'm afraid not.
Five days. Here.
So we have you
for five more days.
Well, there's really
no point in me staying.
I mean,
you're just gonna be--
Excuse me?
Nothing.
[KNOCKING]
Good morning.
Hi, Evelyn.
Has Morty decided
on a lawyer yet?
I don't think so.
Because my nephew Larry
could do it.
He's a brilliant lawyer.
He says Jack has no case.
Well, I'll ask him
when he gets up.
Oh, and I spoke
to Arnold,
and he says that
according to the bylaws
of the condo constitution,
they need six votes
to throw you out
for unruly behavior.
Not five.
Dr. Chernov is the one
you'll have to suck up to.
DAD: Oh.
Oh.
Oh, my back.
Oh, my back!
It's that bar.
Who could hell could sleep
on that thing?
I was very comfortable.
Morty, Arnold says
they need six votes
to throw you out.
It's in the constitution.
Who are you?
I'm a chiropractor.
What, are you
kidding me?
Five more days?
Well, today's almost over,
and weekdays always go by fast,
and Friday, we're leaving.
so it's like two days really.
It's like
a cup of coffee.
It'll go by like that.
Is Florida
not hot and muggy enough
for these people?
They love heat.
If they try to land men
on the sun,
I think these old retired guys
will be the only ones
that will be able to handle it.
They'll just sit there
on the redwood benches,
washcloth on their head,
going,
"Trying to get a sweat going."
[♪]