Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome to the show.
Ah, the extra buttons.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Yeah.
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
What kind of a sicko
really would save these,
have them in a huge file?
Drawers that wide.
You know, you just...
"Where the hell
is that button...?"
I mean, is it that hard to get
black round buttons...
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
that they have to make it
into a whole thing?
Like this is such
a great jacket.
The buttons are so unique,
so one-of-a-kind.
You'll never find them.
We'll save you the trouble
of knocking your brains out.
Because we know
they're gonna fall off too.
That's the other point that
they're trying to make here.
WOMAN:
Everyone in my family
is creative,
and even though I'm working
as an accountant right now,
I'd really like to eventually
work exclusively
on my papier-mâché hats.
I--I don't understand,
paper-mâché hats?
Hmm.
What--?
What if it rains?
They're art.
You hang them on the wall.
Ha-ho! Art. Yeah.
It's my creative outlet,
one of my passions.
Any money in it?
"Whoso belongs only to his age
reverences only its popinjays
and mumbo jumbos."
Of course. Right.
Thomas Carlyle, 1864.
Tommy C.
JERRY:
These are the receipts from '85.
and I'm gonna do '86.
I'm sorry. I thought
it was a legitimate charity.
I didn't know
you'd get audited.
I don't blame you.
I blame myself.
No, blame me.
Okay, I blame you.
No, no, don't blame me.
What was I supposed to do?
You knew I was on
my first date with Elaine.
You come barging in here,
asking me to contribute money
to a volcano relief fund
for Krakatoa.
It was supposed to erupt!
I find the whole thing
very embarrassing.
Well, you know
what my feelings are about this.
I don't even pay taxes.
Yeah.
That's easy
when you have no income.
Hi.
Hey.
Kramer...
[CLEARS THROAT]
do me a favor,
will you?
If you insist on making pasta
in my apartment,
please don't put
the tomato sauce on the pasta
while it's in the strainer.
All the little squares have
hardened red sauce in them.
What's so funny?
Oh, I don't know.
Kramer dating your roommate.
It's funny.
Ha. It's a riot, Alice.
Well, when do you put
the sauce on?
Any other time.
No, no, no.
I like to strain the sauce.
ELAINE:
And...
I could really live
without the tribal music
and the make-out sessions
in the living room.
Yeah, Tina likes the couch.
What are you doing?
What is all this?
Oh, he's, uh helping me
sort my receipts.
I'm being audited.
[GASPS]
You're being audited? What for?
Oh, I contributed
money to a charity
that turned out
to be fraudulent.
It's really very boring.
When was this?
A long, long time ago...
in a galaxy far, far away.
I remember you, uh,
donated to some
volcano thing
on our first date.
Volcano? Really?
Oh, wait a minute.
Don't tell me
that that was--
Something to drink?
What, did you think
That would impress me?
You've got me
all wrong.
I was thinking only
of the poor Krakatoan.
Like you'd make this donation
for 50 bucks,
and I'd start
tearing my clothes off?
Those brave Krakatoans!
[LAUGHS]
East of Java...
who sacrificed so much
for so long.
And now you're being
audited because of it.
See, that's karma.
No, that's Krama.
So, what are
you gonna do?
It's all
taken care of.
How is that?
[CHUCKLES]
JERRY:
An old friend of mine,
whom you may have met,
George Costanza,
has recently become intimate
with a female accountant
who was formerly...
a highly placed official
with a little outfit...
known as the IRS.
And as we speak,
at this very moment,
he is handing
over to her
all of my pertinent
tax information,
and she has assured us
that the matter is well within
her field of expertise.
Mm-hmm.
Why is she doing this?
I don't know.
It must be love.
I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
You're great, but...
I'm --I'm riddled
with personal problems.
What's wrong?
What did I do?
But-- Nothing.
It's not you.
It's me. I...
I have a fear
of commitment.
I don't know how to love.
You hate my earrings,
don't you?
No, no.
And you didn't comment
on the chopsticks.
I love the chopsticks.
I--
I personally prefer a fork,
but they look very nice.
You're not telling me
the truth.
I must've done
something.
I have a fear of intimacy.
Don't give me clichés.
I have a right to know.
What did I do wrong?
Nothing. It's not you.
I want the truth!
The truth!
You want the truth?
It is your earrings!
It is your chopsticks!
But it's so much more!
You're pretentious!
You call everyone
by their full name.
You called my doorman,
Sammy, "Samuel,"
but you didn't even say
"Samuel."
You went "Sam-u-el."
Papier-mâché?
What is papier-mâché?
Keep going.
I-- I think I made
my point.
I'm-- I'm sorry
if I was a little harsh.
No.
I asked for the truth.
Thank you
for being so honest.
Can I, uh...?
Can I walk you
back to work?
I really prefer
to go alone.
How much do I owe?
[SCOFFS]
Oh, please.
Four dollars is fine.
If this audit
had happened to me,
and I didn't have
this woman to help me,
I would've
killed this man.
I would've strangled
the life out of him
with my bare hands.
I don't blame you.
Have you ever been
through an audit?
No.
It's hell!
It's the financial equivalent
of a complete
rectal examination.
I would've
killed this man.
Torn him limb from limb.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Ripped the flesh
right off his bones.
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
Ah, there he is,
the man himself,
George Louis Costanza.
Here I am, about to go
to the electric chair,
and my oldest friend
is dating the governor.
My whole life has been
a complete waste of time.
And there's
so much more to go.
Okay. Now I know
what I'm supposed to do.
It is so simple.
Tell the truth.
That's all.
Just tell the truth.
So, what happened?
You give her my tax papers?
What?
My papers?
Oh...
What?
Oh, the papers.
JERRY: What happened?
You didn't give her the papers?
GEORGE: No, I did.
So?
I broke up with her.
You what?
I'm being audited,
and you broke up
with her?
It's okay.
It's fine.
She'll do it. I'm sure
she'll still do it.
Why? Why would
she still do it?
She hates you now.
People don't do you favors
after you dump them.
No, no. We--
We left on good terms.
How is that possible?
Because I, uh...
I told her the truth.
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
It's unheard of!
She asked me to.
So you lie!
What did you tell her?
I told her that she was...
pretentious.
Pretentious?
The woman has my tax papers.
You told her
she's pretentious?
The IRS...
they're like the mafia!
They can take
anything they want!
How would you it
if someone told you the truth?
Like what?
What could they say?
There are plenty of things
to say.
Like what? I'm bald?
What is it specifically?
Is--? Is there an odor
I'm not aware of?
George, please.
What? Give me one.
You sure?
Yes.
Okay.
You're extremely...
careful with money.
I'm what?
Oh, forget it.
I'm cheap?
You think I'm cheap?
ELAINE: See?
How could you say that to me?
I can't believe this!
You asked me to!
You should've lied!
Ah! So should you!
Okay, wait a second,
wait a second.
What happened
to my papers?
I mean, I'm not really
working right now.
I know!
When I was working,
I spent, baby!
Yeah, I know.
Champagne, limos, cigars.
What happened to the papers?
She put them in her pocketbook.
I guess she took them with her.
Her pocketbook or her handbag?
Is that relevant?
She took them.
Call her office.
Give me the phone.
Yeah, hi. I'd like
to speak to Patrice.
What?
Oh, really.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
Huh.
What? What?
She never came
back from lunch.
This is no good.
Call her house.
[MUTTERS]
Yeah, yeah, call her house.
Hi. Are you okay?
N-No. No, no. N--
[LAUGHS]
She hung up.
Not good.
All right, look, there's
nothing to be worried about.
She's just a little
annoyed right now.
Tomorrow I'll personally
go over there.
I'll apologize.
I'll get the papers.
Don't worry.
Not good.
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
Yeah, it's a windshield.
I can see that.
What's it for?
I found it on the road.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
I just finished working out.
Are you busy?
No. Come on up.
Can you believe
somebody threw this out?
You know, I'm gonna make
a coffee table out of this
and surprise Tina.
Well, wouldn't it be invisible?
I mean, what,
are you gonna
just sense
it's in front of the couch?
I don't know.
Hello.
What's with you two?
You haven't told him?
Told me what?
[SCOFFS]
Go ahead.
Tell him.
I--
I saw her naked.
He saw me naked.
Kramer...
saw me naked.
Well, you know,
it was an accident.
Who walks into a woman's bedroom
without knocking? I wanna know.
I thought it was a closet.
Completely naked?
Completely naked.
Jerry!
How can I go on?
All right,
I'll tell you what.
If it's gonna make you
feel any better,
you can see me naked.
No, thank you.
No, I want you to see me naked.
No, no, no.
No, I want to show you.
No, Jerry! Jerry!
Hold it just a second.
Let's not lose our heads here.
Now, Kramer, you know you're
always welcome in my home,
but as far as
Mr. Johnson is concerned...
that's another story.
[GROANS]
ELAINE:
What is this?
Well, it's a windshield.
It's gonna be
your new coffee table.
Oh...
I'm gonna kill myself
on that thing!
You can't even see it!
You'll sense it.
Well?
What happened?
Was she there?
No. No, she wasn't.
You didn't get my papers?
No, I didn't.
Well, where is she?
A mental institution.
Why is it so difficult,
uncomfortable to be naked?
It's because
when you have clothes on,
you can always kind of make
those little adjustments
which people love to do.
You feel like you're
getting it together.
"Yeah. Yeah, I look pretty good.
Feeling good, looking good,
you know."
but when you're naked,
it's like...
It's so final.
"You're just, well...
"That's it.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
There's nothing else I can do."
That's why I like to wear
a belt when I'm naked.
Because I feel
it gives me something, some--
You know, I'm naked,
but, you know.
I'd like to get pockets
to hang off of the belt.
That would be-- Wouldn't that
be the ultimate thing?
To be naked
and still be able to do this.
I think that would
really help a lot.
JERRY:
A mental institution?
You know
what they do in there?
Did you see
Cuckoo's Nest?
They put those electrodes
in your head.
It's not really
a mental institution.
It's more like
a depression clinic.
She went out to Woodhaven
and checked herself in.
I'm-- I'm sick over this.
Who told you this?
Her roommate.
I've driven women
to lesbianism before,
but never to
a mental institution.
You know, my friend Bob Sacamano
had shock treatments,
but his synapses
were so large...
[CLICKS]
had no effect.
You know, I hate to raise
a crass financial concern,
but was there
any information
as to the whereabouts
of my papers?
Well, she put them
in her pocketbook.
She probably took them
out there with her.
KRAMER: Boy.
So, what now?
I don't know.
Can we go out there?
Where?
Woodhaven.
We could.
GEORGE:
I'm very nervous
about this.
I've never spoken
to a mental patient before.
My cousin Douglas was in
a place like this one time.
Came over to my house
for dinner...
there was no soda...
and he went berserk.
He was screaming, "Where's
the Pepsi? Where's the Pepsi?"
I should be
in a place like this.
I envy this woman.
You get to wear
slippers all day.
Friends visit,
they pity you.
Pity's very underrated.
I like it.
It's good.
Plus they give you those
word association tests.
I love those.
Oh, they're great.
There's no wrong answer.
Potato.
Tuberculosis.
Blanket.
Leroy.
Grass.
Tuberculosis.
Oh, boy.
Here she comes.
[TRIBAL DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING]
Oh, my God.
WOMAN:
Oh, Krame...
Rrrar.
Kramer!
Kramer, could you please
put something on?
Oh... Oh.
Heh, oh.
Oh, boy.
Listen, you want
some leftovers? Uh...
I made some African food.
There's yambalas and sambusa.
WOMAN:
Sweetie...
Are you coming back to bed?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll be right there, babe.
Oh.
Hi, Elaine.
What did you think
of the coffee table?
[KRAMER CHUCKLES]
It's invisible.
So is everything cool
or what?
Yeah, um, you seem
a little bit dysfunctional.
Well...
Come on, Elaine.
Just tell us the truth.
The truth?
You want the truth?
Who are you?
Oh, um...
[GENTLY]
This is my friend...
Jerry.
Why are you talking like that?
[ANGRILY]
What do you want?
Want? What--?
What could I possibly want?
I, uh, just came
because I--
I heard so many nice things
about you from George.
George thinks I'm pretentious.
[SCOFFS]
Pretentious.
Wh-who isn't pretentious?
I mean...
If everyone
that was pretentious
was in
a mental institution...
O-o-obviously, this isn't
a mental institution.
You're just trying
to take it all back
because you're feeling guilty
I'm in here.
No,
that's not it at all.
Don't lie, George!
I'm not a liar!
Uh, we're cool.
Everything's cool.
No problem.
We're good.
Just chatting.
Very friendly.
Alrighty.
No reason for us
to raise our voices.
I know what you said.
You can't change that.
What I said.
I say stupid things
all the time.
I can't go two minutes
without saying
something stupid.
It's one stupid thing
after another.
So let me ask you,
when you come to
one of these places,
what do you bring,
your pocketbook?
You should be the one
criticizing me.
I-I'm lucky to even know
someone like you.
Do you mean that?
Of course
I mean that.
I'm incapable of guile.
He's never guiled.
JERRY:
You know, some women
keep a lot of important
papers in their, uh...
pocketbooks,
like, for example, oh...
someone else's personal
financial papers.
Papers?
Oh, Jerry,
You're the Jerome
with the tax problem.
You know...
after that date
with George,
I got so cuckoo,
I threw out
all your papers.
So I'd love
to help you,
but I'll just need
the copies.
There are no copies.
So...
are you saying you want
to continue seeing me?
Who makes copies?
The truth is...
I think...
Yeah.
You make a very
nice couple.
KRAMER:
Yeah-hah.
Oh...
Oh, Kramer.
[TRIBAL DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING]
Here, Kramer?
No, no.
Let's go to the couch.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
JERRY:
Yes, I'm trying to get a copy
of a receipt for a computer
that I bought there.
It was 1987.
I remember I talked to a guy
had like a maroon sport jacket,
and he might've had a toupee.
Oh, it was a weave.
Okay, uh...
Well, then, I'll come by.
Okay, bye.
Anybody want to take
a walk down to 48th street?
I think I may have
tracked down another receipt.
I can't. I gotta go visit Tina
in the hospital.
George?
I'm going to a poetry reading
with Patrice.
First-time poets.
It's in a burnt-out building
down by the docks.
It's supposed to be good.
Hey.
Are you going
to the hospital now?
Yeah,
I suppose I am.
All right, great, great.
Uh, we'll share a cab.
Oh, you're going by 48th street.
You can give me a ride.
I'm getting in on that.
Yeah.
You know
you're chipping in.
You're going
that way anyway!
Aw, come on!
I was audited last year.
I have been through an audit.
At first I thought, "Well, IRS,
kind of sounds like Toys 'R' Us.
"Maybe it won't be so bad.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Maybe they have a sense of fun
about it, you know?"
But it's-- It's bad.
It's an ordeal...
and they don't do anything
to keep your spirits up
through the ordeal.
I think they should take
all your receipts
and put them in one of those
big Lucite sweepstake drums
and just kind of
crank it around there.
You know, give you a feeling
like you might win something.
You know what I mean?
Then they can pull them out
one by one and go,
"Oh, I'm sorry. That's another
illegal deduction,
"but we do have some lovely
parting gifts for you...
Jail."
[♪]