You give me an explanation as
to why the pharmacist has to be
two and a half feet up
above everybody else.
What the hell is he doing,
he can't be down there
on the floor with you and me?
Brain surgeons, airline pilots,
nuclear physicists,
we're all on the same level.
Oh, no, he's gotta be
two and a half feet up.
"Look out, everybody,
I'm working with pills.
Spread out, give me some room."
The only hard part of
his whole job that I could see,
is typing everything
onto that little, tiny label.
And has to try and get
all the words on there,
keep the paper and
the little piece of paper
in the roller of the typewriter.
Oh, no. He's gotta be
two and a half feet up.
"Yeah, I'd like to get this,
uh, prescription filled."
"All right. You wait down there.
Only I'm allowed up here."
Where'd you
meet her?
I met her on an elevator.
On an elevator?
You met a woman
on an elevator?
Impossible, right?
You got less than
60 seconds.
That's like dismantling
a time bomb.
What got into you?
I don't know.
She was so beautiful,
it was like
a pure reflex.
The words just
came out of my mouth.
Wow. What did
you say?
[COUGHS]
You know, I'm the one
responsible
for those crop circles
in England.
Wow.
Can you believe
I did that?
What did she say?
What crop circles?
[SIGHS]
Not a good sign.
Not everybody knows
what the crop circles are.
You know what
the crop circles are?
Crop circles?
Why don't you buy something?
You got something
in your teeth there.
What?
It's green.
Oh, man, spinach.
I've been walking around
like this all afternoon.
Did you bump into
anybody you knew?
I had a job interview.
How did it go?
Take a guess.
Well, Mr. Costanza,
we have nothing available
at the present time
but should anything open up,
we'll be in touch.
Okay, thanks.
Ah, you don't need a job.
You got Audrey.
Yeah. Right.
What's the matter?
No. Nothing.
What?
You won't think
I'm a bad person?
Too late for that.
Because, believe me,
I would only say this
to you and maybe
a psychiatrist. Maybe.
What is it?
Well...
Her nose is
a little big.
Yeah, she's got
a big nose.
I mean, big would
even be okay.
It's a little
beyond big.
JERRY:
Mmm.
It's a schnoz.
Now I'm aware that my own
physical dimensions
are perhaps a little short
of perfection.
A little.
So who am I
to be thinking
about someone's nose?
I mean, I-I-I should be
grateful
someone like her
even looks at me.
I have no job,
nothing.
But I have to say,
I think about the nose.
I don't wanna
think about the nose,
I don't ask
to think about the nose,
but I think about it.
I go to bed,
I tell myself,
"Don't think about the nose.
Forget the nose."
But I think about it.
I look at her,
I see...
the nose.
Stop being so concerned
with looks.
Have you said anything
to her about it?
No. I could never
do that.
You know, the ironic thing is,
if she had a smaller nose,
I never could've gone out with
her in the first place.
She'd be out of my league
with a smaller nose.
And I really like her.
I know that.
And I know
one other thing:
[LAUGHS]
I'm not getting past
that nose.
All right, shut up.
Here they come.
[GROANS]
How can I
not think about it?
Look at the size
of this thing.
KRAMER:
So my mother's going out
with this guy
who leaves a jacket
in her house.
So, you know,
she gives to me.
Well, two years later,
he shows up
and he takes it back.
And now he's in prison!
Got arrested for mail fraud.
So, Elaine,
all you have to do is
go over
to the apartment,
tell the landlord
that you're his daughter
and you wanna bring him
the jacket in prison.
Won't the landlord know
I'm not the daughter?
No, no. he's never met her.
She's in California.
Are you coming with me?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I have to.
I'm your fiancé.
Peter Von Nostrand.
Why don't you just
commit yourself already?
Wh-what is so special
about this jacket?
No, you really don't wanna know.
God.
He believes
it possesses some
extraordinary power
over women.
What's that splotch
on your hand?
Oh, I got stamped at
the reggae lounge last night.
Yeah, I'm going
back there tonight.
You know, I'm not gonna pay
another cover charge.
What? You didn't wash
all day?
Yeah, I washed.
Just not the hand.
You wouldn't believe
the women at this club.
Ooh, man.
It's amazing how many
beautiful women
live in New York.
I actually find it
kind of intimidating.
Well, you're as pretty
as any of them.
Just need a nose job.
KRAMER:
What?
Kramer!
What? What?
How could you say
something like that?
What? What do you mean?
What?
I just said
she needs a nose job.
No, no. There's nothing wrong
with her nose.
God, I'm so sorry,
Audrey.
Oh, it's okay.
What did you have
to say that for?
Well, I was just trying
to help out.
Yeah, well, you can kiss that
jacket goodbye, Mr. Von Nausen.
You see what happens
when you try to be nice?
But what would the world be like
if people said whatever
they were thinking...
all the time,
whenever it came to them?
How long would a blind date
last?
About 13 seconds, I think.
"Oh, sorry, your rear end
is too big."
"That's okay,
your breath stinks anyway "
"See you later.
No problem. Goodbye."
"Okay, thank you very much."
AUDREY:
Elaine said I can stay with her
another month
AUDREY:
Elaine said I can stay with her
another month
till Tina gets back.
What are you thinking about?
Thinking? Nothing.
[LAUGHS]
What could I possibly
be thinking?
You look like you've got
something on your mind.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, yeah, right.
I wish I had
something on my mind.
So how about
that Kramer, huh?
Yeah, how about him?
Yeah. You know,
the way he just...
says stuff.
I mean...
He sure does.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's quite
a character.
So, what did you think?
About the pizza?
No. About the nose job.
Oh, the nose job.
Yeah. I...
Pffft.
I don't know. I...
Well, what did
you think?
Well, I've--
I've thought about it,
but I don't know.
Yeah.
[SNORTS]
You know, not that I care
one way or the other,
but these doctors today really
do amazing things, you know.
If you were so inclined.
And again,
I'm not suggesting, you konw.
I know. They're good.
Peter Jennings had one.
Really?
Probably. They all do.
In my high school, half
my graduating class had them.
Of course,
I'm from Long Island, so...
Uh-huh.
It's really nothing.
It's like going
to the dentist.
I hate the dentist.
It's a cleaning.
[CHUCKLES]
So you really think
I should do this.
Oh... If it
makes you happy.
I don't focus
on these things.
I will tell you this, though.
Unfortunately...
we live in a very
superficial society.
I don't condone it,
but, uh...
[LAUGHS]
it's a fact of life.
Well, maybe I should.
What the hell?
Aw, now you talked her
into a nose job?
Me? I didn't
say anything.
You encouraged her to get one.
I didn't encourage.
No encourage.
"Peter Jennings had one"?
It's possible.
Okay, well, I think you should
accept her for who she is.
No, George is right.
I wanna get one.
Well, I think
it's a mistake.
Me too. Really.
Unless you'd really
like to get one, then...
I'm going
straight to hell.
No two ways about it.
Well, it might not be hell,
but you're gonna run into
some bad dudes.
Hey, let's get the check.
She's taking the bandages off
at 4:00.
We have time.
It's exciting, isn't it?
She's gonna have a new face.
It is exciting.
Of course,
not as exciting
as Miss Crop Circles,
but...
Please, please. Isabel?
She is the most despicable woman
I have ever met in my life.
I have never been so repulsed
by someone mentally,
and so attracted to them
physically at the same time.
It's like my brain is facing
my penis in a chess game.
And I'm letting him win.
You're not letting him win.
He wins till you're 40.
Then what?
He still wins,
but it's not a blowout.
She wants to be
an actress.
She makes me read these
moronic acting scenes with her,
and I do it.
Because I'm so addicted
to the sex,
I'm helpless.
I'll do anything.
So, finally, Kramer comes in
the other day.
Kramer, I don't want to see
this woman anymore,
but I haven't got the willpower
to throw out her number.
Please help me.
Help me.
I'm proud of you.
[DEEP EXHALE]
So I'm never gonna
see her again.
I'm going
cold turkey.
Good for you.
I'll tell you, the sex.
I was like an animal.
I mean, it was just
completely uninhibited.
It's like going to the bathroom
in front of a lot of people,
and not caring.
It's not like that
at all.
How do you even know
the jacket is there?
Well, I don't.
I'm guessing.
Look, hey,
look, uh...
Audrey, before you take
the bandage off now,
just remember,
I was the one
that encouraged you
to do this, you know.
Now that you're gonna be
a great beauty,
let's not forget
how this all began.
You know, like, if you listened
to your friend Elaine--
George.
Yeah?
Enough.
[QUIETLY]
Right, enough, enough.
All right,
are we ready? Come on,
let's get this show
on the road.
You sure you want us
here for this?
Yes.
Shouldn't a doctor
do it?
No, he said
I could do it.
Okay, here goes.
This is very exciting.
Very exciting.
It's like watching a birth.
[GIGLES]
It looks good.
Great job.
You got butchered.
Head hurt, you know.
I'm good. I'm doing fine.
Let's put him
over here.
I'm okay. I'm all right.
Where are you
going?
To that doctor.
Wh--? Wait. Wait, wait, wait!
I'll go with you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
How you feeling?
Too much salt
in my diet.
Ohh.
Can I get you anything?
Nah. I'm good.
You sure? Anything.
[SIGHS]
Mmmmm...
No.
Boy, it really didn't come out
too well, did it?
ELAINE:
No, it didn't.
It's, like, all dented.
Seems to be.
Well, I'm sure
they'll be able to fix it.
You can't stop
modern science.
Can't stop it.
You can't stop it.
Can't stop science.
Can't be stopped.
No way, no how.
Science just marches--
Shut up, George.
Shut up?
Yeah.
Interesting.
Come on, Kramer. Seriously,
give me her number!
I don't have it. I threw it out.
You're lying. You've got it.
I want that number.
I told you I threw it out.
Give it to me.
You told me not to give it.
You made me promise.
I changed my mind. I want it.
You said no matter what,
I'm not to give it to you.
I was lying. Give it to me.
No, you told me not to!
I want the number!
All right! You want it? Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah.
Yeah, look at you.
Look at what
you've sunk to.
Look at what you've become.
Look in the mirror,
because you need help,
Jerry. You need help.
Because I can't stand by
and do it anymore.
It's turning my stomach.
I can't stand around here,
watching you destroy yourself!
It's eating me up
inside!
[DOOR SLAMS]
The doctor said
that they need to
build the lateral wall
of the septum. Over here.
Yeah.
You see this paranasal
sinus cavity?
Oh, I got it.
See how it's collapsed?
That's what's causing
this huge dent.
Yeah. Oof,
rough, rough.
[SIGHS]
So anyway, George,
you know what
I was thinking about?
[COUGHS]
What?
Remember we talked about
taking a trip together?
We did?
Yeah. We talked about
going to Hawaii.
Hawaii?
Anyway,
I think it would be
great to get away
after all this.
Well, you--
You know, Hawaii could be
a-a little tricky right now.
Uh, there's high-pressure winds
down there this time of year.
There's a lot of debris
constantly flying around,
a lot of...
wood and lava.
Could be dangerous.
I never heard that.
Oh, yeah.
My friend lived there, so...
We could go
to the Caribbean...
I have to tell
you something.
You couldn't get me
on a plane right now.
I get those FAA reports
directly.
My uncle sends them
to me.
He used to be
a pilot, so...
Big investigation
in the, uh...
What's the word there?
Uh...
Offing.
It's in the offing.
But, you know, you shouldn't
let that stop you from going.
You-- You could go.
I don't mind.
George?
Yeah.
I don't think
this is working.
[SOUTHERN ACCENT]
Ever since you came back
from the Army,
you've changed.
I swear, Nelson,
I don't even know
who you are anymore.
I'm Nelson.
That's not the line,
Jerry.
All right, all right,
I'm sorry.
[FLATLY]
Nothing's changed, Elma.
I just need more time.
I swear, Nelson,
sometimes at night
when you're not around,
I just go crazy
thinking about you.
Well, you just
need to relax.
Maybe a hobby.
Bowling is fun.
Yeah, bowling's good,
if you're really gross
and ugly.
JERRY:
Uh-oh. My organs
are playing chess again.
[BRITISH ACCENT]
Well, I'm getting
a little tired of this.
What do you say we play one
for all the marbles?
[NEW YORK ACCENT]
Oh, brain, what are you doing?
You cannot beat me.
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?
Forget about it.
I can't take her
anymore.
I hate reading her
little acting scenes.
Oh, so what?
So you read
from a little play.
You can't put up with that
for an hour to make me happy?
You're so selfish.
Give me one hour.
Then I will take over.
You won't have to think
for the rest of the night.
And what about
tomorrow morning?
Do you have any idea what
that's like for me? Do you care?
No, you don't care.
So long as you get to do
whatever it is you do.
You disgust me.
Oh, go read a book.
Enough chatter.
Let's play.
The only reason
I'm only doing this
is because you took Audrey
to the hospital.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, now, you're clear?
You got everything?
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Um...
Here.
What do I need this for?
Because
we're engaged.
We're engaged?
Mm-hmm.
Kramer, this is too big.
It's my mom's.
Hello!
Oh, uh, hi, um...
I'm Wanda Pepper.
I'm Albert Pepper's daughter.
My father asked me to come here
and pick up his jacket for him.
Oh, hello, Miss Pepper.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And you must be
Professor Von Nostrand.
Yes. Yes, I am.
I've read your book, professor,
and I was quite intrigued by it.
Uh, yes, well,
it's very intriguing.
Tell me,
is it your contention
that Shakespeare
was an imposter?
My contention?
Yes, your contention.
Oh, well, yes,
that's my contention.
I heard him
contend that.
Ah.
Mm.
It's too bad
about your father.
Ah. Well,
it was a frame-up.
A fine man.
He spoke often of you.
He's very proud of the work
you're doing.
Ah, well, we're all proud
of the work I'm doing.
Yes, she does
fine work.
Your father
gave me strict orders
not to turn the jacket
over to anyone
but I suppose I can make
an exception in your case.
The closet's this way.
Oh, good.
How kind of you.
You know, your father has
a very extensive wardrobe.
Yes.
JERRY'S BRAIN:
What's the matter, fella?
You look
a little tired.
[LAUGHS]
ISABEL:
Nelson, don't you see?
You are a part of me.
And I...
I am a part of you.
She's killing me.
That's your move?
Yeah.
Well, that's trouble,
my friend.
That's big trouble.
Checkmate.
[COUGHING]
Getting weak.
Losing power.
You haven't seen
the last of me.
I'll be back.
You're nothing without me.
Nothing.
Little punk.
Isabel, uh...
I don't think
this is working.
Daddy certainly does have
an extensive wardrobe.
He is
a fine dresser.
And I'm sure I don't
have to tell you
he's quite popular
with the ladies.
Oh.
My father? Really?
I had no idea.
Yes, they're crazy
about him.
This one
in particular,
came around
about two years ago.
Looked a lot like you,
professor.
Could have been
your mother.
Hmm, what was
her name again?
Uh...
Carter? Counter?
Kramer. That's it.
Babs Kramer.
Nasty woman.
Many a night I had to
throw her on the street,
drunken stumblebum.
You don't say.
I found it!
The woman used to walk
around here half-naked,
sucking Colt .45
from a can.
Her big, fat stomach
hanging out,
orthopedic hose
up to her knees,
screaming down
the hall,
"Come back to bed, Albert,
you big hairy ape!
And bring back
that box of Danish!"
So I grabbed the guy
by the collar.
Yeah,
and I yelled out,
"Kramer, Kramer,
you're killing him."
So I assume
the jig was up.
Yeah, pretty much.
KRAMER: Yeah.
But look...
Uh?
Ooh.
Yes.
Hi. Here are your keys.
ELAINE: Hi. Thank you.
Hello.
GEORGE [STUNNED]: Audrey.
My God, you look incredible.
I-I can't believe it.
Well, it was his doctor.
He was wonderful.
Mm-hmm.
So will I see you
later tonight?
Not sure.
Well, I'll, uh...
check you guys out
later, huh?
Ready?
I didn't wash.
Neither did I.
Yyyyoop! Ah.
We're off to
the reggae lounge.
Ah?
My nose, my nose.
My kingdom for a nose.
Boy, isn't she beautiful?
Mm.
Her nose is in such
perfect proportions
to the rest of her face.
Mm.
She's breathtaking.
Who would have thought?
She's, like--?
Elaine...
shut up.
Hm.
The technical term
for a nose job is...?
AUDIENCE: Rhinoplasty.
Rhinoplasty.
Rhino. Okay?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Do we really need
to insult the person
at this particular moment
of their lives?
They know they have a big nose.
That's why they're coming in.
Do they really need the abuse
of being compared
to a rhinoceros
on top of everything else?
When someone has a
hair transplant, they don't go,
"We're going to perform
"a cue ball-ectomy on you,
Mr. Johnson.
"We're going to attempt
to remove the...
"skinheadia of your, uh...
"Your chromedomus,
which is what the--
The technical term."
[♪]