So I was in the drugstore
the other day,
trying to get a cold medication.
Did you ever try
and pick one of these out?
It's a wall, it's an entire wall
of cold medications.
You're standing there,
you're going, "All right.
"All right, all right.
Okay, what the hell am I--?
"This is quick-acting,
but this is long-lasting.
When do I need to feel good?
Now or later?"
It's a tough question.
And then we show you
the commercials on TV,
where they show you what's wrong
with the guy, you know,
and they always show you, like,
all the problems that he has.
First of all, they always
show you the human body,
which is usually this guy:
No face, mouth open.
This is how drug companies
see the public.
And he's always
in, like, a certain pain.
It's like red, wavy lines
are going through him, you know,
or he's glowing,
parts of him are on fire
sometimes,
lightning is attacking him...
I never had a doctor say to me,
"Are you having pain?"
"Yes, I am."
"Are you having any lightning
with the pain?"
How did you get fleas?
Because my cousin's imbecile dog
was rolling around outside,
and they got in his carpet.
Maybe you could get yourself
a little bow tie flea collar.
That's real funny.
So are you coming to the party?
Um... I'd go,
but Long Island,
it's so far out.
It smacks
of desperation.
The whole party, everyone's
gonna be saying to me,
"You came all the way out
from Manhattan for this?"
You know,
Ava's gonna be there.
Who?
The nice one
that works in my office.
Eh...
I'll drive.
Oh, well,
now you're talking.
It's supposed
to be a good party.
Well, what does
that mean?
Good dip?
No. There'll be girls there.
There's girls everywhere.
I go out of
my apartment,
there's girls
in the elevator.
They're in cafeterias,
subways. So what?
There's a hundred
different things here.
What's the difference
between these two?
You got propylparaben?
Got it.
You got isobutane 30?
I've got isobutane 20.
A-ha.
You got sorbitan sesquioleate?
Got it.
I have aloe.
You got aloe? I love aloe.
Where do they make yours?
Jersey.
White Plains.
Pfft.
JERRY:
Girls...
There's girls
right here in the store.
Look, look,
there's one over there.
Look.
There's another one.
As soon as I walk outside,
there'll be girls out there.
What's the matter?
I gave her a 20.
She only gave me
change for a 10.
Are you sure?
Oh, boy, here we go.
Excuse me. Um,
I gave you a $20 bill,
and you only actually gave me
change for a 10.
You gave me a 10.
I'm positive I gave you a 20.
I know what you gave me.
You owe me $10.
Will you please step aside.
Next!
All right.
All right, let's... Let's just
examine the situation
for a second.
Who in this situation
would be more likely
to make a mistake?
Me, who had access to my wallet,
knew exactly what was in there,
or you?
You.
No, no, no.
See, you're not
really listening.
What's the problem
here?
No problem.
There's no problem.
She just owes me $10,
that's all.
Oh, he's claiming short.
All right, let's just
take it outside.
Oh, so you don't
believe me either?
Come on, let's go.
You haven't won.
You may think you've won,
but you haven't won.
Do you know why?
It's not over.
This is not over.
I'm not forgetting
what's happening here.
You have my $10.
I will get it back.
All right.
Don't worry.
It's not over.
I'm going now.
Goodbye. I will be back.
Ho-ho-ho!
[SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
ELAINE: Well,
don't stand here.
Let's walk in.
Blend in, blend in.
No, let's survey first,
camp here.
Ava.
What could possess anyone
to throw a party?
I mean,
to have a bunch of strangers
treat your house
like a hotel room?
So guess who just sold
129 West 81st?
Oh, no, you didn't.
GEORGE:
Get out! When?
Yesterday.
I don't believe it.
Ask Mark.
Mark, is this true?
Oh!
Yeah, this has got disaster
written all over it.
How did I ever let you
talk me into this?
I must have been
out of my mind.
Now, listen, let's keep
an eye on each other tonight.
In case one of us
gets in a bad conversation,
we should have a signal
that you're in trouble
so the other one
can get us out of it.
How old are you?
Thirty-six.
What's the signal?
How about this?
Chicken wing.
No, no, no,
I've got a better one.
Head-patting.
Whatever you want.
You came all the way out
from Manhattan for this?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
So, what do you do?
I'm a comedian.
Are you?
Let me ask you
something.
Where do you get
your material?
I hear a voice.
What kind of voice?
A man's voice,
but he speaks in German,
so I have to get it translated.
How come you keep tapping
your head?
Uh, it's a nervous tic.
I'm on L-dopa.
On the other hand,
you take a guy
like George Washington Carver.
The man devoted his whole life
to the peanut.
Imagine having so much passion
for something.
You know, people tell me
I'm a funny guy.
I've often wondered
if he ever worked
with the pecan.
Yeah, me too.
Now, is that considered a nut?
Because I know
the cashew is a legume.
How's it going?
Great.
How about you?
I can't believe
what's happening here.
She hasn't taken her hands
off me all night.
I mean, she was always friendly
around the office,
but that was it.
How do you account for this?
I don't know.
Maybe a safe fell on her head.
Well, she obviously
liked you all along.
No, I would have
picked up on it.
I can always tell
when a woman likes me.
They always somehow
let you know.
With me, they could torture me,
I wouldn't tell them.
If anything,
I try to make them think
I don't like them.
Then they think,
"Oh, look at this guy.
"He's not even looking at me.
He must have something
going for him," you know.
Anyway,
I'm ready to go.
Now?
Well, if not now, when?
Give me a half-hour.
Okay, half-hour.
Peanut brittle,
peanut butter,
peanut oil...
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Oh, excuse me.
What have you been doing?
I've been smacking myself
senseless.
People think
I'm a mental patient.
Hey, I was dying over there.
This guy's going off
on the peanut.
Now, pay attention.
Yeah, I think I've seen you
in a club.
You talk about
a lot of everyday things, right?
Right.
Yeah. I remember you.
I wonder what happened
to my fiancé.
I know he's here
somewhere.
Ellen,
have you seen
my fiancé?
He's upstairs.
Are you going
upstairs?
Tell my fiancé
I'm looking for him.
I have lost my fiancé,
the poor baby.
[AUSTRALIAN ACCENT]
Maybe the dingo ate your baby.
What?
The dingo ate your baby.
You ready?
Listen,
I have a tremendous favor
to ask.
I do favors.
I think something's
happening here.
What?
I think she wants me
to take her home.
Wow.
What should I do?
Go. What can you do?
What about you
and Elaine?
We'll get a ride.
Are you sure?
We'll be fine.
What did she say?
She told me she wants--
She told me she wants me
to make love to her.
What? She said that?
Yeah.
Get out of here.
I swear.
What did you say?
I--
Oh, I-- I can't.
Come on, what did you say?
Please, it's-- It's...
What?
"I..."
"I, uh..."
"I long for you."
"I long for you"?
I was so shocked.
I was lucky I said anything.
It's okay. That's not bad.
I don't like when a woman
says "Make love to me."
It's intimidating.
The last time
a woman said that to me,
I wound up apologizing to her.
Really?
That's a lot of pressure.
"Make love to me."
What am I? In a circus?
What if I can't deliver?
Oh, come on.
I can't perform
under pressure.
That's why I never play
anything for money.
I choke.
I could choke tonight.
And she works in my office.
Can you imagine?
If she goes around
telling everyone
what happened?
Oh, maybe I should cancel.
I have a very bad
feeling about this.
George,
you're thinking too much.
I know, I know.
I can't stop it.
Well, right now,
I'm reading manuscripts
for Pendant Publishing.
JERRY:
Pendant?
Those bastards.
Excuse me.
Listen, George is going home
with this Ava from his office.
Really?
Huh. What a world.
So we can go now.
No, he's taking the car.
Well, what are we going
to do for a ride?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Maybe Kramer
can come pick us up.
Oh, great. Oh, this is great.
How could you let him
take the car?
There's nothing I could do.
It's part of the code.
All plans between men
are tentative.
If one man should suddenly have
an opportunity
to pursue a woman,
it's like these two guys
never met each other
ever in life.
This is the male code.
And it doesn't matter
how important
the arrangements are.
I mean, most of the time,
they scrub
a space shuttle mission,
it's because one
of the astronauts met someone
on his way to the launch pad.
They hold that countdown.
He's leaning against the rocket,
talking to her,
"So listen,
when I get back,
what do you say we get together
for some Tang?"
ELAINE:
Oh, look at that.
Look at what she's wearing.
You see what she's wearing?
Yeah, yeah,
all right.
I can't believe
she's walking around in that.
Just don't make a scene.
Hey, is that real fur?
Oh, boy.
It'd better be, or my ex-husband
owes me an explanation.
Good night.
You don't care
that innocent, defenseless
animals are being tortured
so that you can look good?
Could we talk about this
some other time?
Are you a vegetarian?
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah.
I eat fish occasionally.
So you're a hypocrite.
Hey, I've eaten frogs,
so nobody's perfect.
Anyway, we...
Well, talk to me
when you stop eating fish.
Fish don't feel any pain.
How do you know?
Do you communicate with fish?
Well, they're not kept
in little cages.
Ever seen a goldfish?
Goldfish...
Yeah, I've seen goldfish.
They're not unhappy.
Swim around a bowl for two weeks
and get flushed down the toilet.
That's a good life.
Come on.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Maybe you can run
over a squirrel!
Yeah, well,
that's why we're here
in America.
You're beautiful.
Call Kramer.
All right.
Excuse me.
This is your party,
right?
No, I just live here.
Can I use your phone?
What's in it for me?
A bigger bill.
Hey, go for it.
Kram, Sein.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm stuck out here
on Long Island.
What are your thoughts
about taking a ride?
You're sure?
Okay, but don't leave me
hanging here.
Okay, great.
Let me give you directions.
You--? You sure
you don't need
any help?
No, not really.
I'm sure he'll be here
any minute.
I want them out of here.
Call him again.
I called.
What should I do?
We really
appreciate this.
It's 2:00 in the morning.
Oh, you've got
the Civil War book.
I saw some
of that show.
It was wonderful.
620 million people died.
Thousand.
Thousand, 620,000.
The horror,
the horror...
The wife keeps
giving us dirty looks.
Are you sure you gave him
the right directions?
Yes, yes.
You sure there's
nothing we can do?
No! I am not going to bed
with them in our house.
This is ridiculous.
You know, a friend
of my father's
used to live
right around here.
Mike Wichter.
He sold
plastic straws,
you know, the ones...
You could bend them.
Have you noticed?
People don't use straws
as much as they used to
for some reason.
You know, it doesn't look
as if your friend is coming.
Oh, he's coming.
Maybe you should take a look
at a train schedule.
[DOG BARKING]
[SCREAMS]
That's him.
I'm going to bed.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks.
Great party.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey, how you doing?
Look who's here.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's okay.
I had the directions
on the seat right next to me.
They... They flew
out the window.
Then how did you find
the place?
Well, I knew the exit
on the Long Island Expressway,
and I thought that the address
was 8713 Riviera Drive.
Ha, ha ha.
So I drove around
knocking on everybody's door
that had those numbers.
8317, 7813, 3718, 1837.
Whew... Finally,
I hit it, 8173.
Anyway, thanks a lot
for letting us stay here, Steve.
I really owe you one.
No problem.
And if you're ever
in the city,
you know, you want to come
to a comedy club,
whatever...
Hey, I might
take you up on that.
Here's my address
and number...
and really, thanks again.
Well, you'd better zip up.
I couldn't get the top
on the convertible up.
But it's cold out.
Yeah, wait till we get
on the Expressway.
George, I've been sick all week.
Elaine was too.
Eighty miles an hour,
40-degree temperature
for 50 minutes.
Do the math.
Maybe I will get out,
but let me just stop off
at the drugstore first.
Okay, meet me down there
in 15 minutes.
Then we'll go do something.
Yeah, Selwyn's. Okay, bye.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who is it?
Mr. Pocatillo.
Who?
You mean, you don't
recognize my voice?
Jerry, baby!
Do I know you?
Boy, this comedy's
really frying your brain.
I'm sorry...
See, this is the kind
of lasting impression
I make on people.
Oh, okay.
You said if I was
ever in the city.
I'm in the city!
You certainly are.
What's going on?
I'm just waiting
for a lift back to the Island.
He won't be ready until 11:00,
so I figured
I'd give you a break.
I thought I'd see
what it was like
to hang out
with someone in show business.
Listen, I'm really sorry,
but I'm just on my way out
to meet a friend.
Oh, come on, you can come up
with something better than that.
No, really,
I just got off the phone
with him.
I understand.
Look, you can hang out here
if you want.
Don't be so enthusiastic.
No, it's...
I'm not going to steal anything.
No, of course not.
Just close the door
when you leave.
I think I can do that.
Really, I'm sorry.
Maybe another time.
Yeah, let's have lunch.
JERRY:
The guy is in
my house right now.
What a mistake
that party was.
I never should
have gone.
Yeah, me either.
Oh, come on.
What, "come on"?
Have you ever dated a woman
that worked in your office?
I never had a job.
You know that anxiety
you feel on a date?
That's what I have
every day now.
My worst nightmare's come true.
Every day is a date.
That's one of Dante's
nine stages of hell,
isn't it?
Ava was one of the reasons
I used to like going to work.
She was a friend.
Now we sleep together,
and suddenly, I don't
know how to talk to her.
Every time I go to the bathroom,
I pass her desk.
I have to plan little patter.
I spend half my day writing.
Then afterwards,
I sit in my office
and analyze how it went.
If it was a good conversation,
I don't go to the bathroom
for the rest of the day.
I see her laughing
and talking with other people.
They're all so loose
and relaxed.
I think, "That used to be me."
I want to go back there again.
What are you gonna do?
I have no choice.
I'm quitting.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING,
CROWD CHEERING ON TV]
The party, Long Island.
Kramer, right?
Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm waiting for my ride.
Where's Jerry?
He split.
Let me ask you something.
Is there anything
to drink in here,
or is that, like,
a stupid question?
Uh... well, Jerry,
he doesn't have anything.
[SIGHS]
Well, but I might
have something.
Yeah, I...
I'm going to get this.
This looks good.
How much is that?
$9.60.
$9.60?
Give it to me.
Why?
Don't worry.
I've got it.
What do you mean,
you've got it?
I got it.
Since when are you
treating me to medicine?
What are you doing?
You're stealing this,
aren't you?
I'm not stealing it.
They owe me $10.
They stole it from me.
You're a lunatic.
I have to do this.
It's a matter of honor.
What do you say
to a person like you?
Just-- Just walk.
You don't even know me.
Excuse me.
What do you got there?
What?
What do you got in your shirt?
Oh... I was going to pay
for this.
Okay, come with me.
Where are you taking me?
I was going to pay for it.
Mm-hm.
You don't think
I remember you?
What are you talking about?
I know who you are.
I was watching you.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna call the police?
Come on.
Aah! Where--?
Can I still buy this,
or is this evidence now?
So I'm chasing
these doves
down the street,
and she's screaming
at the top of her lungs,
and then
when the magician
comes back
from Europe,
two of them
turn brown.
Well, I followed
the instructions!
They turned brown!
Brown!
[LAUGHING]
Oh! Oh!
So let me ask you something.
You know any women
we could call?
Not really.
Maybe we should call
one of those escort services.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah.
I saw one of them
advertised before
on that cable station.
555-LOVE.
[LAUGHS]
Are you in on this?
Oh, no, no.
I got a girl
in the next building.
Oh.
Yeah.
WOMAN: Now, I want
my money, mister,
and I ain't leaving
till I get it.
[LAUGHING]
Now, I am through
playing games with you.
I got things to do.
Whew...
Oh, Jerry, Jerry.
Look who's here.
It's Jerry.
What the hell?
Jerry, this is Patti.
Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, I'm sure.
What the hell
is going on here?
I don't know,
but I've got to
do this more often.
[LAUGHS]
[HORN HONKS]
Oh, there's my ride,
finally.
I'm not gonna go anywhere until
I get the rest of my money.
See you, Jer,
and tell Kramer
thanks.
I'll call him
tomorrow.
Oh, Kramer, huh?
Yeah, he's a hoot.
Oh... Goodbye, my dear.
Ouch.
Weekend of the 26th,
come on out.
We're having another party.
I ain't leaving.
Patti.
You got anything
to drink?
All right, how much
does he owe you?
$50.
$50...
This your apartment?
Yeah, but--
You're under arrest
for solicitation
of prostitution.
Oh, wait a second, I--
I have chicken soup.
Is that real fur?
BOTH: Oh, boy.
You had
Sergeant Chadway?
Me too.
He was a nice guy.
Oh, great guy.
Was there a redheaded guy there?
The one with the long sideburns?
Yeah.
Where does he come off?
I know, there's no call
for that kind of attitude.
One of the guys in my cell
threw a piece of gum at him.
Oh, we all hated him.
There's two types of favors,
the big favor
and the small favor.
You can measure
the size of the favor
by the pause
that a person takes
after they ask you
to "do me a favor."
Small favor, small pause.
"Can you do me a favor
and hand me that pencil?"
No pause at all.
Big favors are...
"Could you do me a favor?"
[♪]