The transplant, the hair plug,
is an interesting procedure.
It's really quite amazing.
Hair that was
on your shower soap yesterday,
can be in your head tomorrow.
How did they do
the first transplant?
Did they have the guy
take a shower,
get his soap,
rush it in there by helicopter,
you know, keep the soap alive
on the soap-support system.
And then eventually
move it over?
"We got the hairs, but...
I think we lost the Zest."
Sometimes the body
rejects the transplant...
with organs.
Is it possible
that a head could reject
a hair transplant?
The guy's just standing around
somewhere,
and "bink."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Lands in someone's
frozen yogurt.
MAN:
You see, the gaskets
that you have here
are asymmetrical.
Uh-huh. Really?
So I took off the motor relay
on the compressor
because, y-you...
Uh-huh.
you've got some discoloration.
Oh, whatever you have to do.
I was working with one mount
at a time, you know,
because you don't
wanna disturb
the position of the compressor.
No, you don't.
Hey. What are you
listening to?
Uh, my show
from last night.
Oh, you taped it?
Yeah, I was doing
some new material.
Hey, did you ever do that thing
on the toes that I said?
Huh?
You know how, like,
the big toe is like
the captain of the toes,
but sometimes the toe
next to the big toe gets so big
that there's, like,
a power struggle
and the second toe assumes
control of the foot.
The "coup d'é-toe."
Yeah.
Did you do it?
So?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
I need to use the phone.
Who you calling?
China.
China, really?
Yeah, I'll pay for it.
What for?
I'll tell you what for--
for hair.
Hair?
The Chinese have
done it, my friend.
The Chinese have done it.
Done what?
Discovered the cure
for baldness.
Did you see that last night?
[DOOR OPENS]
It was on CNN.
This Chinese doctor,
Zang Zhao, has discovered
the cure for baldness.
What's this?
Oh, I just got it.
Spector gave it to me.
He's giving everything away.
He's becoming a minimalist.
Is that the guy
who likes fat women?
Yeah.
Doesn't the fat fetish
conflict
with the minimalism?
You. You know what
you should've done?
You should've watched
that report on CNN last night.
I did. I'm trying
to call China.
Well, you can't call China now.
It's like, what,
3:00 in the morning there.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, God. Oh...
Man...
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, brother.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Th-this woman's talking to me
on my tape recorder
while I was on stage.
This is wild.
I never heard anything like this
in my life. Listen to this.
WOMAN ON TAPE:
I wanna slide my tongue
around you like a s...
Oh, my God.
All right,
let me hear.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Who is this woman?
I don't know. I have no idea.
I was just listening,
and she came on.
This is like
a Penthouse letter.
Why can't I meet
women like this?
All right,
come on.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait! Wait!
Where was
the tape recorder?
It was in the back of the room,
on the ledge.
She must've been sitting
right in front of it.
[LAUGHING]
My God.
All right, come on,
it's my turn.
All right, all right. All right.
[MOANING ON TAPE]
How you gonna
find out who this is?
Good question.
Where's the volume?
Ah ya ya!
GEORGE:
What do the Chinese
have to gain
by faking a cure
for baldness?
Look, if it was real,
they would never
let it out of the country.
Imagine no baldness.
It would be like
a nation of supermen.
Hi, boys.
Hello.
What's happening?
Tell her. I wanna hear
her reaction.
All right, this woman
left this really sexy message
on Jerry's tape recorder.
Not that, you idiot!
What?
The Chinese!
The Chinese bald cure!
Oh, I thought
you meant that--
No, I meant
the bald cure.
We were talking
about the bald cure!
Well, what did she say?
MAN:
Seinfeld?
Hey, is that Beder?
I can't believe it.
Get me a cup of decaf.
So did you hear
this message?
[CHUCKLES]
It was unbelievable.
Really?
I can't get over it.
Oh. Sexy?
[SNORTS]
This woman drove us
out of our minds.
Like, uh,
how did she sound?
She had this...
throaty, sexy
kind of whisper.
Really?
Like, uh--
Like, uh...
[SEXILY]
Jerry, I wanna slide
my tongue
around you like a snake.
Ohhhh, ohhhhhh...
Oh, my God.
You?
That was you?
Shhh.
How did you--?
I stopped in the club
to see him,
and I was standing in the back
while he was on, right?
And there was this tape
recorder there, and I...
got this impulse.
[LAUGHING]
What?
No, nothing, nothing.
Now, listen, promise me
you won't tell him, okay?
I wanna have
a little fun with this.
I had no idea
you were filled with such...
sexuality.
Oh, that was nothing.
So, listen,
what about this bald thing?
Oh, some bald thing,
a bald thing.
I don't know. It's nothing.
Remember Beder?
Beder?
Yeah, you remember Beder.
Remember I told you how we went
to the track that one time
and he was yelling
at this jockey?
And the jockey
got off the horse,
started chasing him.
So, listen, what about this girl
on your tape recorder?
[COCKILY]
Oh, Elaine...
What do you think
an enraptured female fan of mine
might say?
I don't know.
JERRY:
She went on
in some detail
about certain
activities,
illegal in some states,
for consenting adults,
things you would know
very little about.
Oh, really?
JERRY: Well,
this type of thing
is very common
when you're
in show business.
Uh-huh.
So, what,
are you gonna ask her out?
No, I can't. She didn't leave
her name or number.
Bummer.
Okay. Good luck finding her.
I'm taking off.
Wh-where're you going?
Home.
What--? What're you
going home for?
Well, I just came
from the gym.
Unless I could shower
at your place.
Sure.
GEORGE:
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
I don't get it.
Why would a woman do that
and then leave no way
to get in touch with her?
Maybe she realized
she could never have you
and she jumped off
the George Washington Bridge.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Yes. Operator.
Beijing?
Why're you doing this?
Why do I do anything?
For women.
Elaine, have you ever
gone out with a bald man?
No.
You know what that makes you?
A baldist.
Oh, this I need.
Hello, hello,
i-i-is this the, uh--
The hair-restoration clinic?
Yeah, yeah.
Does anyone speak English?
Ooh, you're taping.
Just be yourselves.
Oh. Okay.
Ooh. Well, we're talking
with Elaine Benes,
adult-film star...
on the... set
of her new picture,
Elaine Does
The Upper West Side.
Hi. How you doing?
Well, I'm doing fine.
Do you speak English?
English!
Oh, here's the director,
Jerry Seinfeld.
Jerry, you discovered
Elaine Benes.
Well, yes, I did,
that's true.
A couple of guys I knew
in the coast guard
told me about her...
And I sensed that she had
the anger and intensity
that I needed
to make this film work.
Ohh...
English!
Does anybody speak English?
Nobody speaks English.
So, what scene are you
getting ready to shoot now,
Elaine?
In this scene, my co-star,
who's right over here,
♪ Follow me ♪
Is George Costanza,
and he plays
an airline pilot
who's just returned
from Rome,
and I'm about to show him
how much I've missed him.
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
That's my Chinese food.
So, George, is this
your first movie with Elaine?
Uh, I-- I don't know.
So, Elaine, in your movies,
is the sex real,
or is it simulated?
Oh, it's always
simulated.
Except with George.
That's in my contract.
All right, all right.
Kramer, that's enough.
That's enough.
Hello?
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Yeah, hello?
English!
Does anyone speak English?
How much do I owe you?
$15.90.
KRAMER:
$15.90?
Uh, um, excuse me?
Uh, do you speak Chinese?
Chinese, yeah.
Oh, boy. Um...
I'm on with Beijing
at the hair-restoration clinic.
Um, could you
talk to them for me,
and tell them
I-I'd like to place an order?
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[LAUGHING]
They got a billion people
over there.
He found a relative.
If you send money,
they send cream.
They send me? All right,
a-ask them, does it really work?
They say you grow hair,
look like Stalin.
Oh.
Ask them, are there
any side effects?
Impotence.
[LAUGHING]
Oh, funny.
He's a funny guy.
Yeah. All right.
Get a money order
from the Bank of China.
Be here three days
after they get check.
All right,
thank you.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Kind of an expensive call.
ELAINE:
Thanks for driving me home.
What did I do
to deserve this?
GEORGE:
You... do plenty.
So, wh-what are you doing?
You-- You're going in.
Well, yeah. I guess so.
Why, you want to do something?
Yeah.
I-I don't know. What?
There's really nothing to do.
Yeah, no. There's--
There's nothing.
Can you think of anything?
No, no, not really.
I am up for anything.
Really?
[HONKS CAR HORN]
[LAUGHS]
Wow.
I have to say...
You were really good
doing that porno thing.
You-- You're talented.
Oh. I was just
kidding around.
I thought that thing you said
about the sex
not being simulated...
that was really funny.
Yeah, that was f-- Fun.
All right, so I'll speak to you
through Jerry and everything.
Okay.
Thanks a lot for the ride.
Yeah, anytime.
JERRY:
Thanks a million.
I really appreciate this.
Now, you're sure this was
the woman that was sitting
at the table
where I had my tape recorder?
Okay, great.
Thanks again. Bye.
Ah-ha!
Who do these women think
they're dealing with?
Did she think
she was gonna leave
this incredibly
erotic message on my tape
and I was just gonna
let it go?
[COCKNEY ACCENT]
Not bloody likely.
What is that?
That's my Cockney accent.
No, no, that's no good.
Let's hear yours.
[COCKNEY ACCENT]
Not bloody likely!
That's the worst Cockney accent
I ever heard in my life.
Hey, Georgie boy.
Guess what I got?
Oh, is that the bald stuff?
From China.
All the way from China.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me get the camera.
No, don't get the camera.
We don't need
the camera.
Listen, I know
you're skeptical,
but I really believe
in the Chinese.
Yes, I am skeptical.
Why do you have to be
so suspicious of everyone?
This is a great man, Zang Zhao.
He wants to help bald people.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now, let's videotape your head
for the before picture,
so we can watch
how it grows and stuff.
Here, sit down.
All right.
All right, lean back.
KRAMER:
A little bit to the right.
Now, make sure you get
this area here.
Right.
That's where
he needs the help.
All right, all right.
Well, he's
a happy camper, huh?
"Happy camper."
Yeah, I don't hear
that expression enough.
You remember that guy
who took my jacket,
the one I found
at my mother's house?
Yeah.
My mother told me
that he got arrested
for mail fraud.
No kidding?
Yeah, he's in jail.
Well, what happened
to the jacket?
Did he take it with him?
That's what I intend
to find out.
Well, you can see it.
You gonna walk around
like that?
And it stinks.
Can you smell that?
You stink.
How long are you
supposed to leave it on for?
All day.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hello.
It's Elaine Marie Benes.
Well, hello.
Hello. Did you ever find out
who that woman was?
Yes, I got her number.
Hey, is that Elaine?
Yeah.
Hi, Elaine!
So, uh...
( chuckles )
I guess you figure you're in
for a pretty wild night.
Well, as I said,
this type of thing
is very common in show business.
Uh-huh. Well, listen,
I'm at Arlene's.
You want me stop by?
Sure.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Did she say hello?
What?
Oh, I don't know.
What do you mean?
She heard me say hello.
Did she say hello back?
I don't know.
Who keeps track of hellos?
Isn't it polite to say hello
when somebody says hello?
She's coming up.
Elaine's coming up?
Yeah, why? What's wrong?
Where you going?
Nowhere, nowhere.
I'll be right out.
How often
do you cut your toenails?
I would say every two and a half
to eight weeks.
Because the other night,
you know,
I was sleeping with Marion,
and I rolled over
and I cut her ankle
with my big toe.
The big toe, the captain.
What?
The captain of the toes.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
ELAINE: Jerry?
Yeah.
Jerry, listen, um,
I got too much stuff to do.
I can't come over.
Forget it.
Oh, okay, too bad.
So when are you
going to call her?
Soon as I get off the phone
with you.
Ha. Good luck.
Okay. Bye.
What happened?
What, did you take it off?
Yeah. That was--
That was enough.
That's it? You gave up?
No, I'm working on a system.
Who was that?
That was Elaine.
She changed her mind.
She's not coming over.
WOMAN: Hello?
Hello, is this Alicia?
Yes.
This is Jerry Seinfeld.
[CRASH]
So?
I don't get this woman.
We're having
a great time,
couple of laughs,
everything's nice.
End of the night,
I go in for a little contact,
I get the pull-back.
This woman, she said
the filthiest things
I ever heard
in my life.
I get the pull-back.
[CHUCKLES]
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
What's he doing
here now?
So you blew it?
She must be
psychotic or something.
Let me have the number.
I'm not giving you
the number.
I know how to handle
these psychotics.
Sheriff.
What's with the hat?
Phew.
Boy, you stink.
Well, what are you
doing here now?
I have to talk to you
about something.
All right, let's take a look
here, see what we got.
Wait a second.
I think I see
something here, George.
Let's go to the videotape!
Oh, Kramer. No, no.
[SIGHS]
What's up?
I can't tell you now.
He's gonna be back
in 10 seconds.
So just start it.
I can't.
Oh, come on, he'll be
over there for a half hour.
He gets lost over there.
Come on, well,
what is this about?
All right...
I've become
attracted to Elaine.
All right.
Okay. Sit down, George.
Kramer, could we do this later?
No, I got the tape
right here.
Kramer,
let's do this later.
Okay, now...
This is the tape
that we made earlier,
and I think...
that I see a couple of buds...
right here.
Really? You think?
Kramer,
I would like to talk to George
for a minute, please.
About what?
It's kind of private.
Like the big toe captain,
what?
Oh, so you're doing my bit?
I'm not doing the bit!
All right.
Okay, all right.
I'm gonna take
a look at this, huh?
Does she know?
No.
How did it happen?
I can't say.
Well,
why can't you say?
Because I promised her.
I thought you just said
she doesn't know.
She doesn't.
So how can you
promise her?
Because she asked me to.
What is this,
an Abbott and Costello routine?
All right,
you really want to know?
It all started
when she told me that...
She was the voice
on your tape recorder.
What, Elaine?
Yeah.
She made me promise
not to tell you.
It was supposed
to be a joke.
That was Elaine?
Yeah, yeah. Let me hear.
Wait a second.
Just give me a second.
You heard it 50 times already.
No, I haven't.
This is my ex-girlfriend.
I think I have precedence.
Ohhh...
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
Hi, it's Elaine.
Is this a bad time?
Yeah.
Don't tell her
I told you anything!
She'll kill me!
Okay, I promise!
Wow.
Oh, man.
Oh, God.
Oh, brother.
Ohhh! Wow!
What's the matter?
Oh--
I... got a pain in my side...
From, you know...
Oh, hi, George.
How you doing?
Something stinks in here.
Oh.
What are you doing here?
I was the one who talked
into your tape recorder.
I know,
George told me.
You told him?
H-h-h-he threatened me.
Where did you come up
with all that stuff?
Oh, that was nothing.
Elaine...
I-- I have to
tell you something.
George, no.
No, no, no.
George, I'm telling you.
What is it?
I'm very attracted
to you.
Oyyyy...
I found a hair!
Yes!
Okay, come here,
come here.
Take a look
at this.
Ever since I found out
that you left the message
on Jerry's tape recorder,
I--
Whoa.
That was you?
It was a joke.
Wait...
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Elaine, I can't believe
that that is you.
I--
I think I'll get going.
Er, stick around
a while.
It's early.
We'll order
Chinese.
All right,
give me the tape!
I had it first! It was my tape!
Give me the tape!
[♪]
A woman left me a message on
my phone machine the other day
with kind of a breathy voice,
you know.
No matter what a woman says,
if it's in that breathy voice,
you know, it...
[BREATHY VOICE]
"You have cancer."
Really?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Sounds pretty good.
The stewardess could lean over
and whisper in my ear,
[BREATHY VOICE]
"Would you put on
your seat belt?
"We're about to go
into a mountain."
I would go, "Really?
So, what are you doing later
"by the ruptured remains
of the fuselage?
"How about some peanuts
over by the black box?
Look, I'll meet you there."