When I was a kid,
my favorite ride
was the bumper-car ride.
Remember that ride?
Going around in a circle.
There was always one kid
on the bumper cars
that could not do it.
Do you remember this kid?
As soon as the ride
gets started,
he'd be, like, stuck
in a pack of empty cars.
Just:
"Excuse me.
"Excuse me. It won't go!
"Come on!
It's almost over!"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
You know, he always ends up
with the attendant
hanging off that big pole,
helping him steer it. You know.
"Stop crying."
Dsh.
Then there's always
that other--
One other really bad car,
the helpless
father-and-son team.
This is another car
just not going anywhere.
They're never organized.
Who's on the wheel?
Who's pressing on the gas?
They're just:
"Ho, son, turn the wheel."
KRAMER:
All right, Coney Island?
Okay, you can take
the B or the F
and switch for the N
at Broadway and Lafayette.
Or you can go over
the bridge to DeKalb
and catch the Q
to Atlantic Avenue
then switch to the IRT,
2, 3, 4, or 5.
But don't get on the G.
See, that's very tempting,
but you wind up on Smith
and 9th Street,
then you gotta get
on the R.
Couldn't he just take the D
straight to Coney Island?
Well, yeah.
Okay.
What time's your
job interview, George?
9:45.
Remember, don't whistle
on the elevator.
Why not?
That's what Willy Loman
told Biff
before his interview
in Death of a Salesman.
What, you're comparing me
to Biff Loman?
That's very encouraging.
The biggest loser in the history
of American literature.
All right.
I gotta get going.
What time's
the lesbian wedding?
9:30.
Lesbian wedding.
How do they work
the bride and groom on that?
What, do they
flip a coin?
Yeah, they flip a coin.
What, was that not
politically correct?
It's a-- It's a
legitimate question.
[YAWNING]
I'm so tired.
I'm gonna fall asleep
on that train.
I always
get the feeling
when lesbians are
looking at me,
they're thinking,
"That's why I'm not
a heterosexual."
All right,
Jerry, come on.
Let's go. Pick up the check
so we can go.
Oh, I'm paying for breakfast?
Yeah.
Why do I always pay?
What am I,
made of money?
You bunch of
deadbeats.
GEORGE:
How many tickets
you paying today?
Uh, let's see.
Speeding,
running a red light,
no license,
no registration
no plates,
no brake lights,
no rear-view mirror.
Look at that one.
No doors?
Yeah, I'm fighting
that one.
You know, this is gonna cost me
over 600 bucks.
Oh, I can't carry change
in these pants. It falls out.
Here you go.
There you go.
Thank you.
That guy's not blind.
[ELAINE GROANS WITH DISGUST]
So can I convince
anybody
to come down to Coney
Island with me?
Gotta pick up my car
at the pound. George?
I can't believe it. They
actually found your stolen car?
Not only did they find it,
it was simonized,
and the front end was aligned.
[LAUGHS]
It's amazing.
JERRY: So, what do you say?
Ride on the Cyclone.
Hot dog at Nathan's on me.
Who are you, Satan?
I'm close to a job here.
It's my second interview.
All right, Biff.
Elaine?
Merry-go-round?
I can't.
I'm the best man.
Kramer. Bumper cars.
I gotta go to court.
I'll get in trouble.
What's the matter with you?
It could be years till
I get back to Coney Island.
I can't go on the
rides alone.
CONDUCTOR:
42nd Street. Change for the D
and the Double R,
the 2, 3, 4, 5, 7,
C, K, and F trains.
Well.
See you.
Hey!
Rahh!
Yeah!
[SNORES]
You looking for a job?
Me? Why?
Er, well, you're reading
the classifieds.
Oh, uh, no, no, no.
I, uh...
[CHUCKLES]
I was just looking
for the stock page there.
Ah, here it is.
Looking for the quotes.
Gotta check the quotes.
Love a good quote.
Oh, IBM up a quarter.
What do you know?
You didn't look like someone
who needed a job.
Me?
No, no.
I don't, I don't.
Doing very well.
Very well, yeah.
So you're in the market?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
in the market.
Which market?
The, uh...
The big one.
The, uh, big market
with the big board.
Bull market, bear market.
You name the market,
[CLICKS]
I'm there.
[LAUGHS]
So do you work for one of
the big brokerage houses?
They wish.
I hate the big brokerage houses.
Hate them with a passion.
Big brokerage houses
killed my father.
Really?
Well, they hurt him bad.
Really hurt his feelings.
It's a long story.
I-I don't like to
talk about it, but...
I swore there and then
that I would never work
for a big brokerage house.
You see, all they care
about is money.
I'm about more than money.
I'm about...
people.
So I've always gone
my own way and...
I've never looked back.
[HORN BLOWS]
[LAUGHS]
I started riding these trains
in the '40s.
Ah.
Those days, a man would
give up his seat for a woman.
Now we're liberated.
We have to stand.
[CHUCKLES]
It's ironic.
What's ironic?
This. That we've come
all this way,
we made all this progress,
but...
you know, we lost
the little things, the niceties.
No. I-I mean, what does
"ironic" mean?
Oh.
Where you off to with such
a nice present, huh?
Birthday party?
A wedding.
A wedding?
Yeah.
Ha! I didn't think people
still get married.
Oh, it's hard today
with the men and women.
Ha, you're telling me.
So, uh, they're
a nice couple?
Oh, very nice.
Hmm.
What does he do,
if you don't mind my asking?
She.
She?
Oh. She, she works,
he doesn't.
He sounds like my son.
There is no "he."
There's no "he"?
So, uh,
who's getting married?
Um...
Two women.
It's a...
A lesbian wedding.
Lesbian wedding?
Uh-huh. Yep.
Yep, I'm the, um...
[COUGHS]
the best man.
Oh.
Great.
My luck. I don't talk to a soul
on the subway for 35 years...
I get the best man
at a lesbian wedding.
Oh, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
I'm not a lesbian!
I hate men,
but I'm not a lesbian.
ELAINE:
I'm really looking forward
to this.
I love weddings.
Maybe I'll meet somebody.
Mmmmm...
Maybe not.
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
Oh, man. We're stopping?
[LAUGHING]
Well, uh, this is where
I get off.
Oh, uh., you do.
Uh...
Yeah.
Ummm...
Hey, why don't you,
uh...?
Oh, nothing.
No, no. What, what?
Well, I was going to say,
"Why don't you get off with me?"
But you're obviously
very busy,
on your way to some
important meeting or something.
Yeah. Well...
See, I-I knew
it was a bad idea.
Hey, what's another million,
give or take?
I get off when and where
I wanna get off.
I'm stuck. Could you just
pull a little--?
I'll just be a second.
Don't--
Don't start the train!
Here it is.
Here it is, the four horse
in the first race.
Pappernick.
How do you know
he's gonna win?
My UPS guy, Lance.
The guys who own the horse
are his regular customers.
Every horse he's ever given me
has won.
Yeah?
Yeah.
See, they've been
sandbagging,
looking for
a good spot.
He's been getting
in light
because they're using
a bug boy on him.
And the workouts
have been unpublished.
Now they're ready to run
with him..
They're gonna break
his maiden.
He's gonna go for a great price.
Maybe 30-to-1.
I'm telling you,
it's a lock.
But it rained
last night.
Exactly. This horse
loves the slop.
Ahhh.
It's in his bloodlines.
His father
was a mudder.
His mother
was a mudder?
What did I just say?
Come on.
Let's go to the office.
I'll call my bookie.
Hey, don't tell
anybody.
Oh, man.
Okay.
You realize, of course,
you're naked.
Naked, dressed,
I don't see
any difference.
You ought to sit here.
There's a difference.
You got something against
the naked body?
I got something against yours.
How about a couple
of deep knee bends,
maybe some squat thrusts?
Who's got time
for squat thrusts?
All right, how about
skipping breakfast?
I'm guessing you're not
a half-grapefruit
and black coffee man.
I like a good breakfast.
I understand, I like
a good breakfast
long as you don't wind up
trapped in a room,
in overalls and pigtails,
being counseled by Dick Gregory.
I'm not ashamed
of my body.
Exactly.
That's your problem.
You should be.
Don't get up.
Please, allow me.
ELAINE:
Oh, this is great.
This is what I need,
just what I need.
Okay, take it easy.
I'm sure it's nothing,
Probably rats on the track.
They're stopping for rats.
Oh, God, it's so crowded.
How could there be
so many people?
This guy really smells.
Doesn't anyone use deodorant
in the city?
What is so hard? You take
the cap off, you roll it on.
What's that? I feel something
rubbing against me.
These disgusting animals,
these people should be
in a cage.
We are in a cage.
What if I miss the wedding?
I got the ring.
What'll they do?
You can't get married
without a ring.
[HUFFING]
Oh, G...
I can't breathe.
I feel faint.
Okay, take it easy.
It'll start moving soon.
Think about people in
concentration camps,
what they went through.
And the hostages! What would
you do if you were a hostage?
Think about that.
This is nothing.
No, it's not nothing,
it's something.
It's a nightmare.
Help me!
Move it!
Come on!
Move this (bleep) thing!
Why isn't it moving?!
What could go wrong
with a train? It's on tracks.
There's no traffic.
How could a train get stuck?
Step on the gas!
What could it be?
You'd think the conductor
would explain it to us.
"I'm sorry, there's a delay.
We'll be moving
in five minutes."
I wanna hear a voice.
What's that on my leg?!
Nice.
Your, uh, company sends you
on the road often, huh?
Nice.
Oh, hey,
nice ice bucket there.
Make yourself comfortable.
GEORGE:
Make myself comfortable?
What does that mean?
Does she want me
to take my clothes off?
Is she taking her clothes off?
What if I take mine off
and she still has hers on?
Then I really look like
an idiot.
She could get offended
and leave.
S-so maybe I should
leave them on.
But then what if
she takes hers off?
Then she'll feel humiliated.
Make yourself comfortable?
I've got
this unbelievable woman.
And this "comfortable" thing
could ruin me.
I got it.
I'll take my shoes off
and sit on the bed.
There. That's comfortable.
She can't accuse me
of being uncomfortable.
[DOOR OPENS]
Gotta tell you,
I'm pretty comfortable.
KRAMER:
Oh yeah, it's all set.
They got the bug boy on him.
The bug boy?
Yeah,
the little fellow's
been riding his heart out.
They're gonna
break his maiden.
Really?
Yeah.
It's a little slow out there.
It rained last night.
Oh, this baby
loves the slop.
Loves it.
Eats it up.
Eats the slop.
Born to slop.
His father was a mudder.
His father was a mudder?
His mother was a mudder.
His mother was a mudder?
What did I just say?
Yi!
Hey. All right,
uh, 600, Pappernick
to win.
Yes, sir.
They still have no pitching.
Gooden's a question mark.
You don't recover from
those rotator cuffs so fast.
I'm not worried about
the Mets' pitching.
They got pitching.
They got no hitting.
No, hitting,
they got hitting.
Bonilla, Murray.
They got no defense.
Defense, please.
They need speed.
Speed? They've got Coleman.
They need a bullpen.
Franco's no good?
They got no team leaders.
They got Franco.
What they need
is a front office.
But you gotta like
their chances.
I love
Tell you what, if they win
the pennant this year,
I'll sit naked with you
at the World Series.
It's a deal.
ELAINE:
Oh, gee, why couldn't I
take a cab?
ELAINE:
Oh, gee, why couldn't I
take a cab?
For $6, my whole life
could've changed.
What is that on my leg?
I'll never get out of here.
What if I'm here
for the rest of my life?
Maybe I'll get out
in five seconds.
One banana,
two banana
three banana,
four banana
five banana.
No.
I'm still here.
Still here.
When will they start moving?
Move!
[ENGINE HUMS]
It's moving.
It's moving!
Yes!
Yes.
[BRAKES SCREECH]
Mother !
Um...
[CHUCKLES]
Gee, I-I hope you have the key
for these things.
Oh, don't worry. I do.
You know, m-my mother used
to walk around our apartment
in her bra and panties.
S-she didn't look
anything like you.
She was...
really disgusting,
really bad body.
You know,
if you can imagine
an uglier, fatter version
of Shirley Booth.
Remember Shirley Booth
in Hazel?
Really embarrassing
because, you know,
I had the only mother
in the whole neighborhood
who was worse looking
than Hazel.
You can imagine the taunts
I would hear.
Like what?
Like, uh...
"Hey, your mother's
uglier than Hazel."
"Hazel really puts your mother
to shame," you know.
What's, uh, going on?
It was a pleasure doing business
with you, George,
but I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to get going.
[LAUGHS]
Get going?
But, uh, we haven't really,
you know, uh...
Eight dollars?
What are you doing,
you're robbing me?
I wasted my whole morning
on you for $8?
Wait a-- Wait a second,
what're you doing?
I'm taking
your clothes.
No, no, no.
That's my only suit!
It cost me $350!
I got it at Moe Ginsburg!
Bye, George.
Wait, wait.
You can't just
leave me here.
Will I see you again?!
ANNOUNCER:
As they make the home stretch,
Ben Bajanut's Passionate Love's
the leader.
Victor's Hoy's Boy
followed by Jamet
Little Baggit, Kiss Harmony,
and then a long way
to Flagrant. Independent of
Come on!
what is happening.
Into the stretch
with 1/8 mile to go,
Stepagain and Pat Chanel
are battling it out.
They clear from Jamet,
Pappernick's starting
to make some ground,
but Stepagain is the leader.
With a 16th to go,
Come on.
Stepagain clear.
Come on!
Look at Pappernick,
Come on. Yes!
he's sprouting from his weight.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Stepagain jumps the leader.
Yes.
Pappernick flashing home
Stepagain and Pappernick,
Pappernick and Stepagain
Yes!
hit the line in a photo finish.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
By a nose,
the winner is Pappernick.
Yes!
I won. Hey!
[WHISTLES]
Yeah.
Ah?
Hey.
I haven't had a hot dog
at Nathan's in 20 years.
First, we ride
the Cyclone.
Chilly out.
[DEEP INHALE]
Ah,
French fries.
[VIOLIN PLAYS]
[GRUNTS]
Get up.
Hey, hey!
Ah!
Give me the money.
Ah.
Give me the money!
Freeze! Police!
JERRY:
No, I never got the car.
We were having
such a good time,
by the time I got to
the police garage,
it was closed.
That's too bad.
You wouldn't believe
what this guy put away
at Nathan's.
Look at what we won.
You want him?
Get that out of my face.
So you missed the wedding.
You'll catch the bris!
Hare Krishna,
Hare Krishna.
How'd you like
a Hare Krishna fist
down your throat,
you little punk?
George.
Biff.
What, did you whistle
on the elevator?
I have my spare key
in your apartment, right?
Yeah, it's in
the kitchen drawer.
Give me your key.
I gotta get it.
All right, what happened?
Never mind
what happened, just...
give me the key.
Come on,
I'll go with you.
Here. Pay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Give me that.
All right.
So I take the subway
down to Coney Island
to go on the Cyclone.
I'm riding on the subway.
I'm sitting on the D train
for an hour and 15 minutes
to go on a scary ride.
Okay, how dumb is that?
You know that first sharp drop
on the Cyclone?
Fell asleep.