I bought the Ginsu knife.
I did buy the Ginsu knife.
I know, you can't believe it,
but I did, I swear. I saw it.
It was late at night,
I'm watching the thing,
and it started
making sense to me.
I'm thinking,
"Yeah, cut through the shoe,
cut through the can.
Yeah. Yeah, I want that."
So I called up the number
on the screen, you know,
and I said, "I'd like to order
the Ginsu knife,"
and the lady went, "Really?"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I mean, even the Ginsu people
have given up.
It's really so sad, you know?
I guess, to be honest,
I mean, if you need a knife
that can cut through a shoe,
perhaps you're not buying
the highest grade of meat
currently available, you know?
Maybe you ought to think
about not getting the hoof cut
once in a while.
JERRY'S VOICE:
What is it about sleep
that makes you so thirsty?
Do dreams require liquid?
It's not like
I'm running a marathon.
I'm just lying there.
What the hell?
Why is the door open?
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Oh, hey.
Kramer, what're you
doing here?
Okay, Jerry,
now, calm down.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry. God.
I didn't wanna
wake you up.
You know,
I was watching
Thirty Seconds
Over Tokyo,
and I...
you know, I--
I wanted to get
some popcorn,
so I used the spare keys
that you gave me
to come into your apartment
to get your popper.
You scared me!
It's just me.
That's enough!
Yeah, okay.
Forgot the popper.
It's not broken.
[DOORKNOB JIGGLES]
JERRY:
Come on...
Ah.
Kramer!
What are you doing?
What does it look
like I'm doing? What?
Get out of my-- the bathroom!
I've gotta go!
All right, all right.
Whoa.
Come on!
All right.
My drain--
Move it, move it.
Yeah, well,
my drain's all clogged up.
JERRY:
Was that my towel?
Here.
I'm really happy
the movie was sold-out.
Hey, did you
ever pretend
there's, like,
murderers chasing you,
and you're trying
to see how fast
you can get
your keys out
and get into
your apartment?
I'm from Wichita, so...
Oh, oh.
There he is. Come on.
Hurry, Jerry, he's coming.
They're coming, the murderers.
Hurry, hurry. He's coming.
Hurry, hurry.
[GIGGLING]
Oh, Jerry...
[BOTH SIGH]
Oh, boy.
Whew.
That was close.
Did you see the look
on that guy's face?
You were... so fast
with those keys.
Well...
Oh, me.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Beautiful.
Kramer!
Whoa, hey.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Hey, Jerry.
How are you?
Yeah, I thought you were
going to the movies.
All right, that's it.
Hand them over.
What?
You know what.
The keys, I want the keys.
You've lost
your key privileges.
Oh, come on.
No "come on."
What? I thought
you went to the movies.
It was sold-out.
How was I supposed
to know it was sold-out?
That's the point.
What point?
Just-- Look,
just give me the keys.
Just give me
another chance.
Don't ask me.
I'm asking you.
I'm telling you.
Oh, you're joking.
I'm serious.
It's not gonna happen again.
Yes, it will.
Now, give me those keys.
No, no.
Let go.
You let go.
Come on, Jerry, now, stop it.
Stop it now.
Kramer!
Oh, great!
Okay, all right,
fine, you go ahead.
Take the keys, boy,
but you're gonna
regret this.
All right, yeah!
[DOOR SLAMS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Goochie.
So put them in a safe place.
ELAINE:
I will.
Where?
I don't know.
I'll hide them.
So is Kramer upset?
I think so. I mean,
he's acting really weird lately.
He's different.
Maybe you should
give him the keys back.
No, I can't.
[SOFT KNOCKING
ON DOOR]
[WHISPERING]
Is that Kramer?
Who's there?
Uh, Kramer.
Hey.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Oh, you got the k-k-k-key.
Oh, I...
N-- No,
I am not--
No, no, no, no, no,
it's okay, it's okay.
I don't care
about the keys.
It's my fault.
You know, I gave the keys away
with my stupidity.
I broke...
the covenant of the keys.
Jerry, give him the keys back.
Elaine.
Here.
No, no, I don't want them.
What're you doing?
I'm giving him the keys.
Those are my keys.
Oh.
No, let go!
Elaine.
Wait, wait, okay,
now, come on.
Jerry, no!
Come on, give me
those keys back.
Now, stop it, stop it!
I don't want the keys back.
No, I-- I'm glad
the way that things turned out.
I was clinging
to those keys, man,
like a branch
on the banks of a raging river,
and now I have let go,
and I'm free...
to go
with the current...
to float...
and I thank you.
Take the keys. Take them.
No, no.
I want you to have them.
No, I don't want them.
No, I can't.
Take them!
I don't want-- No!
No!
Okay.
Oh, now, one more thing.
I would like my keys back.
Your spare set?
Yeah, that's right.
You want them back?
Yeah, yeah, I think
it would be for the best.
[JINGLING]
Four, five, six...
Gee, Kramer, I, uh...
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
Yes, George, yes.
Yes?
Yes.
Should I give you my keys?
Is, uh--?
Is that the transaction,
trading keys?
Because Elaine has my keys.
Well, you can get them back.
I suppose I could.
Because you see,
George,
having the keys
to Jerry's apartment,
that kept me
in a fantasy world.
Every time
I went over to his house,
it was like I was on vacation--
better food, better view,
better TV...
cleaner, oh-ho,
much cleaner.
That became
my reality.
I ignored the squalor
in my own life,
because I'm looking
at life, you see,
through Jerry's eyes.
I was living
in twilight, George,
living in the shadows,
living in the darkness...
like you.
Me?
Oh, yeah.
I can barely see you,
George.
All right, stop it, Kramer.
You're freaking me out.
Hi. Are you ready to order?
Yeah, what's the--?
No, no, not yet, not yet.
E-excuse me.
Get out.
Oh.
Do you ever yearn?
Yearn? Do I yearn?
I yearn.
You yearn?
Oh, yes.
Yes, I yearn.
Often, I...
I sit and yearn.
Have you yearned?
Well, not recently.
I craved.
I crave all the time,
constant craving,
but I haven't yearned.
Look at you.
Oh, Kramer, don't start.
No, no.
No, you're wasting your life.
I am not.
What you call "wasting,"
I call "living."
I'm living my life.
Yeah, okay, like what?
No, tell me.
Do you have a job?
No.
You got money?
Do you have a woman?
No.
Do you have any prospects?
You got anything on the horizon?
Uh...
no.
Do you have any action at all?
No.
Do you have
any conceivable reason
for even getting up
in the morning?
I like to get the Daily News.
George, it's time
for us to grow up
and be men,
not little boys.
Why?
I'm going to California.
You know, I've got the bug.
Yeah, I think I've got a touch
of something too.
No, the acting bug,
ever since I was
in that Woody Allen movie.
"These pretzels
are making me thirsty"?
That was one line.
You got fired.
I know, I know,
but, man, I never felt so alive.
Now, you coming with me?
Uh, no, I'm not.
All right,
suit yourself.
But let's keep this
between us.
We're key brothers now.
You're not
really gonna go
to California,
are you?
Up here,
I'm already gone.
Anyway, so he gave me
his spare keys,
and now he wants
to have my keys,
so I need mine
back from you.
Just because
you have his keys?
Why does he need yours?
I don't know.
He said he wants
to be my key brother.
That's ridiculous.
That's Kramer.
I'll give you back
your spare keys,
but now I want mine back.
What for?
Because I'll give them to Jerry.
Jerry? Why?
Because he gave me his.
So what?
So if he has my keys,
I should have his.
I don't see why if you have his,
he should have yours.
I just said
the same thing to you.
What?
All right, listen,
I'll give you my keys,
but I don't
have them with me.
Can I please have mine
to give back to Kramer?
Yeah, okay, I'll go get them.
What-- What are you doing?
Would you just put that down?
I've got to get
some new friends.
Did you bring
the keys?
Yes, but I still
don't feel right
about letting you
into Kramer's apartment
without his permission.
This could be an emergency.
You shouldn't have
taken away his keys.
I tried to give them back.
He wouldn't take them.
How'd the Mets do?
They lost.
Kramer!
Open it up.
Kramer?
Hello, boys.
Oh!
Hello, Newman.
Are you looking for someone?
Don't play coy with me, Newman.
I'm not in the mood.
Coy?
I'm not being coy.
Is he being coy?
Yeah, coy.
You're being coy.
Now, where's Kramer, Newman?
Who?
Listen, Tiny...
I want to know where Kramer is,
and I want to know now!
Go ahead and hit me, Seinfeld.
I've got witnesses.
Turn around, George.
Sure.
George?
Will you tell me
where Kramer is,
or do we do this
the hard way?
Help! Help!
Where's Kramer?
Help!
What's going on?
They're going
to beat me up.
No, we're not.
We're trying
to find out
what happened to Kramer.
You want to know
what happened to Kramer?
I'll tell you what
happened to Kramer.
He was ticked off
about the keys.
Yeah, that's right,
He thought
he got a bad rap.
Bad rap?
Yeah, from you.
Me?
You heard me.
So he packed a grip,
and he split
for the coast--
La-la land-- L.A.
L.A.?
[PUNK ROCK BLASTING ON RADIO]
[ENGINE BACKFIRES]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
[ENGINE STALLS]
[ENGINE DIES]
I never should've
taken his keys away,
but he drove me to it.
I had no choice.
He wouldn't take them back.
Elaine, you saw it.
Remember?
I said,
"Take the keys back."
He wouldn't do anything.
You saw it.
Didn't you see it?
Yeah, yeah, I saw it.
I mean, it's complete bullsh--
but I saw it.
Huh?
What?
No, what'd you say?
Nothing.
I-- I didn't say anything.
Oh, you didn't see it?
Yeah, I saw it, I saw it.
I saw-- I saw it. Yeah.
I heard you say something there.
I didn't say anything.
I'm calling
Kramer's mother.
I don't know what you said.
It was something.
I heard something.
Hello? Hello, Mrs. Kramer?
[LOUD OPERA PLAYING]
Mrs. Kramer?
Could you turn
the music down?
The music down?
Ask her about Kramer.
She's drunk out of her mind.
[CAR SPEEDS PAST]
Oh...my keys.
[ANNOYED SIGH]
This is perfect.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Elaine, are you there?
It's me.
I'm locked out of my apartment.
I need my spare keys.
Where are you?
I'm at the coffee shop.
Hey, you ever been
in an accident?
About five years ago,
I was going down this very road,
the same time of day,
going about the same speed
I'm going now.
There was a rock in the road.
It couldn't have been
more than a pebble.
I never really saw it.
Lost control of the bike.
Went flying about 100 feet.
Came down right on my head.
Cracked it wide-open.
Blood and stuff just splattered
all over the road there.
Broke every bone in my face.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, you know,
when they found me,
my eyes were hanging
out of their sockets.
Yeah, they pronounced me
dead at the scene.
I was in a coma for...
well, they told me about a year.
They said I'd be
a vegetable for life.
Yeah, but I showed them.
Of course, since then,
I always wear a helmet.
Lean!
[KRAMER SCREAMS]
BIKER: Lean!
KRAMER: Wait!
Georgie boy,
way to come through
with the keys.
Sit down.
I'm buying you dinner.
I've been thinking about it.
I just don't feel right
about letting you
into Elaine's apartment.
Don't feel right?
What are you talking about?
I shouldn't have
let you into Kramer's.
Now you want to go
into Elaine's.
She entrusted me with her spare
keys, how can I just let you in?
What is the big deal?
Look, just because you have
someone's spare keys,
it doesn't entitle you
to break into their apartment.
That's the reason
you took away
Kramer's keys.
You're not even supposed
to have Elaine's keys.
You're supposed
to give them back to her
so she can give them back to me,
because she has mine,
so, technically,
those are my keys.
Yes, well, if you'd never taken
your keys back from Kramer,
he wouldn't have taken his back
and given them to me,
in which case, I wouldn't have
had to take mine back from her.
Well, I want those keys.
No can do.
George, give them to me.
Let go. No, I'm not--
I don't want
to get physical!
You want to fight?
I'll fight you!
All right, let's get going.
But nothing in the face.
Okay.
All right.
And then the evil ogre
took back the magical keys
from the handsome young prince.
Oh, no.
He didn't take back
the keys.
No way.
Yes, and then
the handsome young prince
was cast out
into the cruel, cruel world.
Oh, man, what a bummer.
That ogre dude
is pretty cold, huh?
He's cold.
Let me tell you
something, Kramer.
If that ogre dude
pulled that crap on me,
I'd stab him!
I'd cut him in half!
I'd gut him
like a fish, man!
That's what I'd do!
Yeah, yeah, that'd be funny.
Uh, hey, you can drop me here!
Hey, what's the rush, man?
Uh, well, you know,
I've gotta be going now.
Hey, Kramer,
have you ever killed a man?
What do you think, Junior?
You think these hands,
they've been soaking
in ivory liquid, huh?
[GROANING]
Don't leave, Kramer.
Stay with us.
Oh, you know so much
about the world.
We need you.
Please, Kramer.
HIPPIES:
Well, now, Star Cloud--
Please, Kramer, please.
You've got to stay.
No, no, no.
HIPPIES:
Please, Kramer. Please, Kramer.
[LAUGHING UNCOMFORTABLY]
Don't you see? You're just
avoiding them middleman
You were gonna give her
her spare keys,
and she was gonna
give them to me,
so all that's happening
is that instead
of giving them to her,
you're giving them to me.
It's just unfortunate
that when she gave you yours,
you didn't give her hers,
because then she
would've given them to me,
because she has mine,
so I wouldn't have had
to ask you for hers
so that I could
get mine.
You're right.
How did I miss that?
Maybe because
it's a crock of sh--
What's that?
Nothing.
I heard something.
I didn't say anything.
So how long have you
been driving this thing?
Going on four years.
Nothing's sexier than a woman
behind the wheel of a semi.
Nothing?
Well...
Listen to you.
You're quite
the sweet-talker.
You know, I always wanted
to drive the big rigs.
I used to watch
those commercials
during the reruns of Gomer Pyle.
You want to give it a try?
Oh, really?
Do you know
how to double-clutch?
Yeah.
Well, come on.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Okay. All right.
[GEARS GRINDING]
They were in here.
I saw her
put them in here.
Well, this is great.
All right,
what do they look like?
Like keys,
they look like keys, George.
They look exactly like keys.
"What do they look like?"
Well, they're
obviously not here.
Well, they've got
to be here somewhere.
Jerry, unless I pull down
on this statuette
and a hidden wall opens up,
we've checked every square inch
of this apartment.
What is this?
Murphy Brown?
What?
"By Elaine Benes"?
Elaine's writing a Murphy Brown?
Let me see this.
Wait a second.
Let me just
look at it.
Give me half.
All right, here.
Why didn't she tell us?
Elaine is writing
a sitcom?
You-- you-- you weasels!
What? What?
How dare you?
We hardly read anything.
It was funny.
Who gave you permission
to come into my house
and just go through
all my things?
You thought it was funny?
Well, you know...
from what I saw...
Well, it's just a first draft!
I was locked
out of my apartment.
I'm just trying
to get my keys.
Why did you let him in?
He forced me to.
I did not!
Yes, you did!
You, get out! Get out, get out!
Wait, wait!
Get out!
I need my spare keys.
Oh, here, here's
your damn keys.
You keep them.
I don't want them
anymore.
Good.
And I want my keys back.
You don't want me
to hold your keys?
No, you can't be trusted.
All right, all right, fine.
And I don't want you
to hold mine.
Good. I won't.
Good. Don't.
Are these my keys?
These aren't my keys.
Whose are these?
I don't know.
["CALIFORNIA GIRLS"
BY THE BEACH BOYS PLAYING]
I just thought I could write it.
Is that something
you want to do?
I don't know.
Those writers
make a lot of money.
What?
Elaine,
let me tell you something
about show business.
Ugh...
I can't believe it.
It's hard work.
You don't just write
a Murphy Brown.
You've gotta
watch the show,
study it, get a sense
of the characters,
how they relate
to each other...
Okay, can I just
watch the show?
Oh, God,
what an ass...
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
I heard something.
Elaine, Elaine,
it's Kramer!
Kramer's on Murphy Brown!
Kramer's on Murphy Brown?
Look, there he is.
He's sitting
at the desk!
Hi. I'm Murphy Brown.
You must be
my new secretary.
Oh, good morning,
Miss Brown.
And you are?
Uh, I'm... Steven Snell.
Snell...
Well, hello,
Mr. Snell.
Steven.
Are you familiar with
this computer system?
Oh... I'm familiar, yes.
Steven Snell,
I know people,
and I have
a very good feeling
about you.
Yes.
So I fly a lot. I like planes.
I was on a plane the other day,
and I was wondering,
"Are there keys to the plane?
Do they need keys
to start the plane?"
Maybe that's what
those delays on the ground are,
when you're sitting
at the gate.
Maybe the pilot's going,
"Oh, I don't believe this.
"Oh, my God.
I did it again."
They tell you
it's something mechanical,
because they don't want
to come on the PA system--
"Ladies and gentlemen,
"we're gonna be delayed
for a little while.
"Oh, God,
this is so embarrassing.
"I...
I left the keys to the plane
in my apartment."
You see the technicians
all running
underneath the plane.
You think they're servicing it,
but they're actually looking
for, like, the magnet hide-a-key
under the wing.
"Maybe he left it
up there somewhere."
[♪]