I would say
the concept behind the car phone
and the phone machine,
the speaker phone,
the airline phone,
the portable phone,
the pay phone,
the cordless phone,
the multiline phone,
the phone pager, call waiting,
call forwarding,
call conferencing,
speed dialing, direct dialing,
and the redialing
is that we all have
absolutely nothing to say,
and we've got to talk to someone
about it
right now.
Cannot wait another second.
I mean, come on, you're at home,
you're on the phone.
You're in the car,
you're making calls.
You get to work--
"Any messages for me?"
You've got to give people
a chance
to miss you a little!
ELAINE [ON TELEPHONE]:
You know, it's bad enough
you have a car phone.
Do you have to use the speaker?
It's safer.
Plus, it's more annoying
to the other person.
Oh, look at this guy.
What's going on?
There's a guy
trying to get in front of me.
He has to ask permission.
Yes, go ahead, get in, get in.
Did you get a "thank you" wave?
No, nothing.
How could you not give
a "thank you" wave?
Hey, buddy,
where's my "thank you" wave?
Give me that wave!
Hey, Jerry,
are you free on Friday?
Yeah, I'm free. Why?
Oh, God.
I bumped into Robin Sandusky
today.
She asked me to have dinner
with her and her husband.
[CRASH]
Oh, my God.
You won't believe
what I just saw.
A car just bashed
into a parked car
and sped off right on my block.
You've got to follow that car.
What?
You can't let him get away
with that.
Elaine,
the guy could be dangerous.
What are you, yellow?
I'm not yellow.
Jerry, if you don't follow him,
you're yellow.
Wait, he stopped. He's parking.
What? What?
I can't hear you. Jerry?
Uh, excuse me...
I was... driving behind you...
you know, a few blocks back,
and I-- I couldn't... help--
Maybe you didn't
realize...
I-- I-- I witnessed that...
that... uh... your...
your left rear tire's
a little low.
You know, that can affect
the performance
of the twin I-beam suspension,
not to mention, you know,
your rack-and-pinion steering.
So I wound up going out
for a decaf cappuccino
with her.
Boy, what a story.
I-- I'm speechless, speechless.
I have no speech.
You know, I really liked her.
We talked, we flirted.
and when she'd laugh,
she'd reach out
and touch my arm.
[LAUGHING]
I love when they touch your arm.
I can't get enough of that.
Me either.
Why is that?
Let's not even analyze it.
So you didn't turn her in.
I wanted to, but I couldn't
go through with it.
Are you gonna
see her again?
Friday night.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE: It's me.
Come on up.
By the way, Elaine does not need
to know about anything.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I dig.
Oh, you dig?
Yes.
I see enormous
potential there.
Why?
Because great couples
always have a great story
about how they met.
That's why I've never been
in a long-term relationship.
I never had
a good meeting story.
I'm wondering if I'm nuts
for pursuing this woman at all.
I don't think so.
Look,
she slammed into a parked car.
She took no responsibility
for mutilating
the property of a stranger,
and then she sped off
like a criminal.
On the other hand...
Does that mean
she should never be allowed
to date again?
You scratch one car,
and you're forbidden
to have social contact
for the rest of your life?
Nah.
What am I drinking? Milk?
Hey.
Hi.
Sweater.
Thank you.
So... what happened?
With what?
With the car.
What car?
The hit and run.
Oh, right, right, right, right,
right, right, right, right,
the hit and run.
Well...
Actually,
the guy went into Queens.
Queens?
Mm-hmm.
You followed him
over the bridge?
Over the bridge.
Well, I...
I didn't know you went
into Queens, Jerry.
Yeah, Queens.
So... then what?
So he gets out of the car.
I said, "Hey, buddy,
I saw you hit that car,"
so he says to me,
"What are you gonna do
about it?"
[GASPS]
So I said to him,
"Whatever's necessary."
I-- I...
I am... speechless.
I am without speech.
Tell her about the shoving.
What?
What shoving?
Oh, it was nothing.
No.
Tell her.
Come on, tell me.
Well, he kind of
lost his temper,
and he was pushing me up
against the car,
so I went into a karate stance.
Hiya!
You know karate?
I know a little.
Well, I--
This is so amazing to me.
Jerry, what did he do?
He backed off.
It was pretty pathetic,
actually.
Hey.
Did you tell Kramer?
Nah.
What, what? Tell me.
Jerry saw this guy
smash into a car,
and he followed him.
KRAMER:
Good for you.
What kind
of a sick lowlife
would do a thing
like that?
You know,
those people,
you know, they're
mentally disturbed.
They should be sent
to Australia.
Australia?
Yeah, yeah,
that's where England
used to send
their convicts.
But not anymore.
No.
Hey, Kramer?
Kramer?
Huh?
What-- What happened
to you right here?
I don't know.
You know,
I was watching
Entertainment
Tonight,
and... suddenly,
you know, I got dizzy,
and the next thing
I know,
I hit my head
on the coffee table.
Well, that is...
that is strange.
Yeah, it-- it's...
ELAINE:
All right.
Oh, Jerry, we're still on
for Friday night, right?
Oh, Friday, no, I can't.
I'm sorry. I have a date.
But last night,
you said you were free.
We just met.
You know, maybe
it was a reaction
to the sardines.
But I-- I can't go alone.
Ask George to go with you.
[GASPS]
George, come on.
I'll pay for you.
You'll pay? I'm there.
Why do you even need anybody?
Because I hate being
at a table alone
with a married couple,
talking
about their married friends
and their married furniture.
They're always trying
to make me feel
like their life
is so much better than mine.
You know,
I have a very exciting life.
It's very exciting.
You went out
with a bullfighter?
Yeah, yeah, well,
an ex-bullfighter now.
Wow.
What was his name?
His name?
His... his name was...
was... Ed-uardo...
Car...ochio.
Pass the salt, please.
Where did you meet him?
Um, actually,
I met him in Switzerland,
and he was fighting...
Is that the word they use,
"fighting"?
Because they don't really fight
the bull.
They avoid fighting the bull.
Bread.
Oh, I just love
meeting new people, you know?
That's how you really do learn
about life.
[SNEEZES]
God bless you.
Thank you.
I wasn't going
to say anything,
but then I could see
that he wasn't going
to open his mouth.
You know
who's a good actor?
Anthony Quinn.
Oh, Anthony Quinn,
fine actor,
but from what I understand,
not a very good driver.
Hits everything
on the road,
but always leaves a note.
Did you ever see
Zorba the Greek?
Excellent film.
In fact, Quinn said
he never felt so good
as when he left a note
after smacking into a car.
Come here.
Really, I-- I was
only kidding around.
He was only joking, Michael.
You think you're
so damn special
because you said
"God bless you"?
I-- I don't think
I'm special.
My mother always said
I'm not special.
He was only joking,
Michael.
I'm sorry.
Oh, right,
take his side!
I am not taking
his side.
Well, whose side
are you taking?
Well, I'm not taking
your side!
[SNEEZES]
Kirk Douglas--
Now, there's another
very bad driver,
but he's such
an unbelievable guy
that when he hits someone,
he doesn't even leave a note.
He sits in his car,
and he waits for the other
person to show up
so he can exchange license,
registration,
and apologize.
I mean, I said "God bless you."
Was that so wrong?
The question is...
Did you allow a space
for the husband
to come in with
his "God bless you"?
Because as the husband,
he has the right
of first refusal.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE: It's me.
Come on up.
Yes.
Yes, I definitely waited,
but let me say this--
Once he passes on that option,
that "God bless you"
is up for grabs.
No argument,
unless she's one of these
multiple sneezers,
and he's holding his
"God bless you" in abeyance
until she completes the series.
Well, I don't think
she is a multiple sneezer,
because she sneezed
again later,
and it was
also a single.
What if she's having
an off night?
Hi.
Well...
if it isn't Mr. Gesundheit.
Oh, yeah,
like there's something wrong
with saying "God bless you."
I was raised
to say "God bless you."
[SNEEZES]
Oh, shut up.
What does it mean, anyway,
"God bless you"?
It's a stupid stuperstition.
A stupid what?
Whatever.
You know, if you want
to make a person feel better
after they sneeze,
you shouldn't say,
"God bless you."
You should say,
"You're so good-looking."
Yeah.
Yeah, that's better
than "God bless you."
Anyway, she left a message
on my machine.
She wants you to call her.
Who?
Robin.
Why?
Well, I assume
she called to apologize.
That's why she called me.
Entertainment
Tonight is on.
Where's the remote phone?
Bedroom.
Hey, grab Jerry's sweater
for me, would you?
[ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT
THEME PLAYING]
MARY HART [ON TV]:
Georgia peach Marla Maples
reportedly threw
yet another stiletto...
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
What's it like out?
It's chilly out.
Should I take
a sweater?
Yeah, I mean,
you could take
a sweater
if you want.
Scarf?
Nah.
Hey, shut this off.
Shut it off.
Hey, what--
What's the matter?
What's going on?
What happened?
What?
I think I hit my head again.
What is wrong?
Hey, hey,
wait a minute.
Let me ask you
something.
Kramer, the last time
you hit your head,
was Mary Hart on TV?
Yeah.
That is it!
What?
Mary Hart's voice!
Don't you see?
There's something
about the sound of
Mary Hart's voice
that's giving you
seizures.
Just like-- just like--
just like that woman
in Albany.
Mary Hart?
GEORGE: Oh, my God.
What?
Well, she apologized,
and then she wanted to know
if we could
get together
Wednesday afternoon.
Get together?
Maybe she just wants
to talk to me.
Married woman
don't get together.
They have affairs.
Oh, my God, an affair...
It's so adult.
It's like with stockings
and martinis
and William Holden...
On the other hand,
it probably wouldn't cost me
any money.
Are you... actually
considering this?
I can't have an affair
with a married woman.
That's despicable.
Ugh...
It's like hitting a car
and driving away
without leaving a note.
Yeah.
Hey, do you know
who owns that car?
What car?
The one that was hit
a couple of nights ago.
Yeah? Who?
That blonde across the street.
You know,
the one with the long ponytail.
She wears those blue sweatpants.
The blonde
with the blue sweat...
pants.
Yeah, I think I've seen her.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I've got to get going.
I'm meeting a guy
with gray sweatpants.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How do you know
it's not John Tesh?
The blonde
with the blue sweatpants.
Who is she?
I've had a crush on this woman
for a year.
I've always been afraid
to approach her.
She looks like she belongs
on one of these Hallmark cards.
Oh, right, right,
the blue sweatpants!
Gee, it's too bad
you can't say anything
because of Angela.
Oh... yeah.
Too bad.
Angela...
Lousy thug.
I mean, what kind
of sick person
does something
like that?
The woman belongs
in prison.
I mean, I actually
owe it to society
to do something
about this.
I can't sit by
and allow this
to go on.
It's a moral issue,
is what it is.
You can't compromise
your principles.
How I am going to
live with myself?
Can't live.
I'm not religious,
but I certainly know
where to draw the line.
This country needs
more people like you.
Don't sell
yourself short,
saying "God bless you"
to every Tom,
Dick, and Harry,
at great
personal risk.
I believe strongly
in that, as you know.
There should be
more people like us.
That's why the world
is in the shape
that it's in.
You're telling me.
Anyway, I just
want you to know
that I'm gonna do
everything I can
to make sure
the party responsible
is made to be responsible,
or something
very close to that.
Well, God bless you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God,
I must be crazy.
What have I done?
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I'll tell you what's wrong.
I just committed adultery.
You didn't commit
adultery. I did.
Oh, yeah.
If I didn't do it with you,
I would have done it
with someone else.
Well, I... I wouldn't
want you to do that.
You know, there's a lot
of losers out there.
Maybe even someone
who didn't say "God bless you."
Well, that's a given.
In three years with Michael,
not one "God bless you."
It must be hell
living in that house.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hi, it's Michael.
Hi, Michael.
Is Robin there?
Robin? No. Why?
Uh... she said
she was gonna be
with you.
No, I haven't spoken
to her all da--
Uh...
Yeah, right, um...
As a-- as a matter of fact,
um, she-- she was here,
and... sh-she left a note,
but I-- I wasn't here,
but I have the note...
right here.
If she's not with you,
then where is she?
Well, I-- I don't know.
Is she
with your bald friend
from the other night?
No... no.
Come on, Michael.
He's finished.
I'm gonna sew his ass
to his face!
I'm gonna twist
his neck so hard,
his lips will be
his eyebrows!
I'm gonna break
his joints
and re-attach them!
[SNEEZES]
You're so good-looking.
Now, you listen to me,
suckface!
You tell anybody
anything,
and I will carve my initials
in your brain tissue.
Let me rephrase--
I'll bash your skull
into a vegematic
like a bad cabbage,
and I'll have a party
on your head!
Hi, Elaine.
This is Angela.
I'll pluck
all your body hairs out
with my teeth!
Well, I think
I get the gist of it.
So you don't say
anything to anybody
about me hitting
that car.
What car?
Good...
I'm glad we understand
each other.
It's not complicated.
Very nice meeting you.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Come on up.
Well, well, well,
Mr. Seinfeld,
that must have been
so frightening
when you confronted
that "guy" in Queens.
Now, let me just see
if I've got
the scenario right.
All right, Elaine.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
because I'm picturing--
What? What?
Oh, French Connection
kind of thing,
you know, sort of
a Popeye Doyle chase
through the city.
It was just
a couple of blocks.
Oh, no, no.
Come on, don't be so modest.
Hey.
Oh...
Did you check
your machine?
No. Why? What's happened?
Michael called me today,
and he asked where Robin was...
Yeah. Okay.
And I said
that I hadn't seen her.
What?
No, George, George,
you don't understand.
She didn't tell me
she was using me as an excuse,
okay, but then--
but then I realized
what was going on,
and I said that
she left a note.
Um...
but he didn't
really buy that,
and then-- and then
he did mention your name.
He mentioned my name?
What did he say?
He said he was gonna...
s-sew your ass
to your face.
What?
Why couldn't you think
of something?
Well, I don't know.
He caught me off guard.
You lie!
How hard is it to lie?
It's not that hard.
Well, who told you
to sleep with her, George?
It's not my fault.
I wasn't gonna do anything
until you got her all juiced up
with your story
about having the affair
with the matador!
Oh, gosh, none of this
would never have happened
if you hadn't said
"God bless you"!
Oh, don't start--
Hold it, hold it,
hold it, people.
Matador?
Oh, God.
What matador?
She told this couple
she had an affair
with a matador.
A matador...
Well, well, well,
uno momento, por favor.
Pray tell,
what was the young man's name?
Uh...
Eduardo... Carochio.
[IN SPANISH ACCENT]:
Eduardo...
Carochio!
That's good.
That's very good.
It kind of just rolls
off the tongue.
I wonder where,
on the Upper West Side,
a single girl
might meet a matador.
Perhaps Zabars...
Well...
[IN SPANISH ACCENT]:
Or Ray's Pizza.
Anyway, this person
told me to tell you
to get an estimate
on the damage.
Well, I already got an estimate.
It's $875.
$875?
That's right.
Uh... well,
I'll tell you what.
Um, I'll give you a check,
and then this person
can pay me back.
Uh, who do I
make it out to?
Becky Gelke.
G-e-l-k-e.
So...
what are you doing this weekend?
You have got some nerve.
You smash up my car,
you don't admit it,
and now you want
to ask me out on a date?
I didn't do it.
Yeah, right.
[SNEEZES]
You are so good-looking.
Thank you.
Jerry, let's go. You ready?
Are you sure
you want to do this?
I'm gonna be on the road
for three weeks.
Excuse me,
I've got a maniac stalking me.
I'm not staying in the city.
All right.
Come on, let's get out of here.
How could you?
What?
Man, I never thought
you were capable of this.
What did I do?
I just talked to Becky Gelke
outside.
She told me how you hit and ran.
I--
I don't even want
to look at you anymore!
All these years of friendship,
and you're-- you're nothing
but a felon.
You're an embarrassment
to the building.
I didn't do it.
I just had to pay her
to cover for somebody else.
Now, you're not gonna lie to me,
are you?
No, never.
All right, well, I'm glad
we got that straightened out,
because I've got a date
with her.
You got a date with Becky Gelke?
Yeah, I'm going out with her
Saturday night.
Jerry, can we
get out of here?
As a matter of fact,
if it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have even had
an excuse to talk to her.
Well, I'm happy to help
in any way that I can.
[ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT
THEME PLAYING]
Liz Taylor...
A man is paralyzed mentally
by a beautiful woman,
and advertisers
really take advantage of this.
Don't you love those ads
where you see, like,
the woman in the bikini
next to the 32-piece
ratchet set?
You know, and she's--
You know, we'll be looking
at the girl in the bikini,
looking at the ratchet set,
going, "All right,
"Well, if she's right next
to the ratchet set,
"and I had that ratchet set,
I wonder
if that would mean that..."
"I'd better just buy
that ratchet set."
[♪]