I tell you,
I never really understood
the importance of the conductor.
I mean, between you and me...
what the hell is this guy doing?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I mean, do you really need
somebody
waving a stick in your face
to play the violin?
Does that really help you out?
I could see how we need him
at the beginning, okay?
Tap, tap, tap.
"Start." Okay.
I could see how you need that.
But once we're going, okay.
Once it's all happening...
what do we need him for then?
I don't see the cellist
looking up, going,
"I'm confused.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do."
And the conductor go,
"Do this, this. Like this."
"Oh, okay, thank you.
Thank you very much."
Why even try anymore?
There's no sense to it.
I'm never gonna meet anybody.
I should just accept it.
Oh, yes, you will.
No, I won't.
Yeah, maybe you won't.
I mean, it's hard enough to meet
a woman you dislike,
much less like.
Are my nostrils getting bigger?
No.
See, why must it be
so difficult?
Why is all this tension
and hostility?
Why can't I just walk up
to a woman on the street
and say, "Hi"?
"I'm George.
How are you?"
Is that so terrible?
H-H-- Hi.
[CLEARS THROAT]
H-Hi.
Hi.
There's just no men out there,
you know?
I know.
I mean, the problem is...
that the good ones
know they're good.
And they know
they're in such demand,
they're just
not interested in
confining themselves
to one person.
I hate the good ones.
Is Jerry
one of the good ones?
That's a good question.
I think he thinks he is.
Well, the mediocre ones
are available.
But they're so insecure about
not being one of the good ones
that they're always going,
"I'm not good enough for you."
And "What are you doing
with me?"
And eventually I just go,
"You're right."
You know,
maybe you need
somebody between
good and mediocre.
No, maybe I need somebody
who has nothing.
Somebody who just has to
appreciates being with me
because he's so desperate.
[SMACKING]
I mean, it's gotten
to the point
where I'm flirting
with operators on the phone.
I almost made a date
with one.
Oh, so there's
still hope.
I don't want hope.
Hope is killing me.
My dream is
to become hopeless.
When you're hopeless,
you don't care.
Mm-hmmm.
And when you don't care,
that indifference
makes you attractive.
Uh-huh.
So hopelessness
is the key.
It's my only hope.
You see, I wouldn't
really mind so much,
but I feel badly
for my mother.
I mean, if my mother weren't
around, it wouldn't be so bad.
But, I'm telling you,
if I'm not married
by the time I'm 40,
I'm gonna have
to kill her.
Because it's
the only fair thing to do.
I just couldn't
put her through that.
Well...
at least
you're not bitter.
Who says I'm not bitter?
Aren't you too young
to be bitter?
No, you can be
young and bitter.
Just maybe not as bitter
as I'm gonna be
10 years from now, but...
I'm bitter.
Anyway,
don't tell anyone.
Don't worry. Your bitterness
is safe with me.
Okay, um...
Order me
a piece of cake.
I'm gonna go
throw up.
JERRY:
Look at my hands.
Look.
They're filthy
from the paper.
You know, they should give you
a Wet-Nap when you buy one,
like at those rib joints.
So, what did you do
last night?
Went out with George.
You?
Went out with Cynthia.
How was it?
What did you talk about?
Oh, you know,
the usual.
The Federal Reserve,
the rain forest.
Cynthia felt we should
nuke the rain forest.
You know, get rid of it
in one fell swoop
so we could
at least eliminate it
as a subject
of conversation.
What about you?
We brushed on that.
Mm-hmm.
Actually, George was in
rare form.
He just can't find
anybody.
Yeah. I know.
Cynthia too.
She's really
given up.
George too.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
Yeah, right.
I've never
fixed anybody up.
Ugh! Me neither
And I am not about
to start with George.
Well, why wouldn't you start
with George?
You think she's too good
for George?
I didn't say "too good."
Did I say "too good"?
No, you implied it.
I didn't say it.
Because if you think
she's too good for George,
you are dead wrong.
Dead wrong.
Who is she?
Who is he?
He's George.
She's Cynthia.
So what?
What, you don't think
she's beautiful?
I don't know.
What's with the eyebrows?
You know
what your problem is?
Your standards
are too high.
I went out with you.
That's because my standards
are too low.
And by the way,
you know,
women kill for
eyebrows like that.
Do you know that?
I mean, women pluck
their real eyebrows
out of their head
one by one
until they're bald, Jerry,
bald above the eyes.
And then they paint in
these eyebrows
to look like that.
Well, let me tell you
something about George.
He is fast.
He can run
like the wind.
And he's strong.
I've seen him lift 100 pounds
over his head
without even knowing it.
And you wouldn't know it
to look at him,
but George can
bait a hook.
He can really do that?
Come on, let's do it. I think
they'll really get along.
What, are you
into this?
Yeah, come on,
it's a good match.
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
They're gonna be telling us
how their dates went.
Are we gonna share
that information?
Naturally.
But wait a minute. We're gonna
tell each other everything?
I mean, every secret?
Everything.
[GIGGLES]
What if it worked out?
Yeah, right.
GEORGE:
Out of the question.
Why?
No.
I'm not gonna do that.
It's one step away
from personal ads.
Then prostitutes.
No! No!
I am not going
down that road.
What does
she look like?
She's good-looking.
How good-looking?
Very good-looking.
Really good-looking?
Really very good-looking.
Would you take her out?
Yes, I would
take her out.
Oh, you hesitated.
What hesitate?
I didn't hesitate.
Something's up here.
You hesitated.
I'm telling you,
she's good-looking.
What about the body?
What kind of body.
Good body. Nice body.
How nice?
Nice.
Just nice?
Pretty nice.
Really good?
Really very nice
and good.
What about personality?
Good personality.
Funny.
Bright.
Smarter than me?
I don't want anyone
smarter than me.
How could she be
smarter than you?
All right, let's see.
Let's see. What else?
What else?
Oh, yeah.
What does she do?
First of all...
what does he do?
He was
in real estate.
Um, now, he's not working
right now--
Oh! He's not working?
No.
No. No. No.
How come he's
not working?
Well-- Well,
I mean,
[LAUGHS]
he got fired.
Why did he get fired?
W-- Uh...
Oh, right.
Um, well, he...
He tried to...
poison his boss.
Excuse me?
It's such a long story,
Cynthia.
Seriously, I mean, he just had
some problems at work.
Is he nuts?
No!
No, no. He's a really,
really funny guy.
[LAUGHS]
What does he look like?
Pardon?
Um... Well, he's got a lot of
character in his face.
Um, he's short.
Um, he's stocky.
He's fat.
Is that what you're saying,
that he fat?
Powerful.
He is so powerful.
He can lift 100 pounds
right up over his head.
And, um...
What else?
Oh, r-- Um
Right, well...
Yeah, he's--
He's kind of--
Just kind of, unh,
losing his hair.
He's bald?
No!
No, no, no.
He's not bald.
He's balding.
So he will be bald?
Yeah.
What kind of hair?
You know,
long, dark hair.
Flowing?
Is it flowing?
I like flowing,
cascading hair.
Thick, lustrous hair is
very important to me.
"Thick, lustrous hair
is very important to me,"
Is that what you said?
Yeah, that's right.
Just clarifying.
Let me ask you this.
If you stick your hand
in the hair...
is it easy
to get it out?
Do you wanna be able
Or do you wanna not be able
to get it out?
I'd like to be able
to get it out.
I think
you'll get it out.
What about the skin?
I need a good cheek.
I like a good cheek.
She's got a fine cheek.
Is there a pinkish hue?
A pinkish hue?
Yes, a--
A rosy glow.
There's a hue.
She's got
great eyebrows.
Women kill to have
her eyebrows.
Who cares
about eyebrows?
Is she sweet?
I like sweet.
But not too sweet.
You could throw up from that.
I don't think
you'll throw up.
She likes to throw up.
Has he ever been married?
No.
Has he been close?
He once spent a weekend
with a woman.
He didn't really try
to poison his boss.
Yeah, he did.
GEORGE:
We had an incredible
phone conversation.
We talked for
like 20 minutes.
I threw away my notes
in the middle of the call.
You know, I thought she had
a great voice timbre.
Is it "timbre"
or "tambre"?
I think it's tambre.
Huh. Why did I think
it was timbre?
Yeah, she could do
voice-over commercials.
Why didn't you tell me
about her voice?
I didn't notice
the voice.
It's mellifluous.
So, Saturday night.
She had to be impressed
by that conversation. Had to.
It was a great performance.
I am unbelievable on the phone.
On the date,
they should just have
two phones on the table
at the restaurant.
Done.
[LAUGHS]
Hi.
Hi!
You know?
Saturday night.
I know.
So, what did she say?
She said you're getting
together Saturday night.
Yeah.
That's it?
She didn't mention anything
about the conversation?
No.
Well, you see?
I don't get that.
What, we had a relaxed,
stimulating, great conversation.
She doesn't mention it?
Why doesn't she mention it?
What?
Well, she could've
mentioned the conversation.
All right. All right.
I'll go on the date,
but that's that.
Hey.
ALL: Hey.
Do you know my friend
Bob Sakamano?
Oh, the guy
from Jersey.
Yeah, he just got a job
at a condom factory in Edison.
Look at this.
He gave me a gross.
Look at that.
What are you gonna do
with all of them?
Oh, well.
Come on. Take some, Jerry.
Grab them.
No, thanks. They look like
they came out of a cereal box.
Hey, come on, Elaine,
here. Take half a bag.
Gotta, gotta.
Half a bag?
What am I, a hooker?
Anyway, they look
kind of cheap.
Naw.
I'll take one.
Yeah.
It's possible.
The problem with the condom
is still...
buying them.
I think we should have,
like, a secret...
signal with the druggist.
That you just walk
into the drug store,
go to the counter.
He looks at you.
And if you go like this--
He puts them in the bag
for you. That's it.
Show up there,
you put
your little shaving cream,
your little toothpaste,
you know.
"How are you today?"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Have a nice day."
"You too."
So where are they already?
It's a quarter to 12.
They should be back by now.
What did they do?
I think they went out
to dinner.
Oh, wait. I got another call.
That must be him.
Hello.
Yeah, it's me. I just got home.
Oh, hold on.
It's George.
He just got home.
Yeah, yeah. I got Cynthia
on the other line.
I'll call you back
as soon as I'm done.
Remember our pact:
full disclosure.
Of course.
Yeah, go ahead.
All right, look,
I'm gonna tell you,
but I made a pact
with Cynthia.
We swore we were not gonna
tell you and Elaine.
You can tell me. I'll vault it.
It's in the vault?
I'm locking the vault.
What? Come on.
We had sex.
Oh, my God,
you had sex?
How did that happen?
I don't know.
I closed my eyes
and made a move.
At your apartment?
Yeah.
She didn't stay over?
No. She left.
But l-listen, you can't mention
any of this to Elaine.
Cynthia will kill me.
We made a deal.
Oh, my God.
He was uncomfortable
because it was our first time.
So he felt he'd perform better
if we did it in the kitchen.
What?
Yeah, he says
the kitchen
is always the most sociable room
in the house.
And he was serious.
So how was it?
How good could it be?
My head was on
a hot plate.
Oh. Wait, I got another call.
That must be Jerry.
Oh, wait. Don't you tell him
any of this.
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Hello?
So, what did she say?
What did he have
to say?
He said he had
a good time.
Her too.
Oh, good.
Anything else?
No.
You?
You sure?
Yeah.
You?
All right, well...
I guess everything
is under control.
Yeah. Okay then.
Alrighty.
Good night.
GEORGE:
I left three messages.
I can't believe
this woman.
She has sex with me,
leaves 10 minutes later,
then I never
hear from her again.
What kind of a person
does this?
I mean, she used me.
I feel...
cheap and violated.
Well, I'm gonna do
something about this.
Oh, what are you
gonna do?
Never mind.
Disgraceful.
Leaves you sitting there
on the kitchen floor like--
Like some kind of
roach trap.
The "Wham, bam,
thank you, ma'am."
"Sir." Whatever.
She's not gonna
get away with this.
I-I-I keep
racking my brain
to try and figure out
what I did.
I was smart.
I was funny. I--
I made great small talk
with the waitress
so she could see I could
relate to the commoners.
You know, I'm a man
of the people.
I'm gonna call her.
No, don't call.
No, I'm calling her.
No, Jerry, don't call.
No, forget it.
I don't want you to.
I'm calling. Get away from me.
Jerry, don't. Give me the phone.
You wanna fight me?
Jerry, I'm gonna kill you.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
Hey, come on, Jerry, George.
Now stop it.
I'll call her when you leave.
I don't care.
You can't. It's none of
your business!
It is so my business.
Give me that!
Hey, hey!
Stop it, boys!
I don't want another word
from either of you.
Well, tell him to give me my--
Hey, hey, hey!
The next one of you that opens
your mouth, says something,
you're gonna have to
deal with me.
You know, I bet I know
what this is about.
It's about a woman, isn't it?
Yeah, but--
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You see?
This is exactly
what they wanna do to you.
They play one
against the other.
You can't let them
manipulate you like that.
But, Kramer--
No, no, no!
I want you guys
to shake hands.
Come on, there are plenty women
out there for all of us.
Let's go.
Shake.
Yes! You see?
Isn't that better
than fighting?
Animosity?
I mean, you wanna fight with
somebody, you fight with me.
Oh, by the way, George. You know
those condoms I gave you?
They're defective.
Don't use them.
What?
Yeah.
Defective?
How could you give me
a defective condom?
[BOTH SCREAMING]
I didn't even know
they were defective.
I didn't even think
you'd use them.
What do you mean--!
All right. Take it easy.
Take it easy.
You guys,
just spread out!
Don't worry about it.
If anything was wrong,
she'd have called you already.
I missed my period.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
I am very worried.
I am never late.
But he used a condom,
right?
I know, but these things
aren't always foolproof.
Oh, no.
What?
Was it blue?
Yeah. How'd you know?
Just a hunch.
JERRY:
Ow!
It says "twist-off."
Twist off!
Twist! Off!
Oh, hi.
Soda?
No, thanks.
So tell me.
What's the problem with
your little flaky friend?
She doesn't
return calls?
Ah, who are you to talk
about her like that?
She'll call him
when she's good and ready.
You don't even know her.
Oh, I know her.
I know her type.
Her type?
What type?
The type that doesn't
return phone calls.
I knew we shouldn't
have done it.
It was a bad idea
in the first place. I told you.
You told me? You pushed
this whole thing on me.
It was your idea.
I was just helping your
bitter, twisted friend.
She's not bitter.
Well, bitter's a judgment call,
but she's twisted.
Twisted? God,
I did you a favor!
You said they had
a good time.
Is there anything else
you're keeping from me?
Are you calling me
a liar?
I'm calling you one
if you are.
You a liar?
Are you?
Get your finger
out of my face.
Get yours out.
I was here first.
I don't care.
Get it out!
Out! Out!
Hey, hey, hey!
All right.
Hey, hey! Come on,
stop it!
Come on. Break it up!
Hey, hey!
What's the matter
with you?
Now, don't you two see...
that you're in love
with each other?
I mean, why can't you
face that already?
You're running around
out there
looking for something
that's not even there
when everything
that you dream of
is right here
right here
in front of you.
Now why can't you
admit that?
By the way, when you see George,
give him these. These'll work.
[GASPS]
I knew those condoms
were defective!
Oh.
How did you know
they were defective?!
Because!
Because she missed
her period!
She missed
her period?
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it.
I'm a father!
I did it!
My boys can swim!
I can do it!
I'm a father!
CYNTHIA:
So he shows up.
He's all out of breath.
He's disheveled.
And he tells me
that no matter happens,
whatever I decide
is fine with him.
[GASPS]
And that I could
depend on him
and that he would
be there
to support me
in whatever way I need.
Elaine, I was speechless.
Wow. Wow.
You see? You think
you know somebody.
I said to him,
"I really appreciate this, but
I just got my period."
Yeah.
And so I asked him to come in--
GEORGE:
Hi.
Oh, hi.
Sorry we're late.
We got so...
hung up in traffic.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
Acting.
Very mature.
Thank you.
Hi, Cynthia.
Hi.
Well, this is a great place
to sit you got here.
It's the best seat
in the house.
Right next to
the kitchen.
Oh, stop it. Stop it.
[LAUGHS]
So, what are these?
Oh, we ordered appetizers.
Start eating.
Oh, fabulous.
Mmm. Mm-mmm.
Mmmm.
This is good.
Oh, this is good.
Is that salt?
Is this salt on this?
Is there salt on this?
But have you ever
fixed anybody up?
Why do we do it? Why?
WOMAN: Good time.
You thought
they would have a good time
and little power trips
for you, isn't it?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Now you're playing God.
Of course, God...
was the first person
to fix people up.
He fixed up Adam and Eve,
you know?
I'm sure he said to Adam,
"No, she's nice.
"She's, uh...
"Yes, she's very free
about her body.
"Doesn't really wear much.
She was going out with a snake.
I think that's over though."
[♪]