Every mall has a Hoffritz
in it.
I'm sorry, this has gotta be
a little bit of a scary place
to work.
I don't know how
you feel about it.
Do you want to be standing there
having people coming in
all day going,
"I need knives.
I need more knives.
"Do you have any bigger knives?
"I'd like a bigger knife.
A big, long, sharp knife.
"That's what I'm
in the market for.
"I like them really sharp.
"Do you have one
with hooks and gouges
"and, like, blades that--
Kind of serrated?
"That's the kind of knife
I'm looking for.
"I need one I can throw.
"I need another one
I can just hack away with.
Do you have anything like that?"
Oh, yeah. Like you know
what you're talking about?
Oh, no. You do.
Well, what do you think,
they put the statue
on a giant raft,
and a tugboat pulled it
all the way from France?
What do you think,
they brought it over in pieces
and screwed it together
like a coffee table?
[CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYING]
What's going on here?
It's a little early
for a Christmas party.
Why did France
give that to us?
It was a gift.
So countries just
exchange gifts like that?
If they like each other.
There's Elaine.
JERRY: See that guy
she's talking with?
That's her new boyfriend.
Really?
He works here
in the office?
Yeah. They're having
a little fling,
so don't say anything
to anyone.
Who am I gonna tell,
my mother?
Like I have nothing better
to talk about.
You don't.
He's a recovering alcoholic.
Really?
Yeah, he's been off the wagon
two years.
"Off the wagon"?
I think it's "off the wagon."
I think it's
"on the wagon."
[SCOFFS]
Jerry, George,
what are you
doing here?
What am I doing here?
Ba-boom.
[GASPS]
My God!
My watch.
You found my watch.
Hey, keep your hands to yourself
if you know what's good for you.
Where'd you find it?
Under the sofa cushion.
And you stopped by
just to give it to me?
It's your Christmas present.
I thought
I'd never find it.
Well, today's
your lucky day.
No, today's
It'd be my first one.
Wanna work here?
What?
Yeah, one of the
readers just left.
There's a job opening.
Oh, Dick, this is Jerry,
and this is George.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Is this the guy?
"The guy"?
Dick.
How can you
just get it?
My boss told me to find someone.
I'm in charge of it.
All you have to do
is meet him. Come on.
But--
Come on. Hold my drink.
Cranberry juice?
And vodka. Come on.
I got the
cranberry juice.
[CHUCKLES]
So, uh...
You're Jerry.
So...I'm Jerry.
So have you
ever done
this kind
of work before?
Well, uh,
you know, book reports.
That kind of stuff.
Who do you read?
I like Mike Lupica.
Mike Lupica?
He's a sports writer
for the Daily News.
I find him very insightful.
No, no, no. I mean--
I mean authors.
Oh...
Well, a lot of good ones.
Lot of good ones.
I don't even want
to mention anybody
because I'm afraid I'm gonna
leave somebody out.
Name a couple.
Who do I like?
I like...
uh, Art Vandalay.
Art Vandalay?
He's an obscure writer.
Beatnik, you know,
from the Village.
Uh-huh.
What's he written?
Venetian Blinds.
I got news for you.
I'm funnier
than you are.
Why don't we get together New
Year's, watch some football?
Where's my drink?
There.
So how'd it go?
I think he's impressed.
Mmm. No, no, no.
This is just
cranberry juice.
Oh, um...
I think maybe Dick
picked up yours.
Dick?
He can't drink.
He's an alcoholic.
I told you
to hold it.
I didn't know you meant hold it.
I thought you meant hold it.
One drink like that,
and he could fall
right off the wagon.
Told you.
I never feel comfortable
in the women's department.
I feel like I'm just
a little too close
to trying on a dress.
Do I really have
to buy her something?
Hey, the woman
got you a job.
The least you could do
is buy her a gift.
How about this?
What is that,
cashmere?
Yeah, she loves
cashmere.
Who doesn't like cashmere?
Find me one person in the world
that doesn't like cashmere.
It's too expensive.
Wow. Look at this.
It's $85,
marked down from 600.
Wow.
Uh, excuse me, miss.
WOMAN: Yes.
How come this sweater's
only $85?
Oh, here.
This is why.
What? I don't see anything.
See this red dot?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's damaged.
Well, it's not really damaged.
Wow. $85, huh?
Mm-hmm. There's no
exchanges on this.
You think she'd care
about the dot?
It's hard to say.
I don't even think
she'd notice it.
Can you see it?
Well, I can see it.
But you know
where it is.
You want me
to not look at it?
Pretend you didn't know
it was there.
Can you see it?
It's hard for me to pretend,
because I know where it is.
Well, just take an overview!
Can't you take an overview?
You want me to take an overview?
Please.
I see a very cheap man
holding a sweater
trying to get away
with something.
That's my overview.
JERRY: Yeah, so?
He's acting
very strangely.
I think he started
drinking again.
Oh, boy. Can you smell it?
No, I can't smell it.
Then he hasn't been drinking.
Oh, you don't always
smell from a drink.
Yes, you do.
What about one drink?
Would you smell
from one drink?
Yes, you would.
Whoa.
I'll prove it.
How?
Would you do me
a favor?
Okay.
Would you take a drink
and let us smell you?
You can smell me
without the drink.
No, no.
I suspect that
this guy I'm seeing
might be drinking,
but I can't smell it.
Come on.
Okay, well,
what am I drinking?
What do you got?
A bottle of Scotch
my uncle gave me,
Hennigan's.
It's been there
two years.
I've been using it
as a paint thinner.
All right.
I don't smell
anything.
We're too close
to the bottle.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
That is damn good Scotch.
I could do a commercial
for this stuff.
Mm.
Boy, that Hennigan
goes down smooth...
and afterwards,
you don't even smell.
That's right, folks.
I just had three shots
of Hennigan's,
and I don't smell.
Imagine, you can walk around
drunk all day.
That's Hennigan's,
the no-smell, no-tell Scotch.
Hello, everybody.
Hey, George, come here.
I'm gonna tell you
what I think.
Oh, I know you don't care
what I think,
but I'm gonna
tell you.
I think that
you are terrific.
That's all.
Mmh!
Thank you.
Hey, what's that?
It's an early
Christmas present.
A Christmas present?
That's right.
For who?
For you.
[GASPS]
Get out of here!
Say you got a big job interview
and you're a little nervous?
Well, throw back
a couple of shots of Hennigan's,
and you'll be
as loose as a goose
and ready to roll in no time.
And because it's odorless,
why, it'll be
our little secret.
♪ H-E-double-N-I-- ♪
Kramer.
JERRY: Kramer.
Yeah. That'll do.
[GASPS]
Oh, George,
this is beautiful.
Is this cashmere?
Of course it's cashmere.
Oh, I love cashmere.
Who doesn't?
Oh, God. George,
this must've cost a fortune.
Ah, money.
God, Jerry, how could you
let him spend so much money?
I tried to stop him.
I couldn't.
He just wants
to make people happy.
God, George, this is one
of the nicest things
anyone has ever
given me.
Ah, good. Good.
Listen, take it off, you know.
You're gonna wear it out
already.
It's for special occasions,
this thing.
Wow.
What's that red dot
on your sweater?
What?
Yeah, listen,
take it off.
I'm getting hot
just looking at it.
Oh, what is this?
It's like a red dot.
What? What red dot?
What are you
talking about?
GEORGE: Jerry,
come here for a second.
Do you see
anything here?
Hmm? Uh, I don't know.
Uh, I don't know.
What don't you know?
I don't know.
Well, do you see it
or don't you?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, say that again.
Do you see it
or don't you?
Do I see it or don't I?
That's the question.
[GASPS]
Now, what did you
ask me again?
[KRAMER SNORING]
You're still here.
You're a dynamo.
I can't believe I get paid
for this.
God.
Eh, I'll see you tomorrow.
How you doing?
Hello.
You had sex with
the cleaning woman
on your desk?
Who are you?
How did you do that?
Hennigan's.
Hennigan's?
I was sitting there
in the office,
and the cleaning woman comes in.
I've always been attracted
to cleaning women.
Cleaning women, chambermaids.
Yeah, chambermaids.
I'm attracted to them too.
Why is that?
It's a woman in your room.
So go ahead.
So, uh...
She starts vacuuming,
back and forth,
her hips swiveling,
her breasts, uh...
Convulsing?
I don't know.
I'm trying to help you.
So then I asked her
if she wanted a drink.
You don't drink.
I know, but I couldn't think
of anything else to say.
So you started
drinking.
So we started drinking,
and, uh...
I'll tell you,
I don't know if it was
the alcohol or the ammonia,
but the next thing I knew, she
was mopping the floor with me.
And how was it?
Well, the sex was okay,
but I threw up
from the Hennigan's.
Good thing the cleaning lady
was there.
ELAINE: Dick was fired.
You mean to tell me
I put that drink
6 inches over
to the right,
and none of this
would've happened?
You knew he was an alcoholic.
Why'd you put
the drink down at all?
What are you saying?
Not saying anything.
You're saying something.
What could I be saying?
You're not saying nothing.
You must be saying something.
If I was saying something,
I would have said it.
Why don't you say it?
I said it.
What'd you say?
Nothing.
It's exhausting being with you.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
Hey, let me
ask you something.
Did George
buy that sweater
knowing the red dot
was on it,
because
it was cheaper?
Okay.
You just gave me the answer.
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did. Yes, you did.
I saw your expression.
I didn't have an expression.
Uh-huh.
I have a deviated septum.
I have to--
I have to open my mouth
sometimes to breathe.
Uh-huh.
How much did he save?
Frankly,
I am shocked
that you could ask
such a question of me,
that you would think--
If I was--
The only surprise
was how
you could even
think of that.
That's what
you were seeing.
I have
to talk to you.
This cleaning woman's
turning the screws on me.
She-- She's pushing for
this whole relationship thing.
She keeps calling me.
She's threatening to go to the
boss and tell him everything.
I could lose my job.
I gotta do something.
[WHISPERS]
Elaine's in the bathroom.
She's wise to the whole
red dot thing.
She's asking me all kinds
of questions about it.
Did you tell her
anything?
No.
You swear?
I'm not swearing.
I don't wanna swear.
Come on, swear!
No.
Oh, you told her,
didn't you?
No, I--
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, George,
did you buy
that sweater
knowing the red dot
was on it
because you could get it
at a discount?
What?
D-did I what?
You did,
didn't you?
Elaine, I'm--
I'm shocked.
Here I go out
in the spirit
of the season
and spend
all my savings
to buy you
the most beautiful
Christmas sweater
I have ever seen
to show
my appreciation to you
at Christmas,
and this is the thanks
I get at Christmas.
[SCOFFS]
Well, Jerry told me
that you did.
How could you tell her?
You squealed on me.
What kind of friend are you?
I didn't tell her,
you stupid idiot.
She tricked you!
Elaine, you don't
understand.
I had a 103 temperature
when I bought that sweater.
I was so dizzy, I was
seeing red dots everywhere.
I thought everything in
the store had a red dot on it.
I couldn't distinguish
one red dot from the other.
I couldn't afford
anything.
I have nothing.
I haven't worked
for a really long time.
I-- I mean, look,
I-- I have no clothes.
Look at what
I'm wearing.
[CRYING]
It was just
a little red dot,
a little red dot.
This is for you.
Oh, Georgie,
you bought this for me?
Oh, I knew you cared for me.
As you care for me,
which is why it's very important
that you never breathe
a word to anyone about, uh...
you know?
What with Clarence Thomas
and everything.
Okay, okay.
Can I open it now?
Of course. Go ahead.
My guess is you're gonna
like this very much.
[GASPS]
Is that cashmere?
Of course it's cashmere.
Oh!
Oh, a cashmere sweater.
Oh, Georgie Porgie.
Just a
little something
for Christmas.
[SIGHS]
When I was a little girl
in Panama,
a rich American
came to our town,
and he was wearing the softest,
most beautiful sweater.
I said,
"What do you call
this beautiful fabric?"
and he said,
"They call it cashmere."
I repeated the word.
"Cashmere, cashmere,"
and I asked him if I could
have it,
and he said,
"No. Get away from me,"
[SOBBING]
and he started to walk away.
Oh, but I grabbed onto his leg,
screaming for him
to give me the sweater,
and he dragged me
through the streets.
Oh, and then he kicked me
with the other foot,
and he threw some change at me.
Ah,
but I didn't want
the change, Georgie.
[GASPING]
I wanted the cashmere.
I had a feeling
you would like it.
I'm going
to try it on.
No, no, no.
Don't try it on now.
Try it on later.
Oh, no, look.
It fits beautiful.
All right. Take it off.
You're gonna ruin it.
What's this?
I was in a men's room
the other day.
They had the hand blower
instead of the paper towels.
You know this thing?
I like the hand blower,
I have to say.
Takes a little bit longer,
but I feel when you're in a room
with a revolting stench,
you wanna spend as much time
as you can.
MAN: The only stench
is coming from you.
Oh, well, wait a second.
I believe we have a heckler,
ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, Dick, look.
I don't know
what your problem is.
It's not my fault
you're back on the wagon.
It's "off the wagon."
Well, in the old days,
how do you think
they got the alcohol
from town to town?
I don't know.
On a wagon.
Don't you think they broke into
a couple of those bottles
along the way?
You can't drink on a wagon.
It's-- It'd be too bumpy.
They had smooth trails.
What about the Cumberland Gap?
What the hell do you know
about wagons?
Well, I know enough
not to get on them.
I'm gonna get
right to the point.
Uh...it's come
to my attention
that you and the
cleaning woman
have engaged
in sexual intercourse
on the desk
in your office.
Is that correct?
Who said that?
She did.
Was that wrong?
Should I not have
done that?
I tell you, I gotta plead
ignorance on this thing
because if anyone had said
anything to me at all
when I first started here
that that sort of thing
was frowned upon...
You know, because I've worked
in a lot of offices,
and I tell you,
people do that all the time.
You're fired.
Well, you didn't have to say it
like that.
I want you out of here
by the end of the day.
What about the whole
Christmas spirit thing?
Any flexibility there?
Nah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
She wanted me to give you this.
You had sex on your desk
with the cleaning woman.
You never had sex
in the office before?
No. I once made out
with someone,
but that's it.
Okay. All right.
So you made out.
Well, that's not sex.
Kissing is sex.
Kissing is not sex.
JERRY: George?
Jerry.
Hey...
Did Jerry leave that drink
next to Dick's on purpose?
No.
JERRY: George?
Over here.
What are you doing here?
I'm taking the kid
out to dinner,
to cheer him up.
Hey, Jerry,
when do you consider
sex has taken place?
I would say, uh...
when the nipple makes
its first appearance.
So, uh,
George told me
that you left the drink
next to Dick's on purpose.
Nice try.
So guess who
heckled me
at the club
last night?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[GASPS]
DICK: Merry Christmas!
Oh, my God, that's Dick.
Dick?
[BANGING, CLATTERING]
It's Cape Fear.
Hide. Hide under the desk.
Ow.
Ow!
Move over.
Get off of me!
I have no room.
I was here.
GEORGE: My foot's sticking out.
ELAINE: Shut up. He's coming.
Shh, shh, shh.
[ORNAMENTS TINKLING]
Is that cashmere?
GEORGE: Of course it's cashmere.
What's this?
But in a way,
I think I inadvertently
turned this guy
into an alcoholic,
and I hate being around
alcoholics
because they're either
telling you
how much they love you
or how much they hate you...
and those are the two statements
that scare me the most.
But I think he's okay now
because I don't know
how he feels about me.
He's finally off the wagon.
You mean "on the wagon."
Don't get smart.
[♪]