So I'm on the plane.
We left late.
Pilot says, "We're going to be
making up some time."
Isn't that interesting?
They just make up time.
That's why you have to
reset your watch when you land.
[LAUGHTER]
Of course when they say
they're making up time
obviously, they're increasing
the speed of the aircraft.
Now my question is,
if you can go faster
why don't you just go
as fast as you can
all the time?
Come on. There's no cops up
here. Nail it.
Give it some gas.
[APPLAUSE]
We're flying.
MAN: Traveling, of course,
is the best education.
[SLURRING SPEECH]
You know, last year
I was in over 40, 45
countries
and I would've gone to more,
but I'd just got a puppy.
And he was too young
to take with me.
But not now. I won't
travel without him.
Is he on the plane now?
Oh, yes.
Yes, he's in
the baggage compartment.
I don't know why they won't
let him sit up here with me.
He's a lot better behaved
than most of the dregs
you find onboard here.
You have any pets?
Just my next-door neighbor.
Well, you are missing out
on a relationship
that could enrich
your life
in ways that you never
even thought possible.
How about picking up
their-- You know?
You find that enriching?
What's the matter?
Oh, I'm feeling
a bit queasy.
MAN: Sir, we're gonna make
an emergency landing
in Chicago and
get you to a hospital.
My dog.
What about my dog?
You have a dog?
Do you know anyone
on the plane, Mr. Palone?
Jerry.
Huh?
How you feeling?
Would you take care of Farfel?
Farfel?
It's his dog.
We're landing in Chicago
to get him to a hospital.
Could you take his dog
to New York?
The dog?...The dog?
I'm sure it's only
for a day or two.
But, you know--
What if, you know?
Give me your address
and phone number. I'll call you.
The dog?
[GRUNTS AND GROWLS]
Let go, Farfel.
[DOG GROWLS]
Let go. Give me that.
Give me that sneaker,
you stupid idiot.
[LOUD BARKING]
Shut up!
So, what would you do?
It's only been three days.
I'm sure he's gonna call.
[LOUD BARKING]
Stop it! Shut Uuuup!
Do you believe this?
Do you believe what
I'm dealing with here?
I got a wild animal
in the house.
He'd deranged. Maybe he's got
rabies. I can get lockjaw.
If only.
Look at this place.
He's going everywhere.
I can't go out of the
house at night.
I haven't performed
in three days.
This will be my first night
out since I got back.
Hey, when you
walk him, do you...?
Do I what?
Do you pick it up?
Yes, I pick it up.
You pick it up?
Well, you have to.
Oh, boy, would
I love to see that.
[BARKING]
Shut up!
Shut up, Farfel! Stop it!
I don't know what to do.
What if I take it to the pound,
and then the guy shows up?
Maybe you should call
the airline.
They might know where he is.
No, I tried.
They don't know anything.
You gotta put
the syrup in first.
No, milk.
I'm telling you.
The guy's a drunk.
He's probably on
a bender.
What is a bender anyhow?
I don't know. They drink and
they bend things at the bar.
I don't know.
I can't believe
he hasn't called.
Two hundred seats
on a plane
I gotta wind up next to Yukon
Jack and his dog Cujo.
[BARKING]
Shut up!
One more day,
and you are pound-bound!
Hey, I'm sorry. I can't
watch the dog tonight.
Why?
We're going
to the movies.
We're gonna see
Prognosis Negative.
I can't. I gotta get
this Ellen out of my life.
You're breaking up?
Oh, yeah.
The sooner the better.
I can't wait to do it.
You know some people you
worry about whether or not
you're gonna hurt
their feelings?
With her, I'm
looking forward to it.
Boy, I'd like to
get it on video.
Watch it in slow motion
and freeze-frame it.
Kramer, I don't know how you
lasted as long as you did.
You didn't like her?
If you could
see her personality
it'd be like one of the
Elephant Man exhibits
you know where they pull off the
sheet and everyone gasps.
I can't believe someone
hasn't killed her yet.
How come you never said
anything?
You can't tell someone how you
feel about their girlfriend
till after they stop--
I tell you.
You. I'm talking about people.
[BARKING]
Are we still going
to the movies tonight?
No, I can't.
I gotta watch Farfel.
You and George can
go without me.
Just me and George?
Sure.
But we need you.
What do you need me for?
[DOOR BUZZER]
Because.
Yeah?
GEORGE:
Prognosis Negative!
Because I relate to
George through you.
We're more like
friends-in-law.
Besides, we said we'd see
Prognosis Negative together.
Can't you put some
newspapers down or something?
No, I can't trust him.
He gets insane.
I won't enjoy myself.
[BARKING]
That's right, Farfel,
I'm talking about you!
Just me and George alone?
Let's go, people. Let's go.
It's Prognosis Negative time.
I can't go.
You can't go? Why not?
Because I have to
watch idiot Farfel.
I thought Kramer was
watching him.
He's breaking up with his
girlfriend.
What's the problem?
Just put newspaper down.
No, I don't want that smell
in the house.
You spritz a little
Lysol on it--
No.
It's like BO and cologne.
They combine forces into some
kind of strange mutant funk.
So we're not going?
Nah. You two go.
Oh... You still wanna go?
Do you?
If you want.
It's-- It's up to you.
Go ahead.
Well, I really wanted to see
Prognosis Negative with Jerry.
You wanna see Ponce de Leon?
Ponce de Leon?
Okay.
You sure you don't wanna go?
I want to, but I can't.
Oh! I tell you what.
How about if I come back here
first and I clean everything up?
And I open up the windows,
and if you're still
not satisfied
we can switch apartments
for the night.
No.
What about this--?
Forget it.
Go ahead. You'll
have a good time.
I know. It's not that.
I just want you to go.
Well, thank you very much.
[BARKING]
I'm telling you, one more day,
stink breath!
On my block, a lot of people
walk their dogs
and I always
see them walking along with
their little poop bags,
which to me is just
the lowest function
of human life.
If aliens are watching this
through telescopes
they're gonna think the dogs
are the leaders.
If you see two life forms,
one of them is making a poop
the other one's
carrying it for him.
Who would you assume
is in charge?
So how long did
you live there?
About three years.
That's pretty long.
It's not that long, really.
Yeah.
Do you--?
So--
And then you came here.
Yeah.
So I've been here
about six years.
'86, '87, '88,
'89, '90
'91.
Yep.
JERRY:
Bad dog.
[GROWLS]
Bad dog!
You go outside!
[BARKING]
Outside!
What do you want from
me? Tell me.
[BARKING]
Money? You want money?
I'll give you money. How much?
I must have been out of my mind.
Look at you.
Why don't you do something
with your life?
You sit around here all day.
You contribute nothing
to society!
You're just taking up space!
I mean, how can I be
with someone like you?
Wouldn't respect myself.
GEORGE: I like herbal tea.
Chamomile's good.
Lemon Lift.
Almond Pleasure.
Jerry likes Morning Thunder.
Jerry drinks Morning Thunder?
Yeah.
Morning Thunder has
caffeine in it.
Jerry doesn't drink
caffeine.
Jerry doesn't know Morning
Thunder has caffeine in it.
You don't tell him?
No.
And you should see him.
Man, he gets all hyper.
He doesn't even know why.
He loves it.
He walks around going,
"God, I feel great!"
You don't tell him?
No.
That is so funny.
I know.
Have you ever seen
him throw up?
[GRUNTING NOISES]
KRAMER:
Please!
I take it all back!
Everything. I take it all back!
Every word!
I love you!
I can't live without you!
I'll do anything!
[BARK]
JERRY: That's right.
Gavin Palone.
What? You're sure?
[BARKING]
He was released on Monday?
Last Monday?
Did he leave a phone number
or address?
Unbelievable.
Well, thank you. Thanks.
Thanks very much.
That's it, Farfel. Party's over.
Start packing up your little
squeeze toys, buddy boy.
You're checking out.
It was weird because George
and I get along so great
in so many situations
but this was the first time we
ever really went one-on-one.
One-on-one's a whole
different game.
Can't pass off.
The only time it wasn't
uncomfortable
was when we were
making fun of you.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello. Boy George, about time.
Beautiful. How soon?
Okay, here's the plan:
We take the dog to the pound,
we go right to the movies.
Right. You, me and Elaine.
Yes, all three of us.
I am going.
Okay, see you in five minutes.
♪ Going to the
Dog pound everybody ♪
♪ Going to the dog pound
Come on, now ♪
What?
Do you have to?
What am I supposed to do?
I don't want to do it.
I like dogs.
I'm not sure this is a dog.
You know the guy might have
just lost your number.
I'm in the book,
and I have a machine.
Jerry, do you know what they do
to dogs at the pound?
They keep them there for a week.
And the if nobody claims them,
they kill them.
Really?
How late are they open?
What?
What is it?
I went back with Ellen.
Oh. That's great.
Oh. Great.
Terrific.
Yeah.
I really think you guys
are good together.
Yes. She understands you,
and she is not demanding.
Do you think that I forgot
what you two said about her?
We're just trying to be
supportive.
Yes.
We knew you
were upset--
From now on when we pass
each other in the hall,
I don't know you,
you don't know me.
Oh, Kramer.
We didn't mean it.
What are you doing?
I'm getting my pot.
Kramer, we like her.
Kramer.
What did we say
that was so bad?
I believe I referred
to her personality
as a potential
science exhibit.
I said, "How come
no one's killed her?"
Well.
Probably shouldn't have
said anything.
I mean, everybody knows
the first breakup never takes.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
GEORGE:
Prognosis Negative.
[BARKING]
Great. Okay, Farfel,
put your shoes on.
Jerry, can't you just give it
one more day?
It's not his fault.
It's not my dog.
I don't know where
this booze hound is.
All right, I tell you what.
How about if you and George
go to the movies
and I stay here and
watch the dog tonight?
I can't let you do that.
What about Prognosis Negative?
We'll see it Sunday.
Tonight's the night, right?
Prognosis Negative.
I'm not going.
I'm gonna watch the dog.
What does this mean?
Well, we'll go see
something else tonight.
We'll see Ponce de Leon.
What is with this dog?
I thought we were
taking it to the pound.
She talked me into one more day.
Talk. I'm going to the bathroom.
Jerry, how long are you
gonna be in there?
I don't know,
regular human time.
Why don't you wait
and go at the movies?
Why shouldn't I go here?
Well, you know.
Sometimes it's good to get there
and make sure you get seats
and then go
to the bathroom.
And isn't it more fun
using the urinal?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, George.
Urinals are fun.
Can I go?
Hey, go.
Who's stopping you?
What, are you doing
me a favor?
Like we care if you go
to the bathroom.
How's it going?
Good.
You?
Things are good.
[WHISTLING]
[SQUEAKS]
Boy, he takes
such a long time.
I know.
You know what he does
in there? He gargles.
Jerry gargles?
That why he takes so long?
Yeah, he does it
like six times a day.
How come we never
hear him?
Because he does it quiet.
He does it quiet.
Look it--
Just like this.
Watch.
[LAUGHS]
Wait, wait. Did you ever
see him throw up?
We talked about
that already.
Oh.
I have nothing to say
to anybody anymore.
I'm so uninteresting.
I'm think I'm out of
conversation.
So why do you call me
six times a day?
All I know about is sports.
That's it.
No matter how
depressed I get,
I could always read
the sports section.
I could read the sports section
if my hair was on fire.
You know what,
Ponce de Leon is sold out.
JERRY:
It is. Oh, yeah,
you're right.
What else is playing?
Nothing except
Prognosis Negative.
Boy, I know she really wants
to see that with me.
Give me that jacket, mud face.
[DOG GROWLING]
This is not Seinfeld
you're dealing with.
When I get
through with you,
you'll be begging
to go to the pound.
[PHONE RINGS]
[DOG BARKING]
Shut up.
Shut up!
Hello?
No. Who's calling?
Oh, my God. The dog guy.
Well, where have you been?
Yeah? Well, you better pick up
your dog tonight,
or he has humped
his last leg.
I could understand if there was
something else playing,
but it's this
or nothing.
I don't know
what to do.
What is this saving movies
thing?
Something's playing, you go.
I know. I know.
So, wh-what, are we gonna
do nothing now?
This is crazy.
It is kind of silly.
Of course it is.
I mean,
it's just a movie, God's sake.
Exactly.
It's not like
she's in the movie.
Right.
You know, we're supposed
to ruin the night
because she
wants to see it?
If I could have seen it
with her, fine.
But I can't control all these
circumstances and schedules
and people's availabilities
of movies.
And she'll
still see it.
You're not stopping her
from seeing it.
How does sitting
next to a person
in a movie theater increase
the level of enjoyment?
You can't talk
during a movie.
You know, this is stupid.
Come on. Let's just go.
Good.
Saving movies.
Ridiculous.
Two for Prognosis Negative.
Phhh!
I'm in big trouble.
Oh, you're dead.
[DOG BARKING]
Bell's Palsy.
The entire side
of my--
O-o-of my--
Of my face
was paralyzed.
[DOG BARKS]
Farfel.
Look, I couldn't--
I couldn't--
I couldn't even
feed myself.
I was completely
incapacitated.
[DOG BARKS]
Quiet, Farfel!
Farfel.
You know, it's interesting
because I called
the hospital,
and they said you were
released on Monday.
Y-y-y-yes, yes,
that's true...
but then, you see, I was taken
to the Bell's Palsy Center, see?
In-- In-- In--
In Rockville.
Absolutely first--
First-rate facility.
Top-- Top-notch
ph-physicians.
KRAMER:
Hey, come on. Come on.
Get off me.
He won't hurt you.
He's just playing.
Now you keep that mutt
away from me.
Mutt? I'll wager his parents
are more pure than yours.
ELLEN:
Kramer, are you coming?
Oh, hi, Ellen.
Get in here.
Listen, it's really
been a pleasure
taking care of
your dog for a week,
but if you don't mind.
Pr-Pr-Prediction:
You'll be calling me to ask
if you can come and visit him
before the month is out.
Prediction:
I never see you or him again
for the rest of my life.
ELAINE:
We made plans.
Why don't we
just rent a movie?
Well, I thought you wanted
to see Prognosis Negative.
No. It's supposed to be
really bad. Really bad.
I mean, it's long.
There's no story.
It's so
unbelievably boring.
I heard. I...
Jerry, you promised me
we'd go.
Well, George told me
the whole story, line for line.
I almost feel like
I've seen it already
and walked out on it.
Wait, wait.
George saw the movie?
I saw him yesterday.
He didn't mention it.
You and George
got together?
Yeah. I wanted to talk about how
we had nothing to talk about.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello.
Hi, hi, hi,
hi, hi.
What's up?
Well, uh...
you were right.
About what?
Ellen.
We, uh...
broke up again.
Aww.
Too bad.
I thought
she was the one.
I'll bring back the pot.
Okay, come on.
It's movie time.
No.
Hey, what are you gonna see?
Prognosis
Negative.
Hey, that's supposed
to be great.
It's not.
Well, how do
you know?
I have an instinct
for these things.
I had a parakeet
when I was a kid.
That was the only pet
that I really enjoyed.
We used to let him
out of his cage,
and he would fly around.
And my mother had built
one entire wall of
our living room was mirrored,
she felt this gives you
a feeling of space.
Have you ever heard this
interior-design principle?
The mirror makes it seem like
you have entire other room.
What kid of jerk walks up
to a mirror and goes,
"Hey, look. There's a whole
other room in there"?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"There's a guy in there,
looks just like me."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
But the parakeet
will fall for this.
You let him out of his cage.
He flies around.
Bang! With his little head.
He would just go:
[CLICKS]
"Oh!"
And I'd always think,
even if he thinks
the mirror is another room,
why doesn't he at least
try and avoid hitting
the other parakeet?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]