Do you think
that the security guards
in the art museums
really ever stop anybody
from taking the paintings?
I mean, are they going up to...
"Hey, hey, hey,
"where do you think
you're going with that?
"Hey, come over here.
Come over here.
Give me that Cézanne."
I mean, look at the job
that this man is hired to do.
He's getting $5.00 an hour
to protect millions of dollars
of priceless art,
with what?
He's got
a light mocha brown uniform
and a USA Today.
This is what he's got.
I mean, crooks must
look at this guy and go,
"All right, all we've got to do
"is get past the folding chair
and the thermos of coffee,
we can get a Rembrandt."
Kramer,
would you hold still?
I can't do this
if you keep moving.
You're sure you don't want me
to take my clothes off?
Because I'll do it.
No, that's the last thing
in the world
I want you to do.
Well, why don't you
take your clothes off.
I don't know.
I don't think
Jerry would like that.
Well, it'll be
our little secret.
GEORGE: God!
[BANGING]
Aah!
Button fly!
Why do they put buttons
on a fly?
It takes 10 minutes
to get these things open!
I like the button fly.
What?
That is one place
on my wardrobe
I do not need sharp,
interlocking metal teeth.
That's like a mink trap
down there.
I'm going to develop
kidney problems.
What are you doing today?
Nothing.
I have to go meet Nina.
You want to come
up to her loft,
check out her paintings?
I don't get art.
There's nothing to get.
No, it always has to be
explained to me,
and then I have to have someone
explain the explanation.
She does a lot
of abstract stuff.
In fact, she's painting
Kramer right now.
What for?
She sees something in him.
Well, so do I,
but I wouldn't
hang it on a wall.
Are you getting
the eyes?
Because they're brown.
Really, they're dark brown,
like rich Colombian coffee.
Tell me about Elaine.
You know, she and Jerry
were a big thing,
like Abe Lincoln and Mary Todd.
But they're still friends.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
They're like this.
Don't you think that's strange?
Why? What's the difference?
Well, are you still friends
with any of your ex-girlfriends?
Well, you know, I...
I have many relationships.
I'll tell you,
I'm a little nervous.
Why?
You know, the friend
meeting the new woman.
I feel like I'm getting
fixed up for a friendship.
I don't know how long
this is going to last.
Really?
Yeah.
I thought
you liked her.
I do, but she's got, like,
a jealousy thing.
I mean, she doesn't like me
having fun with anyone but her.
You know, it's a miracle
you're not married.
Hey, I'm not obligated
to buy anything, am I?
Hi, Nina.
Hi.
This is my friend George.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Hey, look at this guy!
I brought George up
to see some of your paintings.
Oh. Are you
interested?
Uh...
Yeah, sure.
Sure, I'm interested.
George,
you going to buy a painting?
Yeah, sure.
Are you
an art lover?
I'm an art adorer.
I adore art.
Great. Well, uh,
take a look around.
Pick something out
you like.
May I?
[LAUGHING]
Get out of here.
Here. Play with this.
What's this?
My father gave me four tickets
to the Yankee game
for Saturday afternoon.
Owner's box,
first row behind the dugout.
Oh, Saturday. I'm working.
I'm going out of town.
Oh. Well, I'm not going
to go without you.
Hey, you guys want them?
Yeah.
They're right behind
the dugout, George,
first row.
Right behind the dugout?
Are you kidding?
How did you get them?
Oh, my father's
the Yankees' accountant.
It's the owner's box.
All my life,
I've dreamed
of sitting front row,
behind the dugout.
You like that one?
GEORGE:
Look at where we are!
He's not stopping.
He just keeps going
and going and going.
GEORGE: We're not
in the first row?
USHER: No, no.
These are your seats.
She said first row,
right behind the dugout.
Well, it's the second row.
It's just as good.
I was all primed
for the first row.
I was going to put
my feet on the dugout.
Will you shut up?
These are...
These are great.
You can't get
any better than this.
Oh, there's better.
Right there.
That's better.
All right.
Oh, boy.
All right,
who wants a dog?
Yeah. Here you go.
What a great day.
I could have been
at my boss' son's bris
right now.
That's what you were
supposed to do today?
Yeah.
Huh.
What makes him think
anyone wants to witness
a circumcision?
I'd rather go
to a hanging.
Is it that unattractive
to have to take it off?
Have you ever seen one
with it?
No.
You wouldn't even know
what it was.
Anyway, I called him back.
I told him
I had to go visit my father
in the hospital in Maryland.
You better catch it
here, Charlie,
because this ain't
Philadelphia!
George?
Yeah?
Hi. I'm Leonard West.
Nina's father.
Oh, hi, hi, Mr. West.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is my friend Elaine.
Hi.
Hey, .230 ain't going to
cut it in this town, babe!
Hee hee! Ha ha!
And this is Kramer.
Oh, hey,
how you doing?
[APPLAUSE]
Yes! Yes!
How are the seats, huh?
Uh, okay.
Great. They're great.
I hear you bought
one of Nina's paintings.
Yeah, it's, uh...
It's being framed
right now.
I don't even know
what it costs.
Not, uh...
Not too expensive,
is it?
Not if you have
a lot of money.
It was cheaper for me
when she was an actress.
Well...
[CROWD GASPS]
Well...enjoy the game.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh, I think you'd better
take off the Orioles cap.
Yeah. I better.
No, no, no, seriously.
You're in
the owner's box.
I don't think
it's a good idea.
You're not serious.
Yes, yes, yes, I am.
Did he say that?
No, no, but he
gave me the seats,
and I don't think
he'd like it
if you wore
an Orioles cap.
Yeah, well, maybe
you should ask him.
I don't have
to ask him.
Now, are you going to
take the hat off or not?
No, I'm not going to
take it off.
Why should I?
That's ridiculous.
Just take
the cap off.
George, I am
at a baseball game.
This is America.
Look, look, either
you take the cap off
or you leave.
Well, I don't care.
I'm not taking it off.
Elaine, just
take the cap off.
No! Get off of my hat!
What do you mean?
Come on! Stop it!
Just take it off!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
All right, okay,
all right, let's go.
Oh, my God!
Hey.
All right,
get your hands off of me.
I'm leaving.
Wait a minute.
We just got here.
Uh, do you want us
to go with you?
Oh, no, George,
you stay.
Well, I was
just thinking...
Yeah, yeah. Stay!
All right, all right,
we'll go, we'll go.
And then the ball
hits him in the head
and he falls
right over the railing.
Is he okay?
Well, yeah,
he's fine.
We took him
to the emergency room, you know.
The x-rays were all negative.
It was...
It was quite a day.
This is the most amazing story
I've ever heard.
Why did he want you
to take off the baseball cap?
That is so insane.
I know.
Can you imagine that?
Hey.
How you feeling?
Oh, yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Hiya, Carol.
Hey, look.
We made the paper.
Huh? Look at this.
Page two,
sports section.
We're all
in the picture.
Picture?
Picture.
Our picture's in there?
Yeah.
What?
[GASPS]
I cannot believe this.
There's George.
Yeah. Look at him.
Oh, my God,
Lippman could see this.
He thinks I was
visiting my father.
Oh, my God.
I make up
one little white lie,
and they put my picture
in the paper!
Hi, Mr. Lippman.
How's your father?
My-- My father.
Yeah. Yeah.
You went to see him,
right?
Yeah, yeah, I, uh...
I went to visit him.
Uh-huh.
So, what was wrong with him?
Well, you name it.
You know, uh...
Uh...
neuritis, uh, neuralgia.
But he's feeling better now,
right?
Um, yes. Yeah, it's just...
It's such a miracle.
You know, my visit
must have boyed his spirits.
Uh-huh.
"Boo-eed."
What did I say?
You said "boyed."
I did?
Yeah.
[CONTINUES TO
FORCE LAUGHTER]
Well, I got a plane to catch.
Oh. Where are you going?
Going to Houston
for a few days.
Publishers' convention.
Ah.
Can I have
my sports section?
Wh-- Uh...
Sports section.
Ah. Yeah.
I'm saving it
for the plane.
I never miss a Sunday
sports section.
Well, you know,
there's nothing to read.
It's yesterday's
news.
Yeah, well...
You know, the Yankees won,
the Mets lost,
Rickey Henderson's unhappy.
Right, right.
What are you doing?
Oh, God.
That is the third time today
I have done that.
Blah!
I keep, you know,
grabbing newspapers
and just tugging at them.
Well, got to go.
Okay.
Yes, well, you know,
have a nice trip,
and, um...
Alrighty.
Um, uh, I'll just hold down
the, uh, fort.
Oh.
WOMAN:
I sense great
vulnerability,
a man-child
crying out for love,
an innocent orphan
in the postmodern world.
I see a parasite,
a sexually depraved
miscreant
who is seeking only to gratify
his basest
and most immediate urges.
She was a guest
of my father's.
She should have
taken the cap off.
It's preposterous
to ask someone
to take off a baseball cap
at a baseball game.
How can you defend that?
His struggle
is man's struggle.
He lifts my spirit.
He is a loathsome,
offensive brute...
yet I can't look away.
Look, I'm really
getting tired
of all this fighting.
Maybe we should end this
before we really start
hating each other.
Oh, well,
you wouldn't want that,
because you always
have to remain friends.
Well, I like
to remain friends
with people
I was friends with.
Hey, why don't you
just go, then?
Oh, and give this
to George.
Tell him
he owes me $500.
He transcends
time and space.
He sickens me.
I love it.
Me too.
Five hundred dollars?
What?
That's what she told me.
I'm not paying $500 for this.
It's a piece of junk.
That's what it costs.
Why did you even
take it?
You broke up with her.
I wasn't thinking. I don't know.
You weren't thinking.
Well, I mean, she framed it
and everything.
Well, I'm not buying this.
No way. Forget it.
No way I'm buying this.
I mean, look at it.
What is it?
It's a bunch
of squiggly lines.
Are you telling me
you couldn't paint this?
Do you want me
to paint you something?
I'd love to paint you something.
I'm not paying for this.
If you were going out with her,
it would be a different story.
This was in front of your door.
Oh.
Hey, Kramer.
Hi, Mike.
Wow. A letter from Nina.
Whoa! Man.
That is the ugliest thing
I've ever seen.
Oh, my God.
What?
This is amazing.
You can't believe this.
What's it say?
Listen to this.
"I don't know
"what you expect
to find out there, Jerry.
"You know what you want
better than me.
"But there's one thing
I do know.
"I know I can stand here
watching you try to destroy
"everything I've ever wanted
in my life,
"wanting to smash your face
with my fists
"because you won't even
make the slightest effort
"to opt for happiness
"and still know that I love you.
"You mean so much to me
"that I'm willing to take
all your abuse and insults
and insensitivity."
Wow.
She's deep.
"Because that's
what you need to do
"to prove
I'm not going to leave you.
"I'm sick and tired
of running
"from places and people
and relationships.
You want me,
then fight for me--"
[KRAMER BLOWS NOSE]
"Because I'm sure as hell
fighting for you.
I think
we're both worth it."
You know, Jerry,
she sounds like a poet.
Boy, no one's ever written me
a letter like this.
Maybe I was wrong about her.
Get up. Go.
Get in there
and give her a call.
Pick up the phone
and call her.
Should I?
Yes, you're damn right
you should!
Fight for her, Jerry!
She's sure the hell
fighting for you!
All right!
I'll call her!
Don't go in there.
You're going to get shot.
[GUNSHOT]
I told you.
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
Yeah.
It's George.
Come on up.
Well, now we got
to get a posse together.
I love a good posse.
What's the appeal
of the posse?
The appeal of the posse?
The posse has tremendous appeal.
Get away from the job,
you camp out,
you're with friends...
I mean, come on,
it's a week-long game
of hide-and-go-seek
on horseback.
Hello, George.
Hey. Hey, Nina.
Hey...
I owe you some money,
don't I?
Well, I really
love that piece.
Yeah, oh, me too.
Me too. Boy,
oh, boy, oh, boy.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, in fact,
I've been thinking about it,
and, you know, I feel
like I'm stealing from you.
Five hundred dollars.
This is going to be worth
thousands soon.
You know, on...
On second thought,
I can't even accept it.
No, no, no, no, George.
A deal's a deal.
You know, I want you to have it.
This could be
in a museum someday.
It's not safe with me.
It should really be
in a doorman building.
Honestly, George,
the money's not important.
Who said anything about money?
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
Yeah.
It's Elaine.
Come on up.
Elaine?
Yeah.
This person does not believe
in telephones, does she?
She likes the pop-in.
I've told her how
I hate the pop-in.
He likes the pop-in too.
Just popped in now.
I'm a big pop-in guy.
He is.
What about Kramer?
Oh, huge pop-in guy.
Well, I was
leaving anyway.
So, uh, we're on
for tomorrow?
Yeah.
Okay.
Bye.
Hello.
Chatty gal.
Lippman's coming back tomorrow.
I'll be fired.
Oh, if he noticed it,
he would've called you
from Houston.
No. He wants to torture me.
[CHANGING CHANNELS]
Will you give me the clicker?
I hate it
when you have the clicker.
You're too fast.
Get out!
I'm a great clicker.
I have great instincts.
How dare you
impugn my clicking?
You're all over the dial.
You don't know what you want.
I've never seen you
stay on anything
longer than five seconds.
Just give me that.
Let go.
No, come on. I want it, Jerry.
Let go, Elaine!
Then let George do it!
Oh, George can't click!
Give it to me!
Give it! Give it!
Give it!
Pinheads.
WOMAN [SOBBING]:
Maybe I can't...
analyze and theorize
and...
speculate on
why we've been--
[CHANGES CHANNEL]
Wait. Wait a second.
Go back to that.
...you read
all those books,
not me.
That's Chapter Two.
It's Neil Simon.
But one thing
I do know.
I know how I feel.
Wait a second.
Wait a second!
What?
Oh, my God.
The letter.
That's the letter!
What letter?
This is the letter
she wrote to me!
She stole it
right from the movie!
Because you don't
even make...
The slightest effort
to opt for happiness
and still know
that I love you!
This is incredible.
I always thought
there was something funny
about this letter.
She's copied it
right out of Chapter Two.
She's a thief, a bunco artist.
Maybe I won't send her
that check.
You know,
it's not really that terrible.
What are you
talking about?
She completely
misrepresented herself.
"I don't opt
for happiness."
I opt for happiness.
James Caan doesn't opt
for happiness.
Yeah. Yeah.
But she wouldn't
take the cap off?
No.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
But didn't she know
they were
the owner's seats?
Oh, that's unbelievable.
Yeah, okay.
All right, Lenny.
Thanks again.
Take care.
That's Lenny West,
my accountant,
who's a hell of a guy.
Aha.
And he handles
the Yankees too.
It's his biggest account.
Ah. Really.
So every once in a while,
they throw him
a couple of seats,
and last weekend,
he gave them to his daughter.
She's an artist,
by the way.
Anyway,
her daughter gives them
to some friends, you know?
One of her friends shows up
wearing a Baltimore cap.
Wha...?
You're from Baltimore,
right?
Oh, mm...
It's Towson,
Yeah.
and that's
near Baltimore--
Yeah, but you're
an Oriole fan, right?
Well, fan...
You know, my father--
Anyway, she refused
to take the cap off.
She caused a whole big scene.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so impudent.
Yeah, so Lenny
gave me the tickets
for tomorrow night.
I'm inviting Frank and Marsha.
I want you to come.
Oh, uh...
I-I've got plans, though,
Mr. Lippman--
Well, break them.
You missed the bris.
I want you at the game.
Okay. Okay.
Good.
Okay, Mr. Lippman.
Oh, and Elaine...
Yes?
You know
the Baltimore cap
you got in your office?
Wear it.
I'm going to have
a little fun with him.
That will be fun.
How's it coming?
Good. Good.
Seen any
good movies lately?
No, not really.
You?
No.
I like a good comedy...
You know,
like a Neil Simon.
You like Neil Simon?
Neil Simon?
Uh, some of his stuff.
I've seen most of it.
I guess my favorite
would have to be, uh...
Chapter Two.
Have you ever seen that?
I don't know. Maybe.
I have.
Funny. Funny.
In fact, it was on TV
just the other night.
Happened to catch it.
[KNOCKING]
I couldn't help
but notice
a stunning similarity...
Well, we've made
our decision.
We want the Kramer.
GEORGE: Five thousand?
Why would anybody
buy Kramer for $5000?
[GEORGE LAUGHS]
Boy, the Yankees
cannot buy
a hit tonight.
So is it all over
between you
and Marsha Mason?
Yeah.
Oh, and by the way,
can you get this thing
out of my house?
Tell you what.
I'll make a deal with you.
I'll sell it to you right now
for 10 bucks.
Please.
ANNOUNCER:
Uh-oh.
Seems to be
a lot of trouble
in the area just behind
the Yankee dugout.
Behind the dugout?
That's where we were sitting
the other night.
Well, we're not
going to show it.
We don't want
to encourage
that kind of behavior.
It's a young lady,
and, boy,
she's really going at it
with the security guard.
She's a feisty one.
Now they're getting
the other security guard
to come down.
How do you like that,
Seaver?
Boy, she's something,
and a Baltimore fan
at that.
Holy cow.
Then, when I was 17,
I ran away from home
and hopped a steamship
to Sweden.
Mm.
This steak is excellent,
by the way.
More potatoes?
Yeah, yeah, sure. Please.
Yes, yes.
Go on. Go on.
You hopped a steamship
to Sweden.
Mm-hmm, and...
it was a big one.
But, uh,
baseball season's starting.
I'm very excited about that.
Did you ever sneak down
to better seats at the game
and get caught by the usher?
When you're a kid,
it doesn't matter,
because you're always getting
chased from everyplace anyway.
When you're an adult,
it's really embarrassing
to get caught.
You have to pretend
like there's some confusion,
so you put on this whole act.
You're looking at the tickets.
"I don't understand
how this could have happened.
"Let me see.
"Oh, I see the problem.
"These are very good seats.
I have very bad seats.
That's the misunderstanding."
[♪]