Women put on their perfume
in an interesting way.
I love watching them do that.
Do you ever notice that, guys?
They have those-- Their little
key, Stratego little areas.
♪ And la-da-da dah ♪
♪ Da-dah ♪
Places they think we're going.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
And they always hit this one.
Women are convinced that this
is the most action-packed area
that could ever happen
in the dating world.
What--? What is that, ladies?
What is happening here?
Is that in case you slap the guy
or something?
He still finds you intriguing?
Dsh!
"Oh! Chanel!"
GEORGE:
She's a pianist,
a classical pianist!
She plays the piano!
She-- She-- She's
a brilliant woman!
I-I-I sat in her living room,
she played the Waldstein Sonata.
The Waldstein!
♪ Da da da da da da da da da ♪
♪ Di da da da di ♪
[LAUGHS]
We-- W-We did a crossword
puzzle together in bed.
It was the most fun I ever
had in my entire life!
Do you hear me?
In my life!
You know?
Were you talking?
I couldn't hear anything.
I was telling you
about Noel.
Oh, Noel, yeah.
The one that plays
the bongos.
[SARCASTICALLY]
Ha ha ha.
So sidesplittingly funny.
All right, I'm sorry.
What about her?
What, you think I'm gonna
repeat the whole thing now?
I know, you told me
you like her.
Everything's going good.
No, everything's not going good.
I'm very uncomfortable.
I have no power.
Why should she have
the upper hand?
Once in my life,
I'd like the upper hand.
I have no hand,
no hand at all.
She has the hand.
I have no hand.
Hand me that, would you?
Yeah.
How do I get the hand?
We all want the hand.
Hand is tough to get.
You gotta get the hand
right from the opening.
She's playing a recital
this week
at the McBierny School.
You wanna hear her play?
I got two extra tickets.
You and Elaine could go.
Yeah, that sounds like
something.
Then afterwards, maybe we could
all go out together.
You know, she'll see me
with my friends.
She'll observe me as
I really am, as myself.
Maybe I can get some hand
that way.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Hey...
smell my arm.
What? No.
No, smell it. Smell it.
With all due respect,
I don't think so.
Jerry, smell.
That smells good.
What is that?
The beach.
The beach?
Yeah.
Did you go swimming?
It's 29 degrees out.
Nah, I just joined
the Polar Bear Club.
You joined the Polar Bears?
Yes.
What the hell is a Polar Bear?
Well, it's these people,
they go swimming in the winter.
They're-- They're terrific.
I just took my first swim today.
Ooh-ooh uh a-a-a-ah!
It's invigorating.
Yeah...
So is shock therapy.
[LAUGHS]
What is that, a PEZ dispenser?
Yeah.
Do you want one? Take it.
Hey.
I just bought it
at the flea market. You want?
Hey, what goes on there,
exactly?
You don't know?
No, I-I-- I know.
I know.
You think they have fleas there,
don't you?
No.
Yes, you do, Biff.
You've never been
to a flea market,
and you think
they have fleas there.
All right, I think
they have fleas there. So what?
Hey, you want this?
Oh, you don't want it?
No, I bought
five of them.
Oh, great. Thanks.
I don't know how
anyone does this.
This must be
so nerve-racking.
How do they warm up
their fingers?
They have a piano backstage
they warm up on.
No. We would have
heard it.
What do you think?
They just crack their knuckles
and come out?
I told her we'd all
go out afterwards, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Sure.
Don't applaud when she
stops playing the first time.
It's not over yet.
I really resent that.
That's directed at me,
isn't it?
[CLAPPING]
Is this okay?
Can I do this?
[ELAINE SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
[ELAINE STIFLING LAUGHS]
Ssssh.
[CHUCKLING]
Joe Gibbs--
[LAUGHING]
Oh, God.
Something I said?
It's... John Mollica.
Oh. Oh, John.
Oh, hi, John.
Hi.
What are you doing
out here?
Oh, I was just at
this recital and...
Jerry put this PEZ dispenser
on my leg,
and I just
started laughing.
Oh, Jerry's in there?
Yeah.
I heard you guys
broke up.
We did. We did.
We-- We're just
hanging out.
Really?
Boy...
you...
really look great.
Oh. Thank you.
Hey, are you still friends
with Richie, um, Appel?
Oh, Richie?
He's been doing comedy
in L.A.
for a couple of years.
He just got back
a month ago.
He's kind of messed up
on drugs.
Ooh.
I don't know what to do
for the guy.
Have you thought
about an intervention?
What's that?
You know, you get
all his friends in a room,
and they confront him
to try to get him into rehab.
It's a very
popular thing now.
Well, he'd never
listen to anyone.
Oh.
Except, of course,
Jerry.
He'd listen to Jerry.
Jerry would have to
be involved.
He really respects Jerry.
[APPLAUSE]
I'm sorry, George.
I'm sorry.
What did you put
the PEZ dispenser
on her leg for
in the first place?
I don't know.
It was an impulse.
What kind of
a sick impulse is that?
How could I know
she'd start to laugh?
ELAINE [CHUCKLING]:
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I am.
Could we just
go in already?
What are we
gonna tell her?
I'll tell her I was
the one who laughed.
No, don't say a word.
If she thinks my friends
are jerks, then I'm a jerk.
Oh. Remind me to talk to you
about something later.
What about?
Hey, hey hey.
We're discussing something.
I know, but I'm
distracted now.
Oh, what are you,
a baby?
All right, tell him.
When I was outside,
I ran into John Mollica.
Really? John Mollica?
Yeah.
The guy that used to bartend
at the comedy club.
How's he doing?
He's good.
Uh, could we
cut to the chase?
"Cut to the chase"?
Yeah.
Well, what are you,
Joe Hollywood?
A lot of people say it.
I would lose that.
Ah... What's that?
"Lose that"? That's not
a Hollywood expression.
Yes, it is.
Anyway.
So John told me that Richie
is in town from Los Angeles
and he's really
messed up on drugs.
So I told him he should do
an intervention.
Really?
An intervention?
You know, you people, we got
a situation over here!
Yeah... But he wants you
to be a part of it.
Why me?
He says Richie really
respects you,
and he would
listen to you.
Boy, these things are
really hard to load.
All right, okay,
all right.
I'm going in.
All right, we got to
talk about this.
All right.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi. Hi. Hi.
Oh, no.
You were wonderful. Wonderful.
Oh, no, no.
Oh, these are my friends,
Elaine and Jerry. Noel.
You play
a hell of a piano.
Yeah, I was really moved.
Really moved.
Well, didn't you hear
that person laughing?
I couldn't play.
I was humiliated!
Well, I'm sure
it wasn't at you.
Well, then what was
she laughing at?
PEZ?
Uh, no,
thank you.
Did you see her?
Yeah. Me?
No. I-I...
Anyone who would laugh
at a recital
is probably some sort of
lunatic, anyway.
I mean, only a sick,
twisted mind...
could be that rude
and ignorant.
Well, you know,
maybe some...
mental defective
put something stupid
on her leg.
Even if this so-called
mental defective...
did put something
on her leg,
Uh-huh.
she's still the one who laughed.
I'll never forget
that laugh
for the rest
of my life.
Well, I-I'm sure she would
apologize if she could.
Probably someone
is holding her back
maybe against every fiber
of her being.
Well, if she wants to continue
to have a fiber of her being,
she'll be very careful.
Don't hit me.
Stop it.
Come on.
Um...
All right.
So, uh...
you ready?
We'll, uh...
We'll go out, and we'll
have a bite to eat.
I... don't feel
like it tonight.
Uh...
We'll be outside.
Yeah.
It was nice meeting you.
Oh. Mm-hmm.
By the way, how do you, uh,
warm up your fingers
before you play?
I just crack my knuckles.
GEORGE:
Come on, we'll
have a good time.
Well, I'm really
not in the mood.
Aw, come on.
I said, I don't
feel like it.
Um, all right.
Uh...
I-- I-I'll--
I'll call you.
Uh, I'll call you,
and, uh...
we'll talk
on the phone.
Have a...
telephone communiqué.
[LAUGHS]
Um...
So, fine. Everything's fine.
Everything good?
Good. I feel good.
Fine.
That's fine. That's good.
Okay.
Okey-doke.
[DOOR SHUTS]
You know, I think Kramer might
have been indirectly responsible
for getting Richie involved
in drugs in the first place.
What? How?
A few years ago, the comedy club
had a softball team.
Kramer was our first baseman.
Uh-huh.
You couldn't get anything
by him. He was unbelievable.
Yeah.
Anyway, this one game,
we came back to win from,
like, eight runs behind.
Mm-hmm.
So Kramer says to Richie,
"Why don't you dump
the bucket of Gatorade
on Marty Benson's head?"
The club owner.
Yeah.
So Richie goes ahead
and does it.
So? What happened?
What happened?
The guy was, like, 67 years old.
It was freezing out.
He caught a cold,
developed pneumonia,
a month later,
he was dead.
Shut up.
All the comedians
were happy
because he's one of
these club owners
nobody liked,
anyway.
But Richie was
never the same.
What about Kramer?
He's the same.
JERRY:
Are you sure you want me, John?
I mean, I haven't spoken
to Richie in two years.
I don't have a good apartment
for an intervention.
The furniture,
it's very nonconfrontational.
All right,
all right.
Goodbye.
Remember Richie Appel?
Oh, sure.
The guy I told to pour
the Gatorade
that killed
Marty Benson.
Right. Well, John Mollica
is organizing
some kind of intervention
for him. We're having it here.
Can I get in on that?
What do you think,
it's like a poker game?
Is Elaine going?
Yeah.
Well, I knew him
as well as she did.
Yeah, but John invited her.
So wait. What're you saying?
You don't want me to intervene?
No, intervene, go ahead.
Intervene all you want.
I'm just afraid
you might be interfering
while we're intervening.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
Stop smelling your arm!
You know, I got a great idea
for a cologne.
It's called "The Beach."
You spray it on,
and it's just like you came home
from the beach.
Hmm. A cologne that smells
like the beach.
I can't believe
I'm saying this...
but that's not
a bad idea.
Tell me about it.
Why don't you call
Steve D'Giff?
He works in
the marketing department
at Calvin Klein.
Yeah.
In fact,
he's a good friend
of John Mollica
and Richie, also.
Okay.
Well, it's over.
It's definitely over.
She broke up with you?
No,
but she's going to.
I can sense it.
We had this
terrible phone conversation.
I was so nervous
before I called,
I made up this whole list
of things to talk about.
What was on the list?
Uh...
Let's see.
"I'm very good at going
in reverse in my car."
"Why isn't Postum
a more popular drink?"
Yeah, Postum
is underrated.
Anyway, there was
all this tension.
I asked her if she wanted
to go out to dinner
and she said, "No, maybe we
could get together for lunch."
Ha, you know
what that means.
What's wrong with lunch?
Lunch is fine
at the beginning,
then you move on
to dinner.
You don't go back
to lunch.
It's like
being demoted.
I'll never do
another crossword puzzle
with her again,
I know it.
I like the jumble.
You ever do the jumble?
I have no power,
don't you understand?
I need hand!
I have no hand!
Why don't you
break up with her?
What?
You break up with her.
You reverse everything that way.
Hmm, a preemptive breakup.
A preemptive breakup.
Mm?
This is an incredible idea.
Yeah.
I got nothing to lose.
We either break up,
which she would do anyway,
but at least I go out
with some dignity,
or I completely
turn the tables!
Yeah.
This is absolutely brilliant!
GEORGE:
So I'm afraid that I...
am gonna have to
break up with you.
You're breaking up with me?
Yes.
I...
am breaking up
with you.
[GASPS]
Wow.
Shocked?
I really am.
Never expected this,
did you?
I thought
everything was fine.
Well, live and learn.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, I don't understand.
You didn't enjoy being with me?
Didn't we have fun
doing the crossword puzzle?
Kind of.
[SIGHS]
I'm very confused.
Well, I didn't mean
to hurt you, kid.
I thought--
N-Now, stop it, please. This--
What do you want?
I know I can make you happy.
When-- When you're
playing the piano...
do you think about me?
Nnnn...
I don't know.
This is what
I'm talking about.
Okay. I'll think
about you.
All the time?
You know--
Okay.
All the time.
I can't hear you.
All the time!
See?
It's not so hard.
KRAMER:
Go ahead.
Smell. Smell it.
[SNIFFS]
Yeah? So?
Okay, now you recognize it?
I don't know.
The beach.
What are you talking about?
Oh,
I'm talking about
the beach.
What about it?
You know
the way you smell...
when you first come home
from the beach?
Well, I want to
make a cologne...
that captures...
the essence...
of that smell.
Oh, yeah.
That is the dumbest idea
I've ever heard.
Whoa.
Wait a minute.
You.
Did you hear
what I just said?
You think people are gonna
pay $80 a bottle
to smell like, uh...
dead fish and seaweed?
Mm-hmm.
That's why people
take showers
when they come home
from the beach.
It's an objectionable,
offensive odor.
So you don't think
that it's a good idea, hm?
[MUMBLES]
The membranes get dry,
and it just starts bleeding.
Since I was a kid, so I have to
stick a tissue up there.
Uh-huh.
You have to...
work like that?
Yeah. Nobody minds.
Nobody's ever
said anything to me.
There any ice cubes?
Uh, whatever's
in the freezer.
I looked.
I don't see any ice cubes.
Well, then I guess
there's no ice cubes.
I can't drink this.
It's warm.
[SLAM]
Hey, John,
shouldn't we rehearse
this a little
before Richie comes?
What's the plan?
Do I have to talk?
I don't feel like talking.
Well, if he's not
gonna talk,
then I don't want to.
No, we all have to talk!
What's the order?
We'll go in alphabetical order.
You're first, Roberta.
Why am I first?
Albano's your last name.
That's not my name anymore.
I'm divorced.
I'll go first.
Oh. Hey.
Hey.
Is this the interference?
Intervention.
What are you
doing here?
Oh, uh, is it all right
if I stay for the intervention?
He can't stay.
This is for close friends only.
Hey, I'm a friend.
Who do you think
told him
to pour the Gatorade
over Marty Benson's head?
Oh, let him stay.
Yeah.
Hey, you know, I got
somebody to make up
that cologne for me,
bigmouth.
Somebody's gonna
make that crap?
Kramer!
Hey, hey, you guys!
All right!
Hey, come on in.
Hey, these are some of
my Polar Bear buddies.
They can't stay.
You're having a party here?
No, we're having
an intervention.
An intervention?
Who's intervening?
He's a friend of ours
on drugs,
and we're gonna
confront him.
Oh, sure.
We used to do that when one of
our Polar Bears stopped coming.
We'd go to his house,
"What, you don't wanna be
a Polar Bear anymore?
It's too cold for you?"
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
It's him!
What do we do?
Hide!
It's not a surprise party!
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
It's not him.
[MUTTERING]
You don't wanna
go out with me
because I'm a bartender,
right?
Look...
you know,
I don't really think
that this is appropriate
right now.
Is it because I have
a tissue in my nose?
You're getting warm.
Hey, we just...
We just came from, uh,
Chadway's. What's going on?
We're having the intervention.
We're waiting for Richie.
Oh, right, right.
The intervention.
Um...
Should we leave?
Well, uh, I--
Elaine, hi.
Hi, Noel.
Well, you're
looking well.
Jerry, let me
tell you something.
A man without hand
is not a man.
I've got so much hand,
I'm coming out my gloves.
I got to thank Kramer.
Even if I were dragged
through manure...
I still wouldn't put
that stuff on.
This man is a genius!
A genius!
You think so?
No, I don't think so, I know so.
Come here. I gotta talk to you.
What?
The male kangaroo
doesn't have a pouch.
Only the female
has it,
so the male
has pouch envy!
[CHUCKLES]
"Why should she have
this huge pouch,
"and I have nothing?
"I have things
to carry too.
At least-- At least
give me a pocket."
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
[COUGHS]
That laugh.
That's the laugh.
That's it!
You're the one!
No, no.
No, it was an accident.
It w-wasn't my fault!
It was Jerry!
Jerry put a PEZ dispenser
on my leg!
You put a PEZ dispenser
on her leg during my recital?
I didn't know
she would laugh.
And, you.
You lied to me, George.
You lied to me!
N-n-no, no.
I-I-I d-d-didn't.
W-w-w-what--?
What did I do?
What--? Where are
you going?
I...
am breaking up...
with you.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
You can't break up
with me.
I-I've got hand!
And you're gonna
need it.
Noel. Noel!
Hey, Richie!
Hey, Richie.
So, what's going on?
JERRY:
So we start the intervention,
and it's pretty ugly
from the get-go.
He's not listening,
he's hostile,
he's talking back.
I can't do these puzzles.
So he starts to get up.
Suddenly...
he spots the PEZ dispenser
on the coffee table.
[CHUCKLES]
The PEZ dispenser.
He picks it up,
he's staring at it.
It's like
he's hypnotized by it.
Then he's telling us this story
about how when he was a kid,
he was in the car
with his father
and his father was trying
to load one of them.
Well, they're
hard to load.
Tell me something
I don't know.
So as the father's
trying to load it,
he loses control
of the car,
crashes into
a high school cafeteria.
Get out.
Nobody's hurt,
but PEZ was all over
the car.
And the dispenser
was destroyed
virtually
beyond recognition.
Poor kid.
So as he's telling the story,
he starts crying.
Well, what did you do?
What do you think?
I gave him
my PEZ dispenser.
Wow.
Two hours later,
he checks into Smither's clinic.
Talked to the doctor yesterday.
He's doing great on the rehab,
he's hooked on PEZ.
He's eating them
like there's no tomorrow.
What's a three-letter word
for candy?
I can't do those things.
Jawbreakers, to me, was like
the ultimate challenge candy.
It was almost like
candy manufacturers
were sitting
in their laboratories, going,
"I wonder if they'll eat this.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"This seems pretty tough to eat.
"Let's market it as
some sort of an experiment."
But the concept of Jawbreakers,
what was the concept?
Multicolored cement balls
for a quarter?
Was that the idea behind it?
"Let's see if we can hurt them.
"Let's see if they'll pay...
to be hurt."
This is the idea
behind Jawbreakers.
And I did it, I ate them,
I loved them.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Oh, this is very painful.
I'm really hurting.
And this is hurting me a lot.
I love them.