Every time somebody recommends
a doctor, he's always the best.
"Oh, is he good?"
"Oh, he's the best."
"This guy's the best."
They can't all be the best.
There can't be this many bests.
Someone's graduating
at the bottom of these classes.
Where are these doctors?
Is somewhere someone
saying to their friend,
"You should see my doctor.
He's the worst.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Oh, yeah. He's the worst.
"He's the absolute worst
there is.
"Whatever you've got,
"it'll be worse
after you see him. Yeah.
He's just a-- He's a butcher.
The man's a butcher."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
And then there's always that,
"Make sure that you tell him
that, you know, you know me."
Why? What's the difference?
He's a doctor.
What is he--?
"Oh, you know Bob.
"Oh, okay, I'll give you
the real medicine.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Yeah, everybody else
I'm giving Tic Tacs."
WOMAN:
And usually for lunch,
I'll have a salad.
And for dinner,
I eat whatever I want.
What do you think the
worst part of being blind is?
Excuse me?
You know,
if you were blind,
what do you think
the worst part of it would be?
I don't know.
I think it would be
not being able to tell
if there was bugs in my food.
How could you ever enjoy
a meal like that?
I'd constantly be feeling around
with my lips and my tongue.
Well, that's how
my 5-year-old eats.
He's a very picky eater.
Did you hear about
that kid that was kidnapped
the other day in Pennsylvania?
No.
Oh, he's at a carnival
with his mother.
she goes to get a hot dog.
Next thing you know,
she turns around,
boom, he's gone.
Oh.
Imagine how sick a person has
to be to do something like that.
[VOICE TREMBLING]
And these people
are all over the place.
You never know who's crazy.
I could be one of these people.
Have you seen any good movies?
Who takes care of your boy
during the day?
[NERVOUSLY]
We have a woman.
Why?
No, no. I'm just saying,
you know.
She had references.
Oh, I'm sure she did.
I'm sure they're impeccable.
I'm talking about the ones
that forge them.
You know, I think
this is really helping.
[AGGRESSIVELY]
I don't live near here,
you know.
JERRY:
So she's giving me the massage,
and I'm just making
conversation.
I don't like to talk
during a massage.
Neither do I, but I do it for
them. I figure they're bored.
Hey, I do that too.
I feel guilty about
getting the pleasure.
I feel like I don't
deserve it, so I talk.
It stops me
from enjoying it.
There's nothing to eat
in here.
[GASPS]
Oh! I forgot to tell you.
I'm in the middle of a story.
Oh, okay, go ahead.
Why don't you ever
go shopping?
It's not like it's a really
funny story or anything.
What happened?
Well, so she mentioned
that she had a son.
And then for some reason
I launch into the story
about the kid from Pennsylvania
who was abducted.
Oh, wasn't that terrible?
Yes, it was.
Not even an apple.
She doesn't wanna hear that.
That was stupid.
I know it was stupid.
Really stupid.
Hey, I just said it was stupid.
What about this leftover
Chinese food?
Take it.
I can't believe you said that.
Hey, would you stop it already?
So, what did she say?
I don't know, She actually
seemed to get a little paranoid.
[SCOFFS]
GEORGE: This is terrible.
What is this, ginger?
I hate ginger.
I can't understand how
anyone can eat ginger.
I have a good masseuse
you can go to.
No, she's really good.
She's not just a masseuse.
She's a physical therapist.
There's a big difference.
She uses the ultrasound.
It's a real medical procedure.
In fact, if you get
a doctor's note,
it's covered by insurance.
Physical therapy is covered
by insurance?
Yeah.
You don't pay
for the massage?
Not if you have
a doctor's note.
So where do you get
this note?
Well, I've never
actually done it,
but if I really
wanted to,
I could probably get one from
my friend Roy, the dentist.
Right. Your friend Roy.
What's the name of this
physical therapist?
I'll tell you, but don't ask her
anything about her kid.
She's a little off.
And you don't
have to pay?
GEORGE:
We have 3:00 appointments.
George and Elaine,
right?
Right.
Could you fill these out
for me, please?
And, um,
Elaine, you'll be seeing
Julianna.
Okay.
And, George,
you'll be with Raymond.
Excuse me.
Did you say Raymond?
Yes.
But, uh...
Raymond is a man.
That's right.
I can't get a massage
from a man.
Why not?
What, are you crazy?
I can't have a man
touching me.
Switch with me.
Ew, I don't want
the man either.
What's the difference?
You're a woman.
They're supposed to be
touching you.
He'd just be touching
your back.
your back too.
No, it could get sexual.
I know.
That's the point.
If it's gonna get sexual,
it should get sexual
with you.
I wouldn't be
comfortable.
I would?
What if something
happens?
Oh,
[SCOFFS]
what could happen?
What if it felt good?
It's supposed to
feel good.
I don't want it
to feel good.
Then why get
the massage?
Exactly.
[MUTTERS]
Jeez.
George.
Y--
Yes.
I'm Raymond.
Hello.
Are you ready?
And then Julianna asked
me if I wanted
to join her here
in the office.
Really?
Used to be
a flight attendant.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, boy.
You know, why don't you
open those pants.
It's gonna be a lot
easier that way.
So, what do you do?
What?
I said, what do you do?
I-- I don't know.
You don't know
what you do?
No.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, come on.
You're very tense.
Coffee. Too much coffee.
Okay. You should take off
those pants now.
I'll work the hamstring.
Oh, the hamstring's fine.
But you wrote
that it was tender.
[CHUCKLING]
I wrote. I wrote.
I'll check it out.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Take them off.
[SQUISHING]
How did you hurt this?
I don't know.
You don't know?
No.
But you just told me--
Korea.
You hurt it in Korea?
What?
The hamstring.
Korea.
How?
Hamstring.
How did you hurt
the hamstring?
Hotel.
Oh...
[DEEP BREATH]
How'd it go?
George?
JERRY:
No appointments at all?
Because my neck is still tight.
What about Thursday?
And Friday?
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, boy.
Okay.
Thanks anyway.
What's with you?
[SCOFFS]
A, uh...
Yes. A...
A man gave me...
Yes. A man gave you...
[LAUGHS]
a massage.
So?
So he...
had his hands...
And, uh...
he was, uh...
He was what?
He-- He was, uh...
touching and rubbing.
[LAUGHS]
That's a massage.
And then I took my pants off.
You took your pants off?
For my hamstring.
Oh.
He got about, uh...
two inches from...
there.
Really?
I think it moved.
It moved?
It may have moved.
I don't know.
I'm sure it didn't move.
It moved!
It was imperceptible,
but I-I-I felt it.
Maybe it just wanted
to change positions. You know...
shift to the other side.
No, no.
It wasn't a shift.
I've shifted.
This was a move.
Okay. So what if it moved?
That's the sign, the test.
If a-- If a man makes it move.
That's not the test.
Contact is the test.
If it moves
as a result of contact.
Do you think it's contact?
It has to be touched?
That's what a gym teacher
once told me.
Hey.
I just saw Joe DiMaggio
in Dinky Doughnuts.
You know,
I looked in there
and there he was
having coffee and a doughnut.
Joe DiMaggio?
In Dinky Doughnuts?
Yes.
Joe DiMaggio.
No. I'm sorry.
If Joe DiMaggio
wants a doughnut,
he goes to a fancy restaurant
or a hotel.
He's not sitting
in Dinky Doughnuts.
Well, maybe he likes
Dinky Doughnuts.
I don't even like to sit next to
a man on an airplane,
because our knees
might touch.
I can't see Joe DiMaggio
sitting at the counter
at little, tiny, filthy,
smelly Dinky Doughnuts.
Why can't Joe DiMaggio have
a doughnut like everybody else?
He can have a doughnut...
All right. Yeah.
but not a Dinky.
I don't even like
to use urinals.
Always been a stall man.
Look, I'm telling--
I'm telling you,
that was Joe DiMaggio.
The guy slept
with Marilyn Monroe.
He's in Dinky Doughnuts.
All right. Look,
what about this doctor's note?
Let's go see your friend, Roy.
I never said
I'd do that.
What are you talking about?
That's 75 bucks.
I'm not working.
I can't afford that.
I don't know how
I feel about it.
Oh, what are you,
like a Quaker now?
All right, all right.
A stall man, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
JERRY:
So we were just wondering
if it was possible
for you to write us a note.
And if you can't,
believe me, it's fine.
He didn't say he can't.
I mean if you feel
funny about it at all.
He doesn't feel funny.
If he does.
GEORGE: Do you feel funny?
JERRY: Forget it.
He didn't say anything.
He feels funny.
You don't have to do this.
He knows that!
Roy, should we go? Is this
a breach of our friendship?
Oh, can you be
any more dramatic?
Don't be ridiculous.
Holyfield. He's a good friend
of one of my patients.
He's got a hell of a body,
doesn't he?
How would I know?
Do you like him?
What do you mean,
like him?
Do you like him?
Well, I mean,
he's a good fighter
and a nice guy,
but I don't like him.
How come you don't like him?
Why should I?
What is the matter
with you?
Nothing. Why?
You think something's wrong?
Am I different?
So you want the notes?
You don't have to, really.
No, no. It's okay.
We should probably get one
for Elaine too, right, George?
George?
George.
JERRY:
Well, what about
the week after?
No appointments at all?
What?
Well, can I--?
Can I at least just talk to her
so I can apologize?
Forget it.
I can't believe this.
I make one
innocent comment...
about some lunatic
in Pennsylvania,
and I'm cut off.
This woman is insane.
What's with you?
What?
Well, you were too close to me.
I was all scrunched in there.
Hey, you scrunched me.
I sat down here first.
[DOOR OPENS]
KRAMER: Hey.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I saw DiMaggio
in the doughnut shop again.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Joe DiMaggio?
Joe DiMaggio.
You know this time I went in
and I sat down across from him
and I really watched him.
I studied his every move.
For example...
he dunks.
Joe DiMaggio dunks
his doughnuts?
That's right.
See, now I know it's not him.
Joe DiMaggio could not be
a dunker.
Oh, he's a dunker.
Why couldn't he be
a dunker?
And nothing diverts
his attention.
Like, I'm, you know--
Like, I'm sitting
in there, you know
and I start banging
on the table, you know, to--
So that he'll look up.
You know, like,
I'm sitting there, and I:
You know.
He wouldn't move.
So then I started doing
these yelping noises like,
yow!
Yow!
Uh...
No reaction, because the guy
is so focused, you see.
He can just block out anything
that's going on around him.
See, that's
how he played baseball.
He dunks like he hits.
So then what?
Well, then the waitress,
she comes up and she tells me
to shut up
or they're gonna throw me out.
Why didn't you just
call out his name?
KRAMER:
Well--
What happened to you?
These kids called me
a Mary.
A what?
I was jumping
over a puddle.
And for some reason,
I went like this:
And they called me
a Mary.
So I chased them
and I tripped and I fell.
Yeah, you know kids.
They can be very perceptive.
Hey, George.
What is this?
What is that?
No, really. What is that?
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Roy.
What?
Oh, my God.
Well, how did
this happen?
What can I do?
Oh.
I am so sorry.
Okay.
Bye.
That was Roy.
He's under investigation
for insurance fraud.
KRAMER:
♪ He's just a man ♪
♪ And not a freak ♪
♪ Joltin' Joe ♪
♪ DiMaggio ♪
♪ Joe, Joe ♪
♪ Go Joe ♪
JERRY:
I told you.
Told me what?
I told you we shouldn't do it.
I didn't say anything.
He's got a house, a family.
They could take away
his license.
You should've heard him.
Three notes.
How stupid was that?
We never should've got
three notes.
Three notes?
Yeah. You, me and George.
You got me a note?
Yeah.
But I got
my own note.
You what?
I got a note from
my gynecologist.
Why'd you do that?
I didn't know you were
getting me a note.
Of course I was
getting you a note.
But you didn't
say anything.
Neither did you.
Oh.
That's how he got caught.
We sent in four notes
from two doctors.
How could you do that
to your friend?
He's got a wife, kids...
and a lot of other stuff.
Oh...
yyyyyeah.
Hi, Pam.
Hello.
I just thought maybe
I could talk to Roy if--
Pam, did the x-ray
from Mrs. Sloane...?
Hi.
Hi, Roy.
How you doing?
Come on back.
I have a patient,
but she's under.
I don't even know
what to say.
Me neither.
I knew this would happen.
Me too.
I mean, the whole thing,
it's just...
Tragic.
Well, it's not tragic.
No?
No. It's...
Unsettling?
Okay.
I mean, what if they--?
I hope you're both happy.
I'm not happy.
Me, neither.
I've never been happy.
I mean, I'm happy sometimes,
but-- But not now.
In college, maybe.
Those were fun times.
Yeah, college was fun.
Yeah.
You know the whole practice
is in jeopardy.
You know that.
Don't mind her.
Oh, please.
I love her.
I've just met her,
but I'm very impressed.
I don't understand.
I've never had a problem
with these notes before.
Well, what's the next move?
What's gonna happen now?
Well, nothing, really,
as long as we get
the physical therapist
to go along with our story.
What? The physical therapist?
Why?
She just has to say
the complaint was related
to a dental problem.
How you doing?
Hi. Uh, look, I know
I don't have an appointment,
but it's really important
that I talk with Julianna.
I'm sorry, Mr. Seinfeld.
She's not in.
I know she's mad at me, but
I really have to speak with her.
I told you she's not here.
You don't understand.
Look, you have to leave.
I--
Wait a second. Don't you--?
Hi, hi. Look, I don't
know what you think--
Please!
But, you see...
Let me just talk to you
for a second.
See, what I did is
inadvertently sent in
an insurance--
I treated you,
so please just get out
of the office.
But can't you just listen to me?
Run, Billy!
Run to the office
and close the door!
Call the police.
The police.
What is the--?
Hi, George.
Uh... Hello.
Raymond?
ELAINE:
Well, I mean, it's only
a six-month probation.
It's a slap
on the wrist.
Yeah, I still don't see
any dinner invitations
forthcoming.
Men have been popping
into my sexual fantasies.
All of a sudden,
I'll be
in the middle...
Of what?
And a guy will appear
from out of nowhere.
I said, "Get out of here.
What do you want?
You don't belong here."
What do they do?
They talk back.
They go, "Hey, George,
how's it going?" I mean...
I said, "Get the hell
out of here."
Hey, it's the K-Man.
[KNOCKING]
[LAUGHS]
Maybe it's time you got
a different hobby.
Oh, man.
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
I just came from Roy's.
I threw up from the gas.
JERRY:
Did he say anything?
No, no. He's fine.
[WHISPERING]
Oh, my God. It's...
What?
Joe DiMaggio.
Where?
Having a cup of coffee.
ELAINE: And he's dunking.
KRAMER: Yeah. Ah?
Wow. Look at him.
The Yankee Clipper.
KRAMER: Yeah.
Here.
You see? Now, that
is a handsome man.
Oh, please.
Wait, wait.
Hold on a minute. Wait.
Oh.
Yee!
Yee-hee!
See? I told you.
What causes homophobia?
What is it that makes
a heterosexual man worry?
I think it's because
men know that deep down
we have weak
sales resistance.
We're constantly buying shoes
that hurt us,
pants that don't
fit right.
Men think, "Obviously,
I can be talked into anything.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
What if I accidentally wander
into some sort of
homosexual store
thinking it's a shoe store,
and the salesman goes,
"Just hold this guy's hand, walk
around the store a little bit.
"See how you feel.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"No obligation,
no pressure, just try it.
Would you like to see him
in a sandal?"
♪ Hey
Di-di-dee ♪
♪ Wah ♪
♪ Hey
Di-zi-ski-dee ♪
[BETTY BONNEY'S
"JOLTIN' JOE DiMAGGIO" PLAYING]
♪ Started baseball's
Famous streak ♪
♪ That's got us
All aglow ♪
♪ He's just a man
And not a freak ♪
♪ Joltin' Joe
DiMaggio ♪
♪ Joe, Joe
♪ We want you
On our side ♪
♪ He tied the mark
At 44 ♪
♪ July the first
You know ♪
♪ Since then he's hit
A good 12 more ♪
♪ Joltin' Joe
DiMaggio ♪
♪ Joe, Joe
♪ We want you
On our side ♪
♪ From coast to coast
That's all you'll hear ♪
♪ Of Joe
The one-man show ♪
♪ He's glorified
The horsehide sphere ♪
♪ Joltin' Joe
DiMaggio ♪
♪ Joe ♪