You know, there's, like,
always one location
in your neighborhood,
one store location
that's constantly
changing hands?
Everybody has this
in their neighborhood.
It's a leather store,
then it's a yogurt shop,
then it's a pet supply.
It's, like, constantly changing.
Nobody can do business there.
It's like some sort of
Bermuda Triangle of retail,
you know?
Stores open up,
and then they just disappear
without a trace.
Nobody knows what happened
to them.
I guess eventually when, like,
aliens land in the mothership
from Close Encounters,
the bottom will slowly open,
and all these store owners
will come wandering out
in a daze, going,
"I thought there was gonna be
more walk-in traffic,
didn't you?"
She thinks
I'm nice a nice guy.
Women always think
I'm nice,
but women
don't want nice.
This is amazing.
I haven't seen
one person
go in that restaurant
since it opened.
Poor guy.
Why is nice bad?
What kind of a sick society
are we living in,
where nice is bad?
What's that smell?
What are you wearing?
What?
A little cologne.
Manly.
Monica wants me
to wear it.
So why didn't
you say no?
I'm too nice.
Look at this poor guy.
His family's probably
back in Pakistan.
They're waiting for him
to send back money.
This is horrible.
She wants me
to take an I.Q. test.
It's because you're stupid
enough to wear the cologne.
No.
She's taking this
course in education
for her masters.
It's part
of her research project,
so I have to be
a guinea pig.
Never been a guinea pig.
Been a sheep.
Been a toady.
You know what?
I can't talk
to you anymore.
All right.
I'm sorry. Go ahead.
You're taking
the I.Q. test.
Yeah, and she's gonna
find out I'm a moron.
You know,
people think I'm smart,
but I'm not smart.
Who thinks you're smart?
I'm not gonna break 100
on this thing.
What thing?
You don't listen when
people talk to you anymore.
Oh, the I.Q. thing.
Yeah.
I'm sure
I have a low I.Q.
I've been lying about my S.A.T.
scores for 15 years.
What'd you get?
What did I get,
or what do I say I got?
What do you say?
I say 1409.
Fourteen-oh-nine,
that's a good score.
You're telling me.
Well, what did you
really get?
You're my friend, right?
Of course.
I tell you
everything, right?
I hope so.
Well...
This I take
to the grave.
JERRY: He's serving Mexican,
Italian, Chinese.
He's all over the place.
That's why no one's going in.
Why do you
keep watching?
I don't know.
I'm obsessed with it.
It's like a spider
in the toilet,
struggling for survival...
and even though you know
he's not gonna make it,
you kind of root for him
for a second.
Then you flush.
Well, it's a spider.
You know, sometimes
people won't go in a place
if they don't see
anyone else in there.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Do you have to do that?
Jerry, don't do that.
That is so annoying.
Bazooka Joe.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
The buzzer.
It's your house.
My house.
You gotta be on the lease
to press the buzzer.
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
Casus belli.
What's that?
It's Latin.
I read it in some book.
I don't know. I just wanted
to say it out loud.
Come on. Go in.
Go in.
Have you gone in there?
No, I'm afraid
we'll start talking,
and I'll wind up
going partners with him.
Hey.
You know, I could probably
shoot him from here.
I'd be doing us both a favor.
[SNIFFING]
I'm wearing some cologne,
all right?
Sure. Fine.
Casus belli.
What's that?
Since when do you
wear cologne?
Why is what I do so important?
Why must I always be
the focal point of attention?
Let me just be. Let me live.
Hey, how'd you do
on that I.Q. test?
I didn't take it yet.
What I.Q. test?
What's "casus belli"?
Oh, it's nothing.
Is it about me?
Why must you always be
the focal point of attention?
Why can't you just be?
Why can't you live?
It's just a Latin phrase,
George.
It does not mean anything.
Now, what is this test?
This woman he's dating
is making him take
this I.Q. test for this course.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
Yeah, fun.
I.Q. tests are totally bogus.
They prove nothing.
You'll do well. You're smart.
No, see, he's not smart.
People think
he's smart,
but he's not.
What did you get
on your S.A.T.s?
It varies.
You know,
I don't even know my I.Q.
Mine's 145.
145?
Get out of here.
You get out of here.
Maybe you should
take the test for me.
Boy, that'd
be something,
cheating
on an I.Q. test.
Hey, remember in college
when you passed Lettick the test
out the window?
You became a legend
after that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I really had some guts
back then.
Why don't we do it again?
What?
You could take the I.Q. test
for me.
I could pass it to you
out of a window.
We could do it.
She lives on the first floor.
Are you serious?
Why not?
Where would I take the test?
I don't know-- she lives
right around the corner.
You could take it here
or go to the coffee shop.
No. That'd be too noisy.
Take it at The Dream Café.
You won't hear a peep.
Hey, what do you think?
Hey, I love a good caper.
Yeah, that's what it is,
isn't it?
A caper.
You'll do it?
What the hey?
Yeah! Beautiful!
Yeah!
Ooh, sorry.
Welcome
to The Dream Café.
Well, uh, I've been
looking forward to it.
Oh, how did you
hear about us?
Uh... people.
People are talking.
Smoking
or nonsmoking?
We are proud
to offer both.
Nonsmoking would be great.
Very good.
My name is Babu Bhatt.
I will be your waiter.
A steaming hot
folded face towel
for your pleasure.
Thank you. Ah!
Our specials-- tacos, moussaka,
and franks and beans.
Well, what do you recommend,
my good fellow?
Oh, the turkey.
Well, the turkey it'll be.
And may I say you have
a splendid establishment here,
my friend.
I'm sure you'll flourish
at this location
for many, many years.
You're a very kind man,
very kind.
Thank you.
Very kind.
JERRY:
I am kind man.
Who else would do
something like this?
Nobody.
Nobody thinks about people
the way I do.
All right, snap out of it,
you stupid jerk.
You're eating
a turkey sandwich.
What do you want,
a Nobel Prize?
You go
in the living room.
I'll take the test
in here.
But why?
I won't be able to concentrate
in front of you.
Oh, I think you're making
too much of this.
I.Q. tests don't mean anything.
Are you kidding me?
This is the best tool
we have today
of measuring
a person's intelligence.
Well, I certainly don't
place any importance on it.
Well, I think you're wrong
about that.
And now,
if you'll excuse me,
I'd really like
to get started, please.
Good luck.
[CHUCKLING]
Don't need it.
What's been going on
up there?
I've been standing here
20 minutes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Here's the test.
Thanks again
for doing this.
All right, now, what time
do you want me back here?
Uh, 20 to 3:00.
Okay.
Thanks again.
All right.
And don't settle
for 145.
You can do better.
You're a genius.
Thank you, Babu.
You have
quite a flair.
You are quite
the restauranteur,
I must say.
It is indeed
my pleasure.
Oh, please.
Ooh! Welcome
to The Dream Café.
Our specials today--
I'll just have
tea and toast.
Tea and toast.
Eat something!
Babu.
Um... okay.
Well, I'll have the...
The rigatoni.
Oh! Oh, very good choice.
Very good.
Oh, wow,
so you got the test.
You're cheating.
I know.
Hey.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, boy.
Whoop.
Jerry, let me
ask you something.
Hi, Elaine.
Hi.
This guy
leaves this jacket
at my mother's house
two years ago.
Now, she hasn't
spoken to him since,
and now he says
he wants the jacket back.
So?
Well, I'm not
giving it back.
Why not?
Well, because I meet
a lot of women
in this jacket,
you know?
They're attracted to it.
Why do you think my mother
went out with him?
Oh, jeez.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yeah, okay.
What?
Anyway, it's been two years.
I mean, isn't there, like,
a statue of limitations on that?
Statute.
What?
Statute of limitations.
It's not a statue.
No, it's statue.
Fine.
It's a sculpture of limitations.
Wait a minute.
Just wait a minute.
Elaine.
Elaine!
Now, you're smart.
Is it statue or statute
of limitations?
Statute.
Oh, I really think
you're wrong.
Look, Kramer, I have to take
this test, okay?
And I don't have
a lot of time.
What test?
An I.Q. test.
Why are you
taking an I.Q. test?
It's for George.
George?
Yeah, yeah, look,
can I explain it
to you later?
Yeah, but why are you taking
an I.Q. test for George?
Would you please?
What, is it for a job
or something?
Later!
You're positive
it's statute?
Yes! Yes!
BABU: Welcome, welcome.
A steaming hot face towel--
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
[DOORKNOB TURNING]
George?
Yeah?
The door's locked.
Oh, it's locked?
I need
to get something.
Monica, I'm really focused here.
This stuff's a killer.
George!
Wish I could.
[BABU HUMMING LOUDLY]
[HUMMING LOUDER]
Babu!
If you don't mind.
Yeah. Okay.
I'll get this.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my God!
God, it's all over
my test!
I didn't mean it.
I'm terribly sorry.
Oh, man!
Look at this.
I'm out of time anyway.
Please, forgive me,
please.
Go ahead.
I'll take care of it.
Ugh.
Please,
I'm very sorry.
Tell your friends!
It's all right.
She was cheating anyway.
You're
a very kind man.
Babu...
You're Pakistani,
right?
Yes, Pakistani. Yes.
Babu, may I say something?
Of course.
You're very smart man. I listen.
I am not a restauranteur
by any means,
but it occurred to me
that perhaps you might serve
some dishes
from your native Pakistan,
as opposed to, say,
the franks and beans,
for example.
But there are no
Pakistani people here.
It doesn't matter.
You would have the only
authentic Pakistani restaurant
in the whole neighborhood.
Yes.
You see everything, don't you?
Well, you know, not everything.
I do what I can.
I close down today,
and when I open again,
it will be
all-Pakistani restaurant.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
You're a very special
person.
Very special.
JERRY:
I am such a great guy.
Who else would have gone
to the trouble
to help this poor immigrant?
I am special.
My mother was right.
Of course, I've never had
Pakistani food.
How bad could it be?
It was an accident.
What, did you go
on a picnic?
Babu Bhatt did it.
Babu Bhatt?
How am I going
to explain this?
MONICA:
Time's up, George.
Okay...
Here you go.
How did you do?
Piece of cake.
What happened to the test?
What? Oh, I spilled
some food on it.
Food? What food?
What are you talking about?
Where did you get food?
From my pocket.
Your pocket?
I, uh, I had a sandwich
in my pocket.
And coffee?
Yeah. Had some coffee. Yeah.
Where did you get the coffee?
Where did I get the coffee?
Where do you think
I got the coffee?
At the grocery store.
How did you get there?
I walked.
How did you get
out of the apartment?
I didn't see you leave.
I climbed out the window.
You climbed out the window?
Of course.
Why didn't you go out the door?
The door?
Why would I go out the door?
The window's right here.
You're a fascinating man,
George Costanza.
JERRY: The average person
sees a situation like this,
they walk right by it.
Not me.
You're very special.
Hey, do me a favor.
Some guy comes around
looking for me,
tell him
you don't know where I am.
Of course, I always do.
No, no, it's that guy.
He's really been bugging me
about the jacket.
Just give it back to him.
Oh, he'll have to kill me.
Hey, Georgie!
GEORGE:
I'm coming up!
How'd you do
on the I.Q. test?
GEORGE:
Eighty-five!
What?
Eighty-five,
Jerry.
Eighty-five I.Q...
Eighty-five?
Well, well, well.
He's coming up?
Well, I'm no genius, but...
According to my calculations,
he should be here
in a few seconds.
Yeah, but an 85, Jerry,
that's ridiculous.
Well, maybe the test
was gender biased,
you know, a lot of questions
on hunting and testicles.
Oh, hello, professor.
George, I cannot believe--
Please.
No, there's got to be a mistake.
You should have seen her face.
It was the exact same look
my father gave me
when I told him
I wanted to be a ventriloquist.
But an 85.
Listen, there were too many
distractions there.
Babu...
Whatever his name was,
and Kramer,
I couldn't concentrate.
It was a madhouse.
Jerry, it was!
Let me take it again.
Ho, ho, ho,
forget it.
Oh, come on,
come on.
I'll guarantee you 140.
What do you have to lose?
You could do worse.
No! No!
Come on,
I guarantee it.
All right. I'll ask her.
Okay. Now, where
am I going to take it?
Take it here.
I'll leave.
There'll be
no distractions.
[SITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, congratulations,
my friend.
You know, I'm sorry I missed
the grand reopening.
I was out of town
for about a week.
You see how I listen?
I work very hard,
borrow more money.
I think it's fantastic.
It has a certain
indefinable charm.
You wish to eat?
Let me tell you something, Babu.
You go back in that kitchen,
tell your chef
I want the works.
Very good.
JERRY:
Very good?
No, not very good.
Very great.
I am very, very great.
You know, the I.Q. tests,
they always have that sample
question at the beginning,
where they show you
how to fill in the circle.
This should be the first
elimination point right there.
Anybody goes outside
that circle--
"Yeah, you want
to come with us, please?
"Yeah, yeah, you're done.
Your test is over.
You went outside the circle,
okay?"
What are you doing?
Quiet. Shh!
Don't say anything.
[WHISPERING]
What's going on?
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
MAN: Hey, Kramer!
I saw you go in there.
I'm not leaving until you
give me that jacket.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Open up, Kramer!
What did you come
in here for?
Well, I thought
I'd throw him off.
See, he knows where I live.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Look, Kramer, I have
to return this test.
I've gotta
get out of here.
Well, I thought
you took the test.
I had to
take it again.
How come?
What's the difference?
Well, you can't leave now.
What?
Come on, Kramer,
I want that jacket back!
Never!
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come on, George,
open up.
Well?
How you doing?
Where's the test?
You know,
it's the damnedest thing.
I went out the window again
to get a cup of coffee...
Babu...
Babu.
Babu, you know...
I've got to tell you.
I never do this, but the shrimp,
it's just
it's a little stringy.
You have any chicken?
The shrimp is stringy?
Well, maybe your fridge--
Quiet!
No, I--
You shut up!
Well, I...
You make me
change restaurant,
but nobody come.
You say, "Make Pakistani."
Babu Bhatt have
only Pakistani restaurant,
but where are people?
You see people?
Show me people.
There are no people!
You know, I think
I'll just take the check.
You bad man.
You very, very bad man.
JERRY:
Bad man?
Could my mother
have been wrong?
Are you looking for George?
Well, uh... kind of.
George left.
Oh.
Is that the test?
This, um...
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I hope you do
a lot better this time.
Actually, you know,
I think I did.
The first time,
I couldn't really
con...centrate.
You know what it was--
bad location.
Come on, let's not
stand here too long.
We might run into him.
Aren't you cold?
Where's your jacket?
Oh, sorry.
I'm going upstairs.
Hey, guys!
Hey.
I just ran into Monica.
You know what my I.Q. is?
151.
151?
Yeah.
That's a good score.
So, what are you up for?
How about Mexican?
Italian.
No. Chinese.
Know what would be great?
It's tough to do a good deed.
Let's look at your
professional good deed doers,
your Lone Rangers,
your Supermen,
your Batmen, your Spidermen,
your Elasticmen.
They're all wearing disguises,
masks over their faces,
secret identities.
Don't want people
to know who they are.
Too much aggravation.
Superman, yeah,
thanks for saving my life,
but did you
have to come through my wall?
I'm renting here.
They got a security deposit.
What am I supposed to do?
[♪]