Parking lots now, they have
this "compact car only" spot.
Isn't that discrimination
against the size of your car?
CROWD: Yeah!
If I want my ass hanging out
of the back of my parking spot,
that's my business.
There are people out there
with real asses
hanging out of their pants.
Nobody's stopping them.
Nobody goes, "Hey, hold it, sir.
Those are compact jeans.
You can't pull that in there."
Hey.
I got some bad news
for you, buddy.
I think
your car got stolen again.
What are you talking about?
Well, you parked it
on 84th and Columbus, right?
Yeah.
Well, I just walked by there,
and that car is gone.
Vvvvvvvvt!
Oh, yeah, I know.
Whoa. Well, where is it?
What's the difference?
Well, there's
no difference.
You know,
I'm just curious.
You always have to know
everything that's going on,
don't you?
What happened to the car?
If I don't tell you,
it will kill you, won't it?
Yeah, yeah, it'll kill me.
You have to know.
You must know.
I must know.
Well, I'm not telling you.
Oh, come on.
No,
I don't think so.
Well, please?
Not today, pal.
Okay, I beg you.
Now, see, just saying "beg"
doesn't make it a real beg.
You gotta put
some beg into it.
Okay. Please!
Please, tell me!
Come on.
All right, I'll tell you,
but your begging
needs a lot of work.
Okay, okay, what is it?
Come on.
I loaned the car to George.
Ah!
[FINGERS SNAP, HANDS CLAP]
George. All right.
Well, what for?
George and Elaine
went to a flea market
in Westchester.
Okay?
All right.
Ah!
Ah.
I mean, why'd they wanna
go there for?
Would you stop it
already!
You know, why didn't
they ask me to go?
I don't know!
How am I supposed
to know?!
What, they don't like me?
I don't like you!
Well, if they like me,
why didn't they ask me to go?
Oh, yeah.
I really think
it looks good.
Ten bucks.
How can you go wrong?
All bald people
look good in hats.
You should've lived
in the '20s and '30s.
You know, men wore hats
all the time then.
Pssh. What a bald paradise
that must have been.
Nobody knew.
ELAINE:
Well, you can wear a hat
all the time now.
Who's stopping you?
Nah, I can't.
What if meet a woman?
I'd always be worried about that
first moment where I take it off
and see that look
of disappointment on her face.
You sure you like
these sunglasses?
Hmm.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[CRASH]
Ew.
Well, I'm very disappointed
in George and Elaine,
and you know I'm somebody
you don't wanna have
on your bad side.
Why not?
Because I'm like ice, buddy.
When I don't like you,
you got problems.
Oh, is this for the fight?
Yeah. Starts in 35 minutes.
Mmm.
[HUMMING]
Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Yeah.
Oh, hey, you know,
I invited Mike Moffett.
You don't mind, do you?
No. I like Mike.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just got
off the phone with him.
You know, we had a...
great conversation.
Oh, yeah?
What'd you talk about?
Well, actually, um...
we talked about you.
Yeah.
He had some pretty interesting
things to say.
Oh, yeah? What did he say?
You have to know everything,
don't you?
No, come on, Kramer.
What did he say?
Why is that? Why...
do you have to know
everything?
Kramer, just tell me
what the guy said.
Beg me.
Please, don't make me beg.
No, no, no.
I want you to beg,
and I don't want you to say it.
I want you to put
some beg into it. Go on.
Kramer, please,
No.
tell me what the guy said.
No, no, no, no,
that's no good.
No, I really don't think
that's a beg.
No way.
It's close, but...
Kramer!
Look, I can't say anything.
You know, the guy told me
this stuff in confidence.
I'd be betraying a friend.
Well, you can't just mention it
and then not tell me.
All right. I'll tell you,
but you can't say
anything to him.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm putting it in the vault.
I'm locking the vault.
It's a vault.
He thinks you're a phony.
He what?
I told you.
He thinks you're a phony.
A phony?
He called me a phony?
A big phony.
Big one.
Why did you tell me that
if I can't say anything?
You begged me.
[SIGHS]
[CLANGING]
Do you hear that?
Of course I hear that.
You had to move
the mirror.
I wanted to check out
my sunglasses.
I went to look
into the mirror.
It wasn't there.
You threw off my equilibrium.
Oh, yeah, blame it on me
because you can't drive, George.
I can't drive?
Yeah.
Nobody drives like me.
Nobody.
I'm doing things
in this car,
you have no idea
they're going on.
You wanna see me
make a right turn
from the left lane?
Watch this.
No, I really don't.
I can make a left turn
from the right lane.
I'm sure you could.
What're we gonna tell
Jerry about the car?
I don't know.
All right,
start looking for spaces.
Oh, you're never gonna find
a space on Jerry's block.
Just put it in a garage.
Look, I have my system.
First, I look for the dream spot
right in front of the door,
then I slowly expand out
in concentric circles.
No, come on, George,
please put it in a garage.
I don't wanna spend an hour
looking for a space.
I can't park in a garage.
Why?
I don't know.
I just can't.
Nobody in my family
can pay for parking.
It's a sickness.
My father never paid
for parking,
my mother,
my brother, nobody.
We can't do it.
I'll pay for it.
You don't understand.
A garage...
I can't even pull in there.
It's like going to a prostitute.
Why should I pay when,
if I apply myself,
maybe I could get it
for free?
[HORN HONKS]
What?
What do you want?
Go around me.
I'm looking for spaces.
Oh, George, there's
a space right there!
Oh, beautiful.
You just passed it, see?
Look at that,
the dream space,
right in front
of Jerry's building.
Yeah.
Huh? Huh?
Dreams can come true.
What did I tell you?
You didn't even have to
take it out to dinner.
Yeah, all--
[CHUCKLES]
[BOTH LAUGH]
All right.
Now you're gonna see
some parallel parking.
[SPITS]
How I wish you could
make a living
parallel parking.
It's all geometry,
knowing all the angles,
when to make
that first turn,
and then when to...
swing it back in.
That's the key.
Will you just park it
already?
There's nothing
I can even impart to you.
That's the sad thing.
It's so inborn.
I can't pass it on.
Hmm.
Look at this guy.
What are you--?
What are you, crazy?
What are you doing?
Hey, hey!
You're stealing
my space!
George, wait, you don't know
who this guy is.
People kill for
a parking space in this city.
No, no, he's not
getting away with this.
No-- George!
Hey, what--
What are you doing?
I think
I'm parking my car.
You can't do that.
You can't just sneak in
from the back like that.
I'm not sneaking.
I didn't even know
you were parking.
You were just sitting there,
three spaces up.
Well, if you didn't think
I was parking,
why did you
put it in headfirst?
Well, that's the way
I park!
Anyway,
you didn't start backing in
till I pulled in.
I was in the middle
of a conversation.
Hey, buddy,
what can I tell you?
All right, the point is
I was here first.
I was closer to this space
than you were!
But I'm backing in!
You can't put it in headfirst!
I can if I have room!
Are you gonna move the car?
No, I'm not
gonna move the car.
Jerk.
Oh, you're not?
Do-- Do you believe
this guy?
Come on, we'll put it
in a garage.
I am not putting it
in the garage.
It's my space.
What are you gonna do?
You just gonna
leave it here like this?
Oh, I'm going upstairs.
Uh, are you
coming back down?
Yeah, I gotta tell
Jerry we're here.
I gotta go
to the bathroom.
All right,
just make sure
he reserves the good chair
for me.
Wait, what are you
gonna tell him
about the clanking noise
in the car?
Me? No, no, no, you,
you're gonna tell him.
I'm not gonna tell--
No, no,
no, come on,
you're good at this.
What am I gonna say?
I don't know, I don't know.
You'll think of something.
Just break it to him gently.
Oh, man.
[HORN HONKS]
[PANTING]
Oh, God.
Oh, God. I need a drink.
Do you got any Hennigan's here?
Yeah, under the counter.
What happened?
Oh, God.
Oh, Jerry,
it was so terrible
what we just went through
on the way home...
You wouldn't believe it.
What? Tell me
what happened.
[COUGHS]
[GASPS]
Okay, now listen...
we were at the toll booth
at the Henry Hudson Parkway,
okay?
And there were these,
like--
this pack of--
Of e-extremely wild teenagers
in a convertible
behind us, okay?
And for some reason--
I-- I don't know--
they just started
to taunt us.
And so-- And so--
Then we paid the toll,
and then--
And then we went through,
and then they started
to follow us, all right?
So George tries
to lose them.
And-- And-- And--
But they were
in this really,
like, a souped-up car,
you know?
And so he-- He turned off
the road, really suddenly,
and the car was
on two wheels,
and I was just screaming.
And-- And--
And then-- George is
such a great driver.
He is?
Oh, he is fantastic,
and then they fired a gun
right up in the air.
A gun?
I think it was a gun.
And then--
And then they followed us
all the way into the city,
and then they just stopped,
and they turned around,
and they went home.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm all right. God.
Oh, man. Jeez.
Oh, by the way,
the car hit a pothole,
and now it's making
a clanking noise.
Oh, well, I mean, as long as
you're okay, that...
That's the important thing.
Exactly.
Where's George now?
Oh, he's out
in front of the building.
He's arguing with some guy
about a parking space.
What are you talking about?
Well, look out the window.
You'll see.
Hey, Georgie!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Crazy kids, huh?
What?
Ow!
[GROANING]
It's my cuticle.
MAN:
Is that Jerry?
Jerry!
Oh, hey, Mike.
What, you know Jerry?
Yeah, I know Jerry.
How do you know him?
What's the difference?
Because I know him too,
and probably
a lot better than you.
Well, bully for you.
Hey, Jerry!
You know,
your friend here
is a real piece
of work!
I'm coming down.
Hey, will you tell
Kramer I'm outside?
What, you know Kramer?
Hi.
Hello.
Hey, your friend
Mike's outside.
He wants
to talk to you.
Oh.
Hey, Mike.
Come on up!
The fight's almost starting.
What, you're watching
the fight at Jerry's?
Yeah.
Oh, great.
You know that guy
downstairs?
Yeah, he's a real phony.
What's going on?
Hey, will you come on down?
This guy's in my space!
It's my space!
I'll be down in a minute!
Are you going down?
Yeah.
Is anything wrong?
Why should anything be wrong?
[BLOWS HARD]
I'll be down
in a minute.
Hey, pal...
you're not getting
that space.
I mean, I'll sleep in my car
if I have to.
I'll die out here.
He was down there.
Once he passed
his front bumper,
it's no longer his space.
No, it doesn't matter.
He was here first...
[CHEERFULLY] Hey! Jerry!
Long time no see.
Hi, Mike.
Indiana.
Hey, Krame.
Hey.
You know this guy?
Yeah, yeah,
I know him.
You're looking
tremendous.
What are you on,
some kind of regimen?
Yeah, 25-percent
bran flakes.
The 40 percent
was too much,
so I found a store
makes it up special for me.
They take it down
another 15 percent.
[LAUGHS]
That's killer,
killer!
I love that.
You've gotta use that.
That's a definite.
Oh, come on.
Hey.
Your friend here
has some real problems.
Me? You see
what he did here?
You see how he tried
to sneak into my space?
Just because I went front-first,
doesn't mean I'm sneaking in.
You went in front-first
because you saw me backing up,
and you didn't have room
to parallel park!
I went front-first because
I can make it front-first,
and if you pull out,
I'll show you!
You got a prayer.
Hey, I go in front-first
all the time.
Oh, front-first,
that's how you park
when you're pulling
a bank job.
Did you--
Did you talk to him?
Yeah, yeah.
It's all taken care of.
You told him? What--?
What did you tell him?
I did a number on him.
It was a thing of beauty.
You really had to have
been there to appreciate it.
I can't believe it.
What--? What did you say?
I told him a pack of teenagers,
in a convertible,
were terrorizing us,
and they followed us
into the city.
A pack of teenagers?
Yeah, yeah.
By the time I got
to the end of the story,
he was so relieved
that we were alive,
he couldn't care less
about the car.
You are a genius.
Yeah.
It's as simple as that.
What can I say?
You know, it's a gift.
I only wish
I could teach you, but...
you know, it's inborn.
Oh, by the way,
thanks a lot
for inviting me
to the flea market.
BOTH: What?
Yeah, Jerry, he told me
all about it.
Oh, great.
I didn't know.
Oh, so that's why
you were acting so funny.
Well, I didn't know you wanted
to go to the flea market.
A flea market?
You went to a flea market?
Hey,
who's talking to you?
We just didn't
think of you.
You said it,
sister.
Oh, what, every time
I leave my house,
now I have to call everybody
I know, and ask them
if they want to do
what I'm doing?
People forget.
Look at Home Alone.
They forgot.
Yeah, great move telling him,
by the way, real smart move.
I didn't know I wasn't supposed
to say anything.
[WHINING GIBBERISH]
Judgment, Jerry, judgment!
You exercised no judgment.
You're right,
my fault.
I'm sorry, Kramer.
I'm so sorry, really.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I don't care
for that sorry.
What was wrong
with that sorry?
That was a good sorry.
Jerry, was that
a good sorry?
It was a so-so sorry.
[HORN HONKS]
Hey, move this car!
I gotta get through!
You heard
the man.
I guess you'd better
be moving your car.
And, like, you're not
just gonna back it in
if I do that.
Well, somebody better move
something soon.
I got a truck
full of ice cream here!
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
See, they had
to move the car
so the truck could
get through, right?
But these guys
don't trust each other,
so they got
these two non-partisan drivers
to move them.
Wild pack of teenagers,
huh?
Yeah.
Amazing how they pick...
you, out of everyone,
to terrorize.
Yeah, I know.
I said--
I said to myself,
"Why us?"
You remember? I--
Mm-hmm.
Sounds like you did
some pretty nifty maneuvering.
Well, you know, i-i-it's
interesting, when, you know,
un-- under that pressure,
what you're capable of.
Mmm.
Right.
I learned a lot about myself.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
[METAL SCRAPING]
What did you do to my car?
I couldn't help it.
Elaine moved the mirror.
I got discombobulated.
Oh, like you've
ever been bobulated.
I thought you said
you were a good driver.
No, no. I never said
I was a good driver.
I said I was
a good parker.
I think you said
driver.
No, parker. I never said driver.
I said parker, great parker.
Hey, that's not the way it was.
Will you move it?
No, no, no,
that's in the right position.
No, no,
I was further in.
No, you weren't.
Stop there. That's fine.
Do you mind?
Do you?
Hey, somebody better
move these cars.
You're making a commotion.
Hey, Sid.
Who are you?
Never mind who I am.
I know who I am.
Do you know who you are?
Why is it
every time you park a car
in this block,
everything gets disrupted
and disjointed?
Sid, it's completely
his fault.
Oh, right.
Why don't you start
taking the bus?
JERRY:
Okay, George,
come on.
Let's go.
I'm putting it in a garage.
The fight's starting
in two minutes.
It's enough already!
No, don't do it!
What are we gonna do?
Stay out here all night?
Yes, I'm not giving him
the satisfaction.
It's my space.
Why don't you just
flip a coin already?
No, no, no,
this is a matter of principle.
That would just be saying
that anybody can just
pull into any parking space
any way they want.
Well, I'm making a stand here.
I'm saying no
to headfirst parking!
I'm not putting up
with that.
We put up with too much crap
in this city!
We're not putting up
with headfirst parking!
You know, maybe if you hadn't
been sitting there
pontificating about
what a great parker you were,
you might've
got the space.
Oh, so you're
against me now?
Ohhh...
The man, he could've
pulled up to that car
and backed in,
but he chose
to go in headfirst.
No, he couldn't,
because the other car
was already backing in.
No, he wasn't.
All that matters is
who was there first.
Ah, you're not even old enough
to drive, you little puke.
You just spit on me!
Don't you raise
your voice to me!
You're not my father!
Hey, Matthew.
Hi, Jerry.
This guy's really
a jerk.
How you doing?
Okay.
Hey, how's your father?
I hear he's closing his store.
What?
Oh, no, nothing. Nothing.
What's happened to Daddy?
He's going out of business?
No, no, no, no.
We're not going
to have any money?
No.
We're out of money?
No, of course not,
of course not.
Mommy!
Jerry says
Daddy's closing the store.
He's going
out of business.
We don't have
any money?
Jerry,
what's the matter with you?
I didn't...
Boy, I don't know
about your friend, Jerry.
He says some pretty stupid
things sometimes.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Oh,
congratulations.
What for?
Well,
you're pregnant.
What?
You're not pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant.
Are you sure
you're not pregnant?
Yes, I'm sure.
Whew.
That's weird.
Come on, Matthew.
No!
Come on, Matthew!
I thought she was pregnant.
Hey, do you think
I'm a phony?
What?
Mike thinks I'm a phony.
He thinks
you're a phony?
Yeah, but I can't
say anything,
because Kramer wasn't
supposed to tell me.
Oh, you have to
say something.
I can't. I told Kramer
I was vaulting it.
Well, you gotta
open the vault.
Open my vault?
Open your vault.
Once I open the vault,
it ceases to be a vault.
You have no choice.
Oy, the vault.
You wanna know why
you can't go in front-first?
I'll tell you why.
Because it signals
a breakdown
in the social order.
Chaos!
It reduces us
to jungle law.
Well, when can you
park headfirst?
Never!
What're you asking
this guy for?
Who's talking to you?
He's right.
Never.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what if you got
10 car lengths?
Do you have to pull
all the way up to the front car?
Well, if you've got
10 car lengths...
When do you ever have
10 car lengths?
What about Sundays
and holidays, huh?
Oh, please...
Hey, what's
going on here?
Oh, uh, this guy
tried to sneak into my space.
Oh. I really hate
people who do that.
I hope you don't let him
get away with it.
Well, thank you
for your support.
Hey, that's a great hat.
Really? You like it?
Yeah.
I got it
at a flea market today.
Hey, George,
nice hat.
Yeah, thanks.
Can I try it on?
No, it, uh,
wouldn't fit you.
Oh, sure,
it would.
No. Get out of here,
Newman.
Ah, let me try it.
Stop it!
Well, let him
try it on.
I don't want him to.
What is wrong with you?
You wanna see?!
There! There it is!
Run!
All right, here!
You wanna try on the hat?!
Here, try on the hat!
Stop it, George.
I was defending your parking.
Come on, George!
All right, keep it,
just keep the hat!
All right, that's it,
the fight's already started.
I'm going upstairs.
Who's coming? Elaine?
It depends on who's going.
Are you going?
I'm not going if he's going.
Me either.
And I'm not going
if he's going.
Well, I'm going.
If he's going, I'm not going.
But it's your house.
I still don't have to go.
I don't wanna go
if Jerry's not going.
Why won't you go, if I go?
Why? I'll tell you why.
No, don't, Jerry.
Like, you didn't call me
a phony?!
What?
Thanks! Real good!
All right.
Jerry...
First of all,
I think you completely
misunderstood what I said.
I meant it
in a complimentary way.
I mean, you know
when people say, "He's bad,"
it really means,
"He's good"?
That sort of thing?
Uh, you know,
it's slang.
Use it in a sentence.
Man, that Michael Jordan
is so phony.
Why did you tell him?!
He begged me!
He begged you?!
All right, come on,
who wants to watch the fight?
Okay, whose cars are these?
Let's move them. Let's go.
Uh, o-o-officer,
could I just explain
something to you?
Let's go, or I'll write both
of you a ticket in two minutes.
But, officer, he--
He can't pull in headfirst.
Officer, he backed up
from down the street.
He was double-parked.
He was sitting there.
All right,
you move your car.
It's his space.
You can't go in headfirst.
Wait a second.
Why can't
he go in headfirst?
He said the guy was
just sitting over there.
What are you
talking about?
This guy was
there first.
But he didn't
take it.
Hey,
it's his space,
No, it's his space.
What are you...?
MIKE:
You're gonna have to
leave eventually.
GEORGE:
Well, you're gonna have to
go to the bathroom!
MIKE:
Well, you're gonna have to
go to work!
GEORGE: I don't have a job!
MIKE: Neither do I!
GEORGE: Yeah--
[YELLING QUIETS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER:
Seven...
eight...
nine...
ten.
[BELL DINGS]
People will kill each other
for a parking space in New York,
because they think,
"If I don't get this one,
I may never get a space,"
you know?
"I'll be circling for months
until somebody goes out
to the Hamptons."
I think because everybody
in New York City
knows there's gotta be
way more cars
than parking spaces.
You see cars driving in New York
all hours of the night.
It's like musical chairs,
except everybody sat down
around 1964.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
The problem is
car manufacturers are building
hundreds of thousands
of new cars every year.
They're not making
any new spaces.
That's what they should be
working on.
Wouldn't that be great?
You go to the auto show,
and they've got
that big revolving turntable,
and there's nothing on it.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"New from Chrysler, a space."