Do you think
that the people at the airport
that run the stores
have any idea
what the prices are
everyplace else in the world,
or do you think they just feel
they have their own
little country out there
and they can charge
anything they want?
"You hungry?
Tuna sandwich is $9.00.
"You don't like it,
go back to your own country."
I think the whole
airport/airline complex
is a huge scam
just to sell
the tuna sandwiches.
I think that profit
is what's supporting
the whole air travel industry.
I mean, think about it.
The terminals, the airplanes.
It's all just a distraction
so that you don't notice
the beating that you're taking
on the tuna.
It's all departures.
I see nothing but departures.
Do you know
where the arrivals are?
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Do you have the time?
There's a clock over there.
Where?
Over there.
But you have
a watch on.
It's right by the escalator.
Why don't you just
look at your watch?
I told you,
it's right over there.
Let me see the watch.
Hey!
What are you,
some kind of nut?
You know,
we're living in a society!
George.
Jerry, Jerry.
I'm sorry.
The flight was delayed.
How long have you
been waiting?
I just got here.
My car broke down
on the Belt Parkway.
I can't believe-- Why don't you
get rid of that piece of junk?
One mile from the exit,
it starts shaking,
really violently shaking,
like it's having
a nervous breakdown,
then it completely stopped dead.
So you have no car.
No.
So, what good are you?
I'll tell you one thing.
This chauffeur's going to
be waiting a while.
O'Brien's not showing up.
How do you know?
He was in Chicago.
The flight was overbooked.
They wouldn't let him
on the plane.
He kept screaming how he had
to get to Madison Square Garden.
We should take his limo.
Yeah, right.
Wait a second.
Think about it.
He's not showing up.
Wait'll you see
the line for cabs.
It's, like,
45 minutes long.
You said
he's in Chicago.
He's definitely in Chicago.
Well, that guy
is just standing there.
How would we do it?
We just go up to him,
we say, "We're O'Brien."
Maybe he knows O'Brien.
No, he doesn't know
O'Brien.
If he knew O'Brien,
he wouldn't have a sign.
Let's just do it.
Well, what if we get caught?
What's going to happen?
They can't kill us.
Who's going to be O'Brien?
I'll be O'Brien.
Who am I?
You're you.
Just me?
Yeah.
Okay.
What, you don't want
to be you?
Well, if you're
going to be O'Brien,
why can't I be somebody?
Like who?
Dylan Murphy.
Okay.
What, now you want
to be Dylan Murphy?
Well, I like Dylan.
You could be Colin.
Okay. Colin O'Brien.
I'm Dylan Murphy.
I'm Colin O'Brien.
Are we really doing this?
Come on.
Hey, do you have
the time?
Clock over there.
O'Brien.
Yes, sir.
Sorry we're, uh...
we're late.
Here, let me take that for you.
Oh, thank you.
Uh...
I'll get the car
and I'll bring it
around front.
Thank you very much.
Dylan.
Colin.
Can you believe this?
This is incredible.
This is one of
the greatest things
I've ever done
in my life.
I'm going to call
my mother.
What for?
To tell her
I'm in a limo.
Hello, Ma?
It's me.
Guess where I am.
In the back of a limo.
No, nobody died.
It's a long story.
I can't tell you now.
Because I can't.
I said I can't.
If I could, I would.
Would you stop it?
All right, look--
I'm-- I'm getting off.
No, I'm not telling you.
How's this?
I'm never telling you.
I don't care. No!
Fine! Never!
She happy for you?
Can he hear us?
Mm-mm.
Why?
Thought I saw him
look in the mirror
suspiciously.
He can't hear us.
Let's test him.
Hey, driver!
What do you say
we, uh, stop off,
pick up your sister,
have a little fun
back here?
No. He can't hear us.
Where's he dropping us?
Maybe we can get him
to drop us
right at my house.
I'll ask him.
Uh, my dear fellow,
where are you
dropping us?
At Madison Square Garden,
of course.
I have the four passes.
Of course.
The, uh...
the four passes.
Four passes? Four passes
to Madison Square Garden?
Wait a minute.
Of course.
Chicago.
The Knicks are playing
the Bulls tonight.
What?
We are going
to the Knick game!
Michael Jordan!
The Knicks!
We're going
to the Knick game!
Four free passes!
Did I tell you?
I can't believe it!
You may have hit with this one.
Oh, you see?
You see?
I see things as they are,
and I say, "No."
Uh, wait.
Uh, you see things
as they are not,
and you say--
Wait. Uh...
You see thi--
You see things
as they are?
What do you say
when you see things?
Let me call
Elaine and Kramer.
If I see things
as they are,
I would ask,
"Why?" or "Why not?"
Elaine?
It's me.
What are you doing
tonight?
Great.
George and I
have tickets--
Four free passes
to the Knicks-Bulls game
at Madison Square Garden.
Aah!
Lah-dee!
Can you go?
Great.
Listen, call Kramer.
Tell him to meet us
on the corner at 7:00.
All right.
We're going to
pick you up in a limo.
That's right, baby doll.
And listen,
when we pick you up,
I'm Murphy,
and George is O'Brien.
I can't tell you now.
It's a long story.
I am serious.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Excuse me, driver,
we have to make
a little stop first.
I know.
He knows?
Where are we going?
Why are we
pulling off here?
Maybe it's a shortcut.
We're on
the Grand Central.
There's no traffic.
[WINDOW OPENS]
Excuse me, driver,
why are we getting off
this exit?
To pick up the other members
of your party.
Right.
The other members
of our party.
[FORCED CHUCKLE]
The other members
of our party?
What other members
I didn't even know
we were in a party.
Oh, I'm telling you,
the jig is up.
It was a bad jig
to begin with.
We never should've
started this jig.
It was a good jig.
It was a bad jig,
a terrible,
terrible jig.
What are we
going to do now?
They're going to know
you're not O'Brien.
There could be more than one
O'Brien who ordered a limo.
First of all,
you don't look like
any O'Brien, period.
Well, you should've
been O'Brien.
I don't even want to be Murphy
anymore. Do I still have to be?
Yes, you have to.
It makes
no sense, me being Murphy.
You're Murphy.
I'm Seinfeld.
You're Murphy!
Look, let's just
jump out of the car.
We're doing 60 miles an hour.
So we jump and roll.
You won't get hurt.
Who are you, Mannix?
Why are we slowing down?
Are those the people?
All right, put your hands
up over your face.
Pretend you're sleeping.
[DOOR OPENS]
Mr. O'Brien.
Uh, no,
I'm Dylan Murphy.
Mr. O'Brien
had a long trip.
He's sleeping.
[SNORES]
Oh.
[WHISPERING]
Well, I don't want
to disturb him.
We're just
really excited
to meet him
face-to-face finally.
We're faithful readers
of his newsletter.
Newsletter?
And of course
his great book,
The Big Game.
Oh, yes,
he's very proud
of his work
in the, uh...
big game.
[SNORING]
So you've never, uh,
met him before?
[WHISPERING]
No.
Never seen
a picture of him?
Never.
Not even on
the book jacket?
There was no picture
on the book jacket.
Hey, O'Brien, wake up.
Come on. We got company.
[GRUNTS]
Wake up.
GEORGE [LAUGHING]:
Well, hello!
I'm O'Brien.
Hey!
Hey.
You took a cab?
Yeah. So?
How much do you make?
I'm not telling you.
Oh, come on.
No.
I'll tell you
how much I make.
I know
how much you make.
[SIGHS]
I don't even know
why I'm doing this.
I don't even like basketball.
Oh. You ever see
Michael Jordan?
Well, just in those commercials.
Well, maybe you'll see him do
one of those 360 dunks.
What's that?
Oh, it's like this.
Here. You guard me.
What?
The fake!
[CAT MEWLS]
[GARBAGE CANS
CLATTERING]
You know what I never get
with the limo?
The tinted windows.
I mean, nobody cares
who's in the limo anyway.
You see a limo go by,
you know it's either a rich guy
or 50 prom kids with $1.75 each.
Being in the back of a limo,
I'm sorry, it's just...
it's not that cool.
Most of the time,
you feel like you're in, like,
some depressing single guy's
apartment
from, like, 1975.
All that
maroon velour furniture,
a couple of bottles of wine,
three cassette tapes, stains.
You're counting, like,
must've been 10,000 asses
already on this seat.
I don't think we're
going to make the tip-off.
You think someone's
been tipped off?
So, uh...
you've read The Big Game,
have you?
Yes, I've read it,
and...
and I've memorized it.
Ooh. Well...
tell me your impressions.
I would love to hear
what a young woman thinks
of The Big Game.
Well, this is
sort of embarrassing,
but it's changed
my life.
The way you
analyzed the game,
the way you identify
the major players,
well, it left me
breathless.
You're a brilliant...
brilliant man.
Well, it's...
It's just a game.
Remember that, kids.
"Just a game." He's so humble.
Don't forget what you wrote
in the epilogue.
"The fate of the world
"depends on the outcome
of this...
game," hmm?
Well, I was exaggerating a bit.
Just for effect.
He tends to exaggerate.
But, uh,
I mean, it's serious, but...
We are really
looking forward
to your speech tonight.
My-- My speech.
Yes, your secretary
faxed me the copy.
Would you like
to look it over?
Well, you might as well
look it over.
So, what's going on?
How did all this
happen?
Jerry and George
called me from this limo,
and they said
we're all going
to the Knicks-Bulls game.
Limo?
I thought that George
went to pick him up.
He did.
Well, then, why would they
take a limo from the airport?
I don't know.
Well, that's
pretty strange.
He say anything else?
Yeah. He said, um...
He said it's really important
that we call them
O'Brien and Murphy.
O'Brien?
Why would he want
to be called O'Brien?
"And the Jews...
"steal our money
"through their
Zionist-occupied government
"and use the black man
to bring drugs
into our oppressed
white-minority communities."
You're not going to
open with that, are you?
What was that you said
about the myth
of the Holocaust?
Pfft.
Said so many things--
[BANG]
They're shooting!
All right, get down!
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
Oh.
I'm ready
to die for you.
Oh, that's--
That's really very
nice of you, Eva.
Thank you.
But, of course,
you know I would.
I would do anything
for you.
Anything.
Nothing to worry about.
It was just a flat tire,
but rest assured...
[BRIEFCASE CLICKS]
We're prepared to handle
anything that might come up.
Nice-looking Luger.
I'm standing in front
of the Paramount,
adjacent
to Madison Square Garden,
where a growing number
of vociferous
and angry demonstrators
are gathering to protest
the very first
public appearance
of Donald O'Brien,
the leader of the Midwestern
regional chapter
of the Aryan Union,
and reputed to be their
most charismatic spokesman.
The reclusive Mr. O'Brien
is an advocate
of the violent overthrow
of the government.
He has openly professed
a deep admiration
of Adolf Hitler.
Even David Duke
has denounced him
as a dangerous extremist.
There is a full house inside
awaiting his arrival
from the airport.
Sources tell me he is en route
and should be arriving
momentarily.
Police have set up barricades,
but, quite frankly,
Bill and Jean,
I don't think they're any match
for the emotional fuse
that has been lit here tonight.
Reporting from the Paramount,
I'm Jodi Baskerville.
Back to you in the studio.
Something's
very strange here.
George goes
to the airport
to pick up Jerry.
They come back in a limo
with four tickets
to the basketball game
and want to be called
O'Brien and Murphy.
O'Brien. O'Brien?
Why O'Brien?
Elaine?
Dan.
Excuse me a minute.
Hi, Dan.
How are you?
Good.
Um, oh.
This is, um...Kramer.
Kramer.
What's going on?
Huh? Oh.
We're headed down
to protest
this big neo-Nazi rally.
The head
of the Aryan Union
is speaking.
He's in from Chicago.
You should come.
Oh, we can't.
We're going
to the Knicks-Bulls game.
Oh, well, that's...
that's where
the rally is,
at the Paramount,
right next door.
Oh, well, maybe
we'll run into you.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
It's really gonna
be something.
It's the first time he's
ever appeared in public.
No one even knows
what he looks like.
Who?
The head of the Aryan Union.
O'Brien.
JERRY:
What's taking them
so long out there?
Did you see the way
she was looking at me?
She's a Nazi, George.
A Nazi.
I know. I know.
Kind of a cute Nazi, though.
Well, are we gonna
make a plan
before they come back?
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Let's just make
a run for it.
I can't run.
I have a bad hamstring.
How did that happen?
I hurt it in a hotel room.
You know the way they
tuck the covers in real tight
in those hotel rooms?
I can't sleep like that,
so I tried to kick it out
and I pulled it.
Why do they make
their beds so tight?
You sleep with your feet
like that.
It's for a mental patient.
Wait a minute. The phone.
We'll call the police.
911.
She said
she'd do anything.
Yeah, hello. Police?
Listen, we're in the back
of a limo in Queens--
[DOOR OPENS]
Uh...
Astroturf!
You know who's
responsible for that,
don't you?
The Jews!
Oh, the Jews hate grass.
They always have.
They always will.
We'll be ready in a minute.
Would you excuse us
for a minute, Tim-boy?
We're, uh...
kind of in the middle
of something here.
With all due respect,
Mr. O'Brien,
we're just about to leave.
Tim...
who's the head
of the Aryan Union,
you or me?
TIM:
You are.
And who is responsible
for making hate-mongering
and fascism
popular again?
TIM: You are.
Okay?
I think you forgot
something.
I'm sorry.
Good.
Now, get out.
Okay, what are we going to do?
I don't know.
All right, how's this?
We wait till we get
to your street corner,
we see Elaine and Kramer,
then we get out.
They can't shoot us in the city.
Nah. No one's ever been shot
in the city.
I'm telling you,
something is going on.
I can feel it,
sense it.
I'm sure he was just
joking around.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is no joke.
O'Brien's coming in
from Chicago.
Jerry's in a limo,
says he's O'Brien.
That's not funny.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Yes!
What? What is it?
Don't you see?
There's always been something
very strange about Jerry,
always so clean and organized.
So?
Do I have to
spell it out for you?
The limo, the name,
the rally at Madison
Square Garden.
Jerry... O'Brien...
are the same person.
Jerry is the leader
of the Aryan Union!
Jerry's a Nazi?
Oh, boy, I can't even believe
I didn't see it.
Listen, you idiot,
just calm down.
I know Jerry.
He's not a Nazi.
You don't think so?
No. He's just neat.
[WHISTLING
"IF I WERE A RICH MAN"]
TIM: You know,
it's funny.
You don't look
like an O'Brien.
Me?
Yeah, right.
Get a load of this guy.
[LAUGHING]
And you really don't
look like a Murphy.
I may not look
like a Murphy,
but I act
like a Murphy.
He's extremely Murphy.
He's Murphy to a fault.
Where are you from?
Dublin.
Originally.
My parents came over here
when I was 18.
Cereal famine.
Couldn't get a bowl
anywhere.
It was bad.
[IRISH ACCENT]
'Tis a beautiful
country, though.
Lush rolling hills,
and the peat,
ah, the peat.
Sounds more
like Scottish.
We were right
on the border.
Maybe he's with
the company.
What?
The CIA.
Maybe they placed him in there
to infiltrate the organization
from within.
Well, what about
his comedy act?
That's the perfect cover.
All that time on the road...
Look, Jerry, he's too normal
to be a comedian.
These comedians,
they're sick, neurotic people.
Well, what about George?
What about him?
He's part of it.
His whole personality
is a disguise.
There's no real person
can act the way he does.
Elaine, I'm telling you,
they're with the organization.
They're all part of it.
He's in there with Helms
and Hunt and Liddy,
that whole crowd.
Uh-huh.
George and Jerry,
they probably know
who killed Kennedy.
I bet they were
even in on it.
Ah-ha-ha-ha.
All right, all right,
what are we going to do?
I'm not going to
let them hurt you.
I'm not going to...
[MUFFLED] Kramer,
you're hurting me!
Those are our friends
I was telling you about.
Get off of me!
We're going to talk
to them. Pull over.
Get off of me!
It's all right.
Get off!
Hey, O'Brien!
O'Brien!
Is that him?
Yeah, that's him!
Hey, man, look, there's O'Brien!
No-good Nazi bastard!
Let's get him! Get him!
Get him!
What do we do?
Get in the car! Get in the car!
What? What?
[MEN SHOUTING]
Come on, hey!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
O'Brien.
Long time no see.
How's tricks, Murphy?
Why did you call him O'Brien
and him Murphy?
No, he was
talking to me.
He's cross-eyed.
It can be very confusing.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Eva?
It's for me.
EVA: Hello?
It's O'Brien.
O'Brien?
Well, that's weird.
Who are you?
I'm Jerry
Seinfeld.
I'm George
Costanza.
He's Jerry
Seinfeld.
He's George
Costanza.
He's Jerry
Seinfeld.
He's George
Costanza.
This is really
a misunderstanding.
His car broke down.
I told him...
And my car started
shaking violently
about a mile out,
and I...
So he picks me up
without a car.
The limousine
has just pulled up.
It's being surrounded
by a huge crowd of protesters.
This has the makings
of a very ugly scene.
I just didn't have anything
to do tonight,
and then the phone rang,
and it was Jerry...
JERRY: We just wanted
to get a ride into the city.
ELAINE: And he was...
He was supposed
to pick me up, but...
And did I want to go
to the basketball game?
They are banging on the car,
trying to flip it over.
The police seem
unable or unwilling
to control the crowd.
I would imagine
Mr. O'Brien must be having
some very grave doubts
if he made the right choice
for his first
public appearance.
We do not want
to antagonize Nazis.
...the Nazi way.
We have no intention
of upsetting Nazis.
GEORGE:
Do whatever you want...
If you don't bother us,
we won't bother you.
I don't want to make
you unhappy.
I swear.
I swear. I swear.
Get out!
Open the door.
Look! Look, it's Dan!
Hi, Dan!
Elaine?
Hi!
Come on, let's go. Go.
Dan!
I am not O'Brien!
I repeat, I am not O'Brien!
Ask anyone!
Jerry! Jerry!
So I was watching this movie
the other night.
It was a World War II movie,
and, uh, there was Nazis
in the movie,
and I noticed that the Nazis
in those movies
always had, like,
two separate heils.
They had, like, the regular heil
that they would do,
and then, when they were
around the offices,
they had, like,
this casual heil.
Do you remember that one?
Did you ever notice that?
They come in the office,
"Yeah, heil, how are you?
"What's, uh... Is the kid back
with the coffee yet?
"Come on, are you finished
with the copier?
"Yeah, world domination,
Aryan race,
"so whose doughnuts are those?
"Yeah, heil, nice to see you.
Can I have
one of those doughnuts?"
[♪]