You don't want to visualize
your parents having sex.
You know what I mean?
It's somehow
a very uncomfortable thing.
You know, in your mind
that they had to have sex
at least once to have you.
But you still kind of maintain
the image in your head of,
"Well, I don't know.
I'm not positive.
"I can't prove it.
I don't know
if that actually happened."
That's why I think
if I found I was adopted,
that would really come
as great news.
"I'm adopted? That's great!"
I'd be happy to hear that.
That means, technically,
it's possible
that my mother and my father
are really just
really great friends.
I mean, sex is great,
but you don't want to think
your whole life began
because somebody maybe had
a little too much wine
with dinner.
Let me ask you
a question. Mm-hmm.
You're a hostage
captured by terrorists.
Who, me?
You. Anybody. Whatever.
You're in
the little room.
You're chained
to the floor.
You're there
for a long time.
Do you think they would ever
consider doing a laundry?
They'd have to.
It's in the Geneva Convention.
[MIDDLE-EASTERN ACCENT]
"You, take off your socks, pants, underwear.
We're doing a wash. Come on.
Take it off. Take it off."
[JERRY & ELAINE CHUCKLE]
Hey, Georgie.
Hi.
What's the matter?
My mother caught me.
Caught you? Doing what?
You know.
I was alone...
You mean...?
Uh-huh.
She caught you?
Where?
I stopped by the house
to drop the car off,
and I went inside
for a few minutes.
Nobody was there.
They're supposed to
be working.
My mother had
a Glamour magazine.
I started
leafing through it.
Glamour?
So one thing
led to another...
So, what did she do?
First, she screams,
[GRUFFLY]
"George, what are you doing?! My God!"
And it looked like
she was gonna faint.
She started clutching the wall,
trying to hang onto it.
I didn't know whether
to try and keep her
from falling or zip up.
What did you do?
I zipped up.
So she fell?
Yeah.
Well, I couldn't run over there,
the way I was!
No, I guess you couldn't.
I wouldn't
think so.
So she fell, and then
she starts screaming,
"My back, my back!"
So I picked her up,
I took her to the hospital.
[LAUGHING]
Oh! How is she?
She's in traction.
Okay, sorry.
It's not funny, Elaine.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Her back went out.
She's gotta be there
for a couple days.
All she said on the way over
in the car
was "Why, George, why?"
I said,
"Because it's there!"
[CHUCKLES]
Glamour?
[LAUGHS]
All right, I'll tell you
this, though,
I am never doing...
that again.
What, you mean
in your mother's house,
or altogether?
Altogether.
Oh, give me You can stop?
a break. Oh, yeah, right.
Come on.
What? You don't
think I can?
No chance.
You think you could?
Well, I know I could
hold out longer than you.
Care to make it
interesting?
Sure. How much?
Hundred dollars?
You're on.
Wait a second.
Count me in on this.
You?
Yeah.
You'll be out
before we get the check.
I want to be in
on this too.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's a whole other ballgame.
It's apples and oranges.
Why? What?
It's a whole different thing.
Why?
Because you're a woman.
So what?
It's easier for a woman
not to do it than a man.
We have to do it.
It's part of
our lifestyle.
It's like, uh, shaving.
Oh, that is
such baloney.
I shave my legs.
Not every day.
All right, look,
you wanna be in?
Yeah.
You gotta give us odds.
At least 2 to 1.
You gotta put up $200.
No. A thousand.
No. I'll put up 150.
All right.
You're in for 150.
Okay, 150.
All right, now,
how we gonna monitor this?
Well, obviously,
we all know each other
very well.
I'm sure we'll all
feel comfortable
within the confines
of the honor system.
All right. Come on.
ALL: Yeah!
No, Ma.
I'm not gonna see
a psychiatrist.
I don't care
if you do pay for it.
No. Discussion over.
Yeah, all right.
I'll see you later.
Yes, of course,
I'm gonna come by.
All right.
My mother wants me
to see a psychiatrist now.
Why? Because she caught me?
You know,
if everyone who did that
had to go see a psychiatrist...
[CHUCKLES, SNORTS]
Yeah?
Whatever.
[INTERCOM
BUZZES]
How is she?
She'll be fine.
I gotta go to the hospital,
see her tonight.
Yeah?
ELAINE: It's me.
Come on up.
Hey, what are you doing tonight?
Date with Marla.
Oh, the virgin?
Yeah.
Any, uh, progress there?
What's the latest?
Well, I got my troops amassed
along the border.
I'm just waiting for someone
to give me the go-ahead.
Hey, look at this.
Come here.
There's a naked woman
across the street.
JERRY:
Where?
Second floor from the top.
See the window on the left?
Wow!
Who walks around
the house like that?
Maybe she's a nudist.
You know those
nudist colony people.
Yeah.
Let me ask you
a question.
In these
nudist colonies,
do they eat naked
in the dining room?
I would imagine
it's all naked.
What about
the chambermaids,
are they naked too?
They're naked,
the gardener's naked.
Bellhops.
Phew.
It's one
big nude-o-rama.
Hey.
Well, where's my money?
Who caved?
Not me.
What are you
looking at?
There's a naked woman
across the street.
[LAUGHING]
This is gonna be
the easiest money
I've ever made in my life.
So my friend, Joyce,
is teaching an aerobics class.
I'm gonna go tonight.
Yeah, well, the waitress
should've taken it back.
So, then,
I got a call this morning.
You know, I was chosen
to go on the space shuttle.
We're going to Mars.
Uh-huh.
Have a good time.
I'm out.
What?
Yeah, I'm out.
I'm out of the contest.
You're out?
Yeah, yeah.
Wow! That was fast.
Well, it was that woman
across the street.
You know,
you better be careful, buddy.
She's gonna get you next.
And then
there were three.
I don't understand you.
I really don't.
You have nothing
better to do
at 3:00 in the afternoon?
I go out for a quart of milk.
I come home,
and find my son
treating his body
like it was an amusement park.
Ma...
Don't give me "Ma".
It's a good thing
I didn't hit the table.
I could've cracked my head open.
Ma, people can hear you.
Too bad you can't do that
for a living.
You'd be
very successful at it.
You could sell out
Madison Square Garden.
Thousands of people
could watch you.
You could be a big star!
All right, Ma,
that's enough.
I want you to go see
a psychiatrist.
No! I am not
going to see a psychiatrist.
Why? Why not? Why won't you go?
Because I don't want to.
I want you to go see somebody.
Well, I am not going.
It's a good thing
your father's in Chicago.
Hello, Aunt Estelle.
Look at you.
How did this happen?
Is that important, really?
What is this,
a police investigation?
The woman's been through enough.
She has to relive
the experience now?
Hi, Denise. 6:30,
time for your sponge bath.
WOMAN [SENSUALLY]:
Mmmm... Is it 6:30 already?
I fell asleep.
So, George...
What are you
doing now?
I hear you got
some kind of
television-writing
thing.
Yeah...television.
NURSE: Let me help you
off with that.
Here, just slip it
over your head...
Well,
it's about time.
We thought you were gonna
wind up on the street.
[WATER SPLASHING]
So...
what is it
you're doing exactly?
George!
Your cousin, Shelly,
is talking to you!
So when was the last time
you took a class?
Uh, it's been
a while.
Are you psyched?
Yeah. Yeah,
I'm really psyched.
Well, you're gonna thank me
for getting you in here.
Why is that?
See the guy
with the dark hair
and the red shorts?
[GASPS]
Oh, my God.
[SQUEAKS]
John F. Kennedy Jr.'s here.
He's gonna be
in your class today.
In my class?
John Kennedy's
gonna be in my class?
I can get you a spot
right behind him.
He has got a great butt.
Yeah. Butt, butt.
Great butt. John-John's butt.
Let's slow it down
a little.
Slow it down?
Well...you know.
Oh, yeah. I know.
You're okay with that, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
What, you think I care
about the sex?
What kind of person
do you think I am?
That doesn't mean
anything to me.
I don't care about that.
So, I'll see you
Saturday night, then?
Sure.
Saturday night.
All right, then.
Good night.
Not just a good night,
a great night.
[DOOR SHUTS]
♪ Good morning! ♪
Yeah, good morning.
Ha-ha!
Nothing like
some good, solid sack time.
She's not there.
She's doing her wash.
Oh. So...did you make it
through the night?
Yes, I'm proud to say I did!
So you're still
master of your domain.
Yes.
Yes, I am...
[CHUCKLING]
master of my domain.
Ah.
But I will
tell you this:
I am going over
to her apartment,
and I'm telling her
to put those shades down!
Wait, whoa, wh-what
did you just say?
I can't take it anymore.
She's driving me crazy.
I can't sleep.
I can't leave the house.
I'm here,
I'm climbing the walls!
Meanwhile, I'm dating a virgin,
I'm in this contest.
Something's gotta give!
Do you hear
what you're saying?
Can you hear it?
This is a beautiful woman
walking around naked,
and you want to
tell her to stop?!
That's the dumbest thing
I ever heard!
I mean, it's incomprehensi--
I'm not gonna let you do it.
Well, I'm doing it.
Get outta my way.
No, you can't,
you can't.
This is something
that comes about
once in a lifetime.
When we were boys
looking through
our bedroom windows,
we would think, "Why can't there
be a woman out there,
taking her clothes off?"
And now that wish
has come true,
and you want to, pffft,
throw it away?
Look, I'm sorry.
No, I'm not gonna
let you do it, Jerry.
Kramer, get
out of my way.
No. Don't do it, don't do it.
For my sake.
[PLEADS]
God knows, I don't ask you for much!
Now, come on, please, Jerry,
I'm begging you.
Please! Come on! Please!
All right. All right.
Yes!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
She's not there.
Oh, I can wait.
The nurse was giving her
a sponge bath?
Every night at 6:30.
The nurse was gorgeous.
Then I got a look
at the patient.
[CHUCKLES, SNORTS]
I was going nuts.
Oh, man.
So I guess you'll be going back
to that hospital.
Well, my mother, Jerry.
But are you still
master of your domain?
I am king of the county. You?
Lord of the manor.
John F. Kennedy Jr.
What?
He was in my aerobics class.
Really?
Did you talk to him?
No, you don't understand.
He was working out
in front of me.
So, listen,
after the class was over,
I timed my walk to the door
so we'd get there
at the exact same moment,
and he says to me,
"Quite a workout."
"Quite a workout"?
What did you say?
I said, "Yeah."
Good one.
So, then, listen,
listen.
So then I showered
and I dressed,
and I saw him again
on the way out.
So we're walking and talking,
and he asked me my name,
and I think I said Elaine,
but, I mean, who the hell knows?
And so then he says to me,
"Do you want to split
a cab uptown?"
And I said sure,
even though
I was going downtown.
So...we get in the cab,
and, I mean, I have no idea
where I'm going, right?
But this is John F. Kennedy Jr.
we're talking about.
So then he says to me,
"Where do you live?"
And I-- And I was
close to your block,
so I said your building,
so he dropped me off in front,
and I had to take a cab
all the way back downtown
to my house.
Oh, God.
The question is...
are you still
master of your domain?
I'm queen of the castle.
You're back.
Of course, I'm back.
Why wouldn't I be back?
My mother's in the hospital.
I'm gonna pay her a visit.
I know,
but two days in a row?
You didn't have to do this.
You're my mother!
What wouldn't I do
for you?
You know
what you could do?
I haven't eaten lunch or dinner.
I can't eat this hospital food.
Maybe you could run down
to the deli
and get me a sandwich?
You got it, Ma.
A little later.
Could you go now,
Georgie?
I'm very hungry.
I'm weak.
Wait a little while, Ma.
What's the difference?
I don't understand
why you can't do this for me.
I just got here, Ma.
I'd like to spend
a little time with you.
But if you wait,
they won't let you back in.
Visiting hours are almost over.
Ten minutes!
Here, here.
Have some Tic Tacs.
Get the hell outta here!
I'm sorry you came.
NURSE: 6:30.
Time for your bath.
WOMAN:
Mm-hmm.
George...
I'm hungry!
Hang on, Ma. Hang on.
Hi.
Did you get your hair
done today?
No, I just, uh...
fixed it a little bit.
You-know-who isn't here.
He was in
the early class today,
but I think you made quite
an impression on him yesterday.
What? What? Who? M-me?
I made an impression?
What impression?
Let me just put this back.
No, no! Now! Tell me now!
What did he say?
He asked about you.
He asked about me?
John Kennedy
asked about me?
What did he say?
He wanted to know
your situation.
What situation?
I have a situation?
I told him you were single.
That was good.
That was very good.
He said you were just his type.
Okay. You trying to hurt me?
Are you trying to--?
You're trying
to injure me, right?
You're trying to hurt me?
He also told me
to tell you
he'll be
in your neighborhood
tomorrow around 9:00,
so he's gonna stop
in front of your building
if you want to come down
and say hello.
[GASPS]
All right, Ma.
I'll talk to you later.
[SILLY MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing.
I'm watching Tiny Toons
here on Nickelodeon.
It's, uh-- I like kid shows.
They have a very innocent,
wholesome quality.
Okay. All right.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
That's good,
that's good.
That's very, very good.
Well, it's hot in there.
It's hot in there,
so just walk around.
Yeah. That's good.
Don't be ashamed.
That's good. That's good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mm-hmm.
♪ The wheels of the bus
Go round and round ♪
♪ Round and round
Round and round ♪
♪ The wheels
On the bus... ♪
♪ The woman across the block
Has nothing on... ♪
♪ The woman
Across the block... ♪
♪ The windshield wipers
Go whish, whish, whish ♪
♪ Nothing on
Nothing on... ♪
♪ Whish, whish, whish... ♪
All you got
is instant coffee?
Why don't you get
some real coffee?
I don't keep
real coffee in here.
I get my coffee
on the outside!
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?!
It's Elaine.
Come on up!
Where did you get those socks?
I don't know.
I think those are my socks.
How are these your socks?
I don't know,
but those are my socks!
I had a pair just like that
with the blue stripe,
and now I don't
have them anymore.
Right. When you fell asleep
one day on the sofa,
and I took them off
your stinking feet.
They looked so good to me,
I had to have them!
Yeah, well, they're my socks!
They're my socks!
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
What are we doing here?
This is ridiculous.
Can you believe this?
We're fighting. We're fighting!
I haven't been myself lately.
I've been snapping
at everybody lately.
Me too! I'm yelling at
strangers on the street.
Hello.
You caved?
It's over?
You're out?
Oh, my God.
The queen is dead.
I figured you'd cruise,
at least through the spring.
What happened?
It was, uh...
John-John.
Ohhhh... Ohhhh...
John-John. John-John.
But you made it
through the day before.
Yeah, but yesterday, he told
Joyce, the aerobics teacher,
that he wants to meet me
outside here at 9:00 tonight.
Why outside here?
Because he thinks I live here.
Remember when
we shared that cab?
He dropped me off out in front.
He's picking me up.
All right, Costanza.
It's you and me.
And then...
there were two.
[SNIFFS]
Elaine Benes-Kennedy
Junior.
[MARLA MOANING]
Let's go in the bedroom.
Really?
Yes.
You sure?
Yes!
You really want to?
I do. I'm ready.
Okay.
I know how difficult
this must've been for you.
You don't know the half of it.
What do you mean?
Well, it's kind of silly, but--
Contest?! A contest!
This is what you do
with your friends?
Well, no,
it was just a bet.
I mean, it actually started
with George and his mother.
I don't want to
hear another word.
And to think
how close I came
to you being the one.
I must've been
out of my mind!
Marla. Hi.
Oh, I'm glad
I ran into you.
I don't want to have
anything to do with you
or your perverted friends.
What?
Ooh! Get away from me!
You're horrible, horrible,
all of you!
ELAINE:
What happened?
I told her
about the contest.
Oh, boy. She's a wacko.
Hey, what happened?
What?
Thought you were
meeting Kennedy.
Ah. He didn't show.
Yeah, he did.
What? He's-- He's out there?
Oh, my God. I gotta go.
No, no, no.
He just left.
What?
Yeah, he was out there
talking to Marla.
Marla?
Yeah, you know,
she was, like, crying,
and he was consoling her,
and then
she got into his car,
and they just drove away.
He left with Marla the Virgin?
Yeah.
They drove away?
Yeah. Drove away.
You know, I said hello
to him, you know.
Oh, my God in heaven.
[GASPS]
Is that...?
Kramer?!
[GASPS]
He's waving.
Oh, John...
that was wonderful.
Men want to see women naked.
Whatever it is
that you won't show us,
that's what we're obsessed
with seeing.
I mean, if women
always wore hats in public,
all the time,
you'd see men buying
Playhead magazine.
You know...
Skulls of the Big 10.
This would be the only thing
that what we're interested in.
Let's start worrying
about these cultures,
like in National Geographic,
where everybody's naked?
You know, you see
all these peop--
What are the men
in these cultures
trying to look at
when the women walk by?
How could you have a strip club
in a place like that?
Woman goes on stage,
takes off the necklace,
takes out the nose ring.
That's it, show's over.
The men
are in the audience going,
"Boy, did you see
that little indentation there
"in the top of her lip?
I told you, man,
this place is hot!"