ANNOUNCER:
Last week on Seinfeld...
Oh, uh, yeah,
I'm here for the audition.
The Tonight Show called me
to come out
and do the show on the 28th,
and they're giving me
two free tickets to L.A.
You wanna go?
A free ticket?
Yeah, in fact,
we could track down Kramer.
I got a very big meeting.
I got people interested
in my treatment.
Pretty young thing.
She was.
We're going
on a two-day trip.
What are you,
Diana Ross?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I implore you.
Don't look.
It's Fred Savage.
Oh, did I frighten you?
I'm not crazy.
I may look weird,
but I'm just like you.
I'm just a regular guy trying
to make it in this business.
No witnesses?
Just the trees,
Johnny.
Just the trees.
Could you not tuck
the blankets in?
'Cause I can't sleep
all tucked in.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
I think we just
caught a break.
All right.
That's one tuck,
and one no tuck.
So that's when I said,
"Hey, Kramer, dude,
Have you ever
killed a man before?"
You're on
The Tonight Show. NBC.
Who else
is on the show?
I don't know.
Corbin Bernsen.
Do I have a case
for you guys to do
on L.A. Law.
I don't want to tell you
how to run your show.
No, of course not.
Really, it's enough
with the bar already.
He's a very handsome man,
passionate, intense,
but troubled, strange.
Let's pick up this,
uh...Kramer.
Kramer!
Police have just released
a photo of the suspect
being sought in connection
with the slayings.
He is known only as Kramer.
There are many different jobs
in the police.
It seems to me
that "chalk outline guy"
is one of the better jobs
that you can get.
You know,
it's not too dangerous,
the criminals are long gone.
That seems like a good one.
I don't know who they are.
I guess they're people
that wanted to be
sketch artists,
but they couldn't draw too well.
"Listen, Johnson,
forget the sketches.
"Do you think
if we left the dead body
"right there on the sidewalk,
"You could manage
to trace around it?
Could you do that?"
I don't even know
how that helps them
solve the crime.
You know, they look at the thing
on the ground--
"Oh, his arm was like that
when he hit the pavement.
That means the killer
must have been...Jim."
GEORGE: He's on the lam.
He's on the loose!
Would you let go
of my arm?
I'm trying to drive.
You're gonna get us
both killed.
What are we
supposed to do?
What do you do
in a situation like this?
Should we call
a lawyer? The police?
Obviously, we're gonna
call the police
and tell them
he's not the guy.
We hope
Couldn't be the guy.
Nah.
God, I'm starved.
I'm weak with hunger.
How can you
think of food
at a time like this?
At a time like what?
I'm hungry.
My stomach doesn't know
that Kramer's wanted.
I told you
to have breakfast.
You should have had
breakfast!
I couldn't have
breakfast.
It was lunchtime.
The three-hour
time difference threw me.
I wanted
a tuna fish sandwich.
They wouldn't serve me
a tuna fish sandwich
because they were
only serving breakfast.
You should've had
some eggs.
For lunch?
Who eats eggs
for lunch?
Have you ever heard
of egg salad?
Why didn't you
say something?
I gotta tell you
about the existence
of egg salad?
I need food, Jerry.
I'm feeling faint.
I'm getting
light-headed.
I got to call
the police.
There's a pay phone
over there.
Pay phone in L.A.
Look, it's a miracle.
KRAMER:
♪ She'll be comin' Around the mountain ♪
♪ When she comes
Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ She'll be comin' around-- ♪
[SLIPS AND FALLS]
I have no change.
You got any change?
No, I don't have any change.
I never carry change.
Well, I need change,
and all I got is 20s.
I have a 10.
So break it.
I hate asking
for change.
They always make a face.
It's like I'm asking them
to donate a kidney.
So buy something.
What?
I don't know,
some mints or Tic Tacs.
Breath problem?
No, I just want
some change.
Tell me.
Your breath is fine.
It's delightful.
It's delicious.
You know,
I haven't eaten anything.
I just wanna
call the police.
Why don't you
just call 911?
But is this an emergency?
Of course it is.
How is this an emergency?
Your friend
has been accused
of being
a serial killer.
I think
that qualifies.
All right, I'll call 911.
Think he did it?
Could he have done it?
He couldn't have done it.
How could he have done it?
Couldn't do it. Could he?
Hello, 911?
How are you?
I'm sorry. Just a reflex.
I know it's
an emergency number.
It is an emergency.
My friend has been accused
of being the Smog Strangler,
and I know he didn't do it.
They're putting me through
to the detective
in charge
of the investigation.
Making
terrific headway.
What's my name?
Who am I?
I'm, uh...
[QUIETLY]
George Costanza.
What's the matter
with you?
Are you crazy?
What are you
using my name for?
Oh, don't be a baby.
What are you scared of?
What am I scared of?
The same thing you are:
Everything.
Why don't you
use your own name?
Your name is a good name.
Costanza. Sounds like
it stands for something.
They'll believe us.
Really?
Sure.
You think so?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, I have some very
important information
regarding
the Smog Strangler.
Get yourself
a mint or something.
Can I come in
right now?
I suppose.
Where are you located?
Where is that?
I don't know
where we are.
Where are we?
I don't know.
We don't know.
He says
ask somebody.
Ask that guy.
Excuse me, where are we?
Earth.
Hey, you know,
I'm on the phone
with the police.
Some guy just gave me
a wise answer.
Ask that woman.
Excuse me, miss,
what street are we on?
I don't know.
You don't know?
How could you not know
what street you're on?
You don't know.
George, it says here
on the phone.
It's 12145
Ventura Boulevard.
Uh-huh, okay.
Do we know where the 101 is?
No.
Do we know where the 170 is?
Do we know where the 134 is?
No.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
He's gonna send
a black and white
to pick us up.
Black and white?
Cop car.
Why didn't you
just say that?
I thought it sounded
kind of cool.
Yeah, real cool.
You're a cool guy.
Oh, you are.
I guarantee you Lupe's
gonna tuck your covers in.
I'll bet you.
How much?
Her tip.
You got a bet.
Okay.
How much do you tip
a chambermaid?
Which one of you
is Costanza?
Get in.
Hi. How are you?
Guys, listen,
do either one
of you have, like,
a mint
or a piece of gum?
[SNEEZES]
Hey, Jerry,
do me a favor.
Close your window.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, get out of here.
Hey, officer,
he's fooling around back here.
Cut it out back there.
He started it.
I did not.
You guys gonna be
going through
some red lights?
I don't think so.
But you could.
Oh, yeah.
Of course we could.
We could do anything
we want.
We can drive
on the wrong side
of the road.
Yeah, we do that
all the time.
You should see the looks
on the people's faces.
Shoot people.
You guys
ever shot anybody?
No.
Hey, can I
flip on the siren?
What are you
bothering them for?
I'm just asking.
All they have to do
is say no.
Yeah, go ahead.
[SIREN WAILS]
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
Check it out.
Can I try it?
Yeah, go ahead.
Hurry up.
[SIREN WAILS]
Scared the hell
out of that guy!
You know what
I've never understood?
Why did they change
the siren noise?
When I was a kid,
it was always,
"Whaa...Whaa,"
you know,
and now it's,
"Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo.
Whoo-whoo-whoo."
Why'd they do that?
I mean, did they
do some research?
Did they find out
that "whoo-whoo"
is more effective siren
than "whaa"?
Yeah, and, hey,
what about those
English sirens,
you know?
BOTH: "Eee-a, eee-a,
eee-a, eee-a."
Hey!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Come on.
Wow.
I'm dizzy.
Nice shotgun.
Thanks.
Clean as a whistle.
You could eat
off that shotgun.
What is that,
a 12-gauge?
Yeah.
Twelve-gauge.
That seems to be
the most popular gauge.
Big gauge. My favorite.
Mine too.
Love the 12-gauge.
Makes the 11-gauge
look like a cap pistol.
What have we got
over there?
What?
I don't know.
Looks like
a possible 519.
519? What's a 519?
Where?
Think so?
Looks like it.
I can't believe this.
A 519?
Where? Where? I can't see.
This is car 23.
We have a possible 519
in progress, over.
All right,
let's pull over
and check it out.
Pull over?
JERRY:
You can't pull over.
GEORGE:
What are you doing?
Where do you think
you're going?
Pull over?
The lieutenant
is waiting to see us.
Hey, hey, hey,
we're in a rush here!
We have
an appointment.
What are you doing?
Great.
GEORGE: There's a bag
of Pepperidge Farm
cookies up there.
JERRY: What kind?
Milano.
Cops eating Milanos?
What crazy town
is this?
Should I take some?
I think that's a 519.
I'm starving.
OFFICER 1:
Spread 'em.
Hey, they're
busting this guy.
GEORGE:
They're cuffing him.
[SPITS]
I can't believe this.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I can't believe that cops
still have to read
that whole "You have the right
to remain silent" speech
to every criminal they arrest.
I mean, is there anybody
that doesn't know that by now?
I mean, can't they just go,
"Freeze! You're under arrest.
You ever seen a Baretta?"
"Yeah."
"Good. Get in the car."
Hi.
I'm Jerry.
George. How you doing?
Oh. Heh.
What'd you do?
Nothing.
Oh, yeah, right.
Me neither.
Hey, I didn't do nothing.
Shut up.
Hot out.
Brutal.
What do you tip
a chambermaid?
I don't know.
Five bucks a night.
No!
A dollar.
Two, tops.
Hey, you guys
aren't cuffed.
What are you,
narcs?
Narcs.
Imagine.
Us narcs.
No, no, no.
No, actually,
we're friends
of a serial killer.
Just trying
to help him out.
Really?
Yeah.
That's very nice.
Oh, thank you.
Suspected
serial killer.
He didn't
actually do it.
Yeah, well, we don't think.
We're pretty sure.
A dollar a night?
Yeah,
that's a good tip.
Aw, that stinks.
I read it
in Ann Landers.
Aw, Ann Landers sucks!
Hey, shut up
back there.
DISPATCHER [OVER RADIO]:
Attention, all units. Attention, all units.
All units, code three.
All units in the area,
code three in progress,
1648 North Las Palmas.
Units require assistance
in apprehension 702.
That's
the Smog Strangler.
JERRY:
Kramer!
They got him.
Let's go.
[SIREN WAILING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
We've got to go
and see
what's happening.
I don't know
why I'm doing this.
Oh, man.
Jerry! George!
You're under arrest
for first-degree murder
in the death
of Miss Chelsea Lang.
REPORTER:
Why'd you do it?
People want to know,
please!
What possessed you?
Well, I don't know.
You have
any regrets?
How are you?
Hey!
[LAUGHS]
[GLASS BANGS]
Hey, how you doing?
Jerry, George.
We're doing fine. How are you?
What? Oh, me?
Fabulous. Just fabulous.
I got a lot of auditions,
a lot of callbacks.
And I got a lot
of interest
in my movie treatment.
I'm in development.
I'm developing vehicles.
Man, there's a lot
of energy here, man.
You know, the vibe,
it's powerful.
I'm just swept up in it.
Yeah, I'm a player.
A player?
Oh, yeah, I'm a player.
Kramer, do you realize
what's going on here?
Do you know
why you're here?
[LAUGHS]
What, this?
I'll be outta here
in a couple of hours.
Hey, guess
who I met today.
Fred Savage.
Oh, nice kid.
A really good kid.
You know, we're talking about
doing a project together.
Kramer, you've been arrested
as a serial killer.
So?
I'm innocent.
I mean, you guys believe
that I'm innocent,
don't you?
Jerry? George?
Yeah, sure.
[LAUGHS]
Kramer, let's go.
Lieutenant wants to see you.
Yeah, okay, yeah.
All right. Look.
I'll be out of here by noon.
Maybe we'll have lunch together,
huh?
Hey, is it all right
if I talk to them again?
Yeah, okay.
Help me!
Oh, God, help me!
Get me out of here!
George, Jerry, get me out!
Get me--!
I didn't kill anyone.
I swear! I swear to God!
Don't you ever swear
to my god, Kramer.
My god is the god
that protects
the innocent
and punishes
evil scum like you.
Have you got that?
You're making a big mistake.
No! You made
a mistake, Kramer.
Sickies like you
always do.
The only difference
is this time
you're gonna pay.
What?
Now, you might beat
the gas chamber, Kramer,
but as long as I have got
a breath in my body,
you will never, ever,
see the light of day again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You got the wrong man!
It wasn't me!
Oh, yeah, right.
Maybe it was one
of your other
personalities, huh?
What?
The wise guy,
the little kid,
the bellhop,
the ballplayer,
maybe the door-to-door
vacuum cleaner salesman,
but not you, right?
No, you wouldn't
hurt a fly.
You just couldn't
help yourself,
could you, Kramer?
You saw a life
brimming brightly
with optimism
and verve,
and you had to
snuff it out.
All right,
can I talk to somebody?
Can I just explain?
You're not letting me explain.
I'm not interested in your
explanations, Kramer.
Sure, I bet you've got
a million of them.
Maybe your mother
didn't love you enough.
Maybe the teacher didn't
call on you in school
when you had
your little hand raised.
Maybe the pervert
in the park
had a present
in his pants, huh?
Well, I've got
another theory, Kramer.
You're a weed.
No.
Society's filled
with them. No, no.
And you're choking the life
out of all the pretty flowers.
[WHIMPERING]
You see something young,
something pretty,
you just gotta choke
the life out of it.
Don't you,
Kramer, huh?
You killed the pretty flowers,
didn't you, Kramer?
You killed
the pretty little flowers,
didn't you?
You dirty, filthy,
stinking weed!
Didn't you?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I...
Lieutenant.
For you.
[SOBBING]
Martel.
Yeah.
What is it,
lieutenant?
Let him go.
What?
But lieutenant--
You heard me.
I said let him go.
Get him out of here.
They just found
another body
up in Laurel Canyon.
Go on, Kramer,
get out of my sight.
Hey, how'd you know
about the guy in the park?
I said, beat it.
[THUD]
[LAUGHS]
What?
What happened?
Somebody got killed
while they had me in custody.
Really?
Yeah.
You hear that?
Somebody else was killed.
No kidding!
Somebody else
got killed?
While he was in jail.
So you're free!
Yes, I'm free...
♪ 'Cause the murderer
Struck again ♪
Hey!
So, Kramer,
what are you gonna do?
Do? Do?
Hey, I'm doing
what I do.
You know, I've always
done what I do.
I'm doing what I do
the way
I've always done it,
and the way
I'll always do it.
Kramer, what the hell
are you talking about?
Well, what do you
want me to say?
That things haven't worked out
the way that I planned?
That I'm struggling,
barely able to keep
my head above water?
That L.A.'s a cold place
even in the middle of summer?
That it's a lonely place,
even when you're stuck
in traffic
on the Hollywood freeway?
That I'm no better
than the screenwriter
driving a cab,
the starlet turning tricks,
the producer in a house
he can't afford?
Is that what you want me to say?
I'd like to hear that.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not
saying that.
You know,
things are going
pretty well for me here.
I met a girl.
Kramer,
she was murdered.
Yeah, well, you know,
I wasn't looking
for a long-term relationship.
I was on TV.
As a suspect
in a serial killing.
Okay, yeah,
all right.
You guys gotta put
a negative spin
on everything,
don't you?
What do they put
in this tuna?
Tastes like a dill.
I think it's a dill.
So you're not gonna come back
to New York with us?
No, no...
I'm not ready.
You know, I mean,
things are starting
to happen for me.
Taste this.
Is this a dill?
No, it's a tarragon.
Listen, Kramer...
I'm sorry about
that whole fight we had
about you having
my apartment keys
and everything.
Well...
Okay, it's forgotten.
Tarragon?
Yeah.
Oh, you're crazy.
All right.
Take it easy, buddy.
Yeah, okay.
Yep, take care.
Stay in touch.
Hey, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Come on, give me a hug.
Kramer, Kramer,
my sandwich.
You're crushing
You know,
it's so nice
when it happens good.
[GRUNTS]
Mint?
No, thanks.
I gotta tell you,
I'm really disappointed
in Lupe.
It's been three days already.
Forget about Lupe.
Think she gets to take
any of those little bars
of soap home?
No, I don't.
You'd think
at the end of the week
when they're handing out
the checks,
they'd thrown in a few soaps.
Yeah, maybe they should
throw in
a couple of lamps too.
I tell you something.
If I owned a company,
my employees would love me.
They'd have huge pictures of me
up on the walls
and in their home...
like Lenin.
How much did you wind up
tipping her?
Oh, my God, I forgot.
That's why communism
didn't work.
Hey!
[DOOR BANGS]
Oh...
Got any mustard?
This is empty.
Yeah, there's
a new one in there.
No, no, I don't like
this one.
It's too yellow.
[WHISPERS]
Did you know he was back?
No.
Got any pickles?
Help yourself.
Yeah.
All right.
Kramer, what are you
doing here?
I'm getting something to eat.
JERRY: Kramer.
Here.
All right.
Authorities disclosed today
that the latest suspect
in the Smog Stranglings
was apprehended this week
on an unrelated charge,
but somehow managed to escape
from the police car
in which he was being held.
Tobias Lehigh Nagy,
who is also wanted
in connection with a series
of unrelated slayings
in the Northwest,
is still at large,
his whereabouts unknown.
He is described
as 5'5", bald,
and reputedly
a very generous tipper.
The thing about L.A. to me
that kind of threw me
was when, you know,
they have the smog alerts
out there,
and they actually recommend
that people stay indoors
during the smog alert.
Now, maybe I'm way off,
but don't you think--?
Wouldn't you assume
that the air in the house
pretty much comes
from the air in the city
where the house is?
I mean, what do they think,
we live in a jar
with a couple of holes
punched in the top?
What the hell
is going on out there?
It's very strange.
I mean, do you realize
it is now possible
for parents to say
to their children,
"All right, kids,
"I want you in the house
and get some fresh air.
Summer vacation.
Everybody indoors."
[♪]