NARRATOR:
Here's what happened last week.
So George and I
went up to NBC,
and we told them
the idea for the series.
Now we're just waiting
to sign the contract.
Jerry, I want you
to sign that contract.
We're gonna sign it!
In fact, George is out
with the woman from NBC now.
I'm afraid we're
gonna have to pass.
You're passing?
Well, it's much too low.
That's it for this piece
of junk. I've had it.
Is that the one
your parents gave you?
Yeah, but
it never works!
Where's that watch
we bought you? At the jeweler.
I would like somebody to hit me.
So, what's the matter
with this Davola guy?
He's after Jerry now.
You know, I never
had a back problem
until that night I slept
on the convertible sofa.
Cuban cigars.
It's a present from my father.
Here you go.
What? Oh, cigars?
Yeah. Cubans.
[SCREAMING]
Wow!
[VELCRO RIPPING]
[SCREAMS]
What's wrong?
The Velcro.
I can't stand Velcro.
That tearing sound.
Now, listen to me.
I'm negotiating.
Negotiation.
This is what you do
in business.
Leave all my stuff here?
Leave it.
Tell us about the trip.
How's Dr. Reston?
He has this power over me, okay?
I mean, he has this way
of manipulating
every little word that I say.
He's like a "Svenjolly."
You tell this guy
you're seeing somebody else.
That's the easiest way
to get out.
His name is...
Kramer.
Tell this young man
to give me a call.
My wallet's gone!
Where'd you get that watch?
I found it
in the garbage can.
What kind of an idiot
throws away
a perfectly good watch?
It's an entire industry
of bad gifts, aren't they?
All those executive gifts,
any stupid, goofy,
brass, wood thing.
They put a piece of green felt
on the bottom.
"It's a golf, desk, tie
and stress organizer, Dad."
To me, nothing compares
with the paperweight
as a bad gift.
There's no better way
than a paperweight
to express to someone that,
"I refuse to put any thought
into this at all."
Where are these people working
that the papers are just blowing
right off of their desk?
What, are their desks screwed
to the back of a flatbed truck
going down the highway
or something?
What, are they typing
up in the crow's-nest
of a clipper ship?
What do you need
a paperweight for?
[♪]
I don't understand this
jeweler, Jimmy Sherman.
He brings in a watch,
it takes over a week to fix.
He fixed yours in one day.
Oh, you know
these jewelers.
They're enigmas.
They're mysteries
wrapped in a riddle.
She's very attractive.
She's okay.
Just okay?
She's nice.
She's better than nice.
She's all right.
She's beautiful.
She's not beautiful.
I think she's beautiful.
So you ask her out.
I'm not gonna ask her out.
Why not?
If you don't think
she's beautiful,
there's something wrong
with you.
She's pretty.
She's not beautiful.
I should drop dead
if she's not beautiful.
I think that's a little extreme.
She's all right.
Two exact same watches.
He tells you a week,
and him a day.
How could that be?
Something's fishy
about this.
He said what?
"The hell with them."
"The hell with them"?
Those were his exact words.
Oh, boy.
He said, "We've got 500 shows
to choose from.
"Why should we give two guys
who have no idea
and no experience more money?"
He was pretty emphatic?
Pounded on his desk.
Pounded?
I told you
to take the offer.
Look, I-I-I... I had
nothing to do with this.
It wasn't my decision.
It was Jerry. Jerry told me.
I'm the creative guy.
He handles the business end.
You said it was insulting.
I was quoting him!
Why would I
be insulted?
I'm never insulted.
You could call me "baldy,"
dump soup on my head.
Nothing insults me.
Well, there's nothing
I can do.
Don't they make
a counteroffer?
How can he just cancel
our whole deal like that?
What kind of a maniac
is this guy?
I mean, he just--
He says no, and that's it?
Well, yeah, that's
the way Russell is.
He doesn't like
to play games.
Well, he has to play!
He can't just not play!
We're playing!
Look, I-I-I
gotta see him.
How do I get
in touch with him?
You'll have to wait till Monday.
Mo-- No, no, I can't
wait till Monday.
That's impossible.
I gotta talk to him now.
Where does he live?
[LAUGHING]
I can't give you his address.
Address--
[ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
Okay, he wants
to talk to you.
I couldn't talk him
out of it.
So you just tell him
that you're my boyfriend,
and that we're
in love, okay?
Can you do that?
Yeah. I'm your
boyfriend. Yeah.
Okay.
Have we been intimate?
Yeah. Yeah, we've been intimate.
All right,
how often do we do it?
Kramer, how is that important?
Honestly, do you really think
he's gonna ask--?
Elaine, he's a psychiatrist.
They're interested
in stuff like that.
All right. All right.
We do it, uh...
five times a week. Okay?
Ooh, baby.
Oh, my...
All right, listen.
Just tell me something.
What are you gonna say?
I know what I'm gonna say.
But I would like
to hear it.
I don't want to
say it out loud.
Kills the spontaneity.
You know, Gleason,
he never rehearsed.
Go ahead. Do it.
All right. Okay.
you talk to him.
I'll talk to him.
Hey, how's your hair?
Well, yeah, it's good.
You're not the type who should
be playing with matches.
Seriously, Kramer.
Uh, yes. Uh, uh,
Dr., uh, Reston.
Is he in?
Well, this is Kramer,
and he's expecting
my call.
Okay.
♪ Johnny Yuma ♪
♪ Was a rebel ♪
♪ He rode through the land ♪
Is he...?
Yes, yes, uh,
Dr., uh, Reston.
Well, hello there.
Yeah, well,
I'm a good friend of Elaine's.
No, no, not friends!
Well, actually, uh,
we're not friends.
Uh, we're, uh...
We're much more than friends,
and, uh...
Well, I'm afraid we have
a bit of a problem.
Well, the point is, doctor,
I'm very much in love
with Elaine,
and she's very much
in love with me,
and, uh, well, uh,
we would, uh, appreciate it
if you would cease and desist
and allow us to pursue
our courtship unfettered.
If not, I can
assure you, doctor,
that I could make things
very unpleasant for you
and your staff,
if you have one.
[SLAPS SHOULDER]
Yes.
Yeah, but the point that I--
Uh, ye--
Well, no. Well, yeah, that's--
It's possible.
Uh, well,
I suppose I could,
but I'd have to shift
a few things around.
Wait. Hold on for
a second, will you?
Uh, go ahead. Yeah.
All right. Uh...
Y-yeah. Yeah.
Well, okay.
I look forward
to it too.
Yeah. Heh.
Okay. So long.
What happened?
What did he say?
What's going on here?
Uh, okay, now,
he, uh, you know--
He wants to
get together.
Get together?!
Why?
Well, you know,
he wants to talk.
Well, why didn't you just
say no?
[STAMMERING]
That's interesting.
[GROANS]
Did you enjoy your croissant?
It was...different.
And how was yours?
Oh, very good.
You should try our mousse.
It'll change
your life expectancy.
[LAUGHS]
No, thanks. Just the check.
What's the matter with you?
What?
Why didn't you flirt with her?
Come on.
She was flirting with you.
Why didn't you say something?
What am I gonna say?
You just sat there.
Well, you made me uncomfortable.
You're a comedian.
Couldn't you
come up with something?
Where's the bathroom?
In the back,
on your right.
Dad!
Will you stop it.
Jerry, let go. Jerry...
Would you let me pay just once?
You're out of your mind.
How you gonna pay?
You don't even have a wallet!
Don't worry about it!
What are you gonna do?
What's the difference?
We'll figure something out.
You're not paying.
All right, fine.
You figure something out.
I'd be very curious to know
how you pick up a check
with no money.
'Cause if this works,
the whole monetary
system's obsolete.
We're back to wampum.
I'm going to the bathroom.
How the hell am I
gonna pay for this?
[WATER SPLASHING]
They give you
some portion here, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Uncle Leo, I hope
I wasn't rude to you
that day I bumped
into you on the street.
I really did have
to get to a meeting.
Oh, no, no,
I understand.
I got plenty of friends
in show business.
I know you're all
very busy.
So you found that watch
in a garbage can, huh?
Yeah. In fact, it was
right after I ran into you.
Oh...
You know, a friend of mine
has a watch just like that.
I'd love to replace it
for him as a gift.
Well, I haven't seen
too many like these.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe, uh, you want
to sell me that one.
Oh, sure.
[LAUGHING]
Hang on a second.
I got a little
proposition for you.
There is a George Bonanza
to see you.
Costanza. Costanza.
George Costanza.
The guy who pitched him the show
with the stories about nothing.
Jerry Seinfeld.
Jerry Seinfeld's friend.
Seinfeld friend.
He says call him Monday.
Mr. Dalrymple...
Mr. Dalrymple,
I have to talk to you.
It's about the show.
It was all--
Excuse me.
It was a terrible
misunderstanding, sir.
Just five minutes.
Just five minutes
of your time.
Thank you! Thank you,
Mr. Dalrymple.
Very good, sir.
You don't understand.
I can't allow my son
to pay for me.
Look, as soon as I
get back to Florida,
I promise you,
I'll mail you a check.
Why don't you just let him pay,
and then you can pay him back.
No, no, he won't let me do that.
Why don't you just put the money
in his pants pocket
unsuspectingly?
He could wash them.
Monsieur, we are running
a reputable business.
Don't tell me about business.
I sold raincoats for 35 years.
Aha! But you did not
give them away, did you?
You don't understand--
Monsieur, I cannot get involved
with you and your family, huh?
[SCOFFS]
Okay, now, look.
Don't take too long.
Look at this building.
What is this?
I don't know.
It's a building.
The door is
on a diagonal.
So what?
It's architecturally
incorrect.
Just go.
Is this a bad time?
I hope I'm not
disturbing anything.
We were about to sit down
to dinner.
This is Cynthia.
Oh. Oh, hi. Hi.
Hi, nice
to meet you.
What are you having, veal?
No.
Looks like veal.
It's not veal.
Well, it's a good-looking
piece of meat.
Wow, this is some place.
A duplex, huh?
Look at this, you got stairs
in an apartment.
All my life I dreamed about
having steps in an apartment.
Even one step.
Sunken living room.
Although one step
is not all that sunken.
Who gave you my address?
No, that's a fair question.
It is.
Um... Jerry. Yeah.
Jerry's a friend of mine.
He gave it to me.
Unbelievable how many addresses
of people this guy has.
He's got Marlon Brando's.
I could go to Marlon Brando's
house if I really wanted to.
Course, I wouldn't.
I mean, the guy is, uh...
Well, obviously,
the guy has his problems.
So, what's this about?
You wanna talk about the show?
Well, you know,
it's really very funny.
Because you know
what we got here, really?
We really just have
a terrible misunderstanding.
You see, when I
passed on the deal,
I thought that's what
Jerry wanted me to say.
You know, I-- I misinterpreted.
Russell, where's the TV Guide?
Oh, what time is it, 8:30?
I'll tell you what's on.
You got Major Dad, Blossom--
Very funny program.
Blossom's on Monday.
Are you sure?
Oh, look who I'm talking to.
The president of NBC.
Look, Mr. Costanza,
it's too late
now anyway.
I already made a deal
with another writing team.
All right, all right, look.
We're people, you and me, huh?
Businessmen,
colleagues, if I may.
Let's not quibble.
We'll do it for the 13,000.
Thirteen thousand,
and I never came up here,
we never talked, all right?
You take good care.
It's nice seeing you again,
and nice meeting you.
Cynthia, right?
Now, look,
these deals are already made.
All right, let me just say this.
Ten thousand dollars,
all right?
And now I'm going below
what you wanted to pay.
You're having your dinner.
Have your veal,
or whatever it is. Enjoy.
Mr. Costanza...
All right. That's it.
All right. Good.
Eight thousand dollars. Cynthia,
again, nice meeting you.
Have I commented
on the shoes?
I love suede.
It's so thick and rich.
Do you ever rub it
against the grain?
All right.
Russell, can we eat?
All right, 8000.
You made Jerry very happy.
[SOFT KNOCK ON DOOR]
Could I just use your bathroom
for a moment?
All right. 200,
but that's as high as I can go.
I really think
you're being unreasonable here.
Jerry, I'd give you the watch.
It's not the money.
I happen to like it.
Look, I happen to know
how much that watch costs.
It's a $60 watch.
You paid 40
to get it fixed.
That's $100.
I'm offering you 200.
I never seen a band like this.
All right, 300
plus 50 for the repair.
350. That's it.
You have it on you?
Yeah, I think I do.
This is unbelievable.
What the hell
is going on here?
Well, it's a--
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Thank you for coming in.
Well, thank you.
Please, sit down.
Alrighty.
[LEATHER SQUEAKING]
[SQUEAKING]
Could I offer you
something to drink?
Coffee? Anything?
Okay, yeah. I'll have a...
Do you have a decaf cappuccino?
I don't think we have that.
Well, that's a little strange.
Why does that surprise you?
Well, it's, um...
It's a very popular drink.
This is an office.
That's true,
but, you know, I can't help
but think that--
So tell me,
Mr. Kramer--
Okay. Yeah, sure.
Tell me all about, um,
you and Elaine.
Oh, alrighty, um...
[SQUEAKING]
Uh, well, what we have here,
doctor, is, um...
is an extraordinary
situation.
Is it?
Oh, you better believe it.
♪ Travelin' along
Singin' a song ♪
♪ Side by side ♪
[OFF-KEY] ♪ Side by side ♪
Wow. You really have
a terrible voice.
Do I know you?
Uh...I don't think so.
Because you really
look familiar.
Oh, well, you know,
maybe you've seen me.
My face is on, um,
Mount Rushmore.
Oh, yes, of course, that's it.
I guess I'm just
used to seeing it
on a much larger scale.
Oh, yeah, right.
I replaced, um, Teddy Roosevelt.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm.
Trustbuster. Bust this.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[GIGGLING]
You know, I never
thought of it
like that before, doctor.
You are absolutely right.
I'm glad we agree.
Hey, would you like a cigar?
You know, they're Cubans.
I'd love one.
Yeah.
You know, I think Elaine
is a wonderful woman.
You two are gonna make
a wonderful couple.
If you ever feel...
you need
to talk to someone...
Mm-hmm.
...about anything,
you have my number.
Well, that's very kind of you.
These are good, huh?
Uh-oh.
I cannot believe
I'm doing this.
I never meet
people like this.
You're not a nut,
are you?
No, I don't think so.
[LAUGHING]
I-- I can't believe
I'm doing this.
I-- I never do stuff
like this.
Really? I give out my number
to just about every customer
who comes in here.
Really? You don't
seem that desperate.
Oh, yeah. Actually,
I'm a little disappointed.
I kind of had my eye
on Uncle Leo.
Uh-huh.
Well, I'll give you a call,
and thanks for the fish.
By the way, you know
why fish are so thin?
Why?
They eat fish.
[BRAYING NASAL LAUGHTER]
[WHISTLING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Hey...
What happened?
What took you so long?
He's a terrific guy.
What are you talking about?
What did he say?
Well, we talked about
a lot of things.
You talked about
Well, did you
talk about us?
MAN: I'm in love.
I just met her
outside in the street.
Her name's Elaine,
and she is the most beautiful
woman I have ever seen.
DR. RESTON:
Did you say Elaine?
How come with the psychiatrist,
every "the hour"
is only 50 minutes?
What do they do with that
10 minutes that they have left?
Do they just sit there going,
"Boy, that guy was crazy.
"I couldn't believe the things
he was saying. What a nut!
Who's coming in next?
Oh, no, another headcase!"
You should've told me
it didn't work.
I know, I know.
You didn't have
to throw it out.
I was always late.
It was frustrating me.
I'm sorry. I really am.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Well, that must be Leo.
I would've taken you
to the airport.
He has nothing to do.
Neither do I. Yeah?
It's George.
Oh, come on up. It's George.
Oh, George.
Whatever happened
with NBC and the deal?
Oh, George turned it down.
He turned it down?
Yeah.
Why did he do that?
Because of Ted Danson.
What does Ted Danson
have to do with it?
Maybe he doesn't
like Ted Danson.
Hey, who knows? Maybe we'll
wind up getting more money.
Hey.
Hey, Georgie boy!
How are you?
Hey, Mr. Seinfeld,
Hey, Mrs. Seinfeld. How are you?
What's the matter with you?
What did I do?
What about NBC?
Did you hear anything?
Yeah, as a matter
of fact, I did.
We got a deal.
[ALL CHEERING]
You see? He had
the right idea! Hold out.
That's how you get
the big money. Huh, George?
Please, Morty.
No, no, no.
He knows how
to talk to these people.
No one's gonna take
advantage of Georgie!
I'm just happy to be working
with your talented son
who is not doing this
for the money.
Come on.
You have no idea
how refreshing that is.
So, what did we get?
Eight thousand dollars.
Beautiful.
That's, uh,
for the two of us.
Four thousand apiece?
Let me see if I understand this.
In other words,
you held out for less money.
I was wrong. You were right.
You know, the basic idea
of negotiation,
as I understand it,
is to get your
price to go up.
You're smart. I'm dumb.
You know, this is how they
negotiate in the Bizarro World.
[DOOR BUZZES]
That's gotta
be Leo.
Yeah.
It's Leo.
All right, we're coming down.
All right,
let's get going.
Dad, before we go, I got
a little something for you.
A present.
A present?
[CHUCKLING]
Hey! Look at this.
A wallet.
Exactly what
I needed. You see?
Come on, you lost your wallet.
I figured I'd get you
another one.
I hope you didn't spend
too much on that.
I wanna tell you.
This is one of the most
thoughtful gifts
anyone's ever given me.
He's something,
your son, isn't he?
Ah...
All right. Let's go.
You're a terrific kid!
GEORGE: Yeah, he's
something, isn't he?
How can anybody not like you?
You're very special.
Yeah. I'm good
for about $4000.
Hey, let's go. It's 12, uh...
12:22.
All right, Leo.
Hey, Uncle Leo.
Hi, hi.
How you doing?
I got it,
I got it.
Boy, this is some beautiful
parking spot you got here.
And I hate to give it up.
Hey, Dad, you're sure
you don't need any more money?
Jerry...
All right,
I'm just joking.
Listen,
have a nice trip.
Bye-bye, Jerry.
Bye, Mrs. Seinfeld.
Take care.
Thanks again
for the wallet.
Morty, always
a pleasure.
Yes.
Take care, now.
So long.
Like he would really
take your money.
Oh, he took it. I put
$400 in the new wallet.
You're kidding.
He lost all that cash.
That was the only way
I could give it back,
or he wouldn't accept it.
Man, would I love to see
the look on his face.
You believe this?
What?
It's Velcro.
You're kidding.
Who needs this?
Leo, let's go.
The main difference
between the women's wallet
and the man's wallet
is the photo section.
True? Women carry with them
a photograph of every person
they've ever met
every day in their whole life
since the beginning of time,
and every picture's out of date.
You know what I mean?
It's, "Here's my cousin,
3 years old.
"She's in the Marines now.
"This is my dog.
He died during the Johnson
administration." You know.
You get stopped by a cop.
No license, no registration.
"Here's 56 people that know me."
Cop goes, "All right, ma'am,
"just wanted to make sure
you had some friends.
"Move it along.
Routine pal check."
[♪]