Have you noticed that everything
on planes is very tiny?
There's always tiny food,
tiny liquor bottles,
tiny pillows, tiny bathroom,
tiny sink, tiny soap?
Everyone's in a cramped seat
working on a tiny computer.
There's always
"a small problem."
"There'll be a slight delay."
"You'll be a bit late."
"If you could be
a little patient!"
"We're just trying to get
one of those little trucks
"to pull us up
a little closer to the Jetway
"so you can walk down
the narrow hallway.
"There'll be a man there
in a tight suit,
"and he'll tell you
"you have very little time
to make your connecting flight.
So move it!"
ELAINE:
♪ Bah, bah, bah Bah, bah ♪
♪ Boo boo da
Bah bah ♪
♪ Bah da bum ♪
♪ Bah bah bah
Wha-wha-wha-- ♪
Hey, could you
do me a favor? Huh?
Could you shut up?
[LAUGHS]
And open the window,
please.
It's very hot in here.
You're wearing
that heavy jacket.
All right, fine, I'll take
it off. Grab the wheel.
No, Jerry, I don't
want to do that.
Come on, just do it.
No, I don't like to do this.
Elaine, just get it.
Jer--
My hand is stuck.
Okay, don't
fool around.
My hand! My hand!
Don't, Jer--
All right, fine.
Ah! Elaine.
Hey, guess what.
This window doesn't work.
I hate rental cars.
Nothing ever works.
Window doesn't work,
radio doesn't work,
and it smells
like a cheap hooker.
Or is that you?
Gimme 10 bucks
and find out.
So this worked out
pretty good.
Them giving me
an extra ticket, you know?
You get a free trip
to St. Louis.
I did my gig. You got
to see your sister.
Yeah,
worked out good.
And here's the beauty...
What?
George is picking us up
at the airport.
Get outta here. Why?
Yep.
You know that awning
outside my building? Yeah.
He's always bragging
about his vertical leap,
so I bet him 50 bucks
that he couldn't touch
the awning.
So, what happened?
[CHUCKLES]
He didn't come within 2 feet of the thing.
[LAUGHING]
He's waving at it.
So I told him
if he picks us up
at the airport,
he wouldn't
have to pay me.
Hey, how we doing
on time?
Timed out perfectly.
Drop off the car,
pick up the rental-car shuttle,
we walk right on the plane.
Wait up!
Sorry.
Wait! Wait!
MAN: See you later.
MAN 2: See you.
Where you going?
Uh, JFK.
I need some small bills
for a tip.
You got anything?
Yeah. You want a 5?
Uh, gimme a 10.
You're giving him $10?
Well, we got
three bags.
That's a pretty big tip.
That's what they get.
They don't get
that much.
Let's ask him.
You can't ask him.
Let's see
what he says.
Jerry, we don't
have time for this.
Two seconds.
Excuse me.
My friend and I here
were having a discussion.
We were just
kind of wondering
what you usually get
for a tip.
Depends on the person,
depends on the bag.
Well, how about
a couple people like us?
Two people like you?
I wouldn't expect much.
You don't even look like
you know what you're doing.
Come on, seriously.
Well, since you asked...
usually I get $5 a bag.
What?
That's right.
Five dollars a bag?
I don't think so.
Look, you asked, I told you.
You've got some nerve
trying to
take advantage of us.
All right, look,
we're late.
Thank you very much.
You're lucky I don't report you.
Come on.
JFK...
Honolulu.
Wait up!
See, never be late
for a plane with a girl.
Because a girl
runs like a girl,
with the little steps
and the arms
flailing out.
You wanna
make this plane?
You gotta run like a man!
Get your knees up!
BOTH:
The flight's been canceled?
Everything into JFK
is booked.
[BOTH GROANS]
No, wait, I have two seats
into LaGuardia,
but they're not together.
It's boarding right now.
We'll take them.
We're not gonna sit together?
So what? It's not
that long. You'll read.
Well, what about
George?
He's supposed to
pick us up at Kennedy.
We'll call him.
There's no time.
No time.
Is there time?
There's no time.
All right. We'll call him
from the plane.
I have one seat in first class,
and one in coach.
The price is the same
because
your flight was canceled.
Oh.
Well, uh...
Um...
I'll take
the first class.
Jerry.
What?
Why should you
get the first class?
Elaine, have you ever flown
first class?
No.
All right, then.
See, you won't know
what you're missing.
I've flown first class, Elaine.
I can't go back to coach.
I can't. I won't.
You flew here coach.
Yeah, that's a point.
All right, fine.
I don't care.
If the plane crashes,
everybody in first class
is gonna die anyway.
Uh, yeah, I'm sure
you'll live.
Third row, right.
Oh! You're in here, sir.
Welcome aboard.
Bon voyage, Lainey.
Oh, excuse me.
Uh, excuse me, miss,
I think you're sitting
in my seat.
What?
Yeah, 13C.
That's me. Oh.
Sorry.
Ah, it's all right.
Oh.
Ah.
I never check my bags.
Can't stand that waiting
in the baggage area.
Yeah. Great.
Yeah.
[QUIETLY]
Oh, God...
help me.
Excuse me.
I think you're in my seat.
Oh, really?
My mistake.
[QUIETLY] Thank you.
GEORGE:
Hey, thanks for coming with me.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, what made you think
you could touch that awning?
I...confused it
with another awning.
Man...
So how we doing on time?
We're perfect.
I timed this out
so we would pull up
at the terminal
exactly 17 minutes
after their flight
is supposed to land.
That gives 'em
just enough time
to get off the plane,
pick up their bags,
and be walking
out of the terminal
as we roll up.
[BOTH LAUGH]
I tell you,
it's a thing of beauty.
I cannot express to you
the feeling I get
from a perfect pickup.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
What?
The Long Island Expressway?
What're you getting on
the Long Island Expressway for?
Do you know what
the traffic'll be like?
This is
a suicide mission!
Will you relax?
Oh, I had it
perfectly timed out.
The Grand Central,
the Van Wyck.
You've destroyed
my whole timing!
This is the best
way to go!
Do you know what happens
if I miss them?
I don't get credit
for the pickup,
and I lose my 50 bucks.
George, there's no traffic
at this time.
Now, come on, man.
Really?
If anything,
we'll probably
get there early.
I'll have a chance
to go to the
duty-free shop, huh?
The duty-free shop?
Yeah.
[SCOFFS]
Duty-free is the biggest
sucker deal in retail.
You know how much duty is?
Duty?
Yeah, "duty."
Do you know how much duty is?
No, I don't know
how much duty is.
Duty's nothing.
Mm-hmm?
It's like sales tax.
Well, I'd still like to stop
at the duty-free shop.
♪ I like to stop
At the duty-free shop ♪
♪ I like to stop ♪
BOTH:
♪ At the duty-free shop ♪
♪ I like to stop
At the duty-free shop ♪
So he says, "Squeeze
your breasts together,"
and I say,
"I thought this was
an ad for shoes."
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh...
Oh, my.
Is that
the new Esquire?
Yeah.
Turn to page 146.
Oh.
Wow!
Coming out
of the shower.
It's a good thing
they gave you that washcloth
to cover yourself up.
What is this
an ad for?
See those wrinkled jeans
slung over the chair?
Way in the background,
out of focus?
Ah-ha...
How does it look
on your side?
Y--
Oh.
We'll get there.
ELAINE:
Oh, look at this.
He's sleeping,
and I have to go
to the bathroom.
Maybe he'll wake up soon.
What if my kidneys burst?
Is it worth it
not to wake this man up
to damage a major organ?
I hope this disgusting slob
appreciates
what I'm doing for him.
[GUM SQUISHING]
Yeah, make a little more noise
with your gum.
That's helpful.
They're not here.
You cost me 50 bucks!
Look at you,
you run like a girl.
Come on,
run like a man!
Lift your knees!
[MUTTERING]
Look, we're wasting
our time here.
We're
a half-hour late.
They probably took it
off the board already.
No, there it is. There.
"133," and it's canceled.
Canceled?
Do I still get credit
for the pickup?
I was here.
Okay, come on.
Let's go check
over at the ticket counter.
There it is, honey.
"Gate 18A, 8:30."
Did you
see that guy?
No. What guy?
That guy th--
He was standing right here.
No, I didn't notice him.
Listen, you go over
to the ticket counter.
I'm gonna stop
in the gift shop,
pick up a copy
of TIME magazine.
There's supposed to be
a blurb about Jerry,
and I think
he mentioned my name.
I know that guy.
Yeah--
Gotta get my TIME magazine.
I never miss
my TIME...
Okay, get your magazine.
Let's get outta here.
Hey! Hey!
I was gonna take that.
Oh, uh...
Gee, I'm sorry.
I got here first.
I don't care when you got here.
I want the magazine.
Let's go.
See, you don't understand.
There's a blurb about me
in this magazine.
A blurb?
You're a blurb!
Check out the cover, idiot.
GUARD: Okay, let's go.
PRISONER: No, just give--
I want the magazine!
Heh, heh. Uh...no.
You know what I would do to you
if I wasn't in these shackles?
But you are, Blanche.
You are in the shackles.
You little son of a...
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, I can't wait to read
my TIME magazine.
Last copy too.
Maybe I'll read it tomorrow.
In the park.
It's supposed to be
a beautiful day.
Have a nice life...
sentence, that is.
Oh, you...
They're on
a different flight.
They're scheduled
to land
in a half an hour,
only at LaGuardia.
LaGuardia?
All right, come on.
Wait a second.
Come on.
Where do I know
that guy from?
We gotta go. Come on.
ELAINE:
Wake up, you human slug!
Wake up!
[GASPS]
I can't hold it anymore.
Excuse me.
I've gotta go
to the bathroom.
Oh, sheesh...
I've gotta go.
I'm sorry.
Can you move that?
Would you move your seat up,
please?
Hey! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Tsk, tsk.
Tsk!
Tsk, tsk!
Oh, my,
that is refreshing.
Mmmm.
Would you care
for some slippers?
Sounds lovely.
Thank you.
Thank you
very much. May I?
Please.
Why, it's a perfect fit.
You must be Cinderella.
[BOTH LAUGH]
My name is not mentioned
in this blurb.
That's it.
It's Grossbard.
Can you believe this?
I am nowhere
to be found in this blurb.
I knew that face
looked familiar.
It's Grossbard.
Who's Grossbard?
When I lived
on Third Avenue
and 18th Street,
20 years ago,
I had this roommate
who was always behind
in his rent.
And one month,
he asked me to loan him
his share of the rent,
240 bucks.
He took the cash
and pfft! Disappears.
Well, I tried
to find him.
I went to
his girlfriend's house,
even his family.
Uh-uh, never got
that money back.
He screwed me!
And that's the guy,
John Grossbard.
Kramer, come on.
It was 240 bucks
20 years ago.
No, I'm gonna turn around.
I'm gonna get that guy.
No, no, no,
you cannot turn around.
Let go of the wheel.
You can't!
Kramer, you cannot
abandon people
in the middle
of an airport pickup!
It's a binding social contract.
We...
We must go forward...
not back.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
Tia, did you see
all the flowers
in that bathroom?
It's like an English garden
in there.
They're beautiful.
They're gardenias, mostly.
I thought
I smelled lilac.
Yes, there are
a few of those too.
It's almost
overwhelming.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the captain speaking.
Due to equipment problems
on the runway at LaGuardia,
we've been instructed
by the tower
to reroute and land at JFK.
[PASSENGERS GROAN]
We apologize
for any inconvenience.
What did he say?
Well...you're not
gonna believe it.
What?
The plane's been rerouted
back to Kennedy.
We got 45 minutes.
Let's go.
Listen to the bell,
Grossbard.
It tolls for thee.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
We have some delicious
Chateaubriand,
my personal favorite.
Mm.
Or if you prefer
something lighter,
a poached Dover sole
in a delicate white-wine sauce
with just a hint of saffron.
Oh, saffron.
That sounds good. Mm-hmm.
And today, we're featuring wines
from the Tuscany region.
Tuscany! Tuscany!
Hi. Can I get
to my seat?
[GROANS]
You're just gonna
have to wait.
No, but I--
I'm right there.
You just passed it.
I'm sitting
next to that guy.
You're not supposed
to get up
during
the food service.
Well, nobody
told me that.
Look. This plane is full.
I got a lot of people to serve.
Now, please.
You're just gonna have to wait.
There it is.
Gate 46.
We got
plenty of time.
Grossbard's plane leaves
in 10 minutes.
I still got time to catch him.
How are you gonna catch him?
He probably boarded the plane
already.
Give me your credit card.
My credit card? Why?
Just give me the card.
Don't ask any questions.
I'm not giving you
my credit card
unless you tell me
what it's for.
I'm gonna buy
a ticket.
I'm gonna get on
that flight.
What, are you nuts?
You're gonna spend more
for the ticket
than you'll get back
from Grossbard!
No, I'm not gonna use
the ticket.
I'm gonna get my money,
I'll get off the plane,
I'll turn your ticket in
for a refund.
It won't cost you a dime.
Now, come on,
give me the card.
Wait a minute.
This is a great idea.
Here. Use this one.
I get frequent-flyer miles
with every purchase.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Get two tickets.
As long as you're
returning it anyway
for a refund,
what's the difference?
I'll get double
the bonus miles.
[CHUCKLES]
Yes. Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to make you do this,
but I got stuck in the aisle,
and the flight attendant
wouldn't let me get through.
There's no way to get around
that cart.
You're not supposed to get up
during the food service.
I'll try and remember that.
Shoot...
Oh...where's my meal?
He asked me.
But you were
gone so long,
I thought you, uh,
switched seats.
Excuse me.
Um, I didn't get a meal.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
I would know
if a tray of food
had been served to me.
Would you?
Yes!
Well, the only meal left
is a kosher meal.
A kosher meal?
Mm-hmm.
I don't want
a kosher meal.
I-- I don't even know
what a kosher meal is.
I think it means
when a rabbi has
inspected it or something.
No, no, it all
has to do
with the way
they kill the pig.
Come on,
they don't eat pigs.
They do
if it's killed right,
under a rabbi's
supervision.
MAN: Oh, you
know what?
I ordered
the kosher meal.
Then why didn't you
take it?
I ordered it
six weeks ago.
I forgot.
You're eating my food!
Hey, I got earplugs
to collect.
Do you want it
or not?
Mmmm! Mmmm!
Mmm, this is the best sundae
I've ever had.
Oh, man.
You know why?
They got the fudge
on the bottom.
You see?
That enables you
to control
your fudge
distribution
as you're eating
your ice cream.
I've never met a man
who knew so much
about nothing.
Thank you.
Mmmm! Mmmm!
Mmm.
More anything?
More everything!
Hey. Look.
I did good.
I got supersavers.
Come on.
Supersavers?
Are they refundable?
Huh?
You bought nonrefundable
tickets. You idiot!
She talked me into it.
She said it was the best deal.
Do you know how much
this is gonna cost me?
I'll tell you what.
I'll split it with you. Huh?
Uh, uh, uh...
Listen, I'm gonna go
to the bathroom.
Okay, okay.
Hey. Hey.
Huh?
How about that,
huh?
Excuse me?
Do you
recognize me?
No.
Come on. 20 years ago.
What?
18th Street?
I don't know
what you're talk--
Come on.
Give me your money.
What?
Where's your wallet?
Hey. Hey. Hey!
The $240!
GROSSBARD:
Hey! No!
MAN:
Just a minute.
Hey!
MAN 2:
Hey, buddy!
[LATCH CLICKS]
[SIGHS]
Whoa!
Kramer!
George!
Shh!
[QUIETLY]
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What? Oh.
No, nothing for me, thank you.
I'm fine.
What is your name?
Elaine Benes.
[CHUCKLES]
You're going to have to go back
to coach.
No, but there was nobody
sitting here.
Yes, but you're still
not allowed.
These seats are very expensive.
Oh, no, please don't send me
back there. Please.
I'll do anything.
It's so nice up here.
You know, it's so
comfortable up here.
I don't want to
go back there.
Please don't
send me back there.
Oh, you got cookies.
You're gonna have to go back
to your seat.
Okay, fine. I'll go back.
You know,
our goal should be
a society
without classes!
Do you realize the people
up here are getting cookies?!
What is all the racket
back there?
You know, you're trying
to relax on the plane,
and this is what
you have to put up with.
What is going on?
Oh, sir, this woman
tried to sneak
into first class.
Well, you see, that's terrible.
Mm-hmm.
The problem is
that curtain
is no security.
There really should be
a locking door.
You're right,
and I'm so sorry.
I--I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Come on, let go of me.
Look, I'm telling you,
I didn't
do anything wrong!
That guy owes me
240 bucks!
Hey, listen, pal,
you're in big trouble.
Nah...
Couldn't be.
Where are they,
already?
I don't see them
anywhere.
I got my bags.
I'm ready to go.
Yeah, you got
your bags.
["ALOHA 'OE" PLAYING]
That was
the worst flight
I've ever been on
in my entire life.
Yeah, me too.
I'll call you.
Okay.
It's a business thing.
You guys ready?
Yeah.
Where's George?
Uh...
[INAUDIBLE]
But I have to admit
that I like flying.
I like those, uh...
Those little bathrooms
that they have on the plane.
It's kind of like
a small apartment
of your own on the plane.
You go in, close the door,
the light comes right on.
It's like
a little surprise party
every time you go in there.
But, uh, the worst way
of flying, I think, is standby.
You ever fly standby?
It never works.
You know, that's why
they call it "standby."
You end up standing there,
going, "Bye."
That didn't, uh...
Yeah.
So I was on this plane
where the flight attendant--
It was her first day on the job,
so they didn't have
a uniform for her yet,
and that really
makes a big difference.
I mean, here's just
some regular person
coming over to you, going,
"Would you mind bringing
your seat back all the way up?"
"Who the hell are you?"
She says, "Well,
I'm the flight attendant."
Oh, yeah, well,
then I'm the pilot, all right?
So why don't you sit down?
I'm about to bring her in.
[♪]