What are lawyers, really?
To me, a lawyer is basically
the person that knows
the rules of the country.
We're all throwing the dice,
playing the game,
moving our pieces
around the board,
but if there's a problem,
the lawyer is the only person
that has read the inside
of the top of the box.
I think one of the fun things
for them
is to say, "objection."
"Objection!
Objection, Your Honor."
"Objection," of course,
is the adult version of...
"afraid not."
[♪]
To which the judge
can say two things.
He can say, "Overruled,"
which is the adult version
of "afraid so."
or he can say, "Sustained,"
which is the adult version
of "duh!"
So uh...
So you're a lawyer?
What kind of cases
do you handle?
Oh, everything:
divorce, patents,
immigration
and naturalization.
What is that?
Immigrants come over,
you show them
how to act natural?
Are your friends
as funny as you?
No, they're not funny at all.
No, I have no funny friends.
I'm the funny one.
El clown-o.
ELAINE:
Look, I was nice enough
to pick it up
for you.
Hey, I've been back four days.
I want my mail.
It's mostly bills, magazines,
and junk mail anyway.
Elaine, that's what mail is.
Without bills, magazines,
and junk mail,
there is no mail.
Here's my card.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Hey, good
talking to you.
Nice meeting you.
Yeah.
Hi.
Hey, how
are you doing?
You would not believe
what just happened.
I was waiting
for you,
and this woman was
sitting at the counter.
What? The one
who just left?
Yeah, yeah,
and, so, you know,
we started talking,
and she's this lawyer
who's incredible!
You know, everything I said
was funny, you know?
She thought-- She laughed
at everything I said.
She thinks I'm hilarious.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, in a way,
I was almost too good.
I started so good.
I can't go any place
but down now, you know?
I got
no place to go.
Yeah, well,
I guess it's all over.
Hey, is that Babu?
JERRY:
It is.
Hey, Babu!
Jerry!
Look at you.
You got the job.
Yes, yes, they gave me
a job, thanks to you.
Oh, I didn't do anything.
No, no,
you do everything.
Got me a job, a place
to live in your building.
Come on.
You're a very good man.
You did everything for me.
My family and I can
never thank you enough
for everything you do.
You see, this is what
I do with women.
I start out
too strong.
Now I have
to become real.
That's when
it all falls apart.
What good is real?
They don't want real.
They want funny.
No, they don't.
Oh, yes,
they do, Elaine.
No...
You gotta put on a show.
You always gotta give them
a big show.
You always have to be on.
Otherwise,
why would they like me?
They'd just go
for a better-looking guy
with more money.
You mean that's true?
I'm right?
Okay, great.
Well, I'm glad
everything worked out, Babu.
Oh, yes, yes,
everything's wonderful.
Okay, I'll see you
around the building.
I'll see you
in the building.
Remember Babu Bhatt?
Who's he?
Remember that guy
that opened the restaurant
across the street
from the building last year,
and he wasn't doing
so well...
and I told him he should make it
all Pakistani,
and that drove him
right out of business?
So are you going with me
to the auto show Saturday?
Yeah, yeah.
Can you bring my mail then,
please?
What mail?
I picked up his mail
while he was on the road.
Why didn't Kramer pick it up?
Because he's
at that baseball fantasy camp
in Florida.
Oh, yeah, right.
When's he coming back?
Monday, I think.
Kramer goes to a fantasy camp.
His whole life
is a fantasy camp.
People should plunk down $2000
to live like him for a week.
Do nothing,
fall ass-backwards into money,
mooch food off your neighbors,
and have sex without dating.
That's a fantasy camp.
Hey, listen, if you're going to
go out with this lawyer,
why don't you have
dinner with us,
and then maybe you can go
to the auto show with her.
You know, have a little company,
take the pressure off.
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYS]
He never heard
of corduroy.
Jerry, you're
killing me!
He never heard
of corduroy.
[BANGING ON TABLE,
LAUGHING]
True story. True story.
That's funny.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
No, no.
I don't-- I don't think so.
Why?
Well, I think I'm better off
going one-on-one.
I don't know why
you want to play man-to-man
when you could play a zone.
She might not be comfortable.
Why? We're all
very nice.
We're very friendly.
We'll be funny.
No. No...
It's not good.
Hee, hee.
I don't think so.
All right.
Well, if you change
your mind,
we'll wind up at Isabella's
probably around 7:00.
No, no Isabella's.
I don't wanna go to Isabella's.
Why?
No, it's too trendy.
No Isabella's.
Excellent.
Like I really know
what I'm talking about.
Toasting makes
me uncomfortable,
but toast, I love.
Never start the day
without a good piece of toast.
In fact, let's toast
to toast.
[CHUCKLES]
Look who's here.
Georgie boy!
What are you doing here?
I-I thought you said
you hated Isabella's.
Yeah, I talked him
into it.
What happened
to the auto show?
Oh, we're still going.
We're still going.
Elaine,
do the spokesmodel.
The turbo-quadramatic
transmission
offers you
the power and prestige
to propel you
well into
the 21st century.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
Hi.
Cheryl, this is Elaine
and Jerry.
Hi. Nice
to meet you.
Would you
like to join us?
No, no, they don't wanna
join us.
No, it's okay.
Don't be silly.
Oh, okay,
why don't we just
put these two tables
together?
No, no,
you can't do that.
They're round.
It makes an eight,
and it-- Oh, all right.
Yeah,
that's great.
Jerry, Jerry, tell them
that funny story
you were telling me.
No, no!
No, George,
it's so funny.
We saw this cab driver's
picture, right?
You know, we should
really order.
The service
is so slow here.
By the time
you get anything...
Oh, Cheryl,
can I ask you
a legal question?
I'm being sued.
What happened?
[SIGHS]
Well, I ran out
to apologize to a virgin,
and I crossed
against a light...
and I knocked over
the delivery boy.
Was he Chinese?
Yeah.
Is your-- Is your
last name Benes?
How did you know?
Oh, God!
Ping is my cousin.
No.
That's so funny.
I'm handling his case.
What?
You're Cheryl Fong?
That's right.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it!
This is such
a coincidence.
I know!
Wow. Well...
I guess you don't have
any advice for me
on how to win
the case.
Will you excuse me?
I have to make
a call.
Oh, sure.
Tell Ping
I said hello.
Yeah...
tell him you think
you may have broken
the case wide open.
[ALL LAUGH]
I can't
believe this.
What are you doing?
What?
This is not good.
What's the matter?
I just don't think it's such a
great idea for you to sit here.
Why not?
He thinks that
if you're too funny,
he might not look
so funny.
Biff...
What?
You're not worried about that.
No. Of course not.
I mean, so what if I'm funny?
Who cares?
He thinks that if
a woman sees a guy
put on a better show,
she'll walk out
on his show,
go see
the other show.
Well, should we leave?
Let's...
You don't have to be
so funny.
I mean,
would it kill you
not to be so funny
all the time?
That's all
I'm asking.
This woman thinks
I'm very funny,
and now you're
gonna be funny.
So, what am I
gonna be?
I'm gonna be
a short bald guy
with glasses
who suddenly doesn't
seem so funny.
This is
so ridiculous.
Can we just go
over there?
Come on.
Look, I don't have to be funny.
I don't care.
You don't?
No way.
It's completely
under my control.
No, it's not.
You cannot
not be funny.
Of course I can.
Am I being funny now?
A little.
This is funny?
I'm being funny?
Yeah.
George, is this funny?
It's funny.
It wouldn't kill you
to not be
so funny either.
What?
What did I do?
Hi.
[SOMBER]:
Hello.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry. It was
my aunt's birthday.
She makes such
a big deal about it.
Well, nobody likes
to get old, right?
Yeah.
Well, birthdays
are merely symbolic
of how another year
has gone by...
and how little
we've grown.
No matter
how desperate we are
that someday
a better self will emerge,
each flicker
of the candles
on the cake,
we know
it's not to be...
that for the rest
of our sad, wretched,
pathetic lives,
this is who we are
to the bitter end.
Inevitably,
irrevocably...
happy birthday?
No such thing.
Funny guy, huh?
Here, take it. I was glad
to get rid of it.
Well, thank you
very much.
It's about time.
Oh, listen.
So guess what.
Cheryl convinced Ping
to drop the case against me.
Drop the case?
Wow, congratulations.
That'll save you some money.
Yeah, no kidding.
That lawyer was gonna
charge me a fortune.
Oh, great.
Birth announcement
from Arnie and Joy Harris.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Hear that?
Guess who's back.
Oh.
Hey!
Thought you weren't coming back
till Monday.
Well, the camp ended
a few days early.
Why?
Well, there was an incident.
What happened?
I punched Mickey Mantle
in the mouth.
What?
Yeah, I punched him,
and they took him
to the hospital,
and then they canceled
the rest of the week.
You punched who
in the mouth?
Mickey Mantle.
What happened?
Well, you know,
we were playing a game,
and, you know, I was pitching,
and I was really, you know,
throwing some smoke,
and Joe Pepitone, he was up,
and, man, that guy, you know,
he was crowding the plate.
Wow. Joe Pepitone!
Yeah, well,
Joe Pepitone or not,
I own the inside of that plate.
So you know,
I throw one...
you know,
inside, you know,
a little chin music.
Right on his pants,
because I got to
intimidate, you know,
when I'm
on the mound.
Well,
the next pitch,
he's right back
in the same place.
So I had to plunk him.
You plunked him?
Oh, yeah.
Well, he throws down his bat,
he comes racing up to the mound.
Next thing, both benches
are cleared, you know?
A brouhaha breaks out
between the guys in the camp,
you know,
and the old Yankee players,
and as I'm trying to get
Moose Skowron
off of one of my teammates,
you know,
somebody pulls me from behind,
and I turned around,
and I popped him.
I looked down, and whoa, man,
it's Mickey!
I punched his lights out.
Wow,
this is incredible.
BABU:
Leave me alone!
You can't do this
to me.
What's going on out there?
BABU: What are you doing?
This is not right,
people.
You're making a bad
mistake, very bad.
Babu!
I'll be right back.
Yeah, so?
Then Hank Bauer, you know,
he's screaming,
"Mickey, Mickey!
"What have you done with Mickey?
You killed Mickey!"
So, what'd you do?
Well, I got the hell
out of there.
They took Babu away.
They took Babu away?
Yeah, the immigration guy
said his visa was expired.
Poor Babu.
Everything was going so well
for him.
He had an apartment.
He had a job.
What a shame.
BABU:
Jerry!
Help me!
I will, Babu!
I will help you,
Babu!
Don't worry!
Then Hank Bauer,
you know,
he's chasing me around.
He trips over third base
and knocks over Clete Boyer.
Uh-oh.
What?
Well,
this is interesting.
What is that?
It's a letter
from the immigration bureau.
It's Babu's visa renewal
application form.
They must've put it
in my mailbox by mistake.
Well, doesn't he need that?
If you had given me my mail
last week,
this whole thing
never would've happened.
You should've come
to my house to pick it up.
Yeah, so am I
being funny now?
No, actually,
you're not being funny now.
Yeah, see, I told you
I wasn't funny all the time.
Hey, George, look.
I'm not funny now.
No, and you weren't funny
last night either.
In fact, you got us both
so depressed
she asked me to drive
her home after dinner.
Well, look, I need to get
in touch with Cheryl.
Babu needs a lawyer.
His visa's expired.
What do you need her for?
There's a million lawyers.
You said this is one of the
things that her firm does.
All right, all right,
but no funny business.
Same deal
as last night.
Oh,
will you stop it already?
Jerry, please.
How long is this gonna go on?
Till I'm comfortable.
Well, when is
that gonna be?
After consummation.
Consummation?
I don't think you have
enough material.
I actually have
a friend
in the immigration
department
who owes me
a big favor.
You're very lucky.
[SOMBER]
That's wonderful news.
Thank you.
You're a very serious person,
aren't you?
Well, so many people
in the world
deprived and unhappy...
Doesn't seem
like it would be fair
to be...cheerful.
[FLY BUZZING]
I understand.
I think
that's curdled.
I don't care.
Do you ever laugh?
Not really.
Sometimes
when I'm in the tub.
That's so sad.
What do you do?
I'm a comedian.
Oh, let me get that.
You've been
so helpful.
Hey, we're gonna
go see Babu now, right?
Yeah, I'll just pay
for this.
Oh, I'm just gonna
say hi to Cheryl.
Hi.
Listen, gosh,
I wanted to thank you so much
for convincing Ping
to drop the case.
Well, you know, after we met,
you were all so nice,
I just couldn't go through
with it...
but between you and me,
you would've paid
through the nose.
You're kidding.
No, I'm not.
Babu.
[GASPS]
Jerry. Jerry.
Hello, Jerry.
You remember Elaine.
Yes. Yes, of course.
Nice to meet you.
So nice of you both to come.
Oh, Babu.
No, no, you're both very kind,
very kind.
Oh, well, you know.
You know.
We try.
We do what we can.
You see, the problem is,
I never got my visa renewal form
in the mail.
I was expecting it.
Yes, well, see, uh,
here's the thing, Babu.
Um, what happened was, uh...
I was away for a couple of weeks
doing comedy shows--
Yes, yes, the comedy shows.
You're a very funny man.
And, well, Elaine here
was picking up my mail
while I was away,
because, you know,
that little box
can get very full.
Oh, yes, yes, of course.
TV Guide, magazines,
everything.
You know,
I would've picked up your mail.
Your box
is right next to mine.
Oh, I don't want to bother you.
No bother.
You got me a job,
you got me an apartment.
You're a very,
very good man.
Well, yesterday
after they took you away,
I looked in my mail,
and I noticed that the mailman
accidentally put
your visa renewal
in my mailbox.
Come again?
You see, I'd been home
for a week,
and Elaine didn't give me
my mail till yesterday,
even though I asked her
repeatedly for it.
Yeah, but, um,
Babu,
he could've come
to my house to pick it up.
You had my visa application?
Well, not technically.
I'll kill you!
Well, what about her?
I'll kill both of you!
Babu!
No "Babu." No "Babu."
You're a bad man.
You're a very bad man.
A very lazy, bad man.
Babu,
I'm gonna fix everything.
I have a lawyer
who knows someone
in the immigration department.
They're gonna straighten
the whole thing out.
The wheels are in motion.
Things are happening
even as we speak.
The wheels are in motion?
The wheels are in motion.
Things are happening.
Jerry?
I'm very
attracted to him.
You think the person
you were talking to
was him?
That's not even
close to him.
He's funny.
Jerry's funny.
He's never said
anything funny.
He can't not be funny.
No, no, no, he's--
He's dark...
and disturbed.
Dark and disturbed?
His whole life revolves around
Superman and cereal.
What kind of
a friend are you?
You see, I convinced him
to act like that
so that you would think
I was funnier.
That's how
disturbed I am.
You want disturbed?
That's disturbed.
I mean, you can't find sickness
like that anywhere.
You think sickness like that
grows on trees?
Nobody is sicker than me,
nobody.
He's pretending.
I'm the genuine article.
So you're telling me
Jerry's whole thing was an act?
Yes,
and I put him up to it,
because I'm sick.
I'm the one that needs help.
I got to go.
Well, should I
call you later?
Please don't.
But...
But I'm disturbed.
I'm depressed.
I'm inadequate.
I got it all!
So, what's up
with Babu?
How come
he's not back?
I don't know.
I don't understand it.
Cheryl was supposed
to take care of it.
He should be back by now.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
Come on up.
MAN:
Babu, oh!
Babu, my goodness.
Babu must be back.
Well, where's Babu?
He is in Pakistan.
Who are you?
I am his brother.
He knew a lawyer.
It was all going to be fixed.
I'm sure the lawyer
did everything they could.
Then where is Babu?
What happened to Babu?
Show me Babu.
Snapple?
No.
Too fruity.
Hey, what happened?
I thought Cheryl
was gonna help Babu
get his visa.
She didn't help him?
No.
Where is he?
He's in Pakistan.
Oh, boy.
What do you mean,
"Oh, boy"?
Well...
last night,
she told me
that she liked you.
Not you,
the disturbed you.
So I had to tell her
the truth.
Told her the truth?
Well, you got
Babu deported.
What do you mean, I got?
You didn't give him
his visa application.
That's because
she had my mail.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't have had
to get your mail
if he hadn't gone
to that fantasy camp.
Well,
I just came back
from Mickey Mantle's
restaurant.
How could you
go in there?
Well, I had to.
I had to apologize.
I mean, I punched Mickey Mantle,
my idol.
It was...
eating me up inside.
Well,
what happened?
I got down on my knees,
and I went, "Go ahead,
Mickey, hit me.
"I'm begging you,
Mickey, please.
"Hit me.
Come on, hit me.
I love you, Mickey.
I love you."
So, what'd he do?
Well,
the four of them,
they picked me up
by my pants,
and they threw me outside
right into a horse.
[CHUCKLING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MAN: Kramer.
Hey!
Hey, yeah.
It's my Chinese food.
Oh, Ping, hi.
Listen,
thank you so much
for dropping
that lawsuit against me.
Not anymore.
What?
Cheryl call me last night.
Lawsuit back on.
Why?
She call you
and your friends big liars.
You think she
nice girl?
Wait till you
see her in court.
She's a shark.
They call her
the Terminator.
She never lose a case,
and now,
you make her mad.
She double the damages.
Hasta la vista, baby.
[♪]
So his friend had the mail,
but she did not give it to him,
and then he came to visit me.
Said a lawyer would call
and help.
He said the wheels
were in motion,
but there was no motion.
There was nothing...
and so they sent me back here.
This is a terrible story,
Babu.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to save up
every rupee.
For someday
I will get back to America,
and when I do,
I will exact vengeance
on this man.
I cannot forget him.
He haunts me.
He's a very bad man.
He's a very, very bad man.
I am for open immigration,
but that sign we have
on the front
of Statue of Liberty,
"Give us your tired, your poor,
your huddled masses..."
Can't we just say,
"Hey, the door's open.
We'll take whoever you got"?
Do we have to specify
the wretched refuse?
I mean, why don't we just say,
"Give us the unhappy, the sad,
the slow, the ugly,
"people that can't drive,
"if they have trouble merging,
"if they can't stay
in their lane,
"if they don't signal,
can't parallel park,
"if they're sneezing,
if they're stuffed up,
"if they're clogged,
"if they have bad penmanship,
don't return calls,
"if they have dandruff,
"food between their teeth,
"if they have bad credit,
if they have no credit,
Missed a spot shaving..."
In other words,
any dysfunctional,
defective slob
that you can somehow cattle-prod
onto a wagon,
send them over.
We want them.
[♪]