Whenever you ask for
the doggy bag in a restaurant,
there's a certain sense
of failure there, isn't it?
People always whisper it
to the waiter,
[WHISPERING]
"Uh, excuse me, uh...
"I'm sorry,
"you're gonna have to give me
the doggy bag. I--
[TEARFULLY]
I couldn't make it."
And it is embarrassing,
because a doggy bag means either
you were out at a restaurant
when you're not hungry,
or you've chosen
the stupidest possible way
to get dog food
that there is.
How about the doggy bag
on a date?
That's a good move
for a guy, huh?
Let me tell you something.
If you're a guy, and you ask
for the doggy bag on a date,
you might as well have them
just wrap up your genitals too.
You're not gonna be needing
those for a while, either.
[HUMMING]
Is that bothering you?
No. Not at all.
It's the BMW.
Oh, could you please hurry?
[SWEETLY]
"Please hurry."
Look at you.
Look what you've become.
What? What have I become?
I haven't become anything.
Oh, Carl can't wait
a few more minutes?
I don't want
to keep him waiting.
He'll like you more.
That's impossible.
Why do you have to pick
your teeth at the table?
Leave me alone.
WOMAN:
It's disgusting.
Yeah, I'm gonna
get married real soon.
So where am I
dropping you?
His place.
This guy's
got quite a racket.
I take you to dinner, and then
drop you off at his apartment.
And he gets
the rest of my chicken.
So is tonight the night?
♪ You never know ♪
Ooh! Baby doll.
Thank you, brother.
Boy, do you
smell something?
Do I smell something?
What am I,
hard of smelling?
Of course
I smell something.
What is it?
I think it's BO.
What?
It's BO. The valet
must've had BO.
It can't be.
Nobody has BO like this.
Jerry, it's B...O.
But the whole car smells.
So?
So when somebody has BO,
the O usually
stays with the B.
Once the B leaves,
the O goes with it.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe you ski.
I'm a great skier.
Yeah, what else?
Let's see.
I ski, I fish,
I pillage, I plunder.
[LAUGHS]
You pillage and plunder?
When I travel.
See, finally.
Finally I get to meet a man
who pillages and plunders.
I'm so lucky.
[SNIFFS]
This should only
take a second.
Yeah, I'm gonna
poke around.
GEORGE:
Hey, what do you know?
Look at that.
A lesbian sighting.
Ho, ho! My lucky day.
They're so fascinating.
Why is that?
Because they don't want us.
You gotta respect that.
Oh, my God!
It's Susan!
But what do I do?
George?
Hngh-agh!
Susan!
SUSAN:
Hi!
[LAUGHS]
Oh, boy!
What are you doing here?
Renting a video.
What do you
got there?
Oh, some stupid movie.
This is Mona.
Oh, uh...
Hi.
Pleasure to meet you.
Yes. Well...
I'll let you two,
uh, catch up.
You okay?
Yeah. Yes.
I just haven't
seen you in a long time.
And you didn't expect me
to be holding hands
with a woman.
Oh, please!
[CHUCKLES]
Me?
Come on, that's great.
Are you kidding?
I think that's fantastic.
I've always encouraged
experimentation.
I'm the first guy in the pool.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
I know who I'm talking to.
Of course you do, yeah.
It's just, you know,
I never knew...
that, uh...
I like women?
There you go.
So, uh...
how long has this been going on?
Since you and I broke up.
Ssssso after me, you...
went that way?
Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
I think that's fantastic.
Good for you.
Nice. That's very nice.
So, what do you got there?
Oh, I don't--
Ahhh, Rochelle, Rochelle.
It's a foreign movie.
A film is what it is, actually.
Yeah, a lot of nudity
in that, huh?
No, no, no, a t-tiny bit.
It's not even frontal nudity.
It's, uh, side-al nudity.
MAN:
Next!
Ooh.
That's me.
All right, well,
good seeing you, George.
Yes, good to see you, too.
And good luck with, uh...
With the whole thing there.
Uh, what are
you returning?
Uh, Rochelle, Rochelle.
Oh, Rochelle, Rochelle.
A young girl's
strange, erotic journey Yeah.
from Milan to Minsk?
Yeah.
Uh, that'll be $3.49.
$3.49? It says $1.49.
Well, you didn't rewind it.
There's a $2.00 charge
for not rewinding.
Yeah, b-b-b-- But
there's no signs here.
This is an outrage.
What are you--?
George, don't give him
any money for that.
It'll cost you less
to keep it another day,
rewind it,
and bring it back tomorrow.
Don't give him the satisfaction.
I'm not giving you
the satisfaction.
I'm gonna
watch it again.
How could that hurt?
So this morning,
I go down to the garage
to check the car out.
Mm-hmm.
I figure, by this time,
the odor molecules
have had at least 12 hours
to de-smellify.
Right.
I open the car door.
Like a punch in the face...
the stench hits me.
It's almost as if
it had gained strength
throughout the night.
I can think of at least
six known offensive odors
that I would rather smell
than what's living
in your car.
What about skunk?
I don't mind skunk.
Horse manure?
I love horse manure.
Well, I've never seen
anything like this in my life.
In fact, I went
to the car wash.
They want $250
to detail it
and get the smell out.
Oh!
I'm not paying for that.
That's not my responsibility.
No. Mm-mmm.
In fact, I'm driving up
to that restaurant now,
and demand
they pay for it.
Absolutely.
Uh, listen,
let me ask you something.
Um, when you're with a guy,
and he tells you
he has to get up early,
what does that mean?
It means he's lying.
Wow!
Is that what
he told you?
Yeah. Last night.
Oh, come on. Men have to
get up early sometime.
No. Never.
Jerry, I'm sure
I've seen men on the street
early in the morning.
Well, sometimes we do
actually have to
get up early,
but a man will always
trade sleep for sex.
Is it possible
I'm not as attractive
as I think I am?
Anything's possible.
Yeah.
What's the matter
with you?
Steinbrenner!
Ah, yeah.
He's ruining my life!
Ah, yes. Steinbrenner.
I can't think I can take
another season with him.
He'll just trade away
their best young prospects.
Just like he did with Buhner,
McGee, Drabeck, McGriff.
I know the list.
[SNIFFS]
What's that smell?
Wha-what smell?
Ooh!
You stink.
What do you mean, I stink?
Why don't you go take a shower?
I showered.
JERRY:
Oh, wait a second.
Since I showered,
I've been in the car.
So?
Don't you see
what's happening here?
It's attached itself to me.
It's alive!
If it's attached itself...
to you...
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
That's why Carl
said he had to get up early,
because I stink!
Jerry, he thinks I have BO.
Me!
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yep.
Yeah.
This is George.
I'm coming
right down.
All right,
what happened?
What happened?
My car stinks is what happened,
and it's destroying the lives
of everyone in its path.
This is BO?
Yes.
This is unbelievable BO.
I know.
I was at the car wash
this morning,
and the guy told me,
in 38 years in the business,
he's never smelled
anything like it.
So let me ask you,
do you think
I could've done this?
No, no.
It's the valet guy.
No, no. I mean driven Susan
to lesbianism.
Oh! No, that's ridiculous.
What if her experience with me
drove her to it?
Suicide, maybe. Not lesbianism.
And the woman
she was lesbianing with,
Susan told me
she's never been with a guy.
Oh, this isn't even BO.
This is beyond BO.
It's BBO.
There should be a BO squad
that patrols the city
like a smell Gestapo
to sniff 'em out,
strip 'em down,
and wash 'em
with a big, soapy brush.
You know,
the funny thing is,
somehow I find her
more appealing now.
It's like, if I knew
that she was a lesbian
when we went out,
I never would've
broken up with her.
Let me see if I understand this.
On second thought...
JERRY:
Now there he is. That's the guy.
[ROLLS UP WINDOW]
No, thank you.
Go back. No, go back.
No, back, back!
Go back!
I got it!
I'll park it!
I'll park it. Go back.
You go back.
JERRY:
Sorry. Thank you.
Thank you. No.
What do you mean,
"stunk up"?
I mean the car stinks.
George, does the car stink?
Stinks.
Stinks!
Perhaps you are the one
who has the odor.
Hey, I've never smelled
in my life, buddy.
Really? Well, I can
smell you now.
That's from the car.
Maybe you stunk up the car
rather than it stinking up you.
Oh, it's the chicken
and the egg.
Thank you very much.
Well, then,
go out and smell the car.
See which smells worse.
I don't have time
to smell cars.
Forget about smelling the car.
Smell the valet.
Go to the source.
You gotta smell the car.
I'm a busy man.
Come on. One whiff.
All right.
One whiff.
[SNIFFING]
[HITS CAR DOOR]
All right! I give up!
I admit it, it stinks!
Now, would you let me out!
Yeah.
Yeah, you'll pay
for the cleaning?
Yes, $50. I'll give you $50.
Fifty dollars, I don't think
that's gonna cover it.
I'll give you whatever you want!
I want half, $125.
Yes! Yes! $125 is good.
Now, would you please
open the door!
Let me out of here!
All right.
Oh.
GEORGE:
Oh, my God!
What?
The video!
Someone stole the video
right out of the car!
Someone stole
Rochelle, Rochelle?
Well, you left
the window open.
We had
to air out the car.
You know,
you should pay for it.
I'm not paying
for that.
They already
got my $7.
Erotic journey
from Milan to Minsk!
The valet
had such bad BO?
Oh, man,
just rampant, mutant BO.
The O went
from the valet's B,
to the car, to me.
Mm.
It clings
to everything.
[CHUCKLES]
Jerry thinks it's an entity.
[BOTH LAUGH]
But I showered
and I shampooed,
so...
That's a relief.
Yeah.
Phew.
What?
It's still there.
No, no, no.
It can't be.
I shampooed,
I rinsed, I repeated.
It's still there.
I smelled it.
I don't smell anything.
Here, take another smell.
No.
No, here.
Just one more smell!
Please!
CLERK:
Which movie was that again?
Rochelle, Rochelle.
George.
Oh, hey,
thanks for meeting me here.
Yeah, I don't have much time.
Yeah, listen, I got to ask you--
I was a little concerned that...
Perhaps I was responsible
in some way for your, uh...
Metamorphosis.
[TAPPING CALCULATOR]
That'll be $98.
What $98?
That's what
I said, $98.
How could that piece of crap
cost $98?
George,
I really have--
Do you believe this? $98!
Jeez.
Do you have any cash?
I guess.
I need, like, 35. Thanks.
So...was it me?
Oh, don't be
ridiculous.
Is that what you wanted
to talk to me about?
Here.
Oh, thanks, thanks a lot.
I'll pay you back.
Yeah, sure.
I gotta go.
L-l-listen.
Let me
ask you something.
If you and Mona
were ever to dance,
how do you decide who leads?
I mean, do you take turns?
Do you discuss it beforehand?
How does that work?
You're an idiot.
Why? That's a legitimate
sociological question.
I'll see you.
Oh, and, George,
by the way, you stink.
You need a bath. Ugh.
Wait, it's not me! It's the car.
I didn't think I'd come.
I knew you would.
Oh, Mona.
[SOFTLY]
Kramer.
Oh.
We give it the full
executive treatment.
That includes
complete deionization
of the entire vehicle
where we spray everything
with Ozium-D,
let it deionize,
vacuum the spray out
with a deionizing machine.
Hit it with high-pressure
compressed air,
and wet-dry vac it to extract
the remaining liquids.
Then we top it off with one
of our seven air fresheners.
In your case,
I would recommend
the, uh, jasmine
or the potpourri.
Let's do it.
The first thing
that we're gonna do
is flush the follicles
with the five essential oils.
Then we put you
under a vapor machine,
and then a heated cap.
Then we shampoo
and shampoo,
and condition and condition.
Then we saturate the hair
in diluted vinegar.
Two parts vinegar,
10 parts water. Now...
if that doesn't work,
we have one last resort.
Tomato sauce.
Tomato sauce?
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Wait a minute.
It still smells.
It still smells!
How could it still smell
after all that?
I don't know!
Well, what are you
gonna do?
I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do,
I'm selling that car.
You're selling the car?
You don't understand
what I'm up against.
This is a force
more powerful
than anything
you can imagine!
Even Superman
would be helpless
against this
kind of stench.
And I'll take anything
I can get for it.
Maybe I'll buy it.
Are you crazy?
Don't you understand
what I'm saying to you?
This isn't just an odor.
You need a priest
to get rid of this thing.
I still smell!
You see?!
You see what
I'm saying to you?!
It's a presence!
It's the beast.
All right,
let me smell you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
WOMAN:
Kramer? Kramer!
What is that?
What's going on?
WOMAN: Kramer, open up.
I know you're in there.
Susan.
Kramer!
What is going on?
You know what's going on?
First he vomits on me,
then he burns down
my father's cabin,
and now, he's taken Mona
away from me.
He stole your girlfriend?
Yes!
She's in love with him.
Amazing.
I drive them
to lesbianism,
he brings them back.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
KRAMER:
Is she still there?
No, she left.
What is going on?
What did you do?
I don't know,
I didn't do anything.
I was in
the video store,
and I was practicing
my golf swing, you know.
And, uh, you know,
with a broom,
and--
Yeah.
But she saw me take a swing,
and she told me
that the club
is going back too fast.
Well, we started talking.
She's a golf teacher!
So I went to a lesson,
and, you know,
something happened between us,
but she's a golf teacher, Jerry!
I've struck gold!
I've already taken
six strokes off my game.
That's the least of what
you've accomplished.
Listen, I'm having
dinner with her tonight.
Is it all right
if I borrow your jacket?
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Kramer, Kramer,
hold on a second.
I don't get this.
This woman
has never been with a man
her entire life.
I'm Kramer.
I know what
you're going through.
Women! Who knows
what they want?
I just don't know
what she sees in Kramer.
Listen.
You're beautiful.
You're intelligent.
You'll meet other girls.
You think so?
Yes, I know so.
You happen to be
a very eligible lesbian.
You're very sweet.
Hey, I know what
I'm talking about.
And I gotta be
honest with you.
I gotta tell you...
ever since I saw you
holding hands with that woman,
I can't get you
out of my mind.
Really?
Yeah. You're just so...
hip.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's Allison.
I dated her right after you.
She was obsessed with me.
George?
[LAUGHS]
Allison, hi!
Oh, my God! How are you?
Good. You know,
you owe me $50.
Fifty, right, right.
I don't have it on me right now.
Allison, this is Susan.
Susan, Allison.
Nice to meet you.
That's a beautiful vest.
Thank you.
I don't understand it.
I was with her last night
at my apartment.
It was very romantic.
You know, with that
fake wood wallpaper,
the atmosphere
is fabulous in there now.
It's like a ski lodge.
What year did you say this was?
'90.
Anyway, we were on the couch,
I move to hug her,
next thing, she tells me
she's leaving.
She's gotta get up early.
That's strange.
How many miles
you got on this thing?
Twenty-three thousand.
And I was
looking good too.
I had a nice
new shirt on,
I'm wearing your jacket.
[WHISPERS]
Wait a second.
My jacket!
I wore that in the car!
The beast!
Uggggghhh!
This wicked funk.
I can't sell this car.
This...
thing!
It's got to be stopped.
What do you
wanna do?
Sauce me.
Why do we need BO?
What is the function of it?
Everything in nature
has a reason, has a purpose,
except BO.
Doesn't make any sense.
Do something good,
hard work, exercise,
smell very bad.
This is the way
the human being is designed.
You move, you stink.
Why can't our bodies help us?
Why can't sweat smell good?
It'd be a different world,
wouldn't it?
Instead of putting your laundry
in the hamper,
you put it in a vase.
Go down to the drug store,
pick up some odorant
and perspirant.
Probably have a dirty sweat sock
hanging from
the rearview mirror of your car.
And then,
on a really special night,
maybe a little underwear
coming out
of your breast pocket.
Just to show her
that she's important.