To me, the whole concept
of fear of success
is proof that
we are definitely
scraping the bottom
of the fear barrel.
Are we going to have
to have AA-type meetings
for these people?
Going, "Hi. My name is Bill.
"And the one thing
I'm worried about
is having a stereo
and a cream-colored couch."
According to most studies,
people's number one fear
is public speaking.
Number two is death.
Death is number two.
Now, this means,
to the average person,
if you have to
go to a funeral,
you're better
off in the casket than doing the eulogy.
Why? Why can't I
play Kramer?
Look, we've been
through this already.
You're not an actor.
Neither are you.
I know.
Why do we need two people
in the show that can't act?
Oh, come on, Jerry.
How hard is it to act?
You say something,
I'll pretend it's funny.
Come on.
My grandmother's
in the hospital.
[LAUGHING UPROARIOUSLY]
Your grandmother's
in the hospital!
Oh, this is real believable.
What? You didn't think
I was really laughing?
It stinks.
All right,
let's see you do it.
Say something funny.
All right.
I've never been to Mars,
but I imagine
it's quite lovely.
Mine was better than that!
Come on, look.
Why are you two
pretending to be laughing?
We're acting.
Oh. Yeah, real good.
Any word from NBC?
No.
I don't understand.
They're supposed to be
casting this week.
Something's wrong.
Maybe they're not doing it.
Well, at least
let me audition.
He wants to play Kramer
in the pilot.
Out of the question.
Yeah!
Oh!
How could we
not hear anything?
What's with this Russell?
What's he doing?
ELAINE:
Hi, Russell.
Sit. Sit down.
It's okay.
I really appreciate
you coming.
Oh, that's okay. I don't
have much time, though, so...
All right, well,
first of all...
I want to apologize
for all the phone calls.
It's just-- It's just--
I don't understand. I mean,
we went out, once, and--
Yeah, that was
two months ago.
Yes, I know.
And I-- I just-- I can't
get you out of my mind.
Ever since that... That day
in that restaurant when we met.
Do you, uh...have
a ketchup secret?
No, I...
Russell, you are
the president of NBC.
Okay? You can have
any woman you want.
But I want you.
God, I hate
these mixtures.
I don't know why--
Why don't they just put
pretzels out on the table?
Or even peanuts
would be good.
But I don't know who
eats these cheesy things.
Is it something I said?
Or did?
Um... Look, Russell.
You're a very sweet guy.
But, um...I gotta
be honest with you.
I don't like television.
And that's your world.
That's your life.
I mean, maybe
if you were in, um,
I don't know,
Greenpeace or something,
that would be different,
but network television!
I mean, come on, Russell.
You're part of the problem.
Oh, Elaine, we're doing
some really very, very
interesting things right now.
We've got some very exciting
pilots for next season.
We have one with
a bright young comedian,
Jerry Seinfeld.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah,
I've heard of him.
He's that, um,
"Did you ever notice this?
Did you ever notice that?" guy.
He was in the restaurant
the day that we met.
Uh-huh.
Um...well, anyway,
it's a groundbreaking show.
Really?
What is it about?
Well, it's-- It's really--
It's very unusual.
It's about nothing.
What do you mean
it's about nothing?
Mmm. For example,
what did you do today?
Um...I got up,
um, I went to work,
then I came here.
There's a show.
That's a show.
Russell, see, I'm really
not interested in this stuff.
And I do have to
go to work, so...
Elaine, uh...
When-- When are we--
When are we going
to see each other again?
I'm sorry,
Russell.
I'm sorry, okay?
Bye-bye.
So I'll see you later, huh?
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah.
Hello?
Yeah, he's here. Hey!
It's for you.
Oh, yeah?
He's getting phone
calls here now?
Hello.
Yeah.
Hey!
Again with the sweatpants?
What? I'm comfortable.
You know the message you're
sending out to the world
with these sweatpants?
You're telling the world,
"I give up!"
"I can't compete
in normal society.
"I'm miserable,
so I might as well
be comfortable."
KRAMER:
Hold on a second.
I got another call.
Hello.
Yeah, he'll call you back.
Who is it?
That's NBC.
NBC?
Kramer, give me the phone!
I'm in the middle
of a conversation!
Get off the phone!
Look, I'll call you back.
Yeah. All right.
You know I'm waiting
to hear from them!
Who was it?
It was Russell
Dalrymple's secretary.
All right.
Now you're doing
something to help me.
Hello? Yes. Jerry Seinfeld,
returning the call.
Uh-huh.
Okay, great.
Thanks a lot.
Casting tomorrow at NBC, 4:00!
We're in business, baby!
The pilot's on!
You're gonna be successful!
What if the pilot
gets picked up
and it becomes a series?
That would be wonderful,
George. You'll be rich and successful.
Yeah, that's exactly
what I'm worried about.
God would never let me
be successful.
He'd kill me first.
He'll never let me be happy.
I thought you didn't
believe in God.
I do for the bad things.
Do you hear
what you're saying?
God isn't out
to get you, George.
What--
What is that on your lip?
What?
It's like a discoloration.
It's white.
Yes.
Yes, it's white.
Why is that white?
You'd better
get that checked out.
"Better get that checked out?"
I would.
What kind of a therapist
are you?
I'm paying you,
I'm scared that
something terrible's
gonna happen to me,
right away, you start
looking for tumors?
I'm trying to help you!
What are you, like a sadist?
No matter how bad
somebody feels,
you can make them feel worse.
I bet you're rooting
for a tumor.
I think you'd better go.
Oh, I'm going, baby.
I'm going!
Where?
Right here.
Get outta here. It's nothing.
Excuse me, do you see
anything on my lip here?
Yeah. Like
a discoloration.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it's all white.
It's all white, Jerry.
It's all white.
Would you stop?
Oh, I'd get that checked out
if I were you.
Again with the checked out!
I'm not going to the doctor.
If I don't go to the doctor,
nothing will happen.
If I go, he might
find something.
If you go, maybe they'll
catch it in time.
Catch what in time?
Whatever it is.
You think it's something?
Oh, I hate these bums
with their filthy rags.
No, no, no, no!
I don't want it!
Get away! Get away!
Get away from my car!
You know, these squeegee--
Oh, my God,
it's Crazy Joe Davola!
Good luck on the pilot, Jerry.
Yeah, I think I see it.
It's like a...
white discoloration.
What do you think it is?
It's like a white
discoloration.
Okay, guys. Are we
ready to start?
Yeah. Where's Russell?
I thought he was gonna be here.
Oh, you know, I don't know.
I saw him in the hall
this morning,
I said hello to him.
He walked right past me.
He must be worried
about the fall schedule.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a real bear.
So what's going on?
We're gonna shoot the pilot
and then it's gonna be on TV
the following week?
Yeah, right.
[DOOR OPENS]
This is Mark Matts.
He'll be auditioning
for the role of George.
How you doing?
Hey, Mark.
How are you?
JERRY: They've gotta
be kidding.
GEORGE: This guy's perfect!
Okay, let's read this.
I'll be reading Jerry's part.
Anyone call
for Vandelay Industries?
CASTING DIRECTOR:
No, why?
Listen to me.
I told the unemployment office
I was close to a job
with Vandelay Industries
and I gave them
your phone number.
So when you answer
the phone now,
you've got to say,
"Vandelay Industries."
[LAUGHS]
MARK: Right!
I'm Vandelay Industries?
You're in latex.
What is that?
What do I do with latex?
I don't know...
You manufacture it!
This is Michael Barth,
another George.
ALL: Hi, Michael.
How you doing?
Everything all right?
I just came from
the podiatrist.
I got something wrong
with my foot.
I got a little gangrene.
They're
probably gonna
have to amputate.
[LAUGHS]
Uh, yeah.
Any questions?
What are we looking at here?
Is this guy like a real loser?
No, not a loser!
Uh,
let's start with the second scene. You have it there?
Yeah.
Okay.
A man gave me a...massage.
[LAUGHS]
CASTING DIRECTOR:
So?
Uh, well, he, uh...
He had his hands, you know,
and, uh, he was, uh...
He was what?
Well, he was, you know...
touching and rubbing.
That's a massage.
I think it moved.
Melissa Shannon.
Hi!
ALL: Hi, Melissa!
Melissa is reading for Elaine.
It's like a bald convention
out there!
Sorry. I made a faux pas.
No, you didn't.
He knows he's bald.
So how about that guy
wearing sweatpants?
I mean, did he do that
for the part
or does he walk around
like that?
CASTING DIRECTOR:
Okay.
Shall we start?
Uh, you know what?
I'll read with her.
Oh, great!
Oh!
Yeah.
All right. Want to start?
Okay.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What was that look?
What look?
That look you just gave me.
I gave a look?
Yes.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
CASTING DIRECTOR:
Let's see some more Kramers.
ALL:
Hi! How you doing?
How you doing?
Good.
Levels.
What is this about?
Levels?
Yeah. I'm getting rid
of all my furniture.
All of it.
I'm building levels...
with steps.
Completely carpeted...
with pillows.
[ALL LAUGH]
Like ancient Egypt.
I don't know how
you're gonna be comfortable like that.
Oh...I'll be comfortable.
Very good!
Very nice!
GEORGE: Very nice.
Tom, that was terrific!
Thank you for coming in.
It was a wonderful reading.
Yeah, really.
Well, bye!
Thank you. Take it easy!
Now, I thought
he was really good.
Yeah, I liked him.
Very funny.
What happened
to the raisins?
Yeah, there was a box
of raisins there.
Did he just steal
the raisins?
Do you think
he stole them?
This is Martin Van Nostrand.
What are you
doing here?
You two know
each other?
Wait a minute. I know you!
You're the guy from
the Calvin Klein underwear ads.
That's true.
I saw Joe DiMaggio
in Dinky Donuts again.
But this time...
I went in.
[GROANS]
Where's the bathroom?
I think if you
go down the hall,
it's on the right
at the very end.
Be right back.
MAN: Sorry, buddy.
Full house.
MAN: Sorry. Customers only.
MAN: Hey, you need a ticket!
[GROANS]
So who's playing
Elaine?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Very talented, very talented
young actress.
Really?
Yes.
Who is it?
She's an Eskimo,
actually.
Oh, God.
She came down from Juneau by sled.
Uh-huh.
She was in the Iditarod.
Got to the finish line,
just kept going.
She's got the dogs
with her in the hotel room.
Listen, was Russell
at the casting?
No, he didn't show up.
You know, I'm a little bit
worried about him.
I don't understand. We had
one date two months ago.
Am I that charming
and beautiful?
No. No, you're not.
Why do I keep
setting you up?
I don't know.
Could we get
a little more?
You know, ever since
this new owner took over,
the service here
is really slow.
Yeah.
Have you noticed anything else
that's...different
since the new management?
Mmm.
They're putting a little lemon
in the tuna.
I love that.
Mmm. Besides that.
Look at the waitresses.
Yeah?
What physical
characteristic
would you say is common
to all of them?
Uh-- Uh-- Aah.
Ha-ha.
I mean, look at this.
Every waitress working here
has the same proportions,
wouldn't you say?
Yes, I would say.
What's going on here?
How is this possible?
Do you think
it's a coincidence?
No.
I haven't seen four women
like this together
outside of a Russ Meyer film.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hi.
Excuse me. Who does all the hiring of waitresses here?
Um, he does.
We're looking
for another girl, if you know anyone.
Oh.
You know what?
That's discriminatory.
That is unfair.
Why should these women
have all the advantages?
It's not enough they get
all the attention from men?
They have to get
all the waitress jobs too?
Hey, that's life. Good-looking
men have the same advantage.
You don't see
any handsome homeless.
Do you see it?
It's right here. It's-- It's a little white...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I've never
seen this before.
Never seen this before?
I'm gonna have to take
a biopsy on this.
A what?
A biopsy.
A biopsy?
Yeah.
Cancer? Is it cancer?
Do I have cancer?
Well, I don't know
what it is.
He took a biopsy, Jerry,
a biopsy.
What did he say?
He said he didn't know
what it was.
All right, so?
When I asked him
if it was cancer,
he didn't give me
a "Get outta here."
That's what I wanted to hear.
"Cancer? Hey, get outta here."
Well, maybe he doesn't have
a "Get outta here"
kind of personality.
How could you be a doctor
and not say, "Get outta here"?
It should be part of
the training at medical school.
"Cancer? Get outta here!
"Go home! What are you, crazy?
"It's a little test.
It's nothing.
You're a real nut,
do you know that?"
I told you God would never
let me be successful.
I never should have
written that pilot.
Now the show will be a big hit
and make millions of dollars
and I'll be dead,
dead, Jerry,
because of this.
Can't you at least die
with a little dignity?
No, I can't.
I can't die with dignity.
I have no dignity.
I want to be the one person
who doesn't die with dignity.
I lived my
whole life in shame! Why should I die with dignity?
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Hey.
What happened
to you yesterday?
I got mugged.
You got mugged?
Mugged?
Well, I wouldn't have
minded it so much,
but I was running home
to go to the bathroom.
Well, why didn't you use
the bathroom in the building?
It was full.
I tried a few other
places, you know,
but that didn't work.
I mean, it was
an emergency, Jerry.
I was really
percolating.
So I decided to run home,
you know, through the park.
And then these two guys,
they stopped me.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
It's me.
Come on up.
But now I got
a big problem, buddy.
What is it?
Well, I waited so long,
I-- I missed my chance.
You didn't go?
No. And now
I can't get it back.
The best thing to do
is just not think about it.
How could you
not think about it?
Hey.
Hey--
[MUMBLES]
What's the matter
with him?
He's a little backed up.
Oh.
Elaine.
So, I spoke
to some of my sisters
about that coffee shop.
Oh, the sisters.
Have you seen the waitresses
in there lately?
I never had so much coffee
in my life.
ELAINE: So we decided
I should go over there
and apply
for a job myself.
Apply for a job?
What for?
Because it's
discriminatory.
It's a coincidence.
Yeah.
This is what you're gonna wear?
You're not gonna get the job.
Exactly.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Yeah,
I guess we could do that.
At what time?
All right.
Uh, I'll see you there.
Okay. Bye.
Who was that?
TV Elaine.
She wants to get together
and talk about the part.
Oh. What about the dogs?
They're having sex
in the hotel room.
So the Elaine character
is based on someone you know.
Yes.
And she's really
your ex-girlfriend.
Uh-huh, yeah.
I want to get to know her
from the inside.
What is she like?
Tell me about her.
Well, she's fascinated
with Greenland.
She enjoys
teasing animals, Banlon,
and seeing people
running for their lives.
She loves throwing garbage
out the window,
yet she's
extremely dainty.
How would she
eat a hamburger?
With her hands.
What about pasta?
Also with her hands.
Seriously...
I want to experience
everything she's experienced.
Everything?
Everything.
All right, she cuts pasta
with a knife.
That's good.
What's her favorite movie?
Shaft.
You got to
get me a picture.
What about sex?
She likes talking
during sex.
Oh.
Dirty talking?
No, just chitchat. Movies,
current events, regular stuff.
You know, Sandi--
Elaine.
What?
Call me...Elaine.
All right...
Elaine.
How does Elaine kiss?
Well--
Does she kiss...
like this?
Actually,
she has a thing
where she spirals
her tongue around--
It's like--
Like this?
I think you got it.
Now, I like to eat spaghetti
with just a fork,
because I can keep
the strands long
and I can slurp it up
to my mouth like this.
Look.
[SLURPING]
Now, sex,
I like the bottom.
Let them do
all the work, you know?
You should be writing
this stuff down.
Yeah, bran flakes...
100 percent.
I got a big problem.
I'll have a hamburger.
That's it.
Thanks a lot.
That's good.
Oh, now,
I like to play golf.
This stuff
doesn't matter to me.
See,
I'm gonna do the character like me, not like you.
You got to play him
like me. I'm Kramer.
I'm Kramer.
Whoa.
What can I do for you?
Would you like table?
No, I'd like to apply
for a waitress job.
Oh. Have you ever
waited on tables before?
Oh, yeah.
I've been
a professional waitress
for the last 10 years.
And I've worked
all over the city.
These, uh,
are my references.
I'm sure you'll find
that I'm more than qualified.
I don't think I need
anyone else right now.
You're in big trouble,
mister,
and I mean trouble
with a capital T.
What? What did I do?
ELAINE:
Anyway, there's at least
four of them,
and they're all huge.
I mean, one is bigger
than the next.
It's like
a Russ Meyer movie.
Who's Russ Meyer?
Oh, um, he's this guy
who made these terrible movies
in the '70s
with these kinds
of women.
He's obsessed.
He's obsessed
with breasts.
That's hard to say.
Anyway, go on.
Um...
Well, there's not
really much more to tell.
He was looking
for waitresses,
and I went in to apply
for the job,
and he looked me up and down
and he rejected me.
Paul, come here
for a second.
I want you
to listen to this.
Hi.
Paul, the woman here claims
there's a restaurant
on the West Side
that's only hiring
large-breasted women.
Really?
What do you mean
"made up"?
It's made up.
Ha11agen-Dazs is made up.
It's not Danish.
TV KRAMER:
You're crazy.
JERRY:
No, I'm not.
George,
is Ha11agen-Dazs Danish?
What do you mean,
"Danish"?
This guy stinks.
Danish.
Is it from Denmark?
No, they make it
in New Jersey.
It's just
a Danish-sounding name.
I can't believe that.
They fooled me, Jerry.
[WHISPERING] Boy, talk about
a show about nothing.
Uh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
This-- This is not right.
May I?
You see, you're going,
"They fooled me, Jerry."
You want to hit "fooled" more.
You see the difference?
I'm not gonna
say it like that.
Just a suggestion.
[CHUCKLES]
All right, everybody,
take a five!
Yep, that's five!
[ALARM BUZZES]
George?
Um...
I don't have
a lot of experience with this acting stuff,
but, from
what I can gather,
they're a little touchy about
being told how to say the lines.
Why is that?
I don't know,
but they don't seem to like it.
Oh, you're fine. You're fine.
By the way, how am I doing?
So you think this guy playing
Kramer took the raisins?
Why would he steal
a box of raisins?
Yeah.
It's bizarre.
That little bald guy's
driving me nuts.
I'm gonna rip him a new one
if he doesn't leave.
I wish that was
our real problem.
What do you think
the real problem is?
It's Seinfeld.
He can't act.
It's pathetic.
I told you, these
stand-ups can't act.
I'm cringing watching him.
What's with him?
Russell?
RITA:
What?
You okay?
Yeah.
No, I-I was just...
thinking of something.
I'll be back in a second.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You're acting weird.
Is anything wrong?
No.
Are you breaking up
with me?
Are we going out?
You're breaking up with me,
aren't you?
Do you want me
to break up with you?
If that's what
you want.
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Okay, fine.
Break up with me.
All right,
we're broken up.
Can we
still be friends?
Do you remember when you
came to audition?
Yeah.
There was a box of raisins
on the coffee table.
Did you, by any chance, take
them with you when you left?
What are you
talking about?
Well, we were all
eating the raisins.
And I remember you...you were
eating some of the raisins.
And then you left,
and the raisins were gone.
And I was just wondering
if, you know,
maybe you took them with you.
Are you accusing me
of stealing the raisins?
Oh, no, no--
Why would I steal
a box of raisins?
No, you wouldn't.
Nobody would, you know.
It's just that
they were missing,
and, uh, well,
I'm just inquiring.
Let me give you
a word of advice, okay?
I want you
to stay away from me.
I don't want
to talk to you,
and I don't want
to hear any more
of your stupid little notes
and suggestions.
I don't like you.
So if you got
any other problems,
whether it's raisins, prunes,
figs or any other dried fruit,
just keep it to yourself,
and stay out of my way, okay?
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
All right, um...
I don't think we're gonna
have any problem with that.
Good talking to you, Tom.
Really.
Elaine, Elaine,
what do you want?
What can I do?
Um-- Is--
Is it, uh--?
Is it my job?
Is that what it is?
Elaine,
I can't go on like this.
W-w-will you call me?
Would you call me? Uh--
Well, why?
All right, you want--
May I call you?
Elaine? Elaine?
Excuse me, Mr. Dalrymple.
I am so sorry.
David Richardson.
All right, what's your name?
Get out! You're fired!
But, Mr. Dalrymple--
Don't talk back to me!
Didn't you hear what I said?
Get out.
You want me
to call the cops?
I make and break little worms
like you every day.
Do you know
how much money I make?
Do you have any idea?
Do you know where I live?
I could have any woman
in this city that I want.
Any one.
Now, get out!
RUSSELL:
What are you all looking at?!
Go back to work!
[SHOUTING] Back!
Now!
The doctor called
and said the lab's backed up.
So now I'm not gonna get the
results for another two days.
Oh, you're fine.
There's nothing wrong with you.
I'm the one who's dying.
Because I can't act!
What do you mean?
I stink!
I don't know what I'm doing!
I'm gonna make a fool
out of myself
in front of
the entire country.
Oh, come on.
You're, uh-- You're fine.
This show's gonna
ruin my career.
I don't know how
I got involved in this.
What about me?
I was a total failure.
Everything was fine.
Now this thing's
gonna be a success,
and God's gonna give me
a terminal disease.
This actress playing Elaine,
she's out of her mind.
Yeah. The guy playing Kramer
threatened me.
Why?
Because I asked him
about the raisins.
You mentioned
the raisins.
Oh, yeah.
Did he take them?
I don't know.
Well, if he didn't take them,
what happened to them?
That's what I'm trying
to find out.
Hey.
Oh.
Any luck?
No. No, nothing.
I got no peristalsis.
What about bran?
I tried bran.
40 percent, 50 percent,
100 percent.
The bran
isn't working for me.
Did it.
Well, what about Meta--?
Yeah, had it.
How about Ex--?
Milk of magne--?
Yeah, yeah.
Well,
my friend,
it may be time to consider
the dreaded apparatus.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Hold it right there.
If you're suggesting
what I think
you're suggesting,
you're wasting your time.
I am not, Jerry,
under any circumstances,
doing any inserting
in that area.
Oh, it's not that bad.
KRAMER: Yeah!
Yes, it is.
Well, it's all taken care of.
I filed a report.
An investigation is under way.
You going to
the taping?
No. I don't think I should go.
I really don't want
to bump into Russell.
He called me the other day.
He won't quit.
Oh, come on,
you gotta go.
He's harmless.
He's got a little crush on you.
Jerry,
this is not a crush.
This is a complete fixation.
He makes me very uncomfortable.
We need you there.
Hey, are you gonna go?
Uh, no, no.
I'm gonna stay home.
I--
I want to be close
to my home base
in case there's any news
from the front.
[]
Blblblbl!
Bugada,
bugada, bugada, bugada!
No! Pick it up more
in the front.
It's gotta be higher!
Higher!
Make a wall! A wall!
Sandi, are you
in wardrobe?
Sandi?
Try Elaine.
Elaine?
Yes?
It's me,
Wilton Marshall.
Remember?
Camp Tioga, 1978?
Oh.
Remember?
[CHUCKLING]
Right.
Wow.
You know,
you haven't changed a bit.
I can't remember
my lines!
I can't relax!
Just relax. You'll be fine.
I don't know what line.
I don't know any of them!
You're just like George.
George does the same thing.
You're just like him.
It's amazing.
Help me, Jerry! Help me.
George is always
saying that.
I can't believe it.
You don't have
to worry, anyway. It's not live.
It's not on until next week.
Have a good show.
Well, what's my first line?
Just tell me my first line.
"New sneakers?" Right.
"New sneakers?"
That's it.
"New sneakers?" Okay.
Where's Russell?
You know,
I don't know.
I thought he was coming.
I assumed he wouldn't miss it.
He hasn't
been well.
Can I tell you something
in confidence?
I think
it's a woman.
How pathetic.
Yeah. This is George Costanza.
I'm calling for my test results.
Negative?
Oh, my God!
Oh, why? Why? Why?
What?
Negative's good?
Oh! Oh, yes. Yes, of course.
How stupid of me.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
What was I worried about?
[CHUCKLES]
[HUMMING]
Listen, I know we've had
our problems in the past,
but we got a show
to do tonight, hmm?
Time to pull
together as a team. Life's too short.
I say, let's let bygones
be bygones.
If you took the raisins,
if you didn't take
the raisins...
They weren't even
my raisins.
I was just curious,
because it seemed like
a strange thing to do,
to walk into a room,
audition,
and walk out with
a box of raisins.
Anyway, whatever.
If you ever want to tell me
about it,
the door to my office
is always open...
in the event
that I get an office.
You'll come in,
we'll talk about the raisins,
we'll have a nice laugh.
How would you like it
if I just pulled your heart
out of your chest right now
and shoved it
down your throat?
ANNOUNCER: Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to a taping
of the new show Jerry.
Does everybody here know
what a pilot is?
Yeah,
he flies the plane.
No, a pilot
is the taping of a show
that's the first show
before a TV series.
And this show will air
on Thursday.
Are you ready
to meet our cast?
AUDIENCE:
Yeah!
All right.
Good evening, folks.
How you doing?
[APPLAUSE]
Well, you sound like
a great crowd.
We have a show we're gonna
put on for you tonight.
It's a new TV show,
it's what they call a pilot,
and we hope it
becomes a series.
It's called Jerry,
and I'm playing Jerry--
Sic semper tyrannis!
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
What about Davola?
Did you believe that?
What was that thing
he yelled out,
"sic semper tyrannis"?
Yeah.
What is that, Latin?
What John Wilkes Booth
yelled when he shot Lincoln.
It means "Death to tyrants."
Really? What does it mean?
I can see that.
See, now, this is exciting.
This is exciting, huh?
Did I miss anything
already?
No. It starts
in five minutes.
You were there at the taping.
What's the big deal?
Now it's on TV.
It's different.
I told everybody I know
to watch it.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, what about Russell?
Did you hear from him?
No.
Strange, him not showing up
at the taping.
Hey, pistol-packin' mama
You swing that gal around
Allemande left
with the old gray hag
Around and around you go
Yee-ha!
Well, well, well.
Congratulations.
Well, thank you.
You went for
the big E?
Wet and wild.
All right, sit down.
It's about to start.
Oh, yes.
Hey, what is this?
Look, a wallet.
A wallet?
Let me see that.
Here.
Oh, man,
it's my father's wallet,
the one he thought they stole
at the doctor's office
that time.
How do you like that?
This is it!
Get-- Get--
[]
[ALL CHEERING]
You hurt me.
Hey.
Hey, George.
New sneakers?
Yeah.
What do you need
new sneakers for?
I like sneakers.
How do you make a decision
which ones to wear?
I'd go crazy if
I had to decide.
Oh, you're crazy anyway.
ELAINE:
Why did you eat
the top off the muffin?
GEORGE:
So what?
ELAINE:
I can't eat it now.
BOTH:
George.
What kind of stupid show
is this?
Hey, that's that idiot
that took all my records!
[LAUGHS]
John, what are you doing?
Come back to bed.
This, uh, show
looks interesting.
Uh,
isn't he that Seinfeld fella you went out with?
Ooh, he's horrible!
Horrible!
Nevertheless...
Oh, that Jerry's
a funny guy, huh?
Got to love the Sein.
Hate the Sein.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
DONALD:
This is a piece of crap!
Oh, Donald,
you used to like him.
DONALD:
What a sellout!
Give me that remote!
Give me the--
No, Donald!
Donald!
Give me the remote!
Come on, Jerry,
the commercial's almost over.
All right.
You know, Jerry, I really like
this guy playing the butler.
Oh, yeah, he's good.
He's John Ritter's cousin.
Really?
Yeah.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
Hello, Charles.
Hello.
So, uh, where do you want me
to start?
Start in the bedroom.
[GRUMBLING] I'll start
in your bedroom.
Hey.
The butler's here.
He is?
Listen, when he's finished,
send him over to my house.
I'm not sending him
to your house.
Why not?
Because the judge decreed
he'd become my butler,
not my friend's butler.
Jerry, he is your butler.
You can give him
any order you want.
That's what butlers do.
But I don't want to.
Jerry, my house is a pigsty.
Come on.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
It's Elaine.
Yeah?
Come on up.
I need more Pledge.
More Pledge?
I just bought two cans
last week,
and I don't have any wood
in the house.
Well, it goes fast.
Hello.
What's all this about?
We had a date
last week.
You had a date?
You went out with my butler?
Who said you could
go out with my butler?
Well, why do I need
your permission?
Because he's my butler.
Ha ha! That's terrific!
[LAUGHING]
How could anyone not like him?
I like his style.
He has a sort of
casual elegance.
But he picks his nose.
Nevertheless...
He's a member of
our health club, isn't he?
Yeah.
JERRY:
Sure, that's great. 2:00?
You know, that Kim Novak
had some big breasts.
...now a two-one pitch
to Mattingly.
[CHEERING AND WHISTLING ON TV]
You ever notice
a lot of butlers are named Jeeves?
You know, I think
when you name a baby Jeeves,
you've pretty much mapped out
his future, wouldn't you say?
Not much chance
he's going to be a hit man,
I think, after that.
"Terribly sorry, sir,
but I'm going
to have to whack you."
Yeah!
[CHEERS]
Oh, wow!
That was great.
That show
was so funny.
It was really funny.
I'm not just saying that
because I know you, honestly.
All right, well, let's
go out and celebrate.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Seriously, that was so good.
[PHONE RINGS]
You know what? This thing's
gonna get picked up.
You guys are gonna be rich.
Oh, yeah.
Do you really think so?
And God didn't kill me.
RITA: Hi, Jerry.
Hello?
This is Rita Kierson.
Oh, hi, Rita.
I'm calling to let you know
that Russell Dalrymple
is no longer
with this network.
Oh, my God. Did he get fired?
To be honest with you,
nobody really knows.
He seems to have disappeared.
Russell's disappeared?
In any event, I've been made
the new president of NBC.
As you may or may not know,
Russell and I
did not see eye to eye
on many, many projects.
And as my first order
of business,
I'm, uh, passing on your show.
You're passing already?
The show just ended
two minutes ago.
Well, I just got the job.
Goodbye, Jerry.
Yeah. See you.
W-what are you
looking at me for?
It was you!
What? What? What did I do?
Do you realize his obsession
with you cost us a TV series?
I didn't know
that he'd fall for me,
and I'd drive him insane.
I mean, you know,
that's not my fault.
Yes, it is!
You're very charming!
I can't believe this.
What happened to him?
Where the hell is he?
No one knows.
RUSSELL: She works
for Pendant Publishing.
She's the most beautiful woman
I've ever seen.
You know, I used to
work for NBC,
but when I go back
to her this time,
she'll respect me.
You'd better get down.
They might
start firing soon.
[GUNSHOTS]
Hey,
look at this.
What is
going on here?
GEORGE:
Well, well, well.
Nothing has changed.
How did this happen?
Oh, these are
the two guys I talked to
at the Equal Employment
Opportunity Commission.
Hey, what are you two guys
doing here?
I thought you were going to do
something about this.
Now you're eating here?
Oh, well, no,
that's why we're here.
We're checking things out.
You're checking it out?
Yeah, we're checking it out.
See you
back at the office, guys.
Fred, Paul! Lunch and dinner?
Boy, you guys
ought to move in.
How about a piece of pie,
on me, huh?
Sophia, take care
of these fellows.
Hey, come here a second.
I want you
to know something.
You are not gonna
get away with this!
Get away with what?
Oh, "with what?"
You know what.
With the waitresses,
how they're all...alike.
Oh!
Oh! Of course they're alike.
They're my daughters.
Oh!
Your daughters.
Oh, you must be very proud,
Mr. Visaki.
And may I say, sir,
they're lovely girls.
Absolutely lovely girls.
It's nice to see such fine,
upstanding women
in gainful employment,
Mr. Visaki.
Oh, a table right here.
Oh, here's table for you.
Peggy!
All right.
Daughter.
Peggy. His daughter Peggy.
Peggy's coming over
to serve.
One of the family.
Peggy.
My daughter Peggy.
Ah, Peggy,
good to see you.
Thank you very much.
Hi, Peggy.
Guess what
I gotta do tomorrow.
What?
JERRY: Oh.
Start looking for a job.
KRAMER: You know what you
ought to do, George?
You should work
for Greenpeace.
You know those people,
they attack the whalers
out on the open sea.
Are you crazy?
You take your
life in your hands with those nuts.
Keep fighting, matey!
Get your head
above the water!
I've got you, matey!
I got you, matey!
I'll remember her name:
Elaine Benes!
I'll write to her!
I'll tell her all about you
and what you did out here!
Goodbye, matey!
Goodbye!
Now,
I know women often complain
about the number of things
you have to do
to get male attention:
the high heels,
the pantyhose, the makeup.
But let me tell you,
it's even worse if you're a man.
Because if you're a man,
you don't know what to do.
That's why we're building
bridges, climbing mountains,
exploring
uncharted territories.
You think we want
to do these things?
Nobody wants to
build a bridge.
It's really, really hard.
Designing rockets,
flying off into space--
I guarantee you,
every astronaut,
when he comes back from space,
goes up to a girl and goes,
"So did you see me up there?"