I don't belong
to a health club.
I have a strict limit
on the number of naked men
I need to see in one day...
zero.
That's it.
What is with the high level
of security
at the health clubs,
you know what I mean?
The picture ID's,
the security guards,
the people signing in and out.
What is this, the Kremlin?
I mean, the people
that have a membership
go twice a year.
Who's breaking in?
Is this a big problem,
people stealing exercise?
And what if they catch
the person? What then?
They run. It's aerobic.
Makes it even worse.
Hi, Jerry.
Oh, hi, Sidra.
I usually last
about 10 minutes
on the StairMaster.
Unless, of course, if someone's
stretching in front of me
in a leotard,
then I can go an hour.
Really?
That's why they call it
the StairMaster.
You get up there
and stare.
Well, I'm done.
I think I'm gonna
go take a sauna.
All right, I'll see you
Thursday night, right?
Thursday night.
Okay.
Good workout?
Tremendous workout.
She's a pretty girl.
Tremendous girl.
She's the one
you went out with
last night?
Yeah.
I really like her.
You know, uh...
they're fake.
What? Don't say that.
Yeah,
they're fake.
How do you know?
I can tell.
You know how
you're always bragging
how you can
spot a lesbian?
I'm not bragging.
I happen to have
a very keen lesbian eye.
Hi. How you doing?
Oh, right.
Come on.
Don't you think they seem
just a bit
too perfect?
Yes, they do.
I never knew
you were
so into breasts.
I thought
you were a leg man.
A leg man? Why would I
be a leg man?
I don't need legs.
I have legs.
Have you ever seen her naked
in the locker room?
No.
Oh, well, then I can't
accept your testimony.
Maybe if you'd
seen her naked.
I don't wanna
see her naked.
Well, I do.
Well, that's
your problem.
Look, you made
the allegation.
The least you could do
is follow up.
Oh, Jerry,
what am I gonna do?
I'm gonna go in there,
I'm gonna spy on her
in the sauna?
Yes.
Go in there,
do a little
investigative journalism.
I need to know.
But a few more dates,
you can find out for yourself.
Don't be so sure.
Look at George.
He's on his ninth date
with Betsy,
he still hasn't gotten
anywhere with her.
What's his problem?
Every time he tries to make
a move, something screws up.
On their last date,
they were on the couch,
but she was sitting
on his wrong side.
"Wrong side"?
Yeah,
she was on his right side.
He can't make a move
with his left hand.
He can't go left.
He can't go left?
No.
I'm lefty, can't go right.
What about women,
do they go left or right?
No,
we just play defense.
Oh!
Can I ask you
a question?
Would you mind
switching seats?
Oh.
Actually, I'd really
prefer to sit here.
I don't hear very well
out of this ear,
so I, um...
always try to sit
to the right of people.
I'll shout.
Well, I really think
I feel
more comfortable here.
Come on.
Come on, really.
George!
No, come on.
No, I really--
Come on.
See, now,
is that so bad?
What?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Oh, the machine
will get it.
Oh, no, no,
it's not on.
They'll call back.
But, George, what if
it's an emergency?
In the whole world right now,
there's maybe three emergencies.
Why would you think,
on this entire planet,
that you're one
of those three?
George, please.
Hello.
What?
Oh, my God!
All right,
maybe four.
ELAINE:
Boy... I'm really sweating.
Good sweat, beads of sweat,
sweating bullets.
Look at her.
I don't need to see her naked
to know those aren't real.
Why'd she even tie the towel
around her?
She's got a rack on her chest.
Oh, God.
Sidra's taking the towel off.
Whoa, doctor!
That's it.
I knew it. I knew it.
They're definitely fake.
So when's
the funeral?
Well...
Aunt Clarisse
was so ill,
I-- I guess
it was really a blessing.
Yeah, I'll fly home
as soon as I can.
Okay.
You too. Get some sleep.
JERRY:
You sure?
Positive.
This chick's playing
with Confederate money.
Well, then, that's it.
That's the end of that.
What, just because
of that?
"Just because
of that?"
It's like finding out
Mickey Mantle corked his bat.
Oh, come on.
You've dated women
with nose jobs.
What's the difference?
You don't touch the nose,
you don't aspire
to reach the nose,
you don't unhook anything
to get to a nose,
and no man has ever tried
to look up a woman's nostrils.
You've put a lot of thought
into this, haven't you?
Well, I take it
very seriously.
You know,
sometimes when I think
you're the shallowest man
I've ever met,
you somehow manage to drain
a little more out of the pool.
Hey.
You know, I do
kind of wonder
what fake breasts
feel like.
Well, I know
what they feel like.
You? How do you know?
Well, I lived
in Los Angeles
for three months.
I thought you hated Los Angeles.
No, I do.
I just miss the warm weather,
you know?
Jeez. Oh, man.
I wish I could get away.
Real busy now,
down at the office?
No. Huh?
Know who I saw
at the health club?
Salman Rushdie.
[LAUGHING]
I-- no, I...
Yeah, right.
Salman Rushdie.
Ah, well,
I could see that.
You got five million
Moslems after you,
you want to stay
in pretty good shape.
GEORGE:
I know what the problem is.
I like her too much.
That's why I can't make a move.
You put her
on a pedestal.
I put them
on a dental chair.
He puts them
I'm not her boyfriend.
I want to be her boyfriend.
Whew.
It's like a sauna in here.
That's funny.
You're a funny guy.
I never heard that before.
So you going
to the funeral?
Why, do you think I should?
What,
are you kidding?
It's a golden
opportunity
to advance
the relationship.
She's crying,
you put your arm
around her
and console her.
You're
the consolation guy.
I'm the consolation guy?
Consolation guy
is big.
Her aunt dying
is the best thing
that ever happened
to you.
It's like 10 dates in one shot.
This confers
upon you
instant boyfriend
status.
The family's there,
you're taking care
of things,
you're getting
the sandwiches.
You're the rock.
It's in Detroit, though.
It's an expensive flight.
Why don't you get
a death-in-the-family fare?
What?
You go
to the airlines,
you tell them
that you have
a death
in the family,
they give you 50 percent
off the fare.
Really?
In fact...
listen, I'll go down there
with you.
You know, we'll tell them
there's a death in my family.
You buy the ticket,
I'll split it. Huh?
Then I'll get
the bonus miles,
and you'll get to Detroit
for a quarter of the price.
ELAINE:
Boy, I'm getting a good sweat here.
Great sweat.
Good beads, nice beads.
Oh, look who's here...
Silicon Valley.
Oh, uh, so anyway,
we go out on one date,
and he asks me out
for a second,
and then,
out of nowhere,
he says calls me,
cancels the date,
and he doesn't want to
see me again.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help overhearing.
Oh, that's okay.
Did he give you a reason?
Yeah.
He's going back
to his old girlfriend.
Really?
Said
she's mentally ill.
He's one
of those guys
who is obsessed
with neatness
and order.
Everything has
got to be just so.
He would've made
a great Nazi.
Hey, does he ever
talk about Superman?
Yes! How
did you know?
Oh, I know the type.
Oh, so you can
relate?
Oh, yeah.
You know, I've seen you
around the club.
My name's Sidra.
This is Marcy.
Oh, hi.
I'm Elaine.
So, anyway, I stood up
to shake her hand
and then, suddenly,
I lost my balance.
I fell right into her.
You fell on her?
I touched them.
You what?
I...
touched them.
You touched them?
I needed them to help me
break my fall!
If it wa--
If it hadn't have been for them,
I could've really
injured myself.
Wow.
Anyway, uh...
they're real.
Excuse me?
I think
they might be real.
Oh, what
do you know?
You have no breast-touching
experience.
I've touched mine.
So have I.
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Anyway, touching
two breasts
doesn't make you
an expert.
All right, well, anyway,
I think they're real,
and if they are,
I must say,
they are...
spectacular.
What are you doing to me?
[SNIFFLES]
You see, my friend here,
his aunt passed away last night.
Oh, I'm very sorry.
I saw her last week.
She looked healthy
and peaceful, but...
[CHOKING UP]
...she knew.
You poor thing.
I...
You don't think you could
buy the ticket yourself?
Oh. No, no, no. Okay.
All right. No. Please.
[HEAVING, SOBBING]
There, there, there.
You sit.
I'll purchase the ticket
for you.
TICKET CLERK:
You're a good friend.
I understand
you offer
a 50 percent-off
bereavement fare?
Yes. All you have to do
is pay the full fare now,
then return
to any one of our counters
with a copy
of the death certificate,
and we'll refund
half your fare.
The-- the...
[MUTTERING UNINTELLIGIBLY]
The death certificate?
Yes, we do need documentation
or, you know,
people could take advantage.
What kind of a sick person
would do a thing like that?
I know, but it happens.
You want my friend
to ask his uncle,
a man who just lost his wife
of 44 years,
for a death certificate,
so that he can save a few bucks
on a flight?
That would be $387
round trip.
All right,
so you'll need
my frequent flyer
number, huh?
Yes.
I don't know.
One minute,
you're sure they're fake.
The next minute,
you think they're real.
I don't know
what to believe.
Hey,
of the two of us,
I'm the only one
who's touched them.
But you were just
grabbing onto them
to save your life.
If you were drowning
and I threw you
a life preserver,
you think could you tell me
if it was an inflatable?
I wouldn't have said anything
if I knew you were gonna stop
seeing her.
Well, I don't mind someone
with a phony personality,
but I got to draw the line
somewhere.
Hey.
George off
to Detroit?
Yep, and in two days,
I'm off to Puerto Rico.
Hey, Kramer, by the way,
I saw that guy
at the health club.
That is not Salman Rushdie.
Pfft! Wrong.
There's Sidra.
There's Salman.
Where?
Talking to that woman.
Talking to Sidra?
If that's Sidra,
she's talking to Salman.
I don't think that's Salman.
Well, I don't think
they're real.
If that's Rushdie,
If they're real,
that's Rushdie.
Well, I gotta know.
I'm talking to Sidra.
I gotta know.
I'm talking to Salman.
Boy, it's like
a sauna in here, huh?
I feel like
I'm back at the desert.
You've lived
in the desert?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I've, uh...
I spent a little time
in the Mideast.
Hmm...
You ever been
to the Mideast?
Yes,
I've been there.
Look,
my name's Kramer.
Sal Bass.
Yeah.
Pleased
to meet you, Kramer.
So, um...
What kind of work
do you do?
I'm a writer.
Have you met my boyfriend,
George?
Uh, no.
George,
this is Aunt May
and Father Jessup.
Oh, and that's
my brother Timmy.
This is my boyfriend,
George.
Oh, George, how nice of you
to come all this way.
Well,
I'm the boyfriend.
Otherwise,
what's the point
of being
the boyfriend?
This is where
you have to be
when you're
the boyfriend.
Betsy, dear, have you
had anything to eat?
I'm not very hungry.
They have
some very nice snacks.
I'm about to get
myself a snack.
Oh, no, no, no.
You sit right here.
I will get you
a nice snack.
This is, uh,
my...
third wake
this month.
It never gets
any easier.
Well, losing
a loved one is, uh...
I mean,
forget about it.
Mm.
You, um...
you seem to be
of great comfort
to Betsy.
We're very
appreciative.
Oh, comfort,
"shmomfort."
Listen, uh...
Father, can I ask you
a question?
In a terrible time
like this,
who would I get
the death certificate from?
KRAMER:
Oh, Jerry.
Oh, how can you
be so sure?
Jerry,
are you blind?
He's a writer!
He said his name
was Sal Bass.
Bass, Jerry.
Instead of salmon,
he went with bass.
He just substituted
one fish for another.
Look, you idiot,
first of all,
it's Salman, not salmon.
Jerry, Jerry,
you're missing the big picture!
All right.
Maybe it is,
but I've got to get ready.
Sidra's coming over
in a few minutes,
so if you don't mind...
Oh, well,
did you ask her?
Yeah, I'm gonna
find out tonight.
Ooh, yes. Indeed.
Why do you need
a death certificate?
Well, Dr. Allenwood,
um...
I was hoping
to compile an...
admittedly rudimentary
scrapbook of her life.
Something that Betsy
could have and hold on to.
Well, I suppose
I could make a copy of it.
Oh,
that would be wonderful.
Yeah, it's, um...
very nice meeting you, George.
Likewise.
What are you doing?
What?
Did-- Did you just
double-dip that chip?
Excuse me?
You double-dipped the chip.
Double-dipped?
What are you talking about?
You dipped the chip,
you took a bite...
and you dipped again.
So?
That's like putting
your whole mouth
right in the dip.
Look, from now on,
when you take a chip,
just take one dip
and end it.
Well, I'm sorry,
Timmy,
but I don't dip
that way.
Oh, you don't, huh?
No.
You dip the way
you wanna dip...
I'll dip the way
I wanna dip.
Give me the chip!
Hey, hey! Hey!
Give-- Give me--
Give me the chip!
I don't know
what I'm doing here.
I must be crazy.
Hey, would you mind
switching seats?
Why?
Oh, I don't know,
I just like sitting
to the left of people.
Makes me feel
like I'm driving.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
How you doing?
Good.
Feel good.
You know,
that Jayne Mansfield
had some big breasts.
Really big. Huge.
She was just coming out
the top of her dress.
They were, like,
choking her.
I hear that's how
she died.
Yeah.
Have you noticed
that women today
are, you know,
they seem bigger?
Well, a lot of women
are having them done.
Really?
Yeah.
How do you
like that?
A lot of people ask me
if I've had mine done.
Ah, you know,
people.
It gets
a little tiring.
It's really none
of their business.
Oh, the nerve.
You know, some people
have asked me
if you've, uh,
done that.
What do you
tell them?
Whatever you want me
to tell them.
Well, I think you'll
find out soon enough.
[LOUD THUMP]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Aren't you
gonna get that?
No.
Well, what if
it's an emergency?
Oh, there's no emergencies.
KRAMER:
Jerry, come on!
It's an emergency!
Excuse me.
All right.
What is it?
You're interrupting.
Oh, well, you know, I'm, uh,
I'm packing for Puerto Rico.
I need to borrow
your bathing suit.
This is an emergency?
You need
a bathing suit?
Well, I like yours.
I don't know--
My bathing suit?
That's a little familiar.
I don't want your--
your boys down there.
Now, what's the matter
with my boys?
Your boys should stay
in their neighborhood.
All right. Come on!
All right.
It's in
the top drawer.
Hurry up.
Hi, Jer.
Oh, hi, Elaine.
Oh, hi, Sidra.
Hi. Elaine?
Uh...
Hey.
Well, what are you doing here?
I'm looking
for Kramer.
Oh, uh, what's going on?
She was showing me pictures
of places I could visit
when I go to Puerto Rico.
You know,
when you two went?
Oh, yeah. All right.
Well, just, uh....
You know, the--
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
[DOOR SHUTS]
So where were we?
I was just leaving.
Right. You were leaving.
I can't believe
you sent a woman
into the sauna
to do that.
That was an accident!
I think you're both
mentally ill.
Oh!
And, by the way,
they're real,
and they're spectacular.
BETSY:
Stop it, George! Get out! Get out!
I never want
to see you again!
FATHER JESSUP:
Go back to New York!
Get out! Get out!
All right, sir.
Now, all I need
is a death certificate,
and you'll be
on your way.
Well, you see,
what happened
was, um...
the doctor,
the very same doctor
that was attending
my late aunt suffered...
an untimely stroke
and, uh, lost the use
of his right hand,
so, obviously, I was unable
to get the death certificate.
Um, however, I--
I do have this.
What's this?
That's a picture of me
next to the coffin.
WOMAN:
Nice try.
GEORGE:
Not even close, huh?
WOMAN:
No.
The cosmetic surgery procedures
that are available to people
today--
Liposuction,
are you familiar with this?
This is a fat-sucking machine.
Now, you know, somewhere,
somebody is working on a way
that this thing
could go into a restaurant.
And you could just
order it off the menu:
"I'll tell you what.
Give me the cheesecake.
"crank me up to nine,
and put a scoop of ice cream
on the side."