There's no easy way
to break off any relationship.
I think
when you first start dating,
they ought to give you
three "Get out of relationship
free" cards.
You know what I mean?
So you can just
go up to the person and go,
"Uh, here you go. I'm sorry.
I'll grab the tennis racket.
Don't even bother to get up.
Have a good one. Sorry."
Which is fine,
unless, of course,
the person you're
in the relationship with
happens to have
an "Eight more months of guilt,
torture, and pain" card.
"Uh, hold it. I've got
a little something for you."
We're dead.
We're not dead.
We are dead.
Come on, we got
all day tomorrow
to come up
with a story.
All day tomorrow?
We had a month and a half
to come up with something.
We didn't do anything!
So we'll do it
tomorrow.
Let me ask you this,
when's the last time
you went skiing?
About six years ago.
I think you can take
the lift ticket
off your jacket now.
Women like skiers.
So what?
You can't meet anybody.
You're going out
with Susan.
Yeah. Right.
Hey, see those two women
over there?
I almost dated
the one on the right.
She's in
the closet business.
The closet business?
What's the closet business?
What is it
your business?
I'm interested.
She reorganizes
your closet
and shows you how
to maximize your closet space.
She looked
into my closet.
So you thought
she was good-looking
and figured this would be
a good way to meet her.
Yeah.
So what happened?
So she mentioned
she had a boyfriend,
and then it hit me--
What do I need
more closet space for?
Hi, Marla.
Jerry!
George, Marla.
Marla.
George, Jerry, Stacy.
Stacy.
Jerry.
George, Stacy.
Stacy.
George.
Jerry.
Marla.
Stacy!
So how was your
trip to Berlin?
Trip to Berlin?
Remember? That's why you put off
doing the closets.
You said you were going
to Berlin for a while.
Oh, right. Right.
The wall had just come
down, and you told me
you wanted to be part
of the celebration.
Yes. Yes, I did.
But you know,
I was watching it on CNN,
and they covered it so well,
I thought,
"Why knock my brains out?"
You know,
my boyfriend went.
Really?
Yes, I told him
all about you going,
and he got all excited
and decided to go.
Oh, did he like it?
I don't know.
He never came back.
Anyway, we met with NBC
about a month ago,
and they gave us
the green light
to go ahead
and write a pilot.
In fact, we've got a big
meeting with them tomorrow.
They gotta approve
of the story
before we can write it.
Wow. What a great job,
a writer!
Oh.
Not a bad way
to earn a buck.
Sounds great.
Well, I tell
you, Stacy,
it's a lot
of hard work,
but it comes
fairly easy to me.
Some people
write symphonies.
This is my gift.
So you gonna
go out with her?
I might.
What about Susan?
What? I'm not married.
I'm not allowed to go out
with somebody else?
Depends.
Depends on what?
On many factors.
Like what?
Well...
How long you
been seeing her.
What's your
phone call frequency?
Are you on a daily?
Nah, semi-daily.
Four, five times a week.
What about
Saturday nights?
You have to ask her out,
or is a date implied?
It's implied.
She got anything
in your medicine cabinet?
Might be
some moisturizer.
Uh-huh.
Let me ask you this.
Is there any Tampax
in your house?
Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you
what you got here.
Yeah?
You got yourself
a girlfriend.
Oh, no, no.
What, are you sure?
A girlfriend?
I'm looking at a guy
on a semi-daily
with Tampax
in his house
and an implied date
on Saturday night.
I would like
to help you out, but--
Do you believe my luck?
The first time in my life
I have a good answer
to the question
"What do you do?"
and I have a girlfriend.
I mean, you don't need
a girlfriend
when you can answer
that question.
That's what you say
in order to get girlfriends.
Once you can get girlfriends,
you don't want a girlfriend,
you just want
more girlfriends.
You're gonna make
a very good father someday.
Well, it's not fair, Jerry.
It's just not fair.
That's it.
I'm getting out of this thing.
Fine, break up with her,
but you know what
this means, don't you?
No. What?
The script, the pilot,
the TV show, all over.
Why? What do you mean?
Figure it out. She's one
of the executives at NBC
that's gonna
make the decision
whether or not
they pick up the show.
She's one of our
biggest fans.
You drop her off,
you think they're
gonna pick us up?
Oh, right.
Oh, no. Man...
You know, it's a very
interesting situation.
Here, you have a job
that could help you get girls,
but you also have
a relationship,
but if you try and get rid
of the relationship
so you can get the girls,
you lose the job.
You see the irony?
Yeah, yeah, I see the irony.
All right, what--
what about this?
What if I could find some way
to break up with her
so that she'll
still like me
and it doesn't affect
the deal?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hear me out. Hear me out.
Don't dismiss this.
You're very quick to dismiss.
Don't dismiss.
She's got a big crush
on David Letterman.
I mean, a big crush.
She talks about him
all the time.
Suppose I go up
to David Letterman.
He works at NBC.
I work at NBC.
I explain my situation.
He agrees to meet her.
They go out,
they fall madly in love,
and she dumps me
for David Letterman.
This is your plan?
No, no! I'm just thinking.
I don't think you are.
Well, let me tell you
what I see.
Please, and be brutal.
I have no closet sensitivity.
Are you very fussy
about your pants?
I don't think I am.
Because I have
a very radical idea.
Can you handle it?
Try me.
Here's what
I'm proposing.
We'll eliminate
all this--
The hangers, the bar,
the shelves--
and in its place,
install a series of hooks.
We'll put everything on hooks.
Everything?
Everything! The shirts, pants,
sports jackets, pajamas.
We can get 80 hooks on here.
You're quite mad, you know.
[APARTMENT DOOR
OPENS AND CLOSES]
Oh, I don't believe this.
Hey.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I'm watching
The Bold and the Beautiful.
No.
Wait,
wait, wait.
This is not a good time.
No, no, no,
five minutes.
What did you give your TV
away to George for?
Because I've been
watching too much.
It was an addiction.
I couldn't stop.
It was destroying
my brain cells.
Yeah, but now
you're in here all the time.
Well--whoa.
Uh, Marla, Kramer.
Hello.
Hey.
Why don't you go out.
It's nice out.
No, there's nothing out there
for me.
There's weather.
Weather?
I don't need weather.
Weather doesn't
do it for me.
I'm telling George
to give you your TV back.
No, no,
I don't want it back.
Are you gonna watch
the Knick game tonight?
I don't know.
Will you tape it?
Kramer...
Oh, yeah, you, huh?
So your boyfriend never
came back from Berlin?
He never came back.
Oh, you must've been devastated,
being left for a wall.
Well...
It was about to end anyway.
There was this...problem.
Uh-huh.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Excuse me one second.
Yeah?
ELAINE:
It's me.
Come on up.
Uh, it's Elaine. She's
just a friend of mine.
I don't know what
she's doing here now.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
I'm sorry. What?
I didn't get it.
Oh, for...
So you were saying,
there was this problem.
Well, he wanted me
to move in with him.
Snapple?
No, thanks.
Go on.
Well, I wouldn't move in
because...
Yes?
Well, because...
Yeah?
Well, because I'm a...
virgin.
Hello!
Hi. Um...
Marla, Elaine.
Um, I'm sorry. I didn't
know you had company.
I just wanted
to return your tape.
Oh, thanks a lot,
two weeks late.
Now it'll cost me $35
to see Havana.
I'm sorry. I really am.
I just kept forgetting.
I should be going.
No, no, no, no.
I'm leaving.
I like that thing
in your hair there.
Oh, yeah? Hah.
This woman was selling them
at this crazy party
I was at last night.
You'll appreciate this.
Snapple?
No, thanks.
I was talking to
this guy, you know,
and I just happened to throw
my purse on the sofa,
and my diaphragm
goes flying out.
So I just froze,
you know?
[GROANING]
Staring at my diaphragm.
It was just lying there.
So then this woman, the one
who sold me this hair thing,
she grabbed it
before the guy noticed.
So, I mean,
big deal, right?
So I carry around
my diaphragm.
Who doesn't?
I mean, like it's
a big, big secret
that women carry around
their diaphragms.
You never know when you're
gonna need it, right?
Ah...
I should be going.
So, uh...
we'll talk about
the hooks, then?
Yes.
What? Was it something I said?
She's a virgin.
She just told me.
Well, I didn't know.
Well, it's not like
spotting a toupee.
Well, you think
I should say something?
Should I say something?
Should I apologize?
Was I-- Was I being
anti-virgin?
No, no! I mean...
Because I'm not
anti-virgin.
I'm gonna--
I'll be right back.
Elaine. Elaine!
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's George.
She's a virgin?
A virgin.
Wow.
So what are you
gonna do?
I don't know. I'm very
attracted to her.
That accent is so sexy.
I don't think
I could do it.
They always remember
the first time.
I don't wanna
be remembered.
I wanna be forgotten.
You need a little
pioneer spirit.
See, you don't have
any of that
Lewis & Clark in you.
You know, sometimes those guys
don't make it back.
I'm really hungry.
Yeah, me too.
We gotta get something.
I don't wanna go to that meeting
on an empty stomach.
Let's get some Chinese.
You wanna order--
All right, but then
we gotta get some work done.
Let me just call Kramer,
see if he wants anything.
Hey, we're ordering
Chinese food.
If you want anything,
let me know what it is
and, uh...
I'll order it...
for you.
I'm in. Let's go for it.
All right,
what do you want?
I don't care. Whatever.
Why don't we get
a couple of dishes.
We'll just share them.
All right.
What--
what are you getting?
I think I'm gonna
get a Chow Fun.
What's a Chow Fun?
It's a broad noodle.
What do you mean,
a broad noodle?
It's a big, flat noodle.
Well, I don't want
a big, flat noodle.
What kind of noodle
do you want?
Who says
I want a noodle?
All right, look,
I'm getting the Chow Fun.
You don't have
to have any.
I'll get the pea pods,
and you can't have
any of my pea pods.
Fine.
Get extra MSG.
Look, Marla,
this whole sex thing
is totally overrated.
Now, the one thing
you've gotta be ready for
is how the man changes into
a completely different person
five seconds
after it's over.
I mean, something happens
to their personality.
It's really quite astounding.
It's like, uh,
they committed a crime,
and they want to flee the scene
before the police get there.
So they just leave?
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
Well, the smart ones start
working on their getaway stories
during dinner.
How, you know, they gotta
get up early tomorrow.
It's always about
being up early.
They all turn
into farmers suddenly.
Wow. You must be really good
to put up with all that.
Eh.
All right, let's go.
We don't have much time
before the meeting.
Where's the food?
What happened to Ping?
Don't worry,
he'll be here.
We only got
about two hours.
We just need
one good story idea,
and we can get through
this meeting.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
There's your food.
Hey, what about this?
I'm in a car accident.
The motorist is uninsured.
You with me?
Yeah.
My car's totaled.
It's all his fault.
Now, he has absolutely no money.
There is no way
that he could pay me.
So the judge decrees...
that he becomes my butler.
Your butler?
Right.
He cooks my food,
he cleans my house,
he does all my shopping for me,
and there you go.
That's your program.
What about me?
Don't worry.
We find something for you.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
That's the stupidest idea
I ever heard.
Sentenced to be a butler.
Ping, what happened?
There was a bit
of an accident.
Head hurts.
Head really hurts.
What happened?
Marla and I
went out for coffee,
and afterwards,
I was crossing the street,
and he was biking
right towards me.
So I got out of the way
just in time,
but then he ran into
a parked car,
he hit his head,
and everything went flying.
Something happened
to the food?
Could only save
one bag.
Should I call an ambulance?
Want to see a doctor?
I'll get some ice.
The pea pods?
All you saved was the pea pods?
Hey, you got the food?
Yeah, here.
What took so long?
Hey, Ping!
Kramer!
Yeah.
Where's yours, huh?
He dropped it.
Oh, that's too bad.
You should slow down,
you know that?
It's dangerous
to go that fast.
No. No, I have green light.
You jaywalk.
Are you
watching Oprah?
I did not
jaywalk.
You're giving him
back that TV!
Yes, you
jaywalk.
No, I don't
want it back.
Jaywalker.
I'll slap a suit on you!
What?
We've work to do!
What about the meeting?
Look, an hour
with Patrick Swayze.
Month and a half, we had.
We did nothing.
I can't believe we
put it off until today
and then we couldn't
do anything,
because Elaine runs out
to apologize to a virgin,
crosses against the light,
and knocks over
a Chinese delivery boy.
Now we're gonna go
make fools of ourselves.
We got nothing.
You're not even
in show business.
I got a reputation!
You'll drag me
into the sewer with you.
I've been on TV,
buddy boy.
Know how fast word spreads
in show business?
Like that!
Just like that!
One bad impression,
you're out of the business!
All right, let's postpone it.
Let's get out of here.
What do you mean?
They know we're here.
I'll fake an illness.
My back! My back!
I can't move my back!
No, no,
would you get up?
I could do this, Jerry.
No.
All right, I'll tell them
that my sister died.
Oh, my poor sister died.
She was standing
on the street,
and then
she was laughing,
and then they shot her!
That's the kind of a sick city
that we're living in!
They shoot you for laughing!
I must go and comfort
my poor family.
Jerry, come on, take me home
so I can comfort my--
my poor family...
What?
That's David Letterman.
I just saw David Letterman
walk by.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Seinfeld,
they're ready for you now.
Yes, I was very wise
to hitch my wagon to his star.
Jerry...
Hey, Jerry!
Hi. How you doing?
Nice to see you
all again. Hello.
Hello, Jerry.
I'm Rita Kierson.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
Uh, where's Russell?
He, uh, he had to go to L.A.
There's a problem
on the set at Blossom.
Oh...
poor Blossom.
Anyway, he asked me
to sit in for him.
Where's George?
Oh, he ran to say something
to David Letterman.
D-David Letterman's
on the floor?
Yeah, he just walked by.
Well, I think we should
get started anyway.
Yeah. Good idea.
So how are you guys
coming along?
Good, good.
We've got a number of ideas.
Good.
Have you ever been
to a Chinese restaurant,
and they tell you it'll be,
like, five minutes for a table,
and you wind waiting there
for, like, 30 minutes?
Well, we thought
it would be very funny
to do an entire show
where all you're doing
is waiting for the table.
Because we've all been
in that situation.
You know, you're...
you're waiting,
and you're hungry,
and you bump into
somebody you know.
When is Russell coming back?
So that's the idea?
Well, no. That's one.
We have many others.
We have an idea
where, um...
Uh...
I, um...
I get into an accident
with a guy who has no insurance,
and the judge sentences him
to be my butler.
[LAUGHING]
And he cooks,
so he has to cook for me,
cleans up my house,
and he's doing my shopping,
you know...
[LAUGHING]
and I'm walking around
wearing one of those big
neck collars, you know.
Those collars
are funny!
You see somebody
in one of those collars,
you start laughing
immediately.
You're telling them
about the butler story?
Is that beautiful,
or what?
Hey, I'm sorry
I'm late...
Russell.
I'm Rita Kierson.
Ah, Rita.
Hey, Mr. Chermak,
how are you?
Good to see you.
Stu and Jay.
Always a pleasure.
Hi, sweetie.
Yeah, yeah,
that butler idea,
that's beautiful,
isn't it?
Is that a killer?
I thought
I was getting the butler.
Don't worry, we'll find
something for you.
So Letterman didn't spark
to your idea, huh?
No, he said there was nothing
he could do, and that next time,
I should probably
break the Prozacs in half.
Hey, you guys wanna
hold it down.
I'm watching Jeopardy.
Would you give him back the TV?
Oh, by the way, George,
Susan called for you
a minute ago.
Yeah, I'll bet they're
probably doing somersaults
about us over there.
You think they get
butler stories like that
every day?
Who is Joseph Cotton?
Giddyup!
SUSAN [OVER TELEPHONE]:
Hello.
Hi, it's me. It's Georgie boy.
What's going on?
I'll tell you
what's going on.
I'm fired!
Fired? Why?
Because
you kissed me!
You kissed me,
you stupid idiot!
Rita called Russell,
and he fired me
over the phone!
What is pi?
Ooh, giddyup again.
I'm killing 'em.
But I didn't-- I had no idea.
I didn't realize--
You didn't realize?
How could you
not realize?
You're stupid!
You are a stupid,
stupid man!
I just feel terrible.
This is just terrible.
What is the cha-cha?
Yes, indeed.
I'll speak
to you later.
This is great!
He fired her!
This is incredible!
I'm out, baby!
I'm out!
Why did he fire her?
Because I kissed her
in the meeting!
Russell found out!
He fired her over the phone!
Finally, my stupidity pays off!
What is "Here Come The Judge?
Here Come the Judge!"
You can't
break up with her now.
Her life is shattered,
and you got her fired!
You gotta be there for her.
What?
You gotta at least wait
until she gets another job.
Another job?
A couple of interviews.
Oh, this is unbelievable!
I'm stuck!
Every time I think I'm out,
they pull me back in.
Are you going to want to leave
after it's over?
You know, if we have sex?
What? Leave?
Where? Why?
You know, the apartment.
Why would I leave?
This is my apartment.
Well, what if
it was my apartment?
Who gave you this idea
I would want to leave?
Well, Elaine said
men like to leave
after it's over.
Listen, I wouldn't put
too much stock
in anything Elaine has to say
about relationships.
She comes from a broken home,
and I mean that literally.
A tree fell on the roof
and cracked the whole structure.
Her parents got along
beautifully,
but the house
was in bad shape.
Maybe I should be going.
What else did you
say to her?
Nothing. I was just
giving her the straight dope.
More like a dope
was giving it to her straight.
Another cup of coffee with you,
she'll wind up in a convent.
Listen, there was a lot more
I could've told her.
Believe me.
What is this
about leaving after sex?
Did I ever leave with you?
You might've if I had stayed.
So you know what?
I got served
with papers today.
Ping is suing me.
I need your virgin as a witness,
so be nice to her.
I was trying to be.
Look at George.
He lucked out, huh?
JERRY:
Oh, you're not kidding.
Who'd have figured Susan
would break up with him.
They had a good thing going.
Yeah, since she met him,
she's been vomited on,
her family cabin's
been burned down,
she learned
her father's a homosexual,
and she got fired
from a high-paying network job.
Yeah, they had
a real good thing going.
What do I do?
Well, actually, I'm a writer.
In fact,
I'm writing a comedy pilot
for NBC right now.
A sitcom?
How can you write that crap?
Carol!
This guy's
writing a sitcom.
A sitcom?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh, let's go.
A sitcom...
can you imagine?
And he actually tried
to use it to hit on me!
In ancient tribal cultures,
they would actually
sacrifice a virgin.
They thought
that would do something.
They would find some girl
that had never been out
with anybody,
and they would throw her
into a volcano.
I mean, there's a first date
you'll never forget, you know.
Winds up in heaven
talking with Chuck Woolery.
"So tell me, Lisa,
how did the date end?"
"Not well, Chuck. Not well."
"Well, if you'd like to be
thrown into a volcano again,
we'll pay for it."
[♪]