I have a friend
that's about to get married.
They're having
the bachelor party
and the bridal shower
the same day.
So it's conceivable that
while she's getting lingerie,
he'll be at a nude bar
watching a table dancer
in the same outfit.
That is possible.
But, to me, the difference
between being single
and being married
is the form of government.
You see, when you're single,
you are the dictator
of your own life.
I have complete power.
When I give the order
to fall asleep on the sofa
with the TV on
in the middle of the day,
no one can overrule me.
When you're married,
you are part
of a vast decision-making body.
Before anything gets done,
there are meetings.
Committees have to study
the situation,
and this is
if the marriage works.
I think that's what's so painful
about divorce.
You've been impeached.
You weren't even the president.
Hey, is it
my imagination,
or do really
good-looking women
walk a lot faster
than everybody else?
We don't walk that fast.
No, seriously.
Seriously, we don't.
And the better looking they are,
the faster they go.
I mean, I see them out there
on the street.
They're zooming around.
They're a blur.
It's like they got a motor
on their ass.
Hey, Jerry,
come on.
Let's go!
We're gonna miss
the previews.
What's the big hurry?
Hey, how are we getting
to Scott Drake's party
on Saturday night?
Oh, Drake's party.
I forgot to buy a present.
What, I gotta buy
a present now?
Of course you do.
It's an
engagement party.
Oh, it never ends,
this present stuff.
Engagement present.
Then they get married.
You gotta get them
something for that.
Then a baby,
there's another present.
Then the baby starts getting
their presents.
I don't even like Drake.
You don't like
the Drake?
I hate the Drake.
I love the Drake.
How could you
not like the Drake?
Who's the Drake?
The Drake is good.
No...
So listen, what
are you gonna get him?
You know, I haven't
even met the fiancée.
Oh, whatever!
Elaine, look, I drew
this triangle freehand.
It's a doodle.
It's perfect!
So what?
That's easy.
Easy?
Hi.
Hey, have you gotten
a present yet for the Drake?
Uh, no, no, not yet.
Do you like the Drake?
I love the Drake.
I'm looking forward
to meeting the Drakette.
I'm lukewarm
about the Drakette.
Boy, that's
a nice triangle.
It's isosceles.
Ooh...
Isosceles.
You know, I love
the name "isosceles."
If I had a kid,
I would name him
Isosceles.
Isosceles Kramer.
Hey, you know what.
Maybe we should all
chip in for the gift.
The chip-in!
Hey, pretty good idea.
Yeah.
The chip-in!
Definitely.
Let's go to that mall
in Lynbrook
before we go to the party,
but we'll have to take your car.
It's got
the most room.
No, no, my car's
not running.
What about
your father's car?
No, no, no, out of the question.
I was over there today.
He's got the good spot
in front of the good building
in the good neighborhood.
I know he's not gonna
want to move it.
Are you serious?
You don't know what
that spot means to him.
Once he gets it,
he doesn't go out for weeks.
How about this.
You put your car
in the good spot.
That'll hold
the good spot
in front
of the good building,
and we can get
the good car.
Good thinking.
Good to meet you.
ELAINE:
So, what are we gonna get him?
JERRY: We can get him
anything we want.
We're chipping in.
I like this area.
I could live
out here.
Yeah, we ought to
all get a house
and live together.
Yeah, that's
a good idea.
I'll tell you what,
chuckles,
I give you
permission
to sublet my room
right now.
GEORGE:
Look at this.
There's no spaces here.
Excuse me, are you
getting out?
MAN: No.
Why don't you take
the handicapped spot?
You think?
No, no,
we'll find a space.
There's spaces
in the other lot.
Oh, I don't
wanna walk that far.
No! What if a handicapped
person needs it?
Oh, come on.
They don't drive.
Yes, they do.
Have you ever seen
a handicapped person
pull into a space
and park?
Well, the space is there.
They must drive.
No, they don't.
If they could drive,
they wouldn't be handicapped.
So if you can drive,
you're not handicapped?
We're not gonna be
that long anyway.
We gotta get
to the party.
I got news for you.
Handicapped people,
they don't even want
to park there.
They want to be treated
just like everybody else.
That's why those spaces
are always empty.
He's right.
It's the same thing
with the feminists.
You know, they want
everything to be equal,
everything,
but when the check comes,
where are they?
What does that mean?
[SCOFFS]
Yeah.
All right, I'm pulling in.
Go ahead, George.
ELAINE:
George!
GEORGE:
Oh, come on.
It's five minutes.
Make sure
that we don't forget
where the car
is parked.
Don't worry
about it.
[ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
Do you believe the deal
we got on this?
A big-screen TV
at that price.
What a sale, huh?
And how about that store,
delivering it tonight?
We're gonna be swimming
in thank-yous.
What'd I get
the veggie burger for?
You got
a veggie burger,
so I had to get
a veggie burger.
It's like eating
a loaf of crumbs.
No one's gonna have
a better gift
than this
big-screen TV.
Good for them.
Love the Drake.
Yeah.
Got to love the Drake!
[SIRENS WAILING,
POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Hey, what's going on
over here?
ELAINE: There must've
been an accident.
Hey,
what's going on?
Some jerk parked
in the handicapped spot,
so this woman in a wheelchair
had to wheel up this incline,
and, halfway up,
her batteries gave out,
and she rolled backwards
into the wall.
Had to take her
to St. Elizabeth's.
Is she okay?
I don't know.
We're just waiting here
for the owner
of this car to show up.
He may not
get out alive.
Lazy bum, taking up
a handicapped spot.
He's gonna pay.
Sons of bitches!
Well, good luck
finding them--
Him, whatever.
I'd like
to stick around
and get my hands
on him myself,
but I got to take off.
We're gonna get you, you coward!
Oh, my God.
How are we going
to get outta here?
They'll kill us.
Are you happy?
Are you happy now?
How long you think
these people
are gonna be here?
I don't know.
What about the party?
What about the Drake?
Screw the Drake.
I love the Drake.
Let's just take
a bus back
into the city.
I can't leave
the car here.
Why not?
It's my
father's car.
Let's smash it!
ALL: Yeah!
Hey, hey,
leave this car alone!
All right.
Let's get outta here.
We gotta figure
something out.
What are we gonna do? How
are we gonna get out of here?
Even if we go back by the car,
and they're not there,
how do we know they're not
all hiding, waiting for us?
They have to give up sometime.
They can't stay all night.
What are we,
John Dillinger?
I mean, how did this
get to be
the crime
of the century?
It's not like we stuck
a broomstick in her spokes,
and she went flying.
What I don't get is,
just because
the batteries went dead,
you'd think
she'd be able
to roll it up the hill
with her hands.
You'd think.
I mean, batteries
have gone dead before.
Aren't they
prepared for that?
You know, most of them
don't even have batteries.
It must have been
one of those rich,
spoiled,
handicapped people
who didn't want
to do any work.
Just wanted to sit
in her wheelchair
and take it easy.
Yeah.
Well, I'm sorry.
Our big-screen TV
is probably arriving
just about now.
How are we gonna get out
of here? We need a plan.
I got it. We'll give
the keys to Elaine.
Me?
Yeah, you're a woman.
Men won't hit a woman.
Oh, they won't?
Not if they don't
know you.
I'm not going for this.
Kramer should go, you know?
It was all his idea.
No chance in hell.
What if we created
some sort of a diversion?
What if we went
over by the car,
and we just started screaming,
"Hey, there he is!
"There's the guy that took
the handicapped spot,"
and then, when they all run
in the other direction,
we'll jump in the car.
Oh, that's good
Let's give it a try.
That's good.
If that doesn't work,
we'll give them Kramer.
Huh?
GEORGE:
My God.
[WHIMPERING]
You know, a lot
of these scratches
will buff right out.
Eight years
I had that car.
Not a scratch on it.
Eight years!
Two crack.
Three dot.
A beautiful Mercury.
I special-ordered
that bench seat.
Dad, this other car
cut us off.
They had swastikas
all over it.
They-- They were hurling
racial epithets at us.
I could have been killed.
I told you
not to give it to him.
Three crack.
Four bam.
Soap.
You know, my insurance
doesn't even cover this.
The whole thing is a total loss.
Frank, the important thing
is he didn't get hurt.
No, it isn't!
So, what are you
doing now, Georgie?
North.
I'm writing a pilot for NBC.
Where the hell's
my paper?
You're writing a pilot?
With his friend
Jerry Seinfeld,
the comedian.
So, what's it about?
Well, Jerry's car
gets hit,
and the other driver
doesn't have
any insurance,
so the judge
sentences him
to be Jerry's butler.
It's the same situation.
Exactly the same.
Frank, maybe you ought
to make him your butler.
WOMAN:
That is funny.
Flower.
Every time you're
with that Kramer,
something happens.
He's a real
troublemaker.
He didn't have anything
to do with it.
He's altogether crazy,
that one,
and Jerry,
I used to think, was nice.
I don't know
what happened to him.
Nine bam.
One dot.
Two crack.
Three bam.
Mah Jongg.
So it was
a good party, huh?
Oh, you're welcome.
You're welcome.
They loved the TV,
loved it.
Yeah.
Wait a second, I'll ask her.
That's a great idea.
Drake wants to know if we wanna
come to Mineola this afternoon
since we missed
the party last night,
maybe get something to eat.
Sure.
Okay. Don't worry,
I'm taking my car.
Okay, all right.
We'll see you
later. Bye.
The Drake is great.
Hmm. He's so nice.
Man, I'm really happy
for them.
Yeah... Well, I don't know
if I'm happy for them.
I mean, I'm glad they're happy,
but frankly,
it doesn't do anything for me.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
[LAUGHS]
Yes?
GEORGE: It's me.
Come on up.
Hey.
[SIGHS]
I just came
from St. Elizabeth's.
St. Elizabeth's hospital? Why?
Well, the handicapped woman,
I went to see her.
You went to see her?
Yeah.
Wow. What happened?
I'm in love.
What?
Yeah, she is the most
beautiful woman
I have ever seen.
I love her, Jerry.
I mean, I really love her.
I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
She's got everything
I've always wanted
in another human being,
except for the walking.
Oh, what's the difference?
You don't go out that much.
Yeah.
Ah, I'm glad
you're here.
Why?
All right, now,
we gotta go out,
we gotta buy
a wheelchair.
A wheelchair? What for?
Well, you know,
I went
to the hospital today.
I saw the woman,
and the wheelchair is totaled.
We gotta get her another one.
Doesn't she have collision?
George...
I'm in love with her.
Well--
Yeah.
Look, my father works
for the United Volunteers.
Maybe he can get her one.
No. She needs it now.
Well, what about these two?
Aren't they gonna chip in?
Hey, we told you
not to park there.
Can't we just fix
the old one?
All right.
Fine, George,
don't chip in,
but someday we're gonna
be driving along,
we're gonna look
out the window,
see her crawling
along Fifth Avenue.
Is that what you want?
All right, all right!
We'll buy a wheelchair.
Wheelchairs!
Engagement presents!
It never ends!
This is our best model,
the Cougar 9000.
It's the Rolls Royce
of wheelchairs.
This is like...
you're almost glad
to be handicapped.
So now, what's this got?
Inductive joy stick,
dynamic braking,
flip-up arms.
It's fully loaded.
I put Steven Hawking
in one of these two months ago.
He's loving it.
It's rated number one
by Hospital Supply
and Prosthetic Magazine.
How much?
$6200.
Do you have something
a little more...
less expensive?
Hey, Drake!
How you doing?
Hi, Drake!
Hi, Allison.
Hey, there's the TV.
Elaine,
look at this!
My God, this is fantastic!
So tell me, were you guys
just blown away or what?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's fantastic.
I am gonna make good use
of this.
I'm watching
every Super Bowl here,
every big fight.
Oh, man, there is nothing
like a really big TV, huh?
So where we eating?
Well, actually, Jerry...
I'm really hungry.
We just broke up.
Oh.
When did this happen?
About 20 minutes ago.
[INHALING DEEPLY]
Hey, I am really sorry
about this, guys.
Whew!
JERRY: Hell of a picture
on this thing.
Oh, crystal clear.
[CHUCKLING]
They know
how to make them.
[CRYING]
Hey, Drake?
Are there any good
Italian restaurants around here?
Gagliano's.
That's pretty good.
[SOBBING]
Well, we should...
Get moving.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's go.
Hey, Drake, whatever happens,
I'm sure it'll be
for the best.
Yeah, take it easy.
Bye-bye, Allison.
[DRAKE SOBS]
Oh! The remote.
It's, um...
Okay, I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna put it on top
of the television.
I'm just gonna--
Oh, God!
All right.
This one's
about 8 years old.
Not a scratch on it.
It was owned
by some lady
who only used it to go
from the bathroom
to the kitchen
to feed her cats.
But this will
get you around?
Oh, sure. It just doesn't have
any of the frills of the Cougar.
Like what?
For example,
your tremor damping.
Now, what's that?
It helps to control
the direction,
regardless of the operator's
tremors or spasticity.
Well, is it all right
if I try it?
Hop in.
Oh, yeah.
[LAUGHS]
I tell you...
[CRASH]
When I see someone
enjoying themselves
like that...
It reminds me of why
I got into this business
in the first place.
GEORGE:
How much?
How about $240?
We'll take it.
KRAMER: We'll take it.
Drake gave her the TV?
He have her
all the gifts.
He felt guilty.
Well, she can't keep it.
It's not fair.
That's our TV.
I know it is!
Boy, I'm really starting
to dislike the Drake.
Hate the Drake.
Maybe the whole thing
was a scam.
Anybody can just get engaged
and get presents
and just keep them all.
Maybe they're on their way
to Chicago tomorrow,
to do the whole thing
all over again.
They don't know anybody
in Chicago.
Don't worry, they'll make
friends fast with that nice TV.
Hey.
Hey, guess what.
The Drake broke up.
The Drake broke up?
That's fantastic!
Now we get the TV back,
help defray some of the cost
of the wheelchair.
Yeah, I don't know
about defraying.
Why?
We're not getting
that TV.
What do you mean?
The engagement's off,
we get the TV back.
That's business.
The Drakette took it.
She can't take it.
It's not hers. It's theirs.
Once there's no theirs,
there's no hers.
It should be ours.
Well, she has it.
I told you
the Drake was bad.
I hate the Drake.
Maybe we should
call her.
Oh, come on.
Who's gonna call?
You are.
What?
Why is it me who always
has to do these things?
Because that's your thing.
What?
Calling people
I hardly know
and demanding
they return expensive gifts?
That's my thing?
Yeah, that's your thing.
All right.
Give me the phone.
That's my thing.
You know, I'm thinking
about getting a yo-yo.
Really?
Yeah.
I could see that.
Mm.
ALLISON:
Hello?
Allison.
Hi. This is Elaine.
I gave all the gifts
to charity.
Oh. Okay.
Well, thanks a lot.
Sorry again,
about you and the Drake.
I hate the Drake.
Everybody does.
Bye-bye.
She gave it to charity.
Charity?
That's appalling.
How could anybody be
so selfish and inconsiderate?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey. Well, I gave her
the wheelchair.
You should've seen
the look on her face.
And then she told me
that the old wheelchair,
that wasn't any good anyway.
So you see, George,
the whole incident
was a God-blessing.
Yeah.
You mean a blessing
in disguise?
Yeah.
And I would also like
to take this time
to personally thank
our gracious host,
Frank Costanza,
who has earned
the Silver Circle Award,
and is our unanimous choice
for the United Volunteer
representative of the month.
Due to his
tireless effort,
he has personally
raised over $22,000,
and that's a lot
of wheelchairs.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
On behalf of the
United Volunteers
of Greater New York,
we thank you.
Oh, thank you very much.
Mr. Costanza?
Yes.
You're under arrest.
Under arrest? What for?
Reckless endangerment
of public safety
and violation
of Traffic Code 342-A.
What's that?
Parking in a handicapped spot.
Let's go.
FRANK: George! George.
Your father got arrested?
For what?
Parking in
a handicapped spot.
Right in the middle
of his United Volunteers
meeting.
When he got back,
he chased after me
with a baseball bat.
Holy.
Between the car being totaled,
the towing charge,
and the fine,
there's no way
I could ever pay him back.
So, what are you gonna do?
I agreed to become his butler.
What?
Yeesh.
[SIGHS]
What's the matter?
It's over.
What's over?
Me and Lola.
The woman we bought
the wheelchair for?
Yeah. She dumped me.
She dumped you?
She dumped me.
She rolled
right over me!
Said I was
a hipster-doofus.
Am I a hipster-doofus?
No.
Said I'm not good-looking enough
for her.
Not good-looking.
Jerry, look at me.
Look at my face, huh?
Am I beautiful?
George, am I beautiful?
You're very attractive.
Yeah.
She says she doesn't want
to see me again.
Told me to drop dead.
Drop dead?
Boy, even I never
heard that one.
She's pretty rough.
Yes.
Well, we just blew
240 bucks
on a wheelchair.
240 bucks?
Well, it was slightly used.
Used?
[CHAIR RATTLING]
[WHEELS SQUEAKING]
[SCREAMING]
I don't think
you did such
a good job on these.
[VACUUM WHIRS, SHUTS OFF]
What?
You're supposed
to see your face there.
Do you see
your face in there?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Yeah?
Oh, really? Oh.
How about that.
Went right down a hill, huh?
Okay.
All right. Bye.
George,
forget about the shoes.
I want you to do
something for me.
This handicapped woman
had an accident.
Somebody gave her
a used wheelchair
with defective brakes.
Sons of bitches.
[SIGHS]
Anyway, I want you to pick up
this big-screen TV
and deliver it to her.
Big-screen TV.
You think you can handle it?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yes?
Uh, hi. We're from
the United Volunteers.
We've come to pick up the TV.
Oh, great.
It's right over there.
Ooh, it's a big one.
GEORGE:
Who's-- Who's got the receipt?
I do.
All right.
Will they
give us cash?
That's their policy.
I hate this mall.
There are never
any spaces here.
Why don't you park
in front of the hydrant?
What if there's
a fire?
Now, what are
the chances of that?
The handicapped parking spot
is the mirage
of the parking desert.
Do you know that feeling?
You see it, there
in the distance. It's almost--
And you can't believe your eyes.
It's too good to be true.
It's a big, wide spot,
right by the entrance.
Somehow, everybody missed it.
What is the handicapped
parking situation
at the Special Olympics?
They must have to just stack,
like, 100 cars
into those two spots.
How else are they gonna do it?