The basic problem
with the beginning
of the relationship, I think,
is that each person
has their own sexual timetable
of what should happen when
that the other person
knows nothing about.
That's why I really think
we need some sort
of sexual rule book,
where it's written down
and agreed upon,
sexual standard
dating procedure.
You know what I mean?
So if there's any problems,
you can go,
"Look, honey, I'm very sorry,
but we've been out three times,
"and according to Article 7,
Section 5,
"there's got to be
some physical contact,
"as you can see, right there.
"Otherwise, I will
report you to the board,
and they can put out
a warrant for an embrace."
Wait a second,
wait a second.
And then-- And then
the butler says,
"I'm not cleaning it up!
I'm sick of cleaning!"
That's funny.
"I'm sick of cleaning,"
that's very funny.
I've never seen a pilot script
as funny as this.
Yeah. It's funny!
I mean, how funny is this?
It's funny.
I mean, we're not
stupid, right?
We know when
something's funny.
It cannot not be funny.
Now, come on,
let's stay with it.
We gotta
finish this today.
Okay. Hey, you know,
maybe I should give it
to my therapist to read.
She's smart.
I trust her.
Yeah, maybe
I'll give it to Elaine.
Hey, you know,
we haven't brought
the Elaine character
into the show yet.
We should try and get her
into this scene.
Right. Right. Okay.
"Elaine...enters."
Right.
What does she say?
I don't know.
What do women say?
I don't even know
what they think.
That's why
I'm in therapy.
If we bring Elaine in,
there's gonna be so many
people to keep track of.
It's gonna be too hard.
I forget where
everybody's standing.
You, me, Kramer, the butler.
It's too much.
All right, forget Elaine.
All right.
Hey.
You are never gonna believe
who I just ran into today.
Who?
Your old flame,
Gail Cunningham.
Did you talk to her?
Well, I was on my way
to the Y,
I saw her
coming towards me.
I didn't know what to do,
because I remember
you had three dates with her
and she wouldn't kiss you
good night.
So now I'm thinking, you know,
what is my duty to my friend?
Do I acknowledge her?
Do I ignore her?
What is my responsibility?
Well, so, what happened?
Yeah, you know,
she sees me and she goes,
[SQUEALING]
"Ooh, hi, Kramer!"
You know?
Like nothing happened!
Like she never, you know,
went three dates with you,
and refused
to kiss you good night.
I know about
the three dates.
So you know what I did?
I snubbed her.
What do you mean,
you snubbed her?
I walked right
by her, vfft!
Never said a word.
Right by her?
Right by her!
What do you say
about a guy like this?
Huh?
Yeah.
You are some great friend,
I'll tell you.
Snubbed her.
Not that I condone it.
I've never condoned snubbing
in my administration,
but your loyalty
is beyond question.
Yeah, well, you know,
she's lucky
I was in a good mood.
Could've been
a lot worse.
I'm not even in here.
Yeah. I know.
Well, I thought
there was gonna be
a character
named Elaine Benes.
Well, there were too many
people in the room.
We couldn't keep track
of everybody.
George and the the butler...
You "couldn't keep track
of everybody"?
Well, we tried.
We-- We couldn't.
We didn't know how to...
We couldn't write for a woman.
We didn't know
what you would say.
Even right now,
I'm sitting here,
I know you're gonna
say something.
I have no idea what it is.
You "have no idea"?
Something derogatory?
Ah ha ha. I thought
I'd find you here.
Well, Gail Cunningham!
Hi, Gail.
Hi, Elaine.
Nice to see you.
Hey, what is with
your friend Kramer?
Why?
He snubbed me.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
Hey, where are you
going with that?
Gimme that.
Well, I thought you were finished.
I took two bites.
How am I finished?
[COUGHING]
Plus, you're coming down with something.
You want me to get sick?
Bite?
So I want to know,
why did Kramer do that?
Once he leaves the building,
he's out of my jurisdiction.
Well, tell him
that I am mad at him.
All right.
So where are you cooking now?
Pfeiffer's.
Oh, the power-lunch crowd.
Nice shoes.
Oh...
Thank you.
Where'd you get them?
They're, um, Botticelli's.
Ooh! Botticelli's!
Look at you.
I'm afraid to go in there.
Really?
Yeah.
Would you care to join us?
No, no, I got to
get to the restaurant. Oh!
See ya.
[GOOFILY]
"Ooh! Look at you.
Botticelli's."
That bothered you?
Yes, it bothered me.
So I bought a pair of shoes
at Botticelli's?
I'm not allowed to shop there?
That really embarrassed me.
It did?
Yes!
Couldn't you see that?
No.
This is why
you're not in the pilot.
Well, George, I think
you're beginning
to get some perspective
on things.
I think
we're making progress.
Yeah. I feel
like I've grown.
Good. So let's
pick up on this next week.
Great.
Oh, by the way,
did you get a chance
to read the script?
Yes. Yes, I did.
Well, what'd you think?
Uh, it was...good.
You...
You didn't like it?
Well, no...
I-I-I can't
believe this!
What was wrong with it?
What didn't you like about it?
It wasn't funny.
"It wasn't funny"?
What, are you kidding?
No. I didn't find it funny.
You "didn't find it funny"?
This is what I'm paying for?
Well, that whole
story line
about a guy who
gets into a car accident,
doesn't have
any insurance,
so the judge sentences him
to be a butler?
I didn't really
buy that.
Let me-- Let me tell you
who did, uh, buy it.
We pitched this story
to Russell Dalrymple,
the president of NBC,
and he ate it up
with a spoon.
George, if you're going to be
in a creative field,
you're gonna have to learn
how to deal with criticism.
How's this for criticism?
Um...
You stink.
How do you like that criticism?
You know what's funny to me?
That diploma up on the wall.
That is my idea of co-me-dy:
you sitting here,
telling people what to do.
I think you better go.
Oh, I'm going, baby.
I'm going.
It's Jerry's fault.
He took out all my good lines.
He's such a control freak!
So you send me
to this therapist
to help me with
my emotional disorders,
and she criticizes
our script.
What kind of
a therapist is that?
Well, I guess she didn't think
it was funny.
Oh, "she didn't think
it was funny"?
What is she,
Rowan and Martin?
We're supposed to
meet with NBC tomorrow.
She completely shattered
my confidence.
I'm paying for this.
She's my employee.
I thought your mother's
paying for it.
And she slaves
to earn every penny,
so that some day I might be able
to walk up to a woman,
and say, "Yes, I'm bald,
but I'm still a good person."
You know, he's right.
It's not her place
to criticize the script,
which reminds me,
what did you think of it?
You never told me.
What did I think of it?
Yeah.
[COUGHING]
Hey, buddy, I got
something to tell you.
Now, one second. Hold on!
You can't get off that easy.
Tell me what you thought.
Well, you know,
Jerry, I--
I just kissed
Gail Cunningham. Ooh!
You what?
Yeah, I kissed her.
You kissed her?
Right on the mouth.
What kind of great friend
are you?
How do you go from snubbing
to kissing?
Well, you know, I saw her
outside the Y, you know.
She came up to me,
she started yelling, you know,
because I snubbed her.
And, uh, then, uh, you know,
we started talking a little bit,
and I-- I walked her
to her building,
and just before I left,
I put my arm around her waist,
I pulled her to me,
and I-- I planted one.
And what
did she do?
She kissed me back.
I don't get this.
I go out with this girl
three times,
she doesn't want
to shake my hand,
why is she kissing you?
Well...
Because I snubbed her.
You see?
Women, they like that.
Yes! I understand women.
The snub is good.
They love the snub.
No, they don't.
I tried that once.
I snubbed for a year.
Nothing.
Every woman I saw,
I snubbed.
You never saw people
so pleased.
Ooh. So...
I understand you're buying
your shoes now at Botticelli's.
What?
Who told you that?
Gail Cunningham.
I-- I don't understand.
Why is this woman
talking about my shoes?
Why are my shoes
a topic of conversation?
Well, you know,
we were just talking,
and she mentioned how
you're buying your shoes now
at Botticelli's.
"How I'm buying my shoes now
at Botticelli's".
Did you hear this?
So what?
"So what?"
She is talking about my shoes!
She is discussing my shoes!
It is nobody's business
where I buy my shoes!
Hey! Gail!
Yup.
Elaine!
Why are you talking
about my shoes?
What?
My Botticelli shoes.
You've been talking
about my Botticelli shoes.
What are you talking about?
Did you or did you not
tell Kramer
that I got my shoes
at Botticelli's?
It's too spicy.
He wants another one.
You got that
pasta primavera?
Look, Elaine,
I am very busy here.
Who else have you mentioned
my shoes to, huh?
I wanna know why my footwear
is your conversation?
I am not discussing this.
This is insane.
You got that pasta
primavera? Let's go!
Here.
[SNEEZES]
Here you are,
Mr. Dalrymple.
Sorry for the delay.
Enjoy your lunch.
Well, come in.
Hi.
Hi. Hi.
Awfully sorry
to make you come up here,
but I really wasn't
feeling well enough
to go back
to the office,
and, well, it's
the only chance I have
to meet with you
this week.
Are you all right?
Well, it's my stomach.
I think
there must have been something
in the pasta primavera
I had for lunch.
Ah.
Ah. Where did you eat?
Pfeiffer's.
Oh...
I know the chef there.
Yeah, food's usually terrific.
My cousin works
for Bouchard's.
They used to use
the bouillabaisse
for a toilet.
What are you saying?
Well, you didn't
hear it from me,
but needless to say,
if you go in there,
stick with the consommé.
We'd better get started.
My daughter's
gonna be here soon.
Oh, you have a daughter.
Yeah, she just turned 15
last week.
Oh, that's a fun age.
Yeah.
All right.
The script.
Now, I've read this thing
three times...
And every time I read it...
What?
Excuse me for a second.
Would you like
a Pepto-Bismol?
I keep them
in my wallet.
You think he liked it?
[RETCHES]
I'm not sure.
[RETCHING]
[COUGHING]
What was that dish
he said he--?
Pasta primavera.
Yeah.
You know, "primavera"
is Italian for "spring".
No.
Yeah.
I really-- I'm terribly sorry.
It's just, uh...
All of a sudden, it just hit me.
So, uh, you were
saying, um...
about the script.
Right. The script.
Your script needs, um...
It needs, um...
More jokes?
Another ending?
A different name
for the butler?
[RETCHES]
[COUGHING]
Maybe we should go.
We haven't had
his notes yet.
We don't know how
he feels about our work.
[RETCHES]
Oh, no!
Oh, God...
Oh, my God.
I can't listen
to any more of this.
The guy's losing a lung
in there.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Molly.
I'm Jerry.
Uh, George.
We're here discussing
our script with your father.
He just read it.
[RETCHES]
Daddy, are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, sweetie,
I--
I'm fine.
[GROANS]
So you live
with your mother, huh?
Uh, yeah.
Divorce is very difficult,
especially on the kid.
Of course,
I'm the result
of my parents having
stayed together,
so you never know.
It's a crapshoot.
Dad, are you all right?
What's the matter?
It's just
a stomach thing.
Yuck...
Well, we're gonna have
to do this some other time.
So if you give me your number,
I'll call you later.
Suddenly, I'm in the mood
for pasta primavera myself.
Get a good look, Costanza?
What were you doing?
Well, it's not my fault.
You poked me.
You're supposed to just
take a peek after a poke.
You were like
you'd just put a quarter
in those big metal things
on top of the Empire
State Building.
It was cleavage.
I couldn't look away.
What am I,
waiting to win an Oscar here?
This is all I have in my life.
Looking at cleavage
is like looking at the Sun.
You don't stare at it.
It's too risky.
You get a sense of it,
then you look away.
All right.
So he caught me
in a cleavage peek.
So big deal.
Who wouldn't look
at his daughter's cleavage?
She's got nice cleavage.
That's why I poked.
That's why I peeked.
Oh, hi.
Hey! What is with
your friend, Elaine?
What?
She comes to my restaurant,
comes right in my kitchen,
and starts complaining
that I'm talking
about her shoes.
She did?
Yeah, right in the kitchen.
Disgraceful.
Well, I don't like people
coming into my kitchen.
I think she might've sneezed
all over someone's
pasta primavera.
Someone might have gotten sick
because of her.
Yeah...
Pasta primavera?
Is that what she said?
Hey, she's something, huh?
She's a wild one.
She's wearing me out.
She is?
She's real sensual.
You know,
with the cooking and all.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Stu.
From NBC?
Yeah.
What's going on?
What? Really?
Oh, my God.
Did he give you a reason?
Oh, boy.
Okay.
All right. Thanks.
Dalrymple just
canceled the pilot.
JERRY:
If you hadn't gone to her restaurant,
This whole thing
wouldn't have happened.
Look, I don't like people
talking about my shoes
behind my back, okay?
My shoes are my business.
The two of you
shouldn't have been looking
at some 15-year-old's
cleavage anyway.
He poked me!
There was cleavage
in the area!
That's a reflex.
Cleavage, poke.
But she was 15!
You don't consider age
in the face of cleavage.
This occurs
on a molecular level.
You can't control it.
We're like
some kind of weird fish,
where the eyes operate
independently of the head.
All right,
what's the difference?
What are we gonna do now?
He won't take our calls.
We can't get into his office.
You know
what we could do?
He eats at that
restaurant Pfeiffer's.
We could have Gail call
the next time he's there,
go and talk to him.
Yeah, now you're
on to something.
You know,
the whole thing is so stupid.
Like he wouldn't do
the same thing
if Elaine walked by
in a low-cut dress. Yeah.
Well, maybe not Elaine.
No.
No...
Somebody like Gail, though.
Yeah.
What?
What do you mean, Gail?
Hey-hey.
Hey. Kramer, listen.
I want you to ask Gail
to do me a favor.
The next time Russell Dalrymple
comes in the restaurant,
ask her if
she would call me.
Right. I'll call her
right now.
Okay.
What do you mean, Gail?
You don't think
I can attract attention?
I could put asses in the seats?
Look, sweetheart,
you know you've got it all.
But let's face it.
All right, she said
she'll do it.
All right. Great.
Great! Beautiful.
But she wants the shoes.
What?
Yep.
She says
she wants those shoes.
She wants my shoes!
What kind of
person is this?
All right, she's
not getting them!
No, come on,
I'll buy you another pair.
No, these are the last pair
of these that they had.
I'll get you another
one just like it!
These were the only
really cool ones like this.
Don't you see
how everybody likes them
and everybody talks about them?
Elaine...
...this pilot,
it doesn't matter to me.
It's not me I'm concerned about.
It's my mother.
She's already been
in the hospital this year.
Oh, yeah,
because she caught you jer--
Never mind!
Oh, come on, wait a second.
This whole thing is ridiculous.
How does she even know
she wears the same size?
All right,
what size are you?
Seven and a half.
Eh! Bingo.
Sauce this.
Yeah, he's here.
Oh, and one more thing:
Bring the shoes.
Ah-- Hey!
Oh!
Oh! Lookee!
Ho!
Fancy meeting you here.
Ha-ha!
Oh, hello.
Pasta primavera.
Back on the horse.
You know,
it's a funny thing,
because after
the pilot got canceled,
we hadn't heard
from you.
We didn't hear anything.
Didn't know.
We're wondering.
What happened?
Well, it just didn't seem
to be the right project
for us right now.
So, what
were you saying?
Oh, uh-- The--
Yeah, t-the show.
Because if it had
anything at all
to do with
what you perceived as me
leering
at your daughter,
I really have to take
issue with that.
I did not leer.
Did I leer?
No leer.
ELAINE:
Uh...
Excuse me, um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Are you using that ketchup?
Uh, no.
Because if I'm--
If I'm looking straight ahead,
and something enters
my field of vision,
that's merely
a happenstance.
Look...
under the circumstances,
I don't really feel
that we should be
in business together.
Here's your ketchup back.
You know, I have
the hardest time
trying to get some out.
I mean, I just kept..
pounding and pounding
on the bottom of it.
Do you ever have
any trouble?
No.
Do you have a...
[SENSUALLY]
ketchup secret?
No...
...don't have
a ketchup secret.
[GIGGLES]
Because, um...
if you do have
a ketchup secret,
I would really, really
like to know what it is.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Field of vision, huh?
How's everything?
Mm!
Really good.
This pasta primavera
is fabulous.
Very tasty.
How'd everything go
with that NBC guy?
Great.
The pilot's back on.
In fact, Elaine's
going out with him
tomorrow night.
Hey, listen, Elaine.
You know, if Russell mentions
anything about the pilot,
you'll, of course, tell him
how much you liked it.
You know,
I happen to have the script
right here with me,
and, uh...
[CLEARS THROAT]
on page three, for example,
suppose the Elaine character
comes in wearing, uh...
a low-cut dress.
And the butler
is very distracted
and can't work.
Uh, that kind of comedy,
that's a little
broad for us.
Nyah...
Well, I'm sure
it's right up
Russell's alley.
Well, it's a funny idea.
It's funny.
Come on,
funny is funny.
Funny is funny.
Yeah.
We're here
to entertain, right?
[LAUGHING]
All right.
Well, maybe I'll mention it
to Russell tomorrow night.
If you can.
Yeah.
Where's he taking you,
by the way?
Bouchard's on 53rd.
[COUGHING]
I think what he's
trying to say is,
"Get the bouillabaisse."
Men are obsessed with cleavage.
Women are obsessed with shoes.
It's the same for both sexes.
It doesn't matter how many times
we've seen these things,
every time these objects
are presented to us,
we have to look.
We cannot not look.
To men, cleavage
is like the nearest thing
to a nearby UFO landing.
That's what it is.
Women, if women
buy a pair of shoes
that they really love,
this is like boarding
the alien ship.
I think it's entirely possible
that aliens have landed,
and they haven't been able
to get our attention,
because we're so preoccupied
with cleavage and shoes.