I don't think people think
of their office as a workplace.
I think they think of it
as a stationery store
with danish.
You know what I mean?
You wanna get your pastry,
your envelopes, your supplies,
your toilet paper,
six cups of coffee,
and you go home.
Why do people
that work in offices
have pictures of their family
on their desk facing them?
Do they forget
that they're married?
Do they go, "All right, 5:00.
"Time to hit the bars
and pick up some hookers.
"Hold it a second.
"I got a wife and three kids.
I better get home.
Completely forgot."
[♪]
She hasn't told
her father yet?
No, we're supposed
to tell him tonight.
"We're?" What do you
mean "we're?"
Susan wants me
to be there.
You're meeting the father
for the first time?
Yeah.
Well, you'll make
quite an impression on him...
when you tell him
how you burned his cabin down.
I didn't burn it down.
Kramer did.
I mean,
the whole thing is ironic.
Think of it.
Here, the guy's nice enough
to give you a box of
very fine Cuban cigars--
Yeah, I know
what happened.
No, but wait, wait, and then you
dump them off onto Kramer--
I know.
--who proceeds to burn
the man's cabin down
with one of those
very same cigars!
It's very comical.
Listen, maybe-- Maybe we
shouldn't start writing today.
I got a lot on my mind.
No, no, we've put this off long
enough. Today's the day.
I wonder how Susan's father's
gonna react to this.
All right,
what's the worst he can do?
So you burn a house down?
Come on.
Not even a house,
it's like a cabin.
We could build a cabin
like that.
Well, maybe not us,
but two men could.
Bics? What,
did you get Bics?
What, you got a problem
with the pen now?
I like a rolling writer.
They're very smooth.
All right, let's just
get to work.
NBC Pilot.
Seinfeld Project.
Act One, Scene "A."
So you're gonna sit there?
Let me explain to you
one of the key elements
involved
in the writing process,
because it may seem
outwardly
that the pen and the paper
and the chair
play a large role,
but they're all
somewhat incidental
to the actual using
of the brain.
Okay? So just--
Just park yourself.
All right,
Act One, Scene "A."
Drink?
No. No drink.
All right.
Here we go.
Act One, Scene "A."
Weren't you supposed
to call Elaine?
Yes.
[TURNS ON TELEVISION]
Hi. Is Elaine there?
Oh, uh, hi, Sandra.
Uh, yeah, I can hold.
Every time I call,
I gotta chitchat with her
assistant for 20 minutes.
Oh, hi, Sandra.
Listen, I'm at a pay phone.
There's a lot of people
waiting to use it here.
I'll be off in a minute!
Yeah, could you just
put me through to Elaine?
Okay, thanks!
Are you thinking of ideas?
Elaine, is there any way I can
get through to you directly?
Every time I call,
Sandra bends my ear
for like 20 minutes.
So we're on for later?
Yeah, I'll come by after work.
Hey, I got a rubber pencil thing
happening here.
Uh, I gotta go. I gotta go.
Sandra? Sandra?
Hi. Can you come here
for a second?
Okay, let's go.
All right, here we go.
You got it? Here we go.
Yeah.
Okay, how about this?
I'm in my apartment.
You come in.
It's beautiful.
Okay, what do I say?
Could you do me a favor?
Um...when my friends call,
could you not talk to them
for too long?
Why, did Jerry say something?
No. No.
He must've said something.
Oh, no, he didn't say anything.
I can't work for you.
Oh, God...
I can't! I'm leaving.
No, Sandra!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I really am.
Listen, listen, Jerry's under
a lot of pressure right now.
It's very hard
being a stand-up comedian!
Sometimes they don't laugh!
[DOOR OPENS]
All right let's get going.
All right.
Here we go.
Hey...
Kramer, we're kind of
in the middle of something here.
We're trying to do
a little work here.
Yee...
What's with you?
No more golf.
Why?
Well, you remember I told you
about the pro, you know,
at the Westchester Country Club
who's letting me play a round
every time I gave him a couple
of those Cuban cigars?
Yeah, well, I lost them all
in the fire!
Hey, George,
maybe you can ask
Susan's father
for some more, huh?
Are you, crazy?
I can't ask the guy
for more cigars
after you burned down his cabin.
Why, what's one thing
got to do with another?
Kramer, please.
Well, I can't go back
to the public courses now!
I can't! I won't.
I mean, you know
what that's like?
It's crowded.
The grass has big
brown patches in it.
They don't rake the sand traps.
Not to mention the caliber
of people you have to play with.
Look, Kramer, I can't help you.
You're gonna have to get them
someplace else.
Where? They're Cubans.
You know what?
Maybe I should take off.
What?
Well, I gotta go to Susan's
parents' house for dinner,
and, you know, I want
to shower first,
and I want to leave myself
plenty of time.
You got four hours.
What about the script?
I think we got a bite on it.
Doesn't George look
like your sister, Sara?
A slight resemblance.
Her son's a podiatrist,
you know.
Oh, I have
tremendous respect
for people
who work with feet.
I mean, to dedicate
yourself to the foot,
you're-- You're toiling
in virtual anonymity.
I mean...
How you enjoying
those cigars I gave you?
Oh, uh, the cigars.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sucking them down.
I'm puffing
my brains out, yeah.
You know those cigars
are made special for Castro?
I did not know that.
Weird. Wild.
[SUSAN SNIGGERS]
What?
He's doing
Johnny Carson, Daddy.
I didn't care much
for his jokes.
Daddy never laughs.
Oh, well, so what?
Laughter.
What is that?
I mean, what is the point
of opening your mouth
and going, "Ha ha!"
What is that?
Ha ha!
You know, you can't get
those cigars anywhere.
You and your cigars.
Wear some more
lipstick.
Daddy, there's, um...
there's something that
we have to talk to you about.
Oh, I forgot
to ask you.
How'd you like the cabin?
Oh, the, uh, the cabin.
Well...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Right after we
get off the phone,
then you go
and tell her that?
Well, of course she knows
it was me who complained.
Now, I'm responsible
for this woman quitting!
Oh, this is unbelievable.
I know.
I screwed up.
It's all my fault.
Would you call her?
Oh, dial the number.
How could you do this?
I was just trying
to help you.
Oh, trying to help me...
Hello. Sandra?
Hi, uh, this is
Jerry Seinfeld.
Listen, I just
wanted to tell you
there's been a terrible
misunderstanding.
See, I told Elaine
that it was a real treat
talking to you
on the phone,
and she thought
I was being sarcastic,
you know, because
I'm a comedian and all.
She thought I meant,
"Yeah, it's a real treat
talking to her on the phone,"
but I was really being sincere.
No, of course I like you.
Tonight?
Um, uh, ho-hold
on a second.
Now she wants to
have a drink with me.
Just go. Go out with her.
Oh, I don't...
Go.
Yeah, think I can.
Um, yeah,
I know where that is.
Okay, uh,
I'll see you there.
Okay. Bye.
Now I gotta have
a drink with her.
The cabin...
[CHUCKLES]
Well...
Susan?
Uh...about the cabin--
I love that place.
My father built that cabin
in 1947.
My mother was recuperating
from impetigo at the time,
and Dad thought
it would be a good idea
to get her out
into the fresh air.
She died there
the following winter.
Dad passed away 10 years later
to the day.
His last words
to me were,
"Cherish the cabin."
Not, uh,
"Take care of your sister."
She's a paraplegic.
But "Cherish the cabin,"
and I have...for 45 years.
It's often been a...sanctuary
for me.
Kind of like Superman's
Fortress of Solitude.
What?
S-- Uh, Superman.
He, uh, built
The Fortress of Solitude
up at the north pole
to, uh, sort of
get away from it all.
When I go,
I'm passing it on to her.
[LAUGHS DRUNKENLY]
I'll take a hotel any day.
Daddy?
Yes?
Daddy, about the cabin.
Mm!
Look, Henry,
I spilled wine on me.
What about it?
Well, the thing is--
What? What is it?
Well, the cabin
is kind of, uh...
George?
Burned.
Burned?
There was a fire,
and it, uh...
Burned.
The cabin burned?
[CHUCKLING]
Yeah, burned.
Whoo!
Burned...
[LAUGHING]
Was anything found?
Was it all
burned to the ground?
Did they find anything?
No. Nothing.
[LAUGHING]
Nothing?
But, you know,
Mr. Ross,
if you look
at the whole situation,
what with it being
your cigars and everything,
it's really
rather ironic.
One might even say,
in a sense, comical.
[LAUGHS]
Really.
Think about it.
I can't believe
you said that.
What?
How could you say
something like that to me?
What? You were the one
who was talking dirty.
I was just trying to keep up.
That was a weird thing to say.
I was just trying to join in so
you wouldn't feel embarrassed.
Oh, I think
you're really sick.
I'm not sick.
You-- You said
much sicker things than me.
I'm leaving.
I really think
you're making too much of this.
Excuse me.
I mean, let me walk you to a cab.
That's okay.
I mean, the main thing
is that this is
just between us,
and that'll be
the end of it.
Oh, really?
I mean, people,
they're not interested
in things like this.
They don't wanna hear about it.
They really don't.
JERRY: So we're
drinking and talking,
and so she starts
rubbing my leg.
[LAUGHING]
Whoa.
What did you do?
Have you ever told a woman
to stop touching your leg?
Yeah, right.
I mean, I know
it's the wrong thing to do.
She works in Elaine's office.
I know it's wrong,
but I can't get that hand
off my leg.
I mean, I'm looking at the hand,
I'm thinking,
"That hand
should not be on my leg,"
but I can't make my brain
to get my mouth
to say the words,
"Would you mind?"
And yet women have no problem
getting the hand off.
How do they do that?
I don't know, they're working
on a whole other level.
All right, so go ahead.
So then we go back
to my apartment.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
So, we're, uh,
fooling around there.
You know, it's getting
a little passionate, and, uh...
she starts
with the dirty talking.
All right. All right.
Hold on. Time out.
Whoa. Whoa.
What did she say?
You know...the usual.
No, I don't know.
How do I know the usual?
The typical things.
What's typical?
Give me typical.
Give me some typical.
She says, uh...
[WHISPERING]
[KETCHUP SQUIRTS]
That's very dirty.
That's absolutely filthy.
And then she starts
talking about her panties.
I'm going to need
some water here.
So-- So I said something.
Okay, what did you say?
Now, bear in mind,
I am just trying to keep up.
Of course.
Okay?
So she's talking
about her panties...
So, uh...
So I said,
"You mean the panties
your mother laid out for you."
"The panties your mother
laid out for you"?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Just popped out.
Well, how did she react?
She flipped out.
Just left.
Well, that's not offensive.
It's abnormal,
but it's not offensive.
Look, the main thing is
I don't want Elaine to know
about any of this.
I mean, especially
the panty remark.
I mean, it's--
It's embarrassing,
and she'd never let me
hear the end of it.
Well, what if this girl
says something to her?
She will tell her.
She's going back to work.
I talked her into it.
How stupid was that?
Hey, so Susan's father
took that news
pretty hard, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
He went into the bedroom
and started sobbing.
Guess he didn't see
the humor in it.
Yeah. Whoosh.
All right.
You know,
let's go, let's go.
We got a lot of work
to do today.
All right.
Big work day.
That's right.
Okay.
Let's go.
Here we are.
Right now.
Let's do it.
You and me.
Okay.
All right.
What do you got?
I got, you enter,
you go, "Hi,"
and I go, "Hello."
Now, we need
something here.
Oh, hey.
Kramer, hey!
Kramer! Buddy! Come in here!
You guys are working.
I'll come back.
BOTH:
No, no, no, no!
Nah, you guys
should get back to work.
No, don't leave.
We were taking a break!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Uh, George, did you
talk to that guy
about getting me
some more cigars?
I told you,
I'm not gonna do that.
Okay.
Well, I guess I'm just gonna
have to take matters
into my own hands, huh?
All right. I'll see you guys.
Where you going?
Don't run off like that!
BOTH:
Aw...
Buenos dias.
¿Habla ingles?
Si.
Yeah...
Okay. Um...
Um...
I need to talk to someone.
What is this about?
Uh, well, it's a very
private matter,
but extremely urgent.
Are you an American?
Oh, yeah.
I see.
Excuse me.
Okay.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
Aah!
Let's get going.
All right,
let's get focused here.
Come on, now.
Come on, let's get it together.
Yeah.
It's Elaine.
Come on up.
[EXHALING]
All right, you know
what we should do?
We should go to the movies,
get away from this script
for a while.
Yeah, we should.
I just have to go over
to the Ross' apartment
and drop off Susan's sunglasses.
You'll come with me?
Yeah. What,
does she live with them?
No, no, no, no.
Hey, nice going,
Jerome Seinfeld.
What?
I just got a message
from Sandra.
She's coming back to work.
Well, then, you've just
gotta fire her.
Don't even think about it.
There's no two ways about it.
Why? What happened?
Did you talk?
Talk? Did I talk?
I-- I-- You're darned right
I talked to her.
We talked up a storm,
and I've concluded,
from the basis of those talks,
that this isn't anybody
you should be talking to.
Really? You really think
I should fire her?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, in fact, if George
and I weren't so busy here
working on the script,
I'd do it myself.
[KRAMER HUMMING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
Buenos dias.
What is your name, señor?
Uh, Kramer.
So, Señor Kramer...
what is this about?
Cigars.
Cigars?
What about cigars?
Uh, see here, I...
I saved one of the cigar rings.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, you mean...one of these.
Yeah, yeah.
That's them.
Okay, so, I'd like to buy
a couple of boxes
of those from you.
[SNIFFING]
You realize, of course, these
are illegal in your country.
Um, well, uh, illegal, huh?
I like...that jacket.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi!
Hi, how are you?
Hey, Jerry.
Hi.
I thought you two guys
were working today.
Ah, just taking
a little break.
Yeah. Oh, here's
your sunglasses.
Oh, thanks.
Come on in for a second.
This is my brother Ricky.
He's home from college
for the weekend.
Oh, hey, there,
young fellow.
What's your major?
I don't have one.
Well, you should always
consider podiatry.
Nothing wrong
with the feet.
And this is
my Aunt Sara.
He doesn't look like me.
Sara, what do you have
on your wheels?
Nothing. They're clean.
Ricky, did you
wipe her wheels off?
Yes.
Well, they're filthy.
It's just a matter
of common courtesy.
You come in the house,
you wipe your wheels.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Excuse me.
Hello, Raymond.
Yes, the man
from the insurance company
dropped this off
this morning.
He said it was
the only thing left
from the remains
of the fire.
Oh, thank you.
Wow, I've never
seen this before.
Oh, they're letters.
Here.
Oh, sure.
From...
from John Cheever!
Wow.
[LAUGHS]
Ooh...
"Dear Henry,
"last night with you was bliss.
"I fear my...
"orgasm has left me a cripple.
"I don't know how
I shall ever get back to work.
"I love you madly. John.
P.S. Love the cabin."
Well, we...
Yeah.
we really should be...
Look at the time.
...heading out.
Uh, you know,
it's a time...
HENRY: The box!
My letters! Give me that!
Who told you to open that?
Who's John? Who's John?
I knew it.
I want to know who John is!
John Cheever?
Dad, you
and John Cheever?
Yes.
Yes. He was the most wonderful
person I've ever known,
and I loved him deeply...
in a way
you could never understand.
Well, we really should be,
uh...heading out.
Jerry hates to miss
the coming attractions.
Yeah, and because
of the...time.
Time is what
he's indicating there.
We'll see you.
Anyway,
onward and upward.
All right, here we go.
Come on now.
Right now.
Here we go.
You and me.
You got it.
All right, what have you got?
I got you come in,
you say, "Hi,"
and then I say, "Hello."
All right,
so we need something.
Yeah.
How about this?
I say, "How's it going?"
"How's it going?" Beautiful.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Oh, come on,
we were just on a roll now.
All right, did you
get that line?
"How's it going?"
Did you write it down?
I'm writing it.
"How's it going?"
Real good!
What?
You know how much money
you cost me today?
$429.
What? How?
Oh...
I got Sandra transferred
to another office upstairs,
okay?
So she blabs to Lippman
about my long-distance
calls to Europe!
What calls?
[GROANS]
I made a friend when
I was in Europe, okay?
And we've been in touch,
and Sandra told Lippman!
Oh. Did she say
anything else to you?
Anything else?
What do you mean
"anything else"?
So she just left the office,
didn't say a word to you
about anything?
Yeah.
Beautiful.
Why is that beautiful?
Oh, no. Not beautiful.
It's $429!
Hey, look, I'm gonna
pay for that.
No, no.
No, I insist.
I was the one
that encouraged you
to fire her.
The whole thing
was all my...
Okay.
...fault.
Do you smell smoke?
Oh, hey! Hey, Jer,
I want you to meet
my new friends here.
This is Luis, Jorge,
and Umberto.
How you doing?
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, we're heading
up to Westchester.
Gonna hit the links.
Oh...
Hey, uh, isn't
that, uh, your--
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Okay. We're going.
!¡Vámanos, muchachos!
Hey, what are you reading?
Oh, uh, The Falconer,
by John Cheever.
It's really excellent.
John Cheever. You ever
read any of his stuff?
Uh, yeah, I'm familiar
with some of his writing. Yeah.
All right, look,
we gotta get back
to work.
We just had a big
breakthrough here.
Okay, I'll leave
you two alone.
Okay.
Maybe I'll go visit my mother.
She just bought me
some new panties,
and they're all...
laid out for me.
[♪]
There's this whole
talking-during-sex business.
I mean, what are we doing here?
The question is,
does the talking
really improve the sex,
or is the sex act now just there
to spice up the conversation?
Of course, eventually, I'm sure
people will get tired of,
too lazy, even,
for phone sex.
They'll start having
phone machine sex, you know.
"Yeah, I want you really bad.
Just leave it on the tape."
Then I guess the phone company
will come out with sex waiting.
That'll be the new thing.
"Uh, yeah, hold on, honey.
I got another call.
"Oh, hiya, baby. One second.
"Uh, honey,
I've got to take this.
"Yeah, I've got sex waiting
on the other line.
I've got to take this."