You can't just have an adultery,
you commit adultery.
And you can't even
commit adultery
unless you already have
a commitment,
so you have to
make the commitment
before you can even
think about committing it.
There's no commit
without the commit.
Then, once you commit,
then you can commit
the adultery.
Then you can get caught,
get divorced,
lose your mind,
and they have you committed.
But, you know, some people
actually cheat on the people
that they're cheating with,
which is, like, you know,
being in a holdup,
and then turning
to the robber next to you
and going, "All right, give me
everything you have too."
You met her at
the supermarket?
How'd you do that?
Produce section.
Very provocative area.
A lot of melons and shapes.
Everyone squeezing and smelling.
It just happened.
So when are you
going to see her?
Tonight.
What's her name?
I don't know.
How could you
not know her name?
I was a little nervous.
I got distracted.
It had something to do
with a car or a fish.
Look at--
Why do I get bananas?
They're good for one day.
Oh, my God.
I forgot to tell you.
I got a letter today
from the State
Controller's Office.
When I was going to public
school, back in Brooklyn,
every week, I used to
put 50 cents
in the Lincoln Savings Bank.
Yeah, I did that, too.
Yeah. Remember
the little bank book?
Sure.
All right.
So I haven't put anything in it
since sixth grade.
I completely
forgot about it.
The State Controller's
Office tracks me down.
The interest
has accumulated to $1900.
$1900!
They're sending me a check.
Wow.
Yeah, interest,
it's an amazing thing.
You make money
without doing anything.
I have friends that try and base
their life on that principle.
Really? Who?
Nobody you know.
Maybe I'll go down to the track,
put it all on a horse.
Why don't you
put it in the bank?
Bank? This is found money.
I want to parlay it.
I want to make a big score.
Oh, you mean
you want to lose it.
Yeah.
All right.
You got it, huh?
Yes, I did.
Yes!
What's with the gloves?
Well, I'm staining
my floors.
You know, I don't want
to get my hands dirty.
What, the whole apartment?
The whole apartment.
And I'm buying
that fake-wood wallpaper.
I'm going to surround myself
in wood.
It's gonna be like
a log cabin,
'cause I need wood around me.
Wood, Jerry.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Wood.
Wood is good.
Definitely.
We're still going to
play racquetball, right?
Yeah, whenever you're ready.
Okay, as soon as
Elaine gets here.
Yep.
What, you rented
Home Alone?
Yeah.
I thought you
saw that already.
No, I saw Home Alone 2.
Oh, right.
But you hated it.
I was lost.
I never saw the first one.
You mind
if I watch it here?
What for?
Because if I watch it
at my apartment,
I feel like
I'm not doing anything.
I watch it here, I'm out of
the house, I'm doing something.
All right,
go ahead.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
It's me. Are you ready to go?
No. Come on up.
I can't work with these.
What's wrong?
What? You bought me
dishwashing gloves.
There's no fine touch.
You said gloves.
No, no.
These are too thick.
Oh. Is that Home Alone?
Yeah. The original.
Hey, boys-o.
Hey!
Hello.
Hey, get your stuff.
Let's get going.
Well, wait a minute.
There's a slight
change of plans.
Huh?
What?
Remember Roy, the artist?
Oh, the triangle guy.
Yeah, exactly.
The triangle guy.
Yeah, you liked him.
What happened with him?
Yeah, I did.
He was very talented.
He was, uh, just,
I don't know,
a little too...
Artsy?
Fat.
Oh.
He was a fat, starving artist,
you know?
That's very rare.
Yeah.
Anyway, he's in the hospital,
having surgery,
and I feel like
I should visit him.
What's wrong with him?
Eh, something with his spleen.
Anyway, it'll just
take five minutes, okay?
And then the hospital's
right on the way.
All right,
we'll wait for you.
Yeah, maybe I can get some
rubber gloves there. Huh? Yeah.
Listen, Jerry,
could you do me a favor?
Could you go into the room
with me to visit him?
Because I don't want
him to think
that I'm, you know,
interested.
Oh, you want me to pretend
to be your boyfriend?
Well...
Well, I think
I can do that.
I believe I've played
that role before
to some
critical acclaim.
All right, let's go.
All right.
Yep, yep, yep.
What's with him?
You know, a lot of people
have asked that.
Roy!
Elaine!
What a surprise.
Oh, my God!
I hardly
recognize you.
You look so...
Yeah, yeah,
I've lost some weight.
A lot of weight.
I know.
You look terrific.
Thank you.
So do you.
[GIGGLES]
Uh...
this is, uh...
You really
lost weight!
Thank you.
Jerry.
Uh, I'm the boyfriend.
NURSE [OVER PA]:
Dr. Whittenberg, outside call.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Ah...
Ah, the mother lode.
[SILLY, SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't believe it.
You were huge,
like blubber.
I couldn't even get
my arms around you.
Yes. I remember.
Well, that's a positive thing
about getting sick.
You get to lose weight.
Elaine, it wasn't the illness.
It was you.
Me?
After you stopped seeing me,
I was devastated.
I couldn't eat
for weeks.
Get out!
[GASPS]
Really. It's the truth.
Jerry, did you
hear this?
He couldn't eat
for weeks.
[FLATLY]
That's terrible.
I had no idea
I had that kind of
effect on you.
You did.
You know, I can't get
this damn thing to sleep!
Now, listen, Roy,
tell me something.
When are you
getting out of here?
Next Thursday.
Okay,
I tell you what.
How about on Friday
I take you out
for a big meal
because you
are getting too thin.
Honey...
Aren't we going to
the Poconos next Friday?
No, that's the week after.
No, I believe
it's next week.
You're wrong.
No, I'm not.
Shut up.
Pay dirt.
Uh, Roy, this is Kramer.
He's one of our friends.
How do you do?
I do great.
Hi, Roy.
Oh, hey,
Dr. Siegel.
Hey, doc,
check this out.
Hey.
I just learned that.
[CHUCKLES]
I just wanted
to stop by,
see if you
had any questions
about
tomorrow's operation.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
I have--
I have a question.
Um, what do you
know about
interabdominal
retractors?
Are you asking
because you saw
20/20 last night?
I sure am.
Well, that report
was about one very specific
type of retractor,
and I can assure you
we do not
use that retractor
in your friend's
procedure.
But you will
use a retractor.
We have to.
Mm-hmm.
I'll tell you what.
You're obviously
concerned about
your friend's welfare.
A few of my students
will be observing
tomorrow's operation
from the viewing gallery.
How would you like to
watch it with them?
I'd love to watch the operation,
yeah.
I don't know.
Oh, come on, Jerry,
you gotta see
the operation.
They're gonna
cut him open.
His guts will be
all over the place.
Yeah, that's true.
They'll saw
through bone.
Phrrrrrrrr...
Ree-ree-ree-ree-ree-ree!
We'll see
what's inside bone.
[MELANCHOLY DRAMATIC MUSIC
PLAYING OVER TV]
[SNIFFLES]
[SOBS]
Hey.
[TEARFULLY] Hi.
What're you doing?
You're crying?
No.
You're crying from Home Alone?
The old man got to me.
Oh, right.
Just get yourself together.
I don't know if I can
be friends with you anymore
after this display.
Oh, shut up!
What're you doing back
so soon, anyway?
I never even
got to the gym.
Kramer got the gloves,
wanted to come home
and start working
on his floor.
Oh.
How's the guy?
Oh, he's okay.
In fact, him and Elaine
are getting pretty chummy.
Now Elaine wants me
to buy some of his art.
Hmm, that's nerve.
Yeah.
So she and triangle boy
can go out to fancy restaurants.
You know what it is?
It's Clara Nightingale Syndrome.
He falls ill, she falls in love.
You mean Florence Nightingale.
What did I say, Clara?
Yeah, you must have meant
Clara Barton.
Clara Barton?
What did she do?
I'm not sure,
but I think she was nice.
Susan B. Anthony
I'd think have a problem with.
Yeah, I think you would.
So you're gonna buy his art?
No. Why don't you buy it?
You got $1900.
Yeah. That's what
I want, triangles.
All right,
I'm outta here.
Have fun with
what's-her-name.
I will.
You know, now you got
to ask her name.
It's so embarrassing.
No, it isn't. I can find out.
Yeah? How?
There are ways.
JERRY:
You know, I remember
when I was a kid
growing up,
kids would make fun
of my name
like you
wouldn't believe.
"Jerry, Jerry, Dingleberry,"
and...
"Seinsmelled."
Seinsmelled?
Yeah.
What about you?
Did people
make fun of your name?
Are you kidding?
They were merciless.
What do you expect
when your name rhymes
with a part of
the female anatomy?
Of course, not everybody
can be as sweet as you are.
Oh, Jerry.
Oh...you.
Now, let's
try "breast."
Celeste.
Kest.
No.
Rest, Sest.
Hest?
That's not a name.
Well, you should've
just asked her.
I know I should've
asked her.
Well, what're you
gonna do now?
I don't know.
I can't ask her now.
I've already made out with her.
Once you make out with a woman,
you can't her her name.
Aretha.
No.
Bovary.
All right. That's enough.
All right, well, you know
what you gotta do?
You gotta go
through her purse.
You know, credit cards,
driver's license.
Well, how am I gonna do that?
When she goes
to the bathroom.
Ah. There you are.
Hey.
My date stood me up.
Listen, will you guys go
to the operation with me?
You asked a date
to go to the operation?
Well, yeah.
So come on.
What do you say? Huh?
What kind of operation
is it?
Splenectomy.
Isn't that where
they remove the--?
No, no, don't
ruin it for me.
I haven't seen it yet.
Now, come on.
What do you say?
Mulva.
Mulva?
KRAMER: Come on, come on.
You want to go?
All right, all right.
Just let me
finish my coffee.
Then we'll watch them go
slice this fat bastard up.
Now we'll open
the peritoneal cavity,
exposing the body's
internal organs.
Nurse, retractor.
What're you eating?
Junior Mints.
You want one?
No.
Now I can't see.
Psst!
Could you get...?
Where'd you
get those?
The machine.
You want one?
No.
Here.
Take one.
I don't want one.
No, they're good.
Take one.
I don't want any.
Just take one.
No, Kramer, stop it.
[HEART BEATING]
[SPLAT]
Oh, my.
Geh--
...over the balcony,
bounced off
some respirator thing,
into the patient!
What do you mean,
into the patient?
Into the patient, literally!
Into the hole?
Yes!
The hole!
Didn't they notice it?
No.
How could they not notice it?
Because it's a little mint.
It's a Junior Mint.
Well, what did they do?
They sealed him up
with the mint inside.
They left
the Junior Mint in him?
Yes!
Well, I-- I guess
it can't hurt him.
People eat pounds
of those things.
Yes, they eat them.
They don't put them
next to vital organs
in their abdominal cavity!
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
It's me.
Come on up.
Hey.
This wallpaper
is very good.
My place looks like
a ski lodge.
Why'd you force
that mint on me?
I told you I didn't
want the mint!
Well, I didn't
believe you.
How could you
not believe me?
Well, who's gonna
turn down a Junior Mint?
It's chocolate.
It's peppermint.
It's delicious!
That's true.
It's very refreshing!
Well, just don't say anything
about this to Elaine.
Prognosis...
negative.
Prognosis
negative?
He's not doing well.
The doctors don't know
what it is.
They're baffled.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
Just my luck, you know?
Just when he was getting
thin and attractive.
You know, Jerry,
you should buy
some of his art.
That would really
lift his spirits.
It's that bleak?
Mm.
You know...
if the guy dies,
the art could really
be worth something.
We gotta confess!
Really?
Yes!
We could be
tried for murder.
I can't have this
on my conscience.
We're like
Leopold and Loeb.
You're not gonna say anything
Got that?.
You can't stop me.
No, you're not!
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Elaine?
Put me down
for some of that art.
$1900 worth.
Oh, yeah, that's the spot.
What are you
so tense about?
Oh, nothing, really.
Just a homicide.
Oh, that's terrific.
Mulva.
What?
Mulva?
Uh, my, uh...
My aunt's name is Mulva.
She's-- She's a masseuse.
Oh. Um, I'm going
to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Oh, good idea.
What are you doing?
Oh. I was just
looking for, uh, some gum,
or a mint.
Oh, I have
Junior Mints.
No!
No, I mean...
No, thank you. No.
Any news?
[WHISPERS]
No, no news.
You better
get outta here.
Oh, okay.
Wait. Wait a second.
I don't know the name
of this woman
in the bathroom,
so when she comes out,
you introduce yourself,
then she'll be forced
to say her name.
10-4.
Okay.
Oh, hello.
Hello, I'm Kramer.
Nice to meet you.
See you later.
Well, I'd better
get going.
I don't wanna be
late for the play. Oh, okay.
You know, my cousin
knows the producer.
I may get to
go backstage
and meet
Olympia Dukakis.
Hey, there's a name
you don't forget.
Mm. Bye, Jerry.
Bye.
Oh, hi.
Oh.
Hi, I'm George.
Oh, nice to meet you, George.
Yeah.
I gave it a shot.
So. Any word
on the artiste?
No. I haven't
heard anything.
Well, I got my triangles.
Really.
Yeah, you know, they really
spruce up the apartment.
Yeah, I'm sure. Well,
I gotta call the hospital.
I gotta tell them
what happened.
No, no, Jerry.
I wouldn't do that.
Why?
Uh...
You could get
in trouble.
Look, I gotta try
and help the guy.
Who are you to play God?
Every man's time comes!
If his number is up,
who are you to interfere?
Yes, I'd like
to speak with Dr. Siegel.
It's about
Roy Corning's condition.
What, what?
Oh, that's fantastic.
He didn't get better,
did he?
Thank you very much.
Okay, bye-bye.
He's gonna be okay!
Where's the luck?
There's no luck.
Nineteen hundred dollars
down the drain.
You saved
my life, George.
You buying my art
is what inspired me
to get better.
I'll never forget
what you did for me.
Oh, well,
that's great.
It's really
great.
You know, art's
a great investment.
Yeah, they'll look
great in your apartment.
Yes, I look forward
to many years of...
looking at
the triangles.
Well, I'll, uh...
I'll wait
for you outside.
Hey, George.
GEORGE: Yeah?
KRAMER:
All right.
SEINFELD:
That's nice.
Thanks, Roy.
Hey!
There's the guy
who saved my life.
You know, I don't want
to totally discount
the emotional element
in your recovery,
but I think there were
other factors at play here.
What do you mean?
I have no medical
evidence to back me up,
but something happened
during the operation
that staved off
that infection.
Something beyond
science.
DR. SIEGEL:
Something, perhaps...
from above.
Mint?
Those can be
very refreshing.
[WITH MOUTH FULL]
So, Elaine...
Where're we going for
our big dinner on Friday?
Um...
I am so sorry, Roy,
but, actually,
we are going
to the Poconos on Friday.
Right, honey?
I don't think so.
Yeah, I think that
we, uh... We are.
I believe we're not.
[SLURPING]
Please, can we go
to the Poconos?
Well, I'll
think about it.
MYSTERY WOMAN:
Great seats.
You could see
the actors spitting.
Really.
Mm-hmm.
And, afterwards,
we went backstage,
and Olympia Dukakis
autographed my playbill.
Oh. What are you saying,
you got her autograph? Yeah.
Do you have it with you?
Yeah, it's
in my purse.
Uh, let me see.
You know, I really think
I'm falling for you,
Jerry Seinfeld.
Oh, well, I really think
I'm falling for you...
"Joseph Poglia."
I had it autographed
for my uncle.
Yeah, I know.
You don't know
my name, do you?
Yes, I do.
What is it?
It-- It rhymes
with a female body part.
What is it?
Mulva?
Um...uh...
Gipple?
Loleola?
Oh!
Dolores!
At ages zero through 10,
candy is your life.
There's nothing else.
Family, friends, school,
they're only obstacles
in the way
of getting more candy.
And you have your favorite candy
that you love.
You know, there's ones,
"I love those, I hate those.
I hate those, I love those."
And only a seven-year-old kid
could actually
taste the difference
between, like, a red M&M
and a light brown M&M.
That's two
totally different things
when you're a seven-year-old.
"Well, you're right,
it's more of a main-course M&M.
"But the brown,
it's more of a mellower flavor.
It's an after-dinner M&M,
really."