I think the idea
behind the tuxedo
is kind of
the woman's point of view
that men are all the same.
We might as well
dress them that way.
That's why, to me, a wedding
is like the joining together
of a beautiful, glowing bride
and...some guy.
The tuxedo
is a wedding-safety device
created by women
because they know
that men are undependable.
So in case the groom
chickens out,
everybody
just takes one step over
and she marries the next guy.
That's why the wedding vow isn't
"Do you take Bill Simpson?"
It's "Do you take...this man?"
JERRY:
Leave a message. I'll call you back. Thanks.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
Jerry? Joe Davola.
[SPITTING]
I have a hair on my tongue.
Can't get it off.
You know how much I hate that?
Of course you do.
You put it there.
I know what you said about me,
Seinfeld.
I know you bad-mouthed me
to the execs at NBC.
Put the kibosh on my deal.
Now I'll put the kibosh on you.
You know I've kiboshed before.
And I will kibosh again.
[BEEPS]
So, what do you think?
About what?
The opera.
Nah, I don't want to go.
You got to go.
I-I-I don't like
the opera.
What are they singing for?
Who sings?
You got
something to say,
say it.
Jerry, you don't
understand.
That's the way
they talk in Italy.
They sing to one another.
[SINGING IN FAKE ITALIAN]
All right, all right.
That's the way it was, you know?
I mean,
you listen to the language,
it's got
that sing-songy quality to it.
It's the language, Jerry.
The language.
So why don't they
talk like that now?
Well, it's, uh...
It's too hard to, uh, keep up.
You know, they got...
They were tired.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Better get that.
Yeah?
ELAINE: It's me.
Come on up.
So? Huh? What?
Ah, I don't know.
Aw, come on, Jerry,
it's opening night.
Black tie, Pagliacci.
The great clown.
The great, sad, tragic...clown,
Like you.
Well, that's very flattering.
How did you get these tickets?
I heard they're
impossible to get.
Oh, well,
I have many associates.
I don't know.
Opera, it's not
my kind of thing.
You're not going,
I'm not going.
I'm gonna call
the whole thing off.
No, wait a minute.
What about George,
Susan and Elaine?
Why do you need me?
You're the nucleus,
the straw that stirs the drink.
You're the "magliana."
Well, I guess if
I'm the magliana, Yeah.
I should go.
All right,
all right.
Hi.
Hi, Elaine.
You got the tickets,
right?
No, I don't have them on me.
What?
That's why I came
all the way over here.
Yeah, well,
my friend's got them.
I'm gonna pick them up
tomorrow.
Oh, I was going to surprise Joey
with them.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You got an extra one, right?
Oh, yeah!
So I finally get to meet
your pal Joey.
It's killing you,
isn't it?
Yeah.
So Joey's a great lover
of the opera.
Listen...
I got news for you.
It's nice to be involved
with somebody
who's interested in something
other than Nick at Nite.
You know?
He's got a grip on reality.
He's-- He's-- He's happy,
he's well-adjusted.
[OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
Well, I'm looking forward
to meeting him.
I gotta go.
Where you going?
What's the rush?
I'm gonna surprise Joey.
I've never been
to his apartment,
so I'm just gonna...pop in.
Oh, good.
Men love that.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
You got a message,
buddy.
Ooh.
It could be
from that blond.
Ooh.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Jerry? Joe Davola.
[SPITTING]
I have a hair on my tongue.
[CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING WILDLY]
Kramer,
what am I gonna do?
That guy's gonna put
the kibosh on me!
He's crazy,
out of his mind--
Steady, steady.
Now calm yourself!
Come on,
get ahold of yourself!
He's supposed to be
on medication.
He told me
he was getting medication!
Quiet, quiet!
Now let me think!
I'm gonna
call the cops.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm calling the cops.
The cops?! They're not
gonna do anything!
What do you mean
they're not?
They're the cops!
They got to do something!
He'll put the kibosh on me!
Do you know what a kibosh is?
K-k-k-kibosh.
I mean, it's a terrible mistake.
He thinks I ruined
some deal of his at NBC.
I don't know anything
about any deal at NBC.
Call him
and tell him that!
That-- That's
what I'll do.
I'll just call him
and tell him.
I'll tell him.
That's all I'll do.
Right.
He's a human being.
Yeah.
I'll talk to him.
He'll understand, right?
Yeah.
Don't mention my name.
Oh, I got the machine.
What's his message like?
Nice.
Yeah?
Hello, Joe, listen,
this is Jerry Seinfeld.
I-I really think
there's been
a-a-a huge, colossal
misunderstanding.
Big! Big!
And I feel
that if we could just
talk about this,
we could straighten
the whole thing out,
so call me back. Bye.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Joey?
[DOOR THUDS]
Oh, God. It's you.
You scared me.
Good.
Fear's our most primal emotion.
You left your door open.
I know.
I like to encourage intruders.
[LAUGHS]
What--? Uh...
What is all this?
Do you like it?
My home is a...shrine to you.
Where did you get
all these pictures?
I took them myself
with a telephoto lens.
Coming out
of your office,
your apartment,
shopping...
showering.
Sh-showering?
I developed them myself
in my darkroom.
Would you, uh...
Would you like to see?
In the darkroom?
Oh, uh, no, thank you.
Not right now.
♪ I'm a day person ♪
[CHUCKLES UNCOMFORTABLY]
Are--? Are you all right?
Why?
Well, I don't know.
You just don't, uh...
seem yourself.
Who am I?
Who am I supposed to be?
That's a good question.
Good question.
It's very, uh, existential.
Who are you? Who am I?
Yeah. Well...
What are you doing here?
Oh, nothing.
I just, uh...
stopped by to chat.
You know, shoot the breeze.
Were you able to get
those opera tickets
to Pagliacci
from that friend of yours?
I'm really
looking forward to it.
Oh, uh...
no, he couldn't get them.
We're not going.
Really?
Ooh, damn it!
You know,
I just remembered I gotta go.
I, uh...left something on--
the gas, the lights,
the water in the tub.
Something is on somewhere,
so I'm just
gonna get the, uh...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Do you know the story
of Pagliacci, Nedda?
Uh, I'm Elaine.
He's a clown whose wife
is unfaithful to him.
Oh.
Do you think I'm a clown...
Nedda?
Do I think you're a clown?
No!
Not if it's bad to be a clown.
If it's bad to be a clown,
then you are definitely
not a clown.
But if it's good to be a clown,
then I would, you know,
have to rethink the whole thing.
You've betrayed me
with another,
haven't you, Nedda?
Who is he? I want you
to tell me who he is.
I want his name.
Tell me his name.
Ooh, like any man
would ever look at me.
Come on.
I'm gonna...
get out of here.
Pagliacci kills his wife.
See? Now,
that's terrible.
That is, uh...
That's not a nice thing
to do at all.
You know, I would assume--
Um, I don't know
how this Pagliacci thing
actually turns out--
But, I mean, I would assume
that there was big, big trouble
for that clown.
You're not leaving.
[SPRAY HISSES]
Ow! Ooh!
[CRASHING]
But, officer, he threatened me!
I don't understand!
That's not right!
What if it was the president
of the United States?
I'd bet you'd investigate.
Well, so, what's the difference?
I'm a comedian
of the United States...
and I'll tell you,
I'm under just as much pressure.
All right. Thanks anyway.
Okay. Bye.
[DOORKNOB TURNS,
KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who is it?
It's George.
What, are you
locking the door now?
Yeah.
Well, well. Look at you.
It's a little skimpy,
there, isn't it?
You know the last time
I wore this thing?
Six years ago.
When I made that toast
at Bobby Leighton's wedding?
Ooh, that was a bad toast.
It wasn't that bad.
I never heard anybody
curse in a toast.
I was trying to loosen
them up a little bit.
There were
old people there.
All the relatives.
You were like
a Redd Foxx record.
I mean, at the end of the toast,
nobody even drank.
They were just standing there--
They were just frozen.
People were...
That might have been
one of the worst
all-time toasts.
All right, still,
her father didn't have
to throw me out like that.
He could've just
asked me to leave.
The guy had me in a headlock.
Susan's not going tonight,
you know.
What do you mean,
not going? Why not?
She had to pick up
a friend of hers
at the airport.
It cost me $100,
this ticket.
Why didn't she pay for hers?
That's a very
good question.
You know, she and I
go out to dinner,
she doesn't even
reach for the check.
That's all I'm asking for
is a reach.
Is that so much to ask for?
It's nice to get a reach.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Oh! Ow!
Who is it?
KRAMER: It's me!
Why are you locking
the door now?
Because of Davola.
Get in here.
What the--?
How come
you're not dressed?
I am dressed.
You're going like this?
Yeah, yeah. Hey, I want you
to hear something.
I thought you said
people dress up
when they go
to the opera.
Well, people do. I don't.
If you're going like that,
I'm not going like this.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
Do you think
I'm comfortable here?
I can't change.
I got no clothes here.
You gotta go like that!
I can't go like this alone!
Why should I be uncomfortable
just because my apartment's
closer to Town Hall than yours?
That's not the issue.
We're friends!
If I'm gonna be uncomfortable,
you gotta be uncomfortable too!
All right, all right,
I'll wear this!
Bad enough
I gotta go to the opera,
I gotta sit next
to Ozzie Nelson over here.
[OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
Would you turn that down?
What is that crap?
It's Pagliacci.
Oh, beautiful.
Listen, we got
a little problem here.
We got two extra tickets.
Why, what happened?
Well, Susan isn't going,
and Elaine
just left me a message,
her friend isn't going either.
That's fantastic.
We'll scalp the tickets.
We could make maybe,
uh...500 a ticket.
What, really?
Oh, yeah.
What, people are looking
for tickets here?
Are you kidding?
Opening night?
Pavarotti in Pagliacci?
[LAUGHING]
We're gonna clean up!
Oh, man, I knew
I was gonna love the opera!
Oh, yeah, right.
Come on, let's go
get the tickets. All right.
All right, listen,
I gotta wait for Elaine.
You guys go, I'll meet you
in front of the theater.
Now, wait.
Isn't scalping illegal?
Oh, yeah.
[MAN SINGING ARIA
FROM "PAGLIACCI" IN ITALIAN]
You sprayed him
in the eyes
with Binaca?
Cherry Binaca.
It's new.
See, I don't get that.
First, they come out
with the regular.
A year later, they have cherry.
They know we like cherry.
Start with cherry.
Then come out with the regular.
It was like
I didn't even know him.
He was like
a totally different person.
You should hear
the message from my nut.
Where's George
and Kramer?
I don't like
standing out here.
I want to get
inside already.
I feel very vulnerable.
[COIN CLINKS ON SIDEWALK]
Hey. Hey,
what are you doing?
That's my quarter.
No, it's not. It's mine.
I was just flipping it.
That's mine.
No, I dropped it.
It's mine.
You want the quarter,
take the quarter,
but don't try and tell me
it's yours.
Well, it is mine.
What, you think I care
about the money?
Is that what you think?
You want me to show you?
Here, look. Look at this.
Here's a dollar. Look.
There. That's how much
I care about money. There.
Think I care
about money?
That's how much
I care about money.
Why don't you get lost?
Because I was standing here,
that's why.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
I kind of like
this opera crowd.
I feel tough.
Anybody else
got a problem?
Hey, clown!
Clown.
Make us laugh,
clown.
Nice face, clown.
Make me laugh, clown.
[GRUNTING]
[MOANING]
I got two.
I got two, huh?
Pagliacci, huh?
Who needs Pagliacci, huh?
Come on,
the great tragic clown.
Come on, check it out.
He laughs, he cries, he sings.
Pagliacci.
Hey, I got two beauties
right here.
Come on, fella,
check it out, huh?
All right.
Hey, hey, you selling?
Oh, I'm selling.
Where are they?
Orchestra. Row G.
Dead center. Primo.
You'll think you died
and went to heaven.
What do you
want for them?
I'll tell you what I'll do,
because you look like
a nice guy.
A thousand dollars
for the deuce.
Uh, give you
500 for the pair.
Yeah. It's a deal.
Boop. No.
What? No?
Are you crazy?
Look, let me handle this.
That's $500.
That's a great deal.
You're blowing it.
The guy's a pigeon.
Ah...
Oh, God, see, he's walking away.
What is wrong with you?
That was a $300 profit!
You know, I know
what I'm doing here, George.
Look, this is not
a Metallica concert,
it's an opera,
all right?
A little dignity.
A little class.
Just give me my ticket.
I will stand over here
and sell it. Oh, yeah.
Thank you very much.
You just stand over there,
I'll stand over here.
I know where I'm standing.
All right.
Get your Pagliaccis here!
Come on, Pagliaccis
right here, huh?
Where are they already?
I guarantee you
they don't sell either one
of those tickets.
Hey, look,
there's Bobby Leighton's
father-in-law.
Mr. Reichman. George and I
were just talking about him.
That's the guy who threw George
out of the wedding.
Oh, yeah. When George
made that bad toast?
You remember
the curse toast?
Oh, yeah. The curse toast.
So can you believe
that message?
Now I gotta spend
the rest of my life
looking over my shoulder.
Me too.
Crazy Joe Davola...
How do you
know his name?
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't I know his name?
I never told you his name.
Wait a second,
who are we talking about here?
Joe Davola.
Right, Joe Davola.
How do you know his name?
I've been out with him
three times.
I should know the man's name.
Oh, my God!
He's stalking you?
You're going out with a madman
who's trying to kill me?
Oh, Jerry,
why didn't you tell me
his name was Joe Davola?
Why didn't you tell me?
Last night, he accused me
of seeing someone else.
He said, "Tell me his name!"
He said that?
If he sees me with you,
can you imagine what he'll do?
If he thinks I ruined
his NBC deal and stole his girl!
That will be a kibosh for sure.
What about me?
MAN: Excuse me.
[SCREAMING]
Come on. This is Pavarotti.
Three hundred dollars?
That's a lot of money.
You know, Steven Holtzman
did a production
in Tunis last year,
and from what I understand,
the Muslims really took to it.
I'll tell you what,
you seem like a nice guy.
Let's stop jerking around
here, all right?
Give me...$250.
I got people waiting for me.
I gotta get
the hell out of here.
They're scalping!
I told them
to put out extra security.
Excuse me.
Pop, would you buzz off?
I got something cooking here.
Costanza?
Mr. Reichman?
You've still got
a mouth like a sewer!
Give me those tickets.
Harold, don't!
Harold, be careful
of your hair transplant!
Anything is welcome.
I accept...change.
I don't have anything.
I gave it to that guy.
You know,
you could just say no.
You don't have
to humiliate me.
I may be dressed as a clown,
but I am a person.
No, I'm telling you,
the guy took my--
And I don't need
people like you
looking down
their noses at me.
I am just a street
performer out here,
trying to make
enough to get by.
Doctor!
Is there a doctor anywhere?
We need a doctor!
What are you, showing off
for your girlfriend?
Is that it?
Uh, I'm not
his girlfriend.
We dated for a while,
but things didn't work out.
You people make me sick.
That is one angry clown.
The hardest part
about being a clown,
it seems to me,
would be that you're constantly
referred to as a clown.
"Who is that clown?"
"I'm not working
with that clown."
"Did you hire that clown?"
"The guy's a clown."
How do you start into
being a clown?
How do you know
you wanna be a clown?
I mean, I guess
you just get to a point
where your pants look so bad,
it's actually easier
to become a clown
than having
the proper alterations done.
Because if you think about it,
a clown,
if there isn't
a circus around them,
is really just
a very annoying person.
I mean, you're in the back seat
of this guy's Volkswagen.
"What, you're picking
somebody else up?
Oh, man!"
I got one. Who needs one?
Pagliacci. Pagliacci.
The tragic clown...
Paglia...cci.
What did you say?
What, are you a cop?
No, I'm a clown.
Man, you look familiar.
You ever been to the circus?
Well, when I was a kid.
Did you like it?
Well, you know, it was fun.
I was kind of scared
of the clowns.
Are you still scared
of clowns?
Yeah.
We're gonna miss
the overture.
♪ Overture
Curtains, lights ♪
♪ This is it
We'll hit the heights ♪
♪ And, oh, what heights
We'll hit ♪
♪ On with the show
This is it ♪
You know, it is so sad.
All your knowledge
of high culture
comes from Bugs Bunny cartoons.
Oh, there's that clown again.
What does he want from me?
Look, I'm serious,
I'm not kidding.
I don't have the quarter.
That guy took it.
I don't want any money.
[ELAINE SNIFFS]
Huh?
I smell cherry.
It's Binaca.
Binaca?
[SINGING OPERA IN ITALIAN]
[GASPS, SCREAMS]
Go! Go!
What did we say, 275 here?
250.
250?
Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure.
All right, all right. 250.
SUSAN: George!
S-Susan.
I don't believe it!
I'm so glad I caught you!
Yeah...
What are you doing here?
I thought you were going
to the airport.
Oh, there was some problem
with the plane.
They landed in Philadelphia.
Well, so what?
They don't have another plane?
She couldn't take a bus?
She's coming in tomorrow,
but I made it.
Yeah, you made it.
How about that?
Oh, I'm so excited.
Now we get to see
the opera together.
We get to go to
the opera--
[WHISPERS]
Get out of here.
Together.
Who's that?
Oh, that's--
That's Harry Fong.
He's a very good
friend of mine.
He's a big opera buff.
Enjoy the show,
there, Harry!
Come on. Let's go.
You know what?
Come on,
you gotta let us in.
Not without tickets.
We have tickets,
we just don't have them with us.
Well, that's a problem.
Um, excuse me.
Come right in.
You don't understand.
Someone's after us!
A crazy clown.
He's trying to kill us.
A crazy clown is after you?
Yes.
Oh, that's rich.
Now, clear the entrance
so people with tickets
can get through.
Oh, hey, we're with him.
We're with him!.
Are you guys ready?
Yes, yes!
Have you seen George?
We thought he was with you.
Come on,
he's on his own.
Come on!
Okay, here.
Here I come.
These are
great seats, huh?
Yeah.
Boy, some cast, huh?
Pavarotti, Eva Marton.
Eva Marton.
I've heard of her.
Who's she playing?
She's playing
Pagliacci's wife Nedda.
Nedda?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Susan, what are you
doing here?
My friend's flight
couldn't make it.
Hi.
Where's George?
I got his ticket.
He decided
not to come.
He said he was
uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable?
How do you think I feel?
Hey, let me
ask you something.
How much did you pay
for that ticket?
One seventy-five.
Oh...
Kramer, who did you
sell your ticket to?
Some nut
in a clown suit.
[APPLAUSE]
I had some friends drag me
to an opera recently.
They all got those little
opera glasses, you know?
Do you really need binoculars?
I mean, how big
do these people have to get
before you can spot them?
I mean, these opera kids,
they're going 250, 280, 325.
They're wearing big white
woolly vests with--
The women have, like,
the breastplates,
the bullet hats,
the horns coming out.
If you can't pick
these people out,
forget opera,
think about optometry.
Maybe that's--
Maybe that's more your thing.
[MAN SINGING ARIA
FROM "PAGLIACCI" IN ITALIAN]