I am getting a little tired
of pretending I'm excited
every time
it's somebody's birthday.
You know what I mean?
What is the big deal?
How many times
do we have to celebrate
that someone was born?
Every year. Over and over.
All you did
was not die for 12 months.
That's all you've done,
as far as I could tell.
Those astrology things,
where they tell you
all the people
that have
the same birthday as you...
It's always an odd group
of people, too, isn't it?
It's like, Ed Asner,
Elijah Mohammed,
and Secretariat.
I don't want to live.
I don't want to live!
Because of me?
You must be joking.
Who wouldn't want to live
because of me?
I'm nothing.
No. You're something.
You can do better than me.
You could throw a dart
out the window
and hit someone
better than me.
I'm no good.
You're good.
I'm bad, I'm bad.
You're killing me!
So what could I do?
I couldn't
go through with it.
She threatened
to kill herself.
Over you?
Yes. Why?
Is that so inconceivable?
Well...
JERRY: I'm trying to get
reach with Sharon Leonard.
She works for the N.Y.U. paper.
This is Jerry Seinfeld.
She was supposed to meet me
to do an interview.
Oh, what are you
gonna get Jerry
for his birthday?
I got him a great gift.
Really? What?
I got two tickets
to see Guys and Dolls.
Oh, that is
a good gift.
Maybe he'll take me.
No. I'm going to go with him.
GEORGE:
What did you get him?
I got him a two-line phone.
Yeah, that's good.
Unbelievable.
She's not there.
What paper
does she write for?
She works for
the N.Y.U. school newspaper.
She's a grad student
in journalism.
Never been to
a comedy club.
Never even seen me.
No idea who I am.
Never even seen you?
Got to kind of envy that.
You know,
you've been developing
quite the acid tongue
lately.
Really?
Hey, who do you think
is the most
unattractive world leader?
Living or all-time?
All-time.
Well, if it's all-time,
then there's no contest.
It begins and ends
with Brezhnev.
I don't know.
You ever get a good look
at De Gaulle?
Lyndon Johnson was
uglier than De Gaulle.
I got news for you.
Golda Meir could make them all
run up a tree.
Golda Meir.
Good one.
[SOFTLY]
Hey. Come here. Come here.
Those two girls
behind you--
They're eavesdropping on us.
Really?
You know, uh,
just because you two
are homosexuals, so what?
ELAINE: You should just
come out of the closet
and be openly gay already.
So what do you say?
You know
you'll always be
the only man
I'll ever love.
What's the matter
with you?
Come on,
go along.
I'm not going along.
I could just see you
in Berlin in 1939,
goose-stepping past me.
"Come on, Jerry.
Go along, go along."
You're no fun.
You know,
I hear that all the time.
Hear what?
That I'm gay. People think I'm gay.
Yeah, people ask me
that about you too.
Yeah, because I'm single,
I'm thin and I'm neat.
And you get along well
with women.
I guess that leaves me
in the clear.
Hi, Jerry, it's Sharon Leonard
from the N.Y.U. paper.
I'm here at the coffee shop,
and I was a little late.
I guess we must have
missed each other.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Yeah.
Me, too.
SHARON: I'll be here
a little while longer,
and I'll try
to hook up with you later.
Hey.
I just thought
of a great name for myself
if I ever become
a porno actor.
Oh, yeah, what?
Buck Naked?
Yeah. How did you know that?
You told me that already,
like, two months ago.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think of this shirt?
Well...
Uh...
Allison bought it for me.
How are you going to
get out of that one?
I don't know.
I guess I have to wait
for her to die.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
[OVER INTERCOM] It's Sharon from N.Y.U.
Come on up.
Who's that?
Oh, that's that
reporter from N.Y.U.
She's finally going
to do the interview.
I told her to come up here
so we wouldn't miss each other.
Uh, do you want me to stay, or--
Sure. I don't care.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi.
Hi. I'm--I'm Sharon.
Hi. I'm Jerry.
Something the matter?
No, no, no, nothing.
You look familiar.
Have we ever met?
I'm--I'm not sure. Have we?
You look familiar.
Why don't we
do this over here?
This is George.
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
He's going
to hang around,
if that's
all right with you.
Sure. I'd like
to talk to him, too.
Oh.
Really?
Okay.
Well...
Okay, here we go.
GEORGE:
Uh-oh.
Oh,
is that a problem?
No.
I just hate my voice on tape.
It always sounds
so high and whiny.
Shall we start?
Fire away.
Okay, let's see.
Um, are you just a comedian,
or do you do anything else?
Uh, well, right now,
George and I
are writing a pilot
for N.B.C.
Oh, so you also work together?
Yeah.
Jerry, did you wash this pear?
Yeah, I washed it.
It looks like
it hasn't been washed.
So wash it.
You hear the way he talks to me?
You should hear
how my boyfriend talks to me.
What?
GEORGE:
Let me, uh--
Let me
ask you something.
What do you think
of this shirt?
It's nice.
Jerry said he didn't like it.
I didn't say
I didn't like it.
I said it was okay.
Oh, you said
you didn't like it.
Oh, well, so what
if I don't like it?
Is that, like, the end
of the world or something?
So how did you two meet?
Oh, actually, we met
in the gym locker room.
Yeah.
Actually, it was
in gym class.
I was trying
to climb the ropes,
and Jerry
was spotting me,
and, uh,
I kept slipping
and burning my thighs,
and then,
finally,
I slipped and I fell
on Jerry's head.
We've been close
ever since.
Do you guys live together?
Live together?
No. I got
my own place.
Oh, and do your parents know?
Know what?
My parents?
They don't know
what's going on.
Oh, God. You're that girl
in the coffee shop
that was
eavesdropping on us.
I knew
you looked familiar.
Oh, no! No!
I, uh, better get going.
There's been a big
misunderstanding here.
We did that whole thing
for your benefit.
We knew
you were eavesdropping.
That's why my friend
said all that.
It was on purpose.
We're not gay.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
No,
of course not.
I mean, it's fine
if that's who you are.
Absolutely.
I mean, I have many gay friends.
My father's gay.
Look, I--
I know what I heard.
Heard?
It was a joke.
All right, look.
Do you wanna have sex right now?
Do you wanna have sex
with me right now? Let's go!
Come on,
let's go, baby!
Come on!
Hey, come on,
let's go.
I thought we were
going to take a steam.
No steam.
No, I don't wanna steam.
Well, I don't wanna
sit there naked all by myself.
You know, the whole thing
is your fault.
You want me
to talk to her?
I'd be perfectly willing
to talk to her.
I don't think so.
Because you know me.
I walk into a room,
problem's solved.
She says she's gonna
think about it.
Well, so what?
Even if it does come out,
it'll just be in
an N.Y.U. paper.
Why don't you
take your jacket off?
Nah. I'm okay.
I'm gonna
try her again.
Happy birthday! "Faruba!"
Today's not my birthday.
Well, I beg to differ.
Well, I think I know
when my birthday is.
Yeah, well, you'd think so,
but you'd be wrong.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe it is my birthday.
Would you take the jacket off?
Leave me alone.
Get off my back
about the jacket.
Oh, look at this,
a phone!
Yeah.
A two-line phone!
That's terrific.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Now when someone's talking,
I can still make a call.
Look, Elaine,
a two-line phone.
Yeah. I see it.
I'm going to
get one myself.
JERRY:
Where are you going?
I got to go return something.
I got a dial tone.
Okay, this is
the maiden call. Yeah.
Oh, wait. I want to get
the first call, all right?
All right, go to your house.
I'll call you.
Ha, ha!
[RINGING TONE]
KRAMER:
Hello.
Hello. Hey, it's working.
This is great. Thanks a lot.
Happy birthday,
buddy.
Oh, wait,
I got a call on the other line.
Okay, later.
All right,
I'll talk to you later.
Hello?
Jerry, it's Sharon
from N.Y.U.
Oh, hi.
I was just calling
to tell you
I won't play up that angle
we talked about on the story.
Oh, thank you very much.
That's great.
[TELEPHONE CLICKS]
Hold on a second.
I got a call on the other line.
Hello?
GEORGE:
Hey.
Hey, how you doing?
You know, I got that reporter
from the newspaper
on the other line.
So what did she say?
She said she's not going to
play up that angle on the story.
She thinks we're heterosexual.
I guess we fooled her.
Yeah.
All right, I'll get rid of her.
Hold on.
Sharon?
Hello?
Sharon, are you there?
I'm back.
GEORGE:
You know,
I could hear you
on the other line.
What are you talking about?
I heard what you said:
"Sharon, are you there?"
You heard me talking
on the other line?
Are you sure?
Yes, I heard you.
Well, maybe
she was disconnected.
Maybe she wasn't.
Maybe she heard
the whole conversation.
All right, hang on.
Let me call Kramer,
and see if you can
hear anything.
Hold on.
[RINGING TONE]
KRAMER:
Hello.
Kramer, there may be a problem
with the phone. Hold on.
GEORGE:
There may be a problem with the phone. Hold on.
Oh, no!
Kramer, this phone's
a piece of junk. Goodbye.
GEORGE:
This phone's a piece of junk! Goodbye!
Oh, no!
Now she's heard everything!
What are we gonna do?
Now she thinks
we're gay.
Not that there's
anything wrong with it.
No, no, of course not.
People's personal
sexual preferences
are nobody's business
but their own!
Hi.
Elaine, right?
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for
meeting with me.
Sure. Would you like
to take a seat?
Sure. Thank you.
Why don't you
take your coat off?
ELAINE:
So she kept insisting I take off my coat.
I refused,
and then she forcibly tried
to get me to remove it.
She didn't take her coat off
in my house either.
You know,
there are tribes in Indonesia
where, if you keep your coat on
in somebody's house,
the families go to war.
Oh, give me
a break.
So you don't
take your coat off,
and now everyone at N.Y.U.
thinks I'm gay.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
Not at all.
Take that coat off!
Take it off! Get it off!
[CLAMORING]
Anyway, when are we
going to see it?
I'd like to read the article.
They're sending it to me.
All right.
Well, here you go.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Two tickets to Guys and Dolls.
I'm going to go with you.
Guys and Dolls?
Isn't that
a lavish Broadway musical?
It's Guys and Dolls,
not Guys and Guys.
Yeah, you're right.
Guys and Dolls.
Thanks, thanks very much.
All right.
All right, well...
Happy birthday.
Oh, Lainey!
The Collected Works
of Bette Midler.
What? I--
I thought you
liked Bette Midler.
Well, she's all right.
You said
you liked her.
Well, so what?
Maybe I do like her.
So what?
So nothing.
Well, thanks for the CDs.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
Why are
those two people
pointing at you
over there?
I don't know.
What do you
got there?
Oh, the New York Post.
They've got
an article about you.
"Although they maintain
separate residences,
"the comedian
and his longtime companion
seem to be inseparable."
Oh, no. The Associated Press
picked up the N.Y.U. story.
That's going to be
in every paper.
I've been outed!
I wasn't even in!
Now everyone's going
to think we're gay!
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
No, not at all.
"Within the confines
"of his fastidious
bachelor pad,
"Seinfeld
and Costanza bicker
"over the cleanliness
of a piece of fruit
like an old
married couple."
I told you
that pear was washed!
[SIGHS]
I thought we were friends.
Here we go.
How could you two
keep this a secret from me?
It's not true.
Ah! Enough lying.
The lying
is through.
Come on, Jerry.
The masquerade is over.
You're thin,
late 30s, single.
So are you.
Yeah.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
OLD WOMAN:
George?
Mrs. Seinfeld?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Ma?
Jerry?
Ma!
Oh, my God!
My mother!
Jerry...
Ma, it's not true.
It's those damn
culottes
you made him wear
when he was 5.
MRS. SEINFELD:
They weren't culottes,
they were shorts.
MR. SEINFELD:
They were culottes!
You bought them
in the girls' department.
By mistake.
By mistake, Jerry.
I'm sorry.
It looked like
he was wearing a skirt,
for crying out loud.
Ma, it has nothing to do
with the culottes.
Not that there's
anything wrong
with that, Jerry.
I open up the paper,
and this is what
I have to read about?
I fell right off the toilet.
My back went out again.
I couldn't move.
The super
had to come and help me up.
I was half-naked!
It's not true.
Every day
it's something else with you.
I don't know
anything about you anymore.
Who are you?
What kind of life
are you leading?
Who knows
what you're doing?
Maybe you're
making porno films.
Yeah.
I'm Buck Naked.
Who?
Buck Naked?
Jerry, I can see.
He's so neat and thin.
Not that
there's anything wrong with it.
Of course not.
6:30, Scott.
Time for your sponge bath.
SCOTT:
Oh, 6:30 already?
I fell asleep.
NURSE:
Let me help you off with that.
Here, I'll just
slip it over your head.
All right.
NURSE:
Water's nice and warm, isn't it?
SCOTT:
Oh... that feels really good.
George, are you
telling me the truth?
George,
I'm talking to you!
Hey, you'll never guess
who left a message
on my machine.
That reporter from N.Y.U.
I wonder what she wants.
GEORGE:
All right.
Now the play
is tomorrow night.
Would you like to have dinner
first, or just meet there?
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I want you to know it took guts
to come out how you did,
and that you've inspired me
to do the same,
even though that may mean
a discharge from the service.
Thanks.
You know, I think I'll pass
on the Guys and Dolls.
GEORGE: All right,
fine. Don't go.
I try and go out
and do something special
for your birthday,
and this is
the thanks I get!
Everything's tainted now.
Would you keep your voice down?
No, I will not
keep my voice down!
Nothing can make me
If you boys...
cannot control
yourselves...
Then I'm afraid
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave.
[WHISPERING]
Fine, I'll take Elaine.
Yes!
Just don't say
anything to Allison.
No, I won't.
Did she see
the article?
No. I can just
imagine her reaction.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
What?
She hasn't
seen the article.
When she sees it,
she's going to think...
I'm out, baby!
I'm out!
Yeah? So?
Well, this is nice.
They mention your name.
Don't you see
what it says here?
Don't you understand
what that's implying?
No. What?
I'm gay!
I'm a gay man!
I'm very, very gay.
You're gay?
Extraordinarily gay.
Steeped in gayness.
I don't believe it.
All right.
You don't believe me?
Ask Jerry.
I will.
What do you mean, you will?
No, no, no, no.
That's a bad idea.
Jerry's a very private person.
I want to hear it
from Jerry.
Oh,
can you ever forgive me?
I don't know.
All right,
I forgive you.
Mm.
You know,
the funny thing is,
I was attracted to you
immediately.
I was attracted to you too.
You remind me of Lois Lane.
Jerry, oh my God!
What are you doing?
What?
You're with a woman!
I know. What are you doing here?
I leave you alone
for two seconds,
and this is
what you do?
I trusted you!
Would you get the hell
out of here?
What's going on?
Yeah.
All right, tell her.
Go ahead.
Tell her what?
You know, about us.
Are you crazy?
Tell her, Jerry.
Tell her.
I'm not telling her
nothing!
Do you have any idea
what you're saying?
This is too weird.
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute,
wait a minute!
You wrote the article.
Go ahead, tell her.
I'm out of here.
It's not true!
Not that there's anything
wrong with that!
You stupid idiot!
Oh, please,
don't be upset.
Oh, would you
stop it with that stuff?
What's going on?
All right, I'll
tell you the truth.
I'm not gay.
My name's Buck Naked.
I'm a porno actor.
Really?
Oh, my God.
Hey.
How you doing?
Hello.
Hi.
How are you?
All right,
we'll see you later.
He's the phone man.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
I am not gay.
I am, however,
thin, single and neat.
Sometimes if someone's thin,
single and neat,
people assume they are gay,
because that is the stereotype.
You normally don't think
of gay people
as fat, sloppy and married.
Although I'm sure there are.
I don't want to
perpetuate the stereotype.
I'm sure they're the minority,
though,
within the gay community.
Probably discriminated against.
Because of that,
people say to them,
"You know, Joe,
I enjoy being gay with you,
"but it's about time, you know,
you got in shape,
tucked your shirt in,
and lost the wife."
But if people
are going to assume
that people that are neat
are gay,
maybe instead of doing this:
"You know, I think Joe
might be a little..."
They should vacuum.
"You know,
I think Joe might be..."
[IMITATES VACUUM]
Yeah.
"I got a feeling
he's a little..."
[IMITATES VACUUM]