So I went to a fashion show.
First of all,
the whole concept of modeling
is counterproductive
to the fashion industry,
because when these women
are around,
who's looking at clothes?
I didn't notice
any of the clothes.
We're all applauding. "Yeah!"
What are we applauding?
We're applauding, "There's
great-looking women here.
Yeah, this is great!"
We're applauding,
"I'm glad I'm here in this room
with all these
great-looking women."
Anybody can design a shirt.
It takes talent to get
all these girls in one spot.
That's talent.
What is this goofy walk
that the models do?
You know this walk that they do
down the runway.
This, like--
They have to go somewhere.
You know, they're walking
like they're--
Like they're really on the way
somewhere, you know?
And then they get to the end,
and it's like...
"Well, I guess
I'll just go back."
I loved her, Jerry.
I loved her.
No, you didn't.
And she loved me.
Oh, ho, ho. She really did.
No, she didn't.
What am I gonna do now?
I can't live without Susan.
I gotta get her back.
How? How am I gonna
get her back?
ELAINE:
Not only didn't you love her,
you didn't even
like her.
Who says?
You did!
Ah.
A beautiful, successful,
intelligent woman's
in love with me,
and I throw it
all away.
Oh, ho, ho, boy!
Now I'll spend
the rest of my life
living alone.
I'll sit in my disgusting
little apartment,
watching basketball games,
eating Chinese takeout,
walking around
with no underwear
'cause I'm too lazy
to do a laundry.
You walk around
with no underwear?
Yeah. What do you do
when you run out of laundry?
I do a wash.
Who am I gonna meet
that's better than her?
No one, Jerry.
No one's better than her.
When you were with her,
you said you couldn't stand her.
I loved her!
You said going up the steps
to her apartment
was like being taken to a cell.
I would give anything to be
going up those stairs again.
I got to call her.
Should I call her?
George, I don't know
if that's such a good idea.
Why?
You need some
professional advice.
Why don't you
go see Elaine's friend?
She's a therapist.
I'm not going to see that nut
doctor she went to Europe with.
No, no. Elaine, what's the name
of that friend of yours
that's a therapist?
The woman.
Dana Foley.
Right.
She any good?
Yeah, she's terrific.
Why, are you thinking of going?
[MUTTERING]
Tia? Who's that?
It's that model
I met on the plane.
She sent you
a Christmas card?
Mm-hmm.
And we're going out
Saturday night.
My darling Susan.
My darling!
What are you doing?
Date with Fred.
The religious guy?
He's not that religious.
Let us pray.
Hey, you got any Double Crunch?
Yeah.
Kramer, should I call Susan?
Now, what does the little man
inside you say?
See, you got to listen
to the little man.
My little man doesn't know.
The little man
knows all.
My little man's an idiot.
Say, she was clever. You know?
She put her picture on her card.
I should do that.
I never do anything like that.
You want a picture on a
Christmas card? I can do that.
She kept such a nice,
clean apartment.
She was so sanitary.
No. I was just
thinking out loud.
I don't want
my picture on a card.
No, no, I'll take
your picture.
I'll take care
of everything.
She made a big breakfast
every Sunday.
I don't know
what she put in those eggs.
All right,
if you come on over,
I'll have my cereal,
and I'll take
your picture.
Really? Can you really
take a picture?
Yeah, he's good.
He takes good pictures.
He's got equipment over there.
All right.
Yeah.
I don't know about
that outfit, though.
Why, what's wrong
with it?
Well, we'll have to
improvise.
♪ Oh, hey ♪
♪ If you happen to see ♪
♪ The most beautiful girl ♪
♪ Who walked out on me ♪
♪ Tell her I'm sorry ♪
♪ Tell her
I need my baby ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Won't you tell her ♪
♪ That I love her? ♪
♪ Oh, hey-- ♪
George.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
So I'm thinking
of putting in
a tropical fish tank
right here.
Are you sure you're ready
for that kind of commitment?
Well, I figure,
if it doesn't work out,
I can always flush 'em
down the toilet.
That's horrible.
What's that perfume
you're wearing?
Oh, I completely forgot.
I want you to see this.
That Calvin Klein ad
I was telling you about
came out today.
What is that smell?
It's here somewhere.
It smells
like the beach.
Exactly.
Oh, my God. Is that
the new perfume?
Yeah.
I can't
believe this!
My next-door neighbor
had the idea for this exact
perfume last year.
He even met
with an executive
at Calvin Klein.
I can't believe
they stole his idea.
Are you sure?
And you're the model
for this perfume?
[KRAMER'S DOOR CLOSES]
Uh, that's him.
He just came home.
Oh, the door.
Hey.
Hey, man.
How you doing?
Ooh...
Yeah, um...
Yeah, I'll--
I'll see you later.
I just wanted to borrow
your DustBuster.
All right, come on in.
Just wait over here.
What?
Just wait here,
and I'll get it for you.
Kramer,
this is Tia.
Hello.
Hi.
How tall are you?
5'10".
Well, let's see.
Come on,
back-to-back.
No, Kramer!
What's the matter
with you?
I just wanted to see
how tall she was!
Oh, you're tall.
She's tall. I'm tall.
What's the difference
who's tall? We're all tall.
Hey, what's that?
What?
That smell.
What's that smell?
What smell?
[TURNS ON DUSTBUSTER]
It's very familiar.
I can't put my finger on it.
Very familiar.
Oh, they're all the same.
Here. Now, if you'll
excuse us.
Yeah, okay. So I'll
see you tomorrow, huh? Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
And nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you too.
[WHIRS DUSTBUSTER]
Yeah, I'll see you later.
Whew! That was close.
[KRAMER'S DOOR CLOSES]
The beach!
You smell like the beach!
What's the name of that
perfume you're wearing?
It's Ocean
by Calvin Klein.
Calvin Klein?
No, no, that's my idea.
The-they stole my idea.
See, I had the idea
of a cologne
that makes you smell like
you just came from the beach.
I know.
Look at this.
[GASPS]
That's you!
What is going on here?
D'Giff, he laughs at me,
then he steals my idea!
I could have been
a millionaire.
I could have been a fragrance
millionaire, Jerry.
They're not gonna
get away with this.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hello, George.
Come in, come in.
I've heard an awful
lot about you.
Please, sit down.
Well, hello.
Uh, specifically
the reason that I'm here--
I don't know
what Elaine told you--
but, um, I-I broke up
with my girlfriend
a couple of weeks ago.
Actually, she broke up with me,
and, uh--
Well, I-I was the cause of it--
And, uh, I just wanted to
find out from you...
What's with this thing?
So, uh, she broke up with you...
Yeah, and...
Why won't this go down?
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
So why did she
break up with you?
What is with this damn zipper?
It doesn't matter.
You'll fix it later.
Tell me about your girlfriend.
It's stuck on a piece
of cloth, here.
I can't get
the cloth out.
It doesn't matter--
Well, this is
a brand-new jacket.
Boy, this really
burns me up.
George. George,
look at me.
Okay. Forget about the zipper.
[SNORTS WITH LAUGHTER]
What's your girlfriend's name?
Susan.
Okay, we're getting somewhere.
[CHUCKLES]
It's just so frustrating.
It's a brand-new jacket,
for crying out loud.
Anyway, so Fred and I are
gonna do some volunteer work
for that church
on Amsterdam.
Oh, volunteer work.
See, that's what I love
about the holiday season.
That's the true spirit
of Christmas.
People being helped
by people other than me.
That makes me feel good inside.
Oh, look at what we have here,
a Christmas card from Lainey.
Thank you.
Why, you didn't have to go
to that trouble.
Oh, it was no trouble.
My assistant did
the whole thing.
I didn't even see the picture.
How is it?
Oh, you know,
it's a picture.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Looks good.
Kramer did a good job.
Yeah, well, I mean, how hard
is it to take a picture?
Hmm.
What?
Did you look
at this picture carefully?
Carefully?
Because I'm not sure,
and correct me if I'm wrong...
but I think I see a nipple.
What?
Here, take a look.
Wh-what is that?
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
That's my nipple!
That's what I thought.
My nipple's exposed!
I sent this card
to hundreds of people!
My parents, my boss--
[GASPS]
Nana and Papa.
Didn't you look at
the picture?
Oh, God,
I didn't notice.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
You know, your whole life,
you go through painstaking
efforts to hide your nipple,
and then, boom!
Suddenly,
hundreds of people
get their own
personal shot of it!
Hey...
Have you seen
the card?
What card?
My Christmas card.
Uh, well, yeah.
Yeah, of course. I took it.
Well, did you notice
anything unusual about it?
No.
Well, come here
and take a look.
Yeah, so?
So, what's that?
That's a nipple.
Right.
Ooh!
Oh, great.
Didn't you see that?
Uh, no. No,
I didn't notice it. Um...
It's because you made me wear
that stupid shirt.
Well, maybe
no one noticed it.
You didn't
notice it.
Let me go
get Newman.
We'll see if
he sees it.
No, I don't want
him looking!
Oh, what's the difference?
Everybody else you know has it.
Give me that.
Oh, my God. I sent one
to the super of my building,
my mailman--
[GASPS]
My 10-year-old
little nephew.
Sister Mary Catherine,
Father Chelios.
Oh, my God. Fred!
I sent one to Fred.
Okay, what is it?
Here...take a look
at this card.
Tell me if you notice
anything unusual about it.
Yeah, your nipple's showing.
Okay, thanks.
Anything else?
No.
All right.
See you later.
Oh, God...
What? So what?
It's a nipple.
It's a little, brown,
circular protuberance.
What's the big deal?
Hey, everybody's got 'em.
Look, I got 'em.
I got 'em too.
See?
Everybody's got 'em!
See, it's kind of got
a little piece of cloth
that's stuck
underneath and--
Well, can you pull it up
a little bit?
Ugh!
Well, here, you hold it.
Wait, hold it. Hold it.
Damn it, I can't move it.
God, I've never seen
a zipper so stubborn.
Damn it!
I almost had it.
Yeah. Okay. No, no, wait,
that'll separate it.
Take it right off
the track.
No, no, let me try.
You're gonna rip it!
Gahh!
Yah!
I'm afraid we're gonna
have to stop now.
Okay.
Uh, my mother is gonna
pay for the sessions.
Oh, is this Elaine?
Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
No!
No...
No. Oh, no.
I've called every day
for the past four days.
She hasn't returned
one call.
Was it a scratch...
or a pick?
It was a scratch.
Hey, it's me.
Don't you think
I know the difference
between a pick and a scratch?
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
It's me.
Come on up.
Was there any...
nostril penetration?
There may have been
some incidental penetration,
but from her angle,
she was in no position
to make the call.
So let's say, in her mind,
she witnessed a pick.
Okay, so then what?
Is that so unforgivable?
Is that like
breaking a commandment?
Did God say to Moses,
"Thou shall not pick"?
I guarantee you
Moses was a picker.
You wander through
the desert for 40 years
with that dry air...
You're telling me
you're not gonna have occasion
to clean house
a little, huh?
Let me ask you
something:
If you were going out
with somebody,
and she did that,
what would you do?
Would you continue
going out with her?
No, that's disgusting.
You cannot believe
what I am going through.
That card is plastered
all over the office.
Everybody's calling me "Nip."
Yeah. That's my new nickname
at the office. Nip!
These guys keep asking me
out for drinks.
Not only that, Fred, you know
the guy I told you about?
He hasn't called me
in three days.
Oh, hey...
Hey, how come I didn't
get a Christmas card?
Everybody else got one.
Jerry got one,
Kramer got one.
I thought
we were good friends.
I don't get a Christmas card.
I don't get it.
You want a Christmas card?
All right, here.
Here's your Christmas card.
You got any
Double Crunch?
Yeah,
I think I do.
[SNIFFING]
What's that perfume?
What?
It's the Ocean.
That's mine.
That's my smell!
Jerry, you gotta
get that model
to get me an appointment
with Calvin Klein!
I can't.
She won't return my calls
because she caught me
in a pick at a light.
I thought you said
it was a scratch.
But that's not what she thinks.
Hey, why don't you
call her agency?
Maybe she's been out of town
and didn't get the calls.
Get it.
All right.
I'll call the agency.
[DIALING TELEPHONE]
Hello.
Yes, I'm trying to get in touch
with Tia Van Camp.
Do you know
if she's been in town?
Oh, really?
Well, thank you very much.
She has been in town.
She's at Calvin Klein right now.
Let's go.
It'll be different
this time. I promise.
I promise difference.
I'm committed
to difference.
I need someone
a little more stable.
I'm not stable?
I'm like a rock.
I take these
glasses off,
you can't the difference
between me and a rock!
I put these glasses
on a rock,
you know what jumps into
most people's minds?
"Costanza!"
People don't change.
I change.
Two weeks ago,
I tried a soft-boiled egg.
Never liked it before.
Now, I'm dunking
a piece of toast in there
and I'm loving it!
I'm not a soft-boiled egg.
And I am not
a piece of toast.
I just don't think that
we have anything in common.
That's okay.
That's good.
You think Louis Pasteur
and his wife
had anything in common?
He was in the fields
all day
with the cows, you know,
and the milk,
examining the milk,
delving into milk,
consumed with milk,
pasteurization,
homogenization.
And she was
in the kitchen
killing cockroaches
with a boot on each hand.
Why were there
so many cockroaches?
Because there was a lot of cake
lying around the house,
just sitting there
with all the excess milk
from all the experiments.
And they got along?
Yes. Yes.
You know, she didn't know
about pasteurization,
he didn't know
about fumigation,
but they made it work.
WOMAN: You cannot go in there.
KRAMER: I wanna talk to Calvin!
Let me talk to Calvin!
I just want to talk to Calvin.
Kramer?
Oh, Tia. Hi.
Who are you?
I'm here to talk
about The Ocean.
Oh, yes, Kramer.
I think I know
something about this.
Would you
excuse us, Tia?
Yeah.
Now, I don't want
any trouble, Calvin.
Neither do I.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Hello.
There you are.
Hello. What are you
doing here?
Well, I had to
talk to you.
I noticed you haven't been
returning my calls.
Well...I've been busy.
Because I thought we had
a good time the other night,
and the only explanation
I could come up with
is that you think
that you caught me...
A pick.
I'd rather not
talk about this.
I was clearly on the outer edge
of the nostril.
I know what I saw.
But there was no pick!
I-I did not pick.
There was no pick.
I gotta go.
No! No pick.
All right, now,
here's the scoop, Calvin.
I, uh, I came in here
last January
to talk to one of your flunkies.
Interesting face.
Yeah?
And when I told him my idea
about the beach cologne,
you know, he laughed at me.
You're very lithe, aren't you?
Very graceful.
Well, yeah.
Sit down.
All right.
[KICKS COUCH]
Ooh!
You're very lean...
but muscular.
You know,
I try to take care of myself.
I-- You know,
I watch what I eat.
Just recently,
I cut out fructose.
I think you're spectacular.
Oh?
I told you, Fred,
my friend's next-door
neighbor took it.
So, what happened?
Well, I-I-I must've
missed a button.
I forgot to button it.
I really don't see how you could
miss a button like that.
Oh, you've never
missed a button?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Yeah.
WOMAN:
It's your sister, Gail.
Oh, God. My nephew.
Hi, Gail.
Yeah--
Yes, Gail,
I know how old he is.
Hey, Nip, you need
that manuscript,
or can I take it home?
Yeah, take it. Take it,
And stop
calling me Nip!
It was an accident.
Well--
Well, it's gotta be somewhere.
Look under his mattress.
[SIGHS]
About
the focus group?
I have nothing to do
with the focus group.
That's
your department.
Oh.
Wham.
He's sexual,
athletic
and without a trace
of self-consciousness.
MAN: His buttocks
are sublime.
Of course, his pectorals
could use a little work.
I suppose we could get him
into the weight room.
No, let's get him
in the studio today.
We could send these
out immediately.
You've done it
again, C.K.
And what if I did
do it--
Even though I admit
to nothing and never will--
What does that make me?
And I'm not here
just defending myself,
but all those pickers out there
who've been caught...
each and every one of them
who has to suffer
the shame and humiliation
because of people
like you.
Are we not human?
If we pick,
do we not bleed?
I am not an animal!
I did not bare myself
deliberately,
but I tell you,
I wish now that I had.
Because it is not me
that has been exposed,
but you!
For I have seen the nipple
on your soul!
So the minute I started
up the steps to her apartment,
I knew I made
a terrible mistake...
going back with her.
So we're in her apartment.
She goes into the bathroom.
I'm cursing myself. Now,
how do I get out of there?
And then it hits me
like a bolt of lightning:
The pick.
The pick?
She comes out of the bathroom,
I'm in up to my wrist.
You should have seen
the look on her face.
I think I've seen
that look.
Hey, I got
the magazine.
The underwear ad came out.
Hey, Calvin Klein!
Wow!
Hey, you look great!
Ooh, neat.
Boy, they really worked
on your pectorals.
Well...
Your buttocks
are spectacular.
Whoopee.
Oh, my.
What?
Well, I'm not sure,
but...
I think I see your...
The human body
is a lot of maintenance.
It's a lot of showering,
a lot of shaving,
a lot of cleaning, a lot
of clipping, a lot of checking.
If your body was a car,
you wouldn't buy it.
It's too much upkeep.
It's a pain.
But women definitely go
to the absolute extreme.
To me, it's amazing
the way women take care
of all the hair on their bodies.
One of the great mysteries to me
is the fact that a woman
could pour hot wax on her legs,
rip the hair out by the root
and still be afraid of a spider.
[♪]