My parents had
two constant arguments
while they were driving,
over either how fast
my father was going,
or how much gas was left
in the tank.
My father had
a standard defense
for either one of these.
It was always,
"That's because
you're looking at it
from an angle."
[LAUGHTER]
If you were over here--
it looks from where
you're sitting,
it looks like
I'm doing 90 on empty,
[LAUGHTER]
but that's because you're
over there.
If you were over here,
you'd know I'm in the driveway
with a full tank.
JERRY:
So George and I went up to NBC,
and we told them
the idea for the series,
and now we're just waiting
to sign the contract.
And they liked the idea?
Yeah.
What do you got,
leather seats here?
Since when
is George a writer?
What writer?
It's a sitcom.
This is so exciting.
When are you
going to sign the contract?
Soon. There's
a couple of problems.
Jerry, I wanna tell you,
that meal was the worst.
What do you expect?
It's airline food.
They give you
that fish.
How could you
eat fish on a plane?
Because she puts up
such a big stink
every time I have
a piece of meat.
What kind of problems?
Well, George doesn't think
$13,000 is enough money.
What? He's not even working.
George is right.
Those people will try
to get away with murder.
Believe me,
they're all crooks.
Jerry, I want you
to sign that contract.
We're gonna sign it!
In fact,
George is out
with the woman
from NBC right now.
GEORGE:
So I'm...
I'm afraid we're
gonna have to pass.
You're-- You're passing?
Well, it's much too low.
Are you and Jerry
in complete agreement on this?
[SCOFFS, SNORTS]
Yeah, we've talked.
I believe I can speak
for the both of us on this.
Because you know
that because this
is your first show,
it's a pretty standard deal.
Standard?
Yeah.
Is Ted Danson's deal standard?
Ted Danson?
The guy from Cheers.
Yeah, I know who he is.
You're not Ted Danson.
I didn't say I was Ted Danson.
All right.
I'll tell Russell tomorrow.
You tell Russell.
Oh, um, before I forget.
Cuban cigars.
It's a present
from my father.
Do I have to write him
a note or something?
Yeah, I'm sure
he'd appreciate that.
Well, what would I say
in the note?
Oh, you're a writer.
You'll think of something.
Oh.
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
Yeah, I'm a writer.
I forgot.
Were you waiting long
at the gate?
Um, I don't even know.
Where's that watch
we bought you?
Oh, uh...
That's it
for this piece of junk.
I've had it.
Is that the one
your parents gave you?
Yeah,
but it never works.
It's...being fixed.
I got a guarantee
on that watch.
Give it to me.
I'll take it back.
It's at the jeweler.
You send me the bill.
I'm not sending you
the bill.
That watch was a gift.
You shouldn't have to
pay for it.
That's 18.50.
Here, I got it.
What are you
talking about?
It's my car.
Let me pay for the gas.
No, no, put it away.
Dad.
Stop it!
I have money. I make money.
Yeah, yeah,
you make money.
You don't think
I make money.
That's what you think,
isn't it?
No, I don't
think that.
Yes, you do, that's
what you both think.
I'm paying.
Dad, I'm paying.
Get out of here.
You're not paying.
Now, Jerry, please,
do not do this
to your father.
Over my dead body,
Jerry,
I'm telling you
right now.
You're not gonna
do it.
Boy, you got a lot
of stuff here.
Dad,
what are you doing?
Nothing. Nothing.
Leave it.
What about your back?
Morty,
what are you doing?
All right. All right.
You come
all the way up here
to see a back specialist,
and you're lifting
heavy suitcases.
Hey, Morty.
Hey, Mr. Kramer!
Good to see you.
Ah, Mrs. Seinfeld.
Hi.
Oh, what happened to you?
Oh, well, some guy kicked me
in the side of the head.
What guy?
Crazy Joe Davola.
Why?
Well, I was having this party,
and I didn't invite him,
and then Jerry tipped him off.
Why'd you tell
this crazy guy
that Kramer didn't
invite him to his party?
I didn't know
he wasn't invited.
Hey, these are
very comfortable pants.
You know what I paid
for these, Jerry?
So why did you
say anything?
It was a mistake.
They're good
around the house,
and they're good
for outside.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I was a little off last week,
huh, Jerry?
Yeah, but doctor says
it's just a slight concussion.
So what's the matter
with this Davola guy?
He's got, like,
a chemical imbalance.
He needs to be
on medication.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He's after Jerry now.
Kramer...
He's what?
He's joking.
He's after you?
No!
Why is he after you?
He's not after me.
Morty,
do you hear this?
Some crazy guy
is after Jerry.
I'll make a few
phone calls.
Who are you
gonna call?
What are you
worried about?
I want to know what you did
that he's after you.
I didn't do anything.
Well, you must've
done something.
No, he just doesn't like me.
Doesn't like you?
How could anyone not like you?
I know. It seems impossible.
Doesn't...doesn't like you.
How could that be?
Ma, I know this may be hard
for you to understand,
but I'm sure
there are many people
who do not like me.
[GASPS]
Jerry, don't say that.
It's true.
No, it isn't.
It's not true.
You're a wonderful,
wonderful boy.
Everybody likes you.
It's impossible
not to like you.
Impossible. Morty?
Maybe some people don't
like him. I can see that.
Kramer?
Yeah, I like him...
Hey, Jerry,
what time you got?
Uh...I haven't got my watch on.
It's being fixed.
When are you
getting it back?
Uh...next week.
Next week?
How come
it's taking so long?
Huh?
I said, how come
it's taking so long?
I don't know.
They're backed up.
Wait a minute.
Where did you take it?
Where did I take it?
Yeah.
Um...to that place
on Columbus and 85th.
Okay?
What, Jimmy Sherman?
Yeah.
I know the guy. I take my stuff
in there all the time.
Bet I can get your watch back
by tomorrow morning.
No, Kramer,
I don't want you
to say anything to him.
No, I'd be happy to.
He's a friend of mine.
I'd like to follow
the regular procedures.
I don't want
any special treatment.
Hey, I'm gonna get
that watch back for you
by tomorrow, buddy,
you'll see.
Bring me the receipt.
I'll get that too.
Be right back.
[WHISPERING]: Look,
there's no watch.
I threw it
in the garbage can
on the street.
It didn't keep good time.
My parents gave it to me,
but I didn't like it,
so don't mention it again, okay?
Yeah, all right.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait.
[MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
What was that about?
Oh, no.
He's got my calamine lotion...
And I told him not to return it.
If he needs it,
he should keep it.
He's got a thing on his...ankle.
How could anyone not like him?
Hi. Morty Seinfeld.
I have a 2:00 appointment.
Yes, Mr. Seinfeld. Would you
please fill this out.
All this?
This whole thing?
It's gonna take me 45 minutes.
I know.
It's very long.
Look at this.
It's a book.
"Employer's address."
Why do they need this?
You know, I never had
a back problem
until that night I slept
on the convertible sofa.
My back was fine.
Oh, it's not the sofa.
You stick up
for that sofa
like I'm criticizing
a person.
We got it
from Sullivan's.
It's a good store.
Well, one day,
somebody's gonna sleep
on that thing,
and we'll get sued.
I hope this doctor
knows what he's doing.
Leo says
he's the best there is.
Leo.
I'm listening
to Leo now.
You're lucky he was able
to get you this appointment.
You know what the waiting list
is for this guy?
Well, if he fixes
my back,
I'll be happy.
"Have you ever had
a sexually
transmitted disease?"
That's it.
Here. You got my name.
You got my address.
That's enough.
Julie...
you wanna
take him back?
JERRY:
You what?
You passed?
How could you do that?
Jerry,
my young friend...
You're so naive.
You are so, so naive.
You know about a few things.
You know about comedy,
a little bit
about relationships,
some baseball,
but you are so far
out of your element here,
you're embarrassing yourself.
Now, listen to me.
I'm negotiating.
Negotiation.
This is what you do
in business.
Let me explain to you
what you just did.
There are literally
hundreds of people
trying to get
pilot deals
with them this year.
They go with maybe five, okay?
If we pass, that's it.
They go to the next show.
Ooh, I'm scared.
Oh, they're not
gonna do the show.
We're lucky
they're even interested
in the idea
in the first place.
We got a show
about nothing...
with no story.
What do you think,
they're up there going,
"Hey, maybe we should give
those two guys
"who have no experience
and no idea
more money"?
Oh, what are we gonna do?
I'm shaking.
Well, I think you're wrong.
Well, we'll just see.
Yes, we will.
I just said that.
I know you did.
So good for you.
What, are you repeating
everything I'm saying?
Well, George is an idiot.
Well, Geor--
All right.
All right, let's go already!
They keep you in here a year.
They don't give a damn.
I could die in here.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
I'm here 20 minutes.
Can somebody please help me?
Shh!
Quiet. Everyone can hear you.
Twenty minutes,
I've been waiting 20 minutes.
Well, the doctor must be busy.
Well, then, what do they
make appointments for
if they can't keep them?
Look, if I did that
in my business,
I wouldn't have made a nickel.
Hello,
Mr. Seinfeld.
I thought you forgot about me.
We didn't forget.
[VELCRO RIPS, MORTY SCREAMS]
What?
The Velcro.
I can't stand Velcro,
that tearing sound.
I used to be
in raincoats.
I refused to put that
in any of my lines.
Okay, Mr. Seinfeld,
please come this way.
We need some X-rays.
Leave all my stuff here?
Leave it.
Oh, hey,
by the way,
you want a box of Cuban cigars?
I smoked one
last night.
I got nauseous.
No, I don't want them.
I'll take it.
No, I'll take it.
What is it?
Here you go.
What, cigars?
Yeah. Cubans.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, the kind
that Castro smoked.
You can't buy them
anywhere.
Castro, huh?
[IMITATES SPANISH]
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
WOMAN:
Federal Express.
Federal Express?
Come on up.
I'm not expecting a package.
[SIGHS]
You know what you just did?
You let a burglar
in the building.
You think so?
Federal Express? Of course.
That's the oldest trick
in the book.
You know,
it might not be a burglar.
It could be a murderer.
So you wanna just abolish
all home package delivery?
Yes.
It's dangerous.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Wait.
Who is it?
WOMAN:
Federal Express.
Okay...
[ALL SCREAM]
I want one of those.
Kramer!
Oh, God!
I thought you were
in California.
Well, I came back
for you.
Oh, shut up.
I missed you.
Really,
you missed me?
Yeah, seriously.
Yeah, yeah.
Me too, miss.
I missed.
Yeah, big missing
going on around here.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna get a match.
Oh, God.
Whose suitcase is this?
Oh, it's my parents'.
My father came up
to see a back specialist.
Oh, God,
it's probably from sleeping
on that sofa.
Boy, you look
really great. Yeah.
You lie.
No, no, you really look great.
[LAUGHS]
So tell us
about the trip.
How's Dr. Reston?
Oh, he's fine.
Things are good?
Yeah. You know.
Uh-oh.
What, uh-oh?
Did you see that?
Yeah, I saw it.
What?
It's a tell. You got a tell.
What tell?
What's a tell?
When you ask someone
about their relationship,
and they touch their face,
you know
it's not going too well.
Go ahead. Ask me how it's going
with somebody.
Um...how's it going with Alice?
Good. Going good...
And the higher up
on the face you go,
the worse the relationship
is getting.
You know, it's, like,
pretty good...not bad...
I gotta get out.
How high did I go?
You almost hit the nose.
What, are you eating
my peanut butter out of the jar
with your disgusting
index fingers?
This is a sickening display.
What? I'm not eating bread now.
I'm off bread.
You're off bread.
So, what happened?
Is it over?
No, not quite.
Why not?
Well, he was my psychiatrist,
you know?
I mean, he knows
all my patterns.
He knows that in relationships
that I always try to find
some reason to leave,
and so he says, as my doctor,
he can't allow me do this,
so he's not letting me leave.
What do you mean,
not letting you?
He has this power over me, okay?
I mean, he has this way
of manipulating
every little word that I say.
He's like a "Svenjolly."
"Svengali."
What did I say?
"Svenjolly."
"Svenjolly?"
I did not say "Svenjolly."
George?
"Svenjolly."
I don't see how
I could've said "Svenjolly."
Well, maybe he's got, like,
a cheerful mental hold on you.
You know, I can't find
a match anywhere.
You know what you should do?
You should tell this guy
you're seeing somebody else--
easiest way to get out
of these things.
No, it's not gonna work
with this guy.
GEORGE: No,
you just tell him...
an old boyfriend's
come back into your life.
I don't think so.
Nice try.
Took a shot.
It's a good cigar.
[SCREAMS]
So when do I get to see
the doctor?
He'll be in
with the X-rays
in a few minutes.
You can get dressed.
He stole my wallet.
The bum stole my wallet.
My wallet's gone!
I had my wallet
in my back pocket.
It's gone.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
I went in to get my X-rays.
Somebody takes my wallet.
Is that the operation here?
Mr. Seinfeld,
I'm Dr. Dembrow.
I've been going over
your X-rays.
I'm not interested
in the X-rays.
I want my money back.
Somebody stole
my wallet.
I had $225 in there.
I don't see how something
like that could've happened.
Oh, you don't see.
You don't see.
Well, it happened,
believe me.
What's going on?
They stole my wallet.
What?
Yeah, while I was in getting X-rayed.
All right,
Mr. Seinfeld,
I am sorry
about your wallet,
but would you like me
to look over these X-rays?
What kind of clip joint
you running here?
All right. Fine.
The least
you could have done
was heard
your diagnosis.
I'm not interested
in his diagnosis.
He's a bum.
You came all the way
from Florida to see him.
I wanna know what kind
of an office is this
where you can't leave
your pants in the room.
You tell me.
I'm sorry,
but there's somebody else.
Mm-hmm.
Well, it's nothing
I planned on happening,
you know?
It just kind of happened.
Tell me about him.
Well...
There's not really much to tell,
you know?
He's just a guy, really.
Yes, well,
I assume he's a guy...
Right.
And you've known him
how long?
Years...
Many years.
We've been close friends,
and then recently,
something just, you know--
Ahh-- happened.
You mean sexually?
Yeah. Yeah.
Sexually.
[TELEPHONE BUZZES]
I think your, um...
Excuse me.
Yes?
Oh, yes, Bobo.
No, it's just east of Madison.
Around four would be fine.
All right, Bobo.
See you then.
I'm sorry.
Where were we?
Well, I was just telling you
about this other guy.
Elaine.
Yeah?
Do you remember your dream
where you had a sexual encounter
with a Chinese woman?
Yeah.
[COUGHS]
Mm-hmm.
Elaine, I'm concerned about you.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't concern yourself with me,
because I'm good.
I'm very good.
I mean,
I'm really very, very good.
Elaine...
Have you been urinating
a lot again?
No.
And how often
have you been seeing, um...
I'm sorry.
What is his name?
His name?
Yes. His name.
Well, what's the difference?
Are you afraid
to tell me his name?
No, no, I just don't really see
how that's relevant.
It doesn't matter
if you don't see how.
I see how.
Uh, his name.
I don't even know.
All right,
you wanna know his name?
I'll tell you his name.
His name is...Kramer.
Kramer.
Is that his first name
or his last name?
You know,
I'm really uncomfortable
talking about this.
Elaine, I want you
to do me a favor.
What?
I want you to tell
this young man
to give me a call.
It's very important
that I speak to him.
Oh, no, no, no,
I can't do that.
You can do it,
and you will do it.
No, I can't.
You can, and you will.
Okay, okay,
I'll have Kramer
give you a call.
So you didn't even let
the doctor treat you?
I wouldn't give him
the satisfaction.
Why did you leave
your wallet in your pants?
What are you
talking about?
What, was I supposed to
hide it somewhere?
You could've
taken it with you.
Oh, yeah. I'll be lying
on an X-ray table
with my wallet
in my mouth.
Hello.
Hi, Uncle Leo.
I just spoke
to Dr. Dembrow's son.
He said they almost had to call
the police.
What are you
talking about?
I'm the one who should've
called the police.
They stole my wallet.
You know
how hard it was for me
to get
that appointment for you?
You can't just walk in
on this guy.
He did me
a personal favor...
All right, Leo.
And you walked out
without paying.
How was I
supposed to pay?
I didn't have
my wallet.
Well, I hope
you send him a check.
What for?
This man was nice enough
to see you.
He did me
a personal favor.
That's the second time
you said personal favor.
Why do you keep
saying that?
I said it once.
Twice...
and Dembrow doesn't
even know you.
His son happens to live
on your floor.
Leo, where did you
get that watch?
You know
where I got this?
I found it in the garbage can.
It kept terrible time.
I brought it over
to Jimmy Sherman
right here
on 85th and Columbus.
Gave it to me back
the next day.
Works great.
What kind of an idiot
throws away
a perfectly good watch?
Doesn't that watch look
like the one that we gave Jerry?
Hey,
where's the waiter?
Dad, what do you say,
we have some
red meat tonight?
Let's live a little.
Let's see that.
Could we continue this
another time?
Don't you hate
"to be continueds" on TV?
It's horrible when you sense
the "to be continued" coming,
you know?
You're watching the show.
You're into the story.
Then there's, like,
five minutes left,
and suddenly you realize,
"Hey, they can't make it.
"Timmy's still stuck
in the cave.
There's no way they wrap this up
in five minutes."
I mean, the whole reason
you watch a TV show
is because it ends.
If I wanted a long, boring story
with no point to it,
I have my life.
A comedian can't do that.
See, I can't go,
"A man walks into a bar
with a pig under his arm.
Can you come back next week?"