The life expectancy now
is, uh,
72, I think, for men.
Seventy-five or six
or something for women.
It's amazing to think that just
a couple thousand years ago,
life expectancy was 30.
Which, in our terms, would mean
that you'd get
your driver's license around 5,
you'd marry at 9,
divorced at 15.
In your late teens,
you move down to Florida.
I guess that's how spring break
got started, I don't know.
Then, eventually, people
are saying things about you
like, "Well, it's amazing.
"He's 28,
but he's still very alert.
"His mind is so sharp,
you would think you're talking
to a 2-year-old."
Aw, what's the point?
[SIGHS]
When I like them,
they don't like me.
When they like me,
I don't like them.
Why can't I act
with the ones I like
the way I do
with the ones I don't like?
Well, you've only got
another 50 years or so to go,
and it'll all be over.
Maybe I need someone
who doesn't speak English.
Yeah. How about a mute?
A mute would be good.
Ah, where are you
gonna meet a mute?
This is what my life
has come to,
trying to meet a mute.
I don't know, Jerry.
Something's missing.
There's a void, Jerry.
There's a void.
A deep, yawning chasm.
There's got to be more to life
than this.
What gives you pleasure?
Listening to you.
I listen to this for 15 minutes,
I'm on top of the world.
Your misery is my pleasure.
Hey, boys.
Hey, how you doing?
Good. Okay.
Well, it's all set.
I start tomorrow.
Start what?
I signed up
to do volunteer work
with senior citizens.
Really?
ELAINE: Yeah.
God, I can't
tell you how I feel.
I mean,
I feel so good!
I really
feel good!
The strange thing is,
I mean, I haven't even
met the woman yet.
Volunteer work, huh?
What are you gonna
do down there?
Well, they say
all it is,
is you go over
to their apartment,
and, I don't know,
you take them out for a walk,
you get
a cup of coffee,
and it's supposed to
make them feel good.
That's what I do
with him.
When did you get this idea?
Last time I had
lunch with you here.
You were going on
and on and on
about how you wanted
to meet somebody
who didn't speak English.
What, you break it in with her,
then you try it out on me?
All right.
A-a-and anybody could do this?
Yeah.
Really?
Helping people.
Of course.
Of course!
It makes perfect sense.
How could I not be doing this?
I am gonna help somebody,
damn it!
What about you?
Nah, it's not for me.
Jerry, if anybody should be
doing this, it's you.
What kind of a person are you?
I think I'm pretty much
like you...
only successful.
This is a wonderful thing
you're doing.
They're so grateful
just to have
someone to talk to.
And I can tell you
that everyone who participates
finds the experience
extremely rewarding.
Well, I feel better
already.
I-- I'm feeling
like a good person.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Hey, what's
your guy's name again?
Fields, Sidney Fields,
87 years old.
Wow, 87. Hmm.
Yeah.
How about your guy?
Uh, Ben Cantwell, 85.
Hmm!
Huh?
You think we'll make it
to that age?
"We"? No.
Hey.
So, what's up, diggety-dog?
George and I just signed up
with the senior citizens
volunteer agency.
Same thing Elaine's doing.
Oh, that's too bad.
Now, don't say I didn't
try to warn you.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Jerry,
I'm surprised at you!
What?
It's a con!
These agencies
are usually a front
for some money-laundering
scheme,
or they're bunco artists
bilking people
out of their life savings.
Oh, yeah.
Where do you get this?
The alternative
media, Jerry.
That's where
you hear the truth.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
NEWMAN: Kramer?
Huh?
Kramer?
Kramer!
Where are you?
Kramer! Kramer!
Come on.
I'm in here.
There you are.
Yeah.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Jerry. George.
So did you ask him
about the records?
What records?
Uh, well, uh...
Newman and I
are going partners,
selling used records.
Yoo! Yoo! Yoo! Yoo!
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!
You know Ron's Records
down on Bleecker?
They pay big cash
for used records.
Yeah, so we thought
if you had
any of those big,
you know, old-fashioned,
useless records just,
you know, lying around--
We'll take them
off your hands, free of charge.
Let me ask you something.
What do you do for a living,
Newman?
I'm a United States
postal worker.
Aren't those the guys
that always go crazy
and come back
with a gun
and shoot everybody?
Sometimes.
Why is that?
Because the mail never stops.
It just keeps coming
and coming and coming.
There's never a let-up!
It's relentless.
Every day, it piles up
more and more and more!
You gotta get it out! The more
you get out, the more comes in!
And then
the bar-code reader breaks,
[GASPING]
and it's Publisher's Clearing House day!
All right,
all right, all right!
Just take the records.
They're in the bedroom.
Take them.
Take anything you want.
KRAMER:
Yeah. Yeah.
Whoo!
I'll give you five bucks.
BOTH:
Five bucks!
Well, do you know
how much
those records
are worth?
Yeah, I do-- $5.
Those records are worth
more than $5!
He's gypping us.
You're gypping us!
Well, what do you got here?
You know, you got
Don Ho Live in Honolulu,
You got Jerry Vale
Sings Italian Love Songs.
And you got Sergio Mendes.
Now, come on!
Wait, wait, wait. Sergio Mendes
has a cult following.
They follow him
like a cult.
Yeah, he can't even walk down
the street in South America.
Look, that's his problem,
all right?
Now, you don't like it, too bad.
I don't like it.
Well, then get the hell
out of my store, all right?
You bring me something decent,
I'll give you some money.
All right.
We'll be back, Jack.
We'll be back...
Jack.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hi. I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
The agency sent me.
[SENEGALESE ACCENT]
Agency?
Uh, yeah.
Is this Sid Fields' residence?
Sid Fields.
What the hell is it?
Mr. Fields?
What?
Hi. I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
The agency sent me.
The agency?
What agency,
the CIA?
No, no, the, uh--
Who let you in here?
Uh, the-- The woman--
Oh, her.
She steals from me,
steals my money.
She said
she doesn't speak English.
My ass,
Plays that freakin'
voodoo music,
tries to hypnotize me.
She thinks she's gonna turn me
into a zombie
and then rob me blind.
Well, I wasn't born yesterday.
I might drop dead today,
but I sure as hell
wasn't born yesterday.
Now, get the hell
out of my house.
But, Mr. Fields,
I'm here to spend
some time with you.
Oh, really?
Are you the boyfriend?
I know she's got a boyfriend.
Are you gonna kill me?
I'm an old man,
for crying out loud!
You gonna kill an old man,
you coward?
No, Mr. Fields, look, really.
Here's my identifi--
I can't read that, you fool.
What's
all this stuff?
Trash, garbage.
You're throwing
this out?
I believe
that's what you do
with garbage,
you idiot.
You don't want
any of this?
Well, if I wanted it,
I wouldn't be
throwing it away,
would I, Einstein?
You know, I have some friends
that would really love
to have these.
Well, take it.
I sure as hell
am not gonna give it
to my family.
Well, uh,
do you want to go out
and go for a walk, get
a cup of coffee? With you?
I'd rather be dead.
Well, maybe I'll get going,
then.
I just remembered
I've got an appointment
to get my, uh...
tonsils out.
Good! Thank God!
Good riddance.
Oh, listen.
Uh, before you go,
would you mind
changing my diaper?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, I feel great for 85.
You know,
the average lifespan
for an American male
is, like, 72.
You're really...
kind of pushing the envelope
there.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I never think about it.
You don't?
Boy, I think about it a lot...
I think about it at my age.
Imagine how much
I'll be thinking
about it at your age.
All I'll do is just
keep thinking about it
till it drives me
insane.
I'm grateful
for every moment I have.
Grateful?
How can you be grateful when
you're so close to the end?!
When you know that any second,
poof, bammo,
it could all be over!
I mean,
you're not stupid.
You can read
the handwriting on the wall.
It's a matter of
simple arithmetic,
for God's sake.
I guess I just don't care.
What are you talking about?
H-how can you sit there
and look me in the eye
and tell me
that you're not worried?
Don't you have any sense?!
Don't you have a brain?!
Are you so completely senile
you don't even know what
you're talking about anymore?!
What--?
W-w-w-wait a second.
Where are you going?
Life's too short
to waste on you.
W-w-wait, please.
Get out of my way.
But...
But, Mr. Cantwell, you...
You owe me for the soup.
Mrs. Oliver?
Yes, my dear.
Oh!
What's the trouble?
Are you
all right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yes.
It's my goiter,
isn't it?
Did you--?
Did you say "goiter"?
Wha--? What goiter?
This football-shaped lump
jutting out
the side of my neck.
Oh.
That goiter.
Hey...
[CHUCKLES]
What do you know?
Does it
bother you?
Bother me? Oh!
Pfft.
Why would a little goiter
like that bother me?
No, not a bit.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
It's, um-- in fact, It's, um--
It's very distinctive,
you know, um...
I mean, you want
to know something? I--
I wish I had one.
Really.
JERRY:
Come on, Elaine. It's just a goiter.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I can't look the woman
in the face.
I mean, I keep thinking
that goiter's gonna start
talking to me.
You'd think
that they'd mention
something like that
before they sent you
over there.
"Oh, by the way,
this woman almost has
a second head."
But, no, no, I didn't get
any goiter information.
They really should
mention that
in the breakdown:
height, weight, goiter.
You know, you try
to do some good,
you want to be
a good person,
but this is too much
to ask.
Yeah, well, I'll tell you,
I'd rather talk
to a goiter
with a nice disposition
than the nut
they sent me to.
Hey, Georgie,
what happened with your guy?
I don't think
it's gonna work out.
What do you mean?
He fired me.
What?
He fired you?
How do you get fired
from a volunteer job?
I don't know.
I was just talking to the man,
and he walked out on me.
Well, I don't know
about you two,
but I'm quitting.
I hate my guy.
He's a mean,
mean guy.
I wish I could quit.
So quit.
Yeah. I'm a great quitter.
It's one of the few things
I do well.
I come from a long line
of quitters.
My father was a quitter.
My grandfather was a quitter.
I was raised to give up.
Hey.
Well, here's your albums.
What happened?
Five dollars.
He offered us $5.
I mean, what kind of stuff
are you listening to?
You embarrassed me
at that store.
That guy thought we were
a couple of total squares.
Oh, yeah, you
and your Sergio Mendes.
Hey, hey, hey.
That guy can't even go to
the bathroom in South America.
Well, you should've seen
the pile of albums
this old guy
I was visiting today
was throwing away--
Sinatra,
Duke Ellington,
Al Jolson,
Benny Goodman.
Wait, wait, wait. Now,
he's throwing them out?
I asked if my friends could
have them, and he said yeah.
The old coot's sitting on
a mountain of gold. Yeah. Shh.
But you have to get them.
I'm not carrying them all.
But you're coming
with us?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going there tonight.
You should see
this housekeeper he's got.
She's from Senegal.
Wild, wild stuff.
Senegal?
So you don't speak
any English at all?
English?
No.
Hey, what are those bums
doing back there?
Well, you said they could come
and take the records.
It's like watching
a couple of hyenas
going through the garbage.
You don't speak
any English?
No English.
I would like to dip
my bald head in oil
and rub it
all over your body.
You-- You don't
understand.
It's a miracle!
You don't understand
because you-- You
don't speak English.
So, Mr. Fields,
I just don't know--
Hey! I don't like
what's going on around here.
I want all of you bums
out of here.
Now, calm down--
Don't tell me
to calm down!
Please, Mr. Fields--
Get your hands off me!
Aw, cool it, pops.
Why, you little--
Wait, wait,
Mr. Fields.
Mr. Fields...
Ah! He's biting me! Ah!
MR. FIELDS:
My teeth!
Where's his teeth?
I thought I saw
something fly over here.
Well, turn
the light on.
[GRINDING]
That's the garbage
disposal!
[GRINDING STOPS]
[RATTLING]
MR. FIELDS:
My teeth!
You idiots!
Well, we'll take you
to your dentist, Mr. Fields.
Where is your dentist?
Downtown!
All right, George,
Kramer, look after Mr. Fields.
I'll go get
the cab.
Bunch of morons.
Get over.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Where's the old man?
I thought that George
was keeping
an eye on him.
Me? I thought
you were.
All right. Come on.
We lost the old man.
Let's go.
Get out of the car.
Come on.
We've got to find him.
He can't
have gotten far.
Come on.
And we would take
long automobile trips.
Oh, well, that sounds
like a lot of fun.
Staring
out the window.
Uh-huh.
You see a long view
of rolling pastures.
[YAWNS]
Well, get you going,
right there.
Brahman cows...
Oh, cows.
Oh, that's...
That's when I...
Fascinating.
began my affair
with Mohandas.
What?
Mohandas.
Gandhi?
Oh...
The passion.
The forbidden
pleasure.
You had an affair
with Gandhi?
He used to dip
his bald head in oil...
and rub it
all over my body.
Here. Look.
Oh, my God.
The Mahatma?
KRAMER:
We're supposed to be out there looking for the old man.
NEWMAN:
Oh, we will. We will.
Twenty bucks.
Twenty bucks?
Are you
out of your mind?
Well, take it or leave it.
Take it
or leave it?
We got Al Jolson here!
Al Jolson!
Al Jolson?
What the hell
do I care about Al Jolson?
I'd just as soon
hear you sing "Mammy."
This guy is nothing
but a piece of crap.
You are nothing
What'd you call me?
A piece of crap.
I find you
extremely ugly.
I find you extremely ugly.
Do you?
You emit a foul
and unpleasant odor.
Oh, is that right?
I loathe you.
That's it!
You get out of my store!
Make us!
Make us. M-m-make us.
I'll make you!
Calm down.
Wait a minute.
Wait! Wait!
[SCREAMING]
Do you realize how
irresponsible this is?
Well--
Our agency's sole purpose
is to care
for senior citizens,
and in one fell swoop,
you have single-handedly
destroyed our reputation.
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
Yes, but...
Uh, yes?
It's Tim Fields,
Mr. Fields' son.
Uh, all right. Come on up.
Oh, great...
I-- I don't know
what happened.
we were just trying to
take him to the dentist.
Why were you taking him
to the dentist?
Uh, well, his false teeth
got mangled up
in the garbage disposal.
What were his false teeth
doing in the garbage disposal?
Well, after he bit my friend--
Bit your friend?!
What the hell is going on here?
How do you lose a human being?
Well, I-- I am sorry--
And who were these other people?
What were they doing
in the apartment?
Well, I brought them up there
to take his records.
Take his records?
Do you realize how valuable
that record collection is?
There you are.
Did you find him?
Nah. Uh, you know, we took
the old man's records
over to Ron's,
and he tried to screw us,
and then we got into a fight.
It was
a real melee.
Yeah, a real brouhaha.
Then all
the records broke.
The records?
My father's records?
Uh--
Did anybody try and call him?
Yeah, I called,
but there's no answer.
Well, the line's busy now.
The line's busy.
He must be home.
[WILD, EXOTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
W-w-we, uh...
We-- We couldn't
find him.
What the hell's
the point?
When you like them,
they don't like you,
and when they like you,
you don't like them.
Oh, you don't know
what you want.
You should see a psychiatrist.
Yeah, I got fixed up last week.
Yeah. I never would
get "fixed up."
I go to pick her up,
and she opens the door,
and she's got this huge goiter
growing out
of the side of her neck.
It looked like a football.
Well, what did you do?
Well, we get
to talking,
and as it turns out,
the woman knew Gandhi.
Huh.
We talked for hours.
Well, uh, are you gonna
see her again?
We were getting along real good,
and then she made some tea.
Put some milk in it
without asking me.
Now, that's a turnoff.
Ah, you don't need that.
To me, the thing
about old people
is that everything about them
gets smaller.
You know,
their bodies get smaller.
They move into smaller places.
They sleep less time.
They eat smaller meals.
Except the car.
The older they get,
the bigger their car gets.
I've never understood that.
And old people have a way
of backing out of the driveway.
You know what I mean?
They don't turn
from side to side.
They just go, "I'm old.
I've been waiting a long time.
I'm backing it out."
You know? "I'm coming back.
Watch out, buddy. I'm coming."
You know?
And you've got to watch out
for them.
And then,
once they get out there,
they drive so slowly,
and I would think
the less time you have in life,
the faster you would want to go.
You know?
I think old people should
be allowed to drive their age.
If you're 80, do 80.
If you're 100, go 100.
They can't see
where they're going anyway.
Let them have
a little fun out there.