In the hospital,
everybody lies in bed.
Whatever's wrong with
a human being...Lie down.
Doctor never says to you:
"Well, your condition isn't as
bad as we originally thought.
"We want you to kinda
lean against the doorjamb
for 7-10 days,
see how that feels."
Right? It's always a bed,
unless you go to the emergency
room, then it's a chair.
You been shot, stabbed,
run over, have a seat.
[♪]
There's always a very
interesting cultural, ethnic mix
to the hospital staff.
It's like a local
news team in there.
The doctor's like
the anchor man.
He's got white hair.
He's in charge.
The nurse is like
the feature reporter, you know.
You listen to her,
but it's always,
"and now,
back to your doctor."
And the orderlies come in
with the food and bed pans.
And that's like your
sports and weather.
[♪]
And then a baby's head
comes out, and I'm screaming,
and my brother, who's
videotaping the whole thing,
turns green. His eyes roll up
in his head and he blacks out.
He drops the camera.
The camera breaks.
And then the placenta
comes flying out.
Whoa!
And then a doctor says--
Hey, thanks.
That's enough.
Will you look
at that kid?
Sucking away. Sucking like
there's no tomorrow.
Suck, suck, suck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look at that, Jerry!
Yeah, I looked!
I-I-I saw it.
This doesn't make
you uncomfortable?
No, no.
Uncomfortable?
Not at all.
My friend's wife's breasts
are sticking out.
Why would that
make me uncomfortable?
Look at him!
So how long
do they do this?
Year or two.
No break?
After that
comes the weaning.
After the sucking
First the sucking,
then the weaning.
Gotta wean.
Must wean.
[TAPPING]
What about
that spot I got?
Yeah.
I saw the spot.
You open the door
to the car, boom!
You walk right
into the hospital.
You can't beat that spot!
Hoo-hoo! I am on a roll!
Yeah!
I'm just willing
these great parking spots.
George.
Maybe the baby would like
to see the spot.
A positive, uplifting message
to start his life out with, huh?
You can still get a great spot
in this city
if you apply yourself!
Hey where's Kramer?
Shouldn't he be here by now?
Did you gave him
the room number?
Yeah. 1397.
Kramer:
1937.
1937, 1937.
Excuse me. Do you know
where the elevator is?
Uh, yeah. It's right
around the corner there.
1937.
Oh!
[WHEEZING]
Oh, God!
It's a pig-man!
A pig-man!
So, anyway, Jerry, Elaine,
we have something to ask you.
You gotta look at this.
I pulled it in
perfectly equidistant
from the car in front of me
and the car behind me.
Would you shut up, George?
I'm taking a cab home.
I can't
take this anymore.
I'm sorry about this.
Myra and I would like
you and Elaine
to be the godparents
of Steven.
Oh, wow!
Me?
A godfather?
Yes.
[AS DON CORLEONE]
Never go against the family, Elaine.
What?
Hey, I just saw
a pig-man.
A pig-man!
He was sleeping, and then
he woke up and he looked at me,
and he made this horrible
sound, this...
[SQUEALING]
Kramer, what the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
a pig-man!
I walked into the wrong room,
and there he was!
A pig-man?
A pig-man!
Half pig, half man!
That's great, Kramer.
So, anyway,
tell us what's involved
in being a godparent.
[AS DON CORLEONE]
Elaine, never ask me about my business.
Godfather?
The most important thing
is you help with the bris.
The bris?
A bris? You mean
circumcision?
Yeah.
I would advise
against that.
Well, Kramer,
it's a tradition.
Yeah, well, so was sacrificing
virgins to appease the gods,
but we don't
do that anymore.
Well,
maybe we should.
Hey.
Why are all those people
milling around my car?
Maybe they're
admiring your spot.
KRAMER:
They're looking up.
Hey, there's a guy
up on the roof!
KRAMER:
Whoa! That's the guy I told where the elevator was.
Oh, God, I hope
he doesn't jump.
[ALL GASPING]
[THUD]
My car!
A mohel? What the hell
is a mohel?
A mohel is the person
that performs a circumcision.
Well, where am I
gonna find a mohel?
Motels, models,
how do you find
a mohel?
Finding a mohel
is a piece of cake.
Any idiot can
find a mohel.
I have to hold the baby
while they do it!
That's a tough job!
How would you like that?
Hey, Jerry,
you ever seen one?
Well, you mean
that wasn't, uh...
Yeah.
No. You?
What did you think?
It had no face,
no personality.
It was like
a Martian.
But, hey, you know.
That's me.
Hey.
Well,
I got the estimate.
It's gonna cost more to repair
the roof than the car is worth!
I'm going over and seeing that
hospital administrator today.
Someone is gonna pay for this
damage, and it's not gonna be me!
Oh, you're screwed.
I know.
Swan dives
from 20 floors up.
Lands right on top!
What do I got,
a bull's-eye up there?
He couldn't move over
2 feet?
Land on the sidewalk.
It's city property!
Well, I have to
interview a mohel.
How about our little
Elaine, huh?
Attended the finest finishing
schools on the Eastern Seaboard.
Equestrian competitions,
debutante balls.
Look at her now:
interviewing mohels.
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
Don't ever question
my instincts,
because my instincts
are honed.
Look at that.
What now?
Look.
"Hospital receives grant
to conduct DNA research.
Government funds genetic
research at area hospital."
Yeah? So?
Pig-man, baby.
Pig-man!
If I have to hear about
this pig-man one more time--
Hey, I'm telling you,
the pig-man is alive!
The government has been
experimenting
with pig-men
since the fifties!
Oh, will you stop it.
Just because they're
conducting DNA research doesn't
mean they're creating a race of mutant pig-men!
Jerry, will you
wake up to reality?
It's a military thing!
They're probably creating
a whole army of pig warriors!
I'll tell you something.
I wish
there were pig-men.
You get a few of these pig-men
walking around,
suddenly I'm looking
a lot better.
That way if someone
wanted to fix me up,
they could say,
"Hey, at least he's no pig-man!"
Believe me, there'd be plenty
of women going for these pig-men.
Whatever their
deformity is,
there's always some group
of perverts attracted to it.
"Ooh, that little tail
really turns me on!"
That's just about
enough.
This doesn't
interest you?
Oh, no, it's fascinating,
but could you do me a favor?
Could you tape the rest of
"The Pig-men and the Women
Who Love Them" discussion,
and I'll listen to it
the next time I'm here.
I got to go find
a mohel.
You know, you should
call that off, Elaine.
It's a barbaric ritual!
Well, perhaps one day
when the pig-men roam free,
it will be stopped,
Kramer.
Until then,
off with their heads!
Kramer, isn't it
a question of hygiene?
It's a myth.
Besides, it makes
sex more pleasurable.
Yeah. So how does
that help me?
George,
you ever see one?
Yeah. My roommate
in college.
Yeah?
What did you think?
I got used to it.
I want to see the pig-man.
Show me the pig-man.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm going to show you.
and you'll never
be the same.
Maybe he's just a guy
with a nose like this.
You know a lot of people
have a nose like this.
They're not
necessarily pig-men.
Believe me, Jerry.
Somewhere in this hospital,
the anguished oink of pig-man
cries out for help!
Well, if I hear an anguished
oink, I'm out of here.
I don't see any pig-men.
I see human, human,
human.
Wait a second!
What?
Oh. It's George.
The administrator's
on the third floor,
so I'll meet you guys
back at the car.
Wait, George. You got room in
the car for the pig-man, huh?
The pig-man
can take the bus.
George, if the pig-man had a
car, he would give you a ride.
How do you know?
What if the pig-man
had a two-seater?
Be realistic, George.
I'll tell you what.
If pig-man shows up,
we'll squeeze him in.
I'll see you later.
Mr. Costanza,
come in. Come in.
It's been a very trying couple
of days around the hospital.
Doctors, patients,
everyone just grief-stricken
over this
unfortunate occurrence.
Well, I join them
in their grief.
Horrible thing!
Flew right past
the children's wing.
All the sick children in the
playroom looking out the window
just traumatized
by the incident.
Apparently, they thought
he was flying.
You know how
children are.
"Oh, look, a man is flying!
A man is flying!"
And then...splat.
That's where I come in,
um...on splat.
You see,
Mrs. Sweedler--
or is it Hospital
Administrator Sweedler?
Mrs. Sweedler.
Thank you very much.
You see, this tragedy
has affected me in a very...
very personal way.
How is that?
Yes, well,
you see...
the deceased...
landed on my car.
The splat, as it were,
actually occurred
on the roof of my car.
Now, of course,
I can't help but feel
that had it been
a convertible,
this whole tragedy
might have been averted.
But I've never really been
the kind of guy
to buy a convertible,
what with the baldness
and everything.
Well, I have known bald men
who owned convertibles.
They wore a hat.
Yes, but then everything's
all pulled down, and--
Ah, Anyway.
The damage,
unfortunately, has...
marred an otherwise
fine automobile,
rendering it
virtually undrivable.
Yes. Well,
that is a shame.
Yes! A shame. That is exactly
how I would put it.
Now, Mrs. Sweedler, with all due
discretion and sensitivity,
and taking in the whole
scope of the situation,
I just can't help
but think that...
the hospital
is somehow responsible
for compensating the other
still living victim
of this horrendous,
horrendous tragedy.
Mr. Costanza,
Yes?
a man plummeted tragically
to his ultimate demise, Yes.
and you greedily, callously
want to profit from it?
Well, "profit"?
I--
I think you'll see
from the estimate
that I'm not really
profiting that much.
It might be
a little high, but--
Get out.
Get out now.
Get out of my office!
Should I
just leave--?
Get out!
This is it.
KRAMER:
Uh, wait. Uh, excuse me.
What happened to the guy
that was in there before?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
No, you know. This.
No...
This doesn't look
familiar to you?
Uh, sir, uh--
Wait, now, look, look.
I know
what's going on.
The oink, oink?
Yes, well If you'll excuse me.
I have some patients I really--
Now, listen to me,
you little quack!
There was a half-man, half-pig
in that room over there!
Now, where is he?
Where is he?!
Half what?
You know what I mean!
Pork! Sausage!
"Abdee-abdee--
that's all folks!"
I think he's been
released.
Ugh.
He's lying!
All right, Kramer.
Enough of this.
I gotta go
find George.
All right.
You go ahead.
Kramer.
[♪]
Where's the mohel?
He'll be here.
He's late already.
Relax! You'd think
you were getting whacked.
I don't know why he asked me
to be the godfather.
We're not that close.
Just 'cause we're on the softball team?
I'm the pitcher,
he's the catcher.
He thinks we have
a special relationship?
I thought pitchers and catchers
did have a special rapport.
Well, maybe in hardball
with all the signals
and everything,
but I'm just lobbing it in.
We don't have any conferences.
He doesn't come out
to the mound and encourage me.
Well, what about me?
I just watched
a few games with her,
sitting in the stands.
Don't they have
any closer friends?
They're level jumping
on our friendship.
Yes, it is
level jumping!
[WHISTLING]
So, uh...Been
to a bris before?
No.
I been to a few of 'em.
If you start to get
woozy later,
which is quite common,
you know, stay close to me.
I'll get you through it.
I'm a cardiologist.
I think I'll manage.
Oh!
KRAMER:
Hey, we're not talking about a manicure.
Imagine. This is going
to be his first memory
of his parents
just standing there
while some stranger
cuts off a piece
of his manhood
and then serves
a catered lunch!
Myra?
She'll be okay.
Kramer, what's
the matter with you?
Me?
Oh, that's the mohel!
GUESTS:
Mohel.
Hi!
Hello! Hello!
Hello. I'm the mohel.
It's very nice
to meet you all.
[CLANGING]
What was that?
Jeez, it scared the hell
out of me!
My God, I almost
had a heart attack!
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm fine. Anyway...
We're here to perform
the mitzvah of the bris.
[BABY CRYING]
Is the baby going
to cry like that?
The baby cries with that
loud, sustained squealing cry?
'Cause that could
pose a problem.
Do have any control
over your child?
Because this would be
the time to exercise it,
when baby is crying in
the high-pitched squealing tone
that can drive
you insane!
Did you find
the place all right?
Did I find it
all right?
Could you send me to a more
dangerous neighborhood?
I'm dreading walking
back to the subway,
someone shouldn't smack
me and steal my bag.
Because I'll be lying there
And people will spit
on me and empty my pockets.
I'll be lying in the gutter like
a bum, a dog, a mutt, an animal!
God forbid anybody should
help me or call an ambulance!
Oh, no, that's
too much trouble,
to pick up a phone
and press some buttons!
Ahhh. What's the point?
Oh, yeah.
Darling, you see
where that glass is?
You see how the glass is near
the edge of the table?
You've got the whole
table there to put the glass.
Why you chose
the absolute edge
so half the glass
is hanging off the table--
You breathe, and that
glass falls over,
and then you got
broken glass on the carpet.
Embedded in the carpet fibers,
deep, deep in the shag,
Broken glass. Bits of broken
glass you can never get up.
You can't get it up
with a vacuum cleaner.
Even on your knees,
with a magnifying glass,
you'll never get
all the pieces.
And then you think
you got it all.
And then one day, two years
later, you're walking barefoot,
you step on broken glass
and kill yourself!
I don't think that's
what you want. Is it?
Do you? Huh? Huh?
Uh...
He's very highly
recommended, so...
You're holding
the baby?
No, no!
Hello? Who's holding
the baby?
Who's holding the baby?
Jerry is. Jerry,
do you wanna--?
Yeah. I'm holding
the baby.
Okay, go.
I'm going. I am.
I'm going.
Don't push me!
Okay, you sit there.
Now I need the baby.
Bring me the baby.
I need the baby!
No, I'm not going
to let you!
STAN:
Kramer! Hey, what are you doing?
Come back here!
[CLAMORING]
MOHEL:
People, people!
Compose yourself!
This is a bris!
We're performing a bris here,
not a burlesque show!
This is not
a school play!
This is not a baggy pants farce!
This is a bris.
A sacred, ancient
ceremony
symbolizing the covenant
between God and Abraham...
or something.
Oh!
No, don't touch anything.
Don't touch a thing!
I could have been a kosher
butcher like my brother.
The money's good.
He's got a union
with benefits.
And cows don't have
families.
You make a mistake with a cow,
you move on with your life.
Anyway...
JERRY:
Hurry up, George. Step on it!
All right,
all right!
Damn mohel!
He circumcised my finger.
The mohel circumcised
my finger!
You flinched.
Flinched? I did not flinch.
George, did I flinch?
Oh, how would he know?
He blacked out! He fainted!
It was
very dramatic.
The last thing I remember
was you flinching.
Then everything
went black.
Who's got tissues?
I need more tissues.
Look at this thing.
It's my phone finger!
Will you be careful? You're
getting blood all over the car!
What about the baby?
Oh, the baby's fine.
They just took him
to the hospital as a
precautionary measure.
But look at me!
I'm the one who's hurt!
Will you stop it? You're just
gonna need a few stitches!
Few stitches.
I never had stitches!
I'll be deformed.
I can't live with that.
Goes against my whole
personality. It's not me.
Hey,
look at that!
Boy,
are you lucky!
Another great spot right
in front of the hospital!
In an emergency yet!
How lucky are you, huh?
Is that
unbelievable?
How unbelievable
is that, huh?
Come on, give it to me!
Give it to me!
GEORGE:
I have never seen a mohel like that.
That was a one
in a million mohel.
I said I'm sorry.
Look at this.
It'll be okay. I'll see
you later, huh?
Where is he
going?
I'm going to look
for a bathroom.
Oh, well, if it isn't
shaky the mohel!
Nice job
on the circumcision,
but it's not supposed
to be a finger!
The circumcision
was perfect.
It was your fault.
You flinched.
Oh, who made you
a mohel?
Did you get your degree
from a matchbook?
You see?
He flinched again!
Nice mohel picking Elaine.
You picked a hell of a mohel!
One more peep, I'll slice you
like a smoked sturgeon!
Don't threaten me,
butcher boy!
Butcher boy?
Yeah, what was this?
What was this?
It was
your fault!
Jerry, the mohel's
got a knife!
Hey, what's going on
out here?
You should be ashamed
of yourself! The both of ya!
Ah! Blood!
Oh, How's the baby?
There's nothing wrong
with the baby.
The circumcision
went fine.
Thank God the flincher
didn't harm the baby!
I'll get you
for this!
This is my business!
This is my life.
No one ruins it
for me! No one!
Here's my card.
KRAMER:
Get out of my way!
[SNORTING]
I can't do it.
[AS DON CORLEONE]
Look what they did to my boy.
They massacred my boy.
You really do the worst
Godfather I've ever heard.
You're not even close.
Ahh.
[BUZZING]
Oh, that's the
Flicks.
It's a '76
Chevy Impala.
No, they stole it right
in front of the hospital.
I saw the guy
drive off in it.
Well, he's about 5 feet tall,
hairless,
pink complexion.
Looks like a pig.
Yeah. All right.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So...
Any word from
the pig-man?
No.
No. And he's not
a pig-man, is he?
No, he's not.
He's just a fat,
little mental-patient.
Myra, Stan.
Don't touch him!
What's
the matter?
You're out as godfather.
You too. You're both out.
But I didn't do--
No! No "buts."
We've made up our minds.
We want Kramer.
He showed us how much
he cares about Steven.
[AS DON CORLEONE]
Don't ever go against the family, Jerry.
[♪]
Godfather.
Yes.
To me what's really amazing,
that for every job there is
in the world, there's
someone willing to do it.
Someone goes: "Yes, I will stand
in the tunnel breathing exhaust
fumes, watching the cars go by,
making sure everything's okay."
Someone goes: "Yes, I will
work behind the elephant
with the big shovel.
I will do it."
Doctors go: "Yes, I will confine
myself to one particularly
"objectionable part of the human
body all day, every day.
I will do it."
I think a lot of people
that are unemployed
are not really unable
to find work,
they're just easily
disgusted.
"Yes, I'm starving and my family
has no clothing or shelter,
but I'm not cleaning
that up."