I had glasses
when I was 10 years old.
Anybody beat that? Anybody
got 'em younger than that?
WOMAN: Seven.
Seven?
Two?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Anybody born with glasses?
Come out...
Actually come out
of the birth canal and go,
"That was a hell
of a delivery,
"I'll tell you that.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Can I clean these?
"Does anybody have one
of those little cloths?
"I was just born.
They're a little...
Little smudgy."
Mmm!
Fantastic.
I told ya.
How good is this?
It's good.
How good?
Very good.
I know it.
They put real blueberries
in this. Real blueberries
What kind did you get?
Coffee.
They grind up the coffee beans
and put it in!
Let me test-taste that.
Huh? Huh?
Mmm! !¡Qué rico!
Suave.
And it's nonfat.
See, how could this
not have any fat?
It's too good.
You wanna taste mine?
Oh, you wanna taste mine.
No, I don't.
If you wanna taste mine,
you don't have to offer me
some of yours.
All right,
let's just forget it.
Kramer's gonna
clean up on this place.
What do you mean?
He invested in it.
No kidding.
Yeah, we've been coming
here everyday.
This is so [BLEEP] good!
Jerry!
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's nice.
All right,
we should get goin',
but I'm going to get
a little bit more, okay? Yep.
Oh, God,
look who's here.
Who is it?
This guy from
my old neighborhood,
Lloyd Braun.
He's a big adviser
to Mayor Dinkins.
He thinks he's so cool.
Ah, really?
Hey, George!
Hey!
Lloyd!
My friend Jerry.
Hi.
So I hear you're living back
home now or something?
Yeah, there was a fire
in my apartment.
Fire, huh? Hmm.
There's a lot of major chicks
in this place, huh?
Something wrong
with your arm?
Uh...
Uh, yeah,
actually.
I-I bumped my elbow
on a desk
and, uh,
injured something.
And...now it sort of
moves involuntarily.
Wow. That's
a bitch, huh?
So how are
your parents doing?
Oh, pretty good.
This place does
some business, huh?
Yeah, this is
my first time here.
Hey, she's a doll.
Hi.
Hello.
Uh, Elaine,
this is Lloyd.
Hi.
Oh, hi. Very nice
to meet you.
Nice to
meet you too.
[CHUCKLES]
[GIGGLES]
Well, I'm really sorry
I gotta run now.
Oh...
[GIGGLES]
Well, take it easy,
huh, George?
Yeah, yeah.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
[GASPS]
Boy, he is really cute.
He's a jerk.
He's gone,
George.
All right,
all right.
So there were a lotta
people there, huh?
Oh, man,
that yogurt place--
You're gonna
make a fortune. Yeah.
They're doing
incredible business.
I told you
to go in on it.
How did you know?
Well, I tasted it
at the one downtown.
It's got
a remarkable texture.
You'd never know
it was nonfat.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
Me.
Uh.
Hey, I had the show
of my life last night.
I ad-libbed, like,
10 new minutes.
Yeah, but did you tape it?
Vfft!
Yeah.
Right there.
I got it.
I did this thing on
the Ottoman Empire.
Like, what was this,
a whole empire based
on puttin' your feet up?
Yeah.
I'm tellin' ya,
I got, like, a whole new
Tonight Show here.
Hi.
Hey.
What's the matter?
Oh, I-- I was havin' lunch,
and I bit down on the fork. Ngh.
Boy, it's hard to believe,
with so much biting experience,
a person could still
make a mistake like that.
Yommm!
What?
You're gettin' heavy.
Yeah, you look like
you put on 5...
10 pounds.
Kramer!
And I'll tell ya
something else,
you look a little chunky
yourself, buddy.
Me?
Yeah.
No.
Where's your
bathroom scale?
ELAINE:
Oh, my God! I've gained 7 pounds!
JERRY:
I've gained 8!
I told ya.
I thought I put on a couple,
but 7 pounds!
How did I gain
7 pounds?
How--? How did
I gain 8?
I don't get it.
I've-- I've been doing
the same exercises.
I haven't been eating
anything different.
Me either.
Wait a second.
Maybe it's that yogurt.
No, no, no.
That's 100-percent nonfat.
How else could
this have happened?
Well, maybe it's the Oreos.
I don't eat Oreos.
You don't eat Oreos?
The way you break 'em open.
You're ahhhhh-uhhh-agh.
You're practically
havin' sex with 'em.
What about me?
You? You're gettin' old.
Maybe your yogurt
isn't so nonfat.
Oh, guess again,
tubby.
Jerry, there's gotta be a way
we can find that out.
There must be some lab
that would do that kinda thing.
Oh! I've got it!
What?
I'll call the Food and
Drug Administration.
Hey, I'll tell
you what, chubs.
If that yogurt has fat in it,
I will put myself on
an all-yogurt diet...
[SNAPS]
...for a week.
Well, let's start
the insanity.
Nnnn, giddyup.
"Tommy Tune is
a very good dancer."
You ever see Tommy Tune
dance, George?
No.
I like tap-dancing.
FRANK:
Tap-dancing.
Anyone can tap-dance.
It's all in those shoes.
Are you kidding?
They practice for years,
those people.
What's for supper?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Somebody's at the door.
Tommy Tune is very tall.
That helps.
It makes him lankier.
Lloyd!
Hello,
Mrs. Costanza.
Georgie,
Lloyd Braun is here.
FRANK:
Hey, Lloyd!
What are you
doing here?
Well, I was just in the
neighborhood visiting my mother,
so I thought I'd drop by,
say hello.
Georgie, come here
and say hello.
How you doing?
I hear you're a big adviser
for Dinkins now.
That's right.
Hey, George.
Hey, Lloyd.
How's it goin'?
I ran into George
yesterday in the city.
Ow!
What's the matter
with you?
So, uh,
how's the arm?
It's good.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Yeah, his arm moves
like this.
Your arm
moves like this?
Yeah.
I've never seen your arm
move like this.
Me either.
Well, it comes
and goes.
It's like some kind
of a...spasm.
I asked Mr. Dinkins
if he knew
any good orthopedists,
and he said
he had the best.
So I made an appointment
for you. Dr. Dekter.
Mayor Dinkins got
an appointment for him?
You mentioned George's name
to Mayor Dinkins?
You discussed George
with the mayor of New York?
Dinkins was talking about you.
He was discussing you!
You know, Lloyd,
I've been to the doctor.
There's really nothing
they can do.
Hey! Mayor Dinkins
set this up for you.
You know what kind of a doctor
he must be if Dinkins knows him?
All right, all right!
I'll go.
Well, that's great.
And I'll be very interested
to hear the diagnosis.
ELAINE:
Uh-huh.
Okay, well,
we're coming down.
All right. Okay.
I got a place
that can analyze it.
It's in Brooklyn.
We have to drive there.
They said
they could do it?
Yeah. It's 45 bucks.
All right, let's go down
to the yogurt store,
and get a specimen.
Mm-hmm.
[KNOCKING]
Well, I hope you're satisfied.
What?
Every word out of
my son's mouth now is:
[BLEEPING]
You know what he said to me
five minutes ago?
Where's my [BLEEP] cupcake?
Gee, I'm really sorry.
He wants to be like you
because you're a comedian.
Maybe you could
talk to him?
I'd be happy to.
Thank you.
Uh, Mary, we've been eating
a lot of your husband's yogurt
at the yogurt place.
Yeah.
Does that have
any fat in it?
No [BLEEP] way.
Well, it was very nice
seeing you again.
Oh, it was good
seeing you.
Oh, by the way,
who was that gorgeous woman
I saw you with the other day?
Oh, uh...
just a friend of mine.
You must mean Elaine.
Isn't she adorable?
She is, she is. How about
givin' me her number, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, you know, Lloyd,
I really don't have it.
She works at
Pendant Publishing.
Elaine Benes.
Oh. Great.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Oh, that Lloyd Braun!
He is something, isn't he?
Well, I wouldn't
hear of it.
I said,
"Nice try, granny,"
and I sent her
to the back of the line.
[ALL LAUGH]
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
Say, this yogurt is
really somethin', huh?
And it's nonfat!
I've been waitin' for somethin'
like this my whole life,
and it's finally here!
[LAUGHING]
Hey, Seinfeld.
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
using obscenities around my son.
It was an accident.
I'm gonna talk to him.
I'll have a small, plain
vanilla, in a cup, to go.
That's nonfat, right?
That's right.
I'm on a special diet,
and the doctor said
I can't have any fat.
Yeah, well,
there is no fat.
Hey, another round of strawberry
for me and my friends!
[LAUGHING]
Hurry, Jerry, hurry!
How's it doin'?
Not so good.
Well, you can't have this
tested now. It's melting.
So what?
It changes the molecules.
Oh, you don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Hey, fatso, I got
a 90 in biology.
You call me fatso
one more time,
you're gonna be
walkin' back.
Um, hi, hi. I called earlier
about getting the yogurt tested?
Oh, right.
Would you fill this out,
please?
Does it matter
if it's melted?
No.
You know, this is gonna
take a couple of days.
That's okay.
Hello, there.
Hello.
Mm.
Ooh, test tubes.
[CHUCKLES]
Cool.
What do you got there?
Actually, this is
Mr. Giuliani's blood.
We're doing a cholesterol
workup on it.
Okay, I'm done.
[CHUCKLING]
It was really nice
meeting you.
Well, the pleasure's
all mine, hm?
You can't take
that chemist out.
Why not?
Because she's
like the jury.
She's gotta be
sequestered.
I'm not taking her out
just to influence the results.
Well, I think
the whole thing stinks.
It smells. Smells bad.
Smells really bad.
That's enough.
What?
With the "smells."
So he made an appointment
for me to see Dinkins' doctor.
He's just trying
to humiliate me.
Uh-huh.
And I have to go.
If I don't go,
he'll know I'm lying.
Well, so, what're
you gonna do?
Sit in the doctor's office
doing this?
He's gonna think
you're a mental patient.
I don't care.
Look, Lloyd doesn't know
what he's up against.
This is nothing to me.
My whole life is a lie.
Hey.
So guess who
called me?
Oh, don't tell me.
Lloyd.
We're going out
tomorrow night.
All right, look,
he's gonna ask you
about my arm.
So just tell him
I banged it against a desk,
and it's been moving
involuntarily ever since.
I can't say that.
Why not?
What if I like him?
I'm gonna start out
lying to this guy?
So you're taking
his side?
No, but what if
we get married or something?
We'll always have that
between us.
Already you're
marryin' this guy?
You never know.
Believe me, you're not
gonna marry him.
All right, well, then, what if
we become a couple, George?
Every time we see you,
you're gonna be walkin'
around goin' like this?
Even you can't keep that up.
No, I believe
he can.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
You know Jerry.
Of course.
He's a funny [BLEEP].
MARY:
See?
Listen, Matthew, I-I wanna
explain something to you.
Now...
cursing is not something
that most comedians do.
You did it.
That's true,
but it was an accident,
and I haven't done
it since,
and I would never
do it again.
And if you
continue cursing,
you'll never become a comedian
like me when you grow up.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Excuse me one second.
You know, Lloyd advises Dinkins
on everything he does.
Yeah, yeah. Big adviser.
He tells him what soap to use.
What the [BLEEP] are you doin',
you little piece of [BLEEP]!
[CLATTERING]
Shh!
We don't want to disturb
the security guard.
Where's the lights?
Oh.
How about this?
Mmm.
A Bunsen burner.
Oh, yeah, huh?
Ooh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoo.
Yeow!
Mmm.
You want a taste?
No.
It's cappuccino.
Hmm.
Yes.
Mmm...
Hm?
It's delicious.
I hear you.
Nonfat?
Well...
you tell me.
Is the verdict in yet?
No.
Well...
this is in case
there's a tie, hm?
Well, as far as
I know,
he bumped his arm
into a door,
and it's kind of
got this
in...voluntary movement.
It's, um, sort of
a, ahem, spasm.
So anyway, you're a big adviser
to Dinkins, huh?
Yeah, yeah. It's coming
right down to the wire.
Wow. You know what I would do
if I was running for mayor?
One of my campaign themes
would be
that everybody should wear
nametags all the time
to make the city
friendlier.
Nametags, huh?
Everybody would
know everybody.
It would be like
a small town.
Maybe I'll mention that to him.
Really?
Wow.
You sure you don't
want any yogurt?
No, I'm watching
my weight.
Oh, it's nonfat.
Yeah, so they say.
I'm done. Shall we go?
Yeah, okay.
Three days, he hasn't called me,
and you know why?
Because he thinks
I'm too fat.
He said that?
No, but I saw
the look on his face
when he put
his arm around me.
And then we went
to his apartment,
and I sat on
one of his chairs...
and it broke.
And he says,
"Boy, you're a lotta woman."
[WHISTLING]
Hey...
So hear anything
on the yogurt?
No, but I expect
to hear anytime.
Well, I wouldn't
get your hopes up.
Why do you say that?
No reason.
Oh!
Did you hear about that Dinkins?
What about him?
You didn't hear?
He's proposin' a plan
where everyone in the city
should wear nametags.
Nametags?
So people can go around
saying hello to one another.
Oh, I see.
So you can go,
"Hey, you know who I saw
wilding today? Herb!"
He's becoming
a laughingstock!
You know the Times
has already stated
it could cost him
the election.
[LAUGHING]
Nametags!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Well...
the yogurt
verdict is in.
Fat!
Yeow!
The next morning,
I-- I woke up...
and it was going like this.
I-I can control it
if I really concentrate,
but otherwise--
Oh!
Uh-huh.
Yes, well,
I'm going to have to be
perfectly honest with you.
Please, doctor.
I've examined you.
Yes.
I've looked at your x-rays.
Uh-huh.
And I find
that there's absolutely
nothing wrong with you.
Hmm.
Really.
Nothing?
Nothing...
that would indicate
involuntary spasms.
Well, it's kind of
a mystery, isn't it?
No, not really.
How so?
May I suggest the possibility
that you're faking?
Faking?!
What makes you think
that I have time
to see doctors, take x-rays,
make appointments,
when there's absolutely
nothing wrong with me?
What kind of a person
would do a thing like that?
I don't know what kind of person
would do something like that.
Obviously,
a very sick person.
A very immature person.
A person who has no regard
for wasting other people's
valuable time.
Goodbye.
Now, see here,
doctor--
I said, goodbye.
Fine.
Ow!
ELAINE:
Jerry, come on, look.
Let's go over to
that yogurt store.
Look, Elaine, I've been
thinkin' about this.
This has gotta be
a massive conspiracy.
Who knows how deep it goes?
Hey, look, wait a second.
Kramer, turn that up.
MAN [ON TV]:
Rudy Giuliani, who underwent a physical last week
received some
startling news today
when his cholesterol count
turned out to be
a whopping 375.
What effect this will have
on the minds of the voters
remains to be seen.
In another development,
Mayor Dinkins has fired
his top advisor, Lloyd Braun,
who was believed
to be responsible
for the nametag fiasco.
We now take you
to Giuliani headquarters,
where Rudy Giuliani
is about to make a statement.
It's hard to understand
because I've been doing
everything I normally do.
I've been watching
my diet carefully.
I exercise regularly.
My only indulgence, I guess,
would be that I eat a lot
of frozen yogurt,
but it's nonfat.
Nonfat yogurt?
Oh, my God.
They got Giuliani,
and he doesn't know it!
Now look what
you've done.
Well, we've got
to do something.
I'm calling Giuliani's
headquarters.
GEORGE [LAUGHING]:
Nametags!
What kind of
an idiot thinks
anybody would be interested
in an idea like that?
I don't think it's so bad.
People should wear nametags.
Everyone would be
a lot friendlier.
"Hello, Sam."
"How ya doin', Joe?"
Hey.
Your arm,
it moved again.
I thought you said it went away.
I banged it on the desk
in the doctor's office.
[WHIMPERS]
Quiet!
They're starting
the press conference.
GIULIANI [ON TV]:
My campaign staff has received
some very disturbing
information
regarding the fat content
in yogurt that's being sold
throughout the city.
I pledge to you now
that if I'm elected mayor,
as my first order of business,
I'll appoint
a special task force
to investigate this matter.
I promise you,
my fellow New Yorkers,
that Mayor Giuliani
will do everything possible
to cleanse the city
of this falsified
nonfat yogurt.
JERRY:
The old yogurt was so much better.
Oh, this is terrible.
Pheh!
Oh, it stinks.
Mine too.
We got one
more day.
I can't eat this.
Hey. Jerry.
Thanks a lot.
I hope you're happy.
It had fat in it.
It's not good for you.
I don't care!
It was good!
I was enjoying it.
Had to interfere.
Couldn't leave
well enough alone.
Well, I will get even
with you for this.
You can count on it!
ELAINE:
Hey, you guys.
Listen to this.
"Apparently some blood spilled
into Mr. Giuliani's test tube
"causing
his cholesterol count
"to be 150 points higher
than was initially reported.
"Ironically, the mishap,
"by bringing
the nonfat yogurt scandal
"to the attention
of the public,
"probably clinched the election
for the Republican.
"It was the one issue
"which seemed
to electrify the voters
and swept Giuliani
into office."
So in effect, the yogurt
won him the election.
I wonder what actually
happened in that lab.
Yeah. Me too.
I can't eat this!
Thanks for ruining
my daddy's business,
you fat [BLEEP].
[♪]
There's nothing more fun
than cursing when you're a kid.
I mean, it's like gettin'
the keys to the car, isn't it?
You're doin' something
you're not supposed to do,
and that's all you want.
And there's nothing less fun
than when you're an adult,
and having to use
those wholesome curses.
"Fudge!"
"Sugar!"
"Consarnit!"
What the hell is
"consarnit," anyway?
I mean,
you've stubbed your toe,
and you say, "Consarnit,"
you might as well say,
"Yippee!"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
But if you've ever been
to a foreign country,
the first thing you learn
are the curse words, right?
Travel halfway around the world
to experience some centuries-old
exotic civilization,
the first thing you ask is,
"How do they say 'doodie' here?"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]