I never get enough sleep.
I stay up late at night
'cause I'm "night guy."
Night guy wants to stay up late.
"What about getting up
after five hours of sleep?"
"Oh, that's
morning guy's problem.
"That's not my problem.
I'm night guy.
I stay up as late as I want."
So you get up in the morning,
the alarm,
you're exhausted, groggy.
Oh, you hate that night guy.
See, night guy always
screws morning guy.
There's nothing
morning guy can do.
The only thing
morning guy can do
is try and oversleep
often enough
so that day guy
loses his job,
and night guy has no money
to go out anymore.
Do you ever spit
on anybody from here?
No. You?
No.
Do you ever
think about it?
Yeah.
Me too.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Well, I got it.
You got me the air conditioner?
Well, what do you think?
Beautiful.
What air conditioner?
Well, my buddy works
in an appliance store,
and he got us 30% off.
Is it a good one?
Good one?
It's a Commando 8.
Commando 8?
Twelve thousand BTUs.
I thought you hated
air conditioning.
You've never had
an air conditioner.
Yeah, but Amy likes
air conditioning.
Oh, you're getting
an air conditioner for Amy.
Amy doesn't like
the temperature up here.
She's a little hot.
All right.
Okay,
so I'm gonna measure
the window up, okay?
Yeah.
Well...
rock on!
I gotta get out of this city.
So you're tunneling
to the center of the Earth?
I'm at the health club.
And while I'm in the pool,
some guy walks off
with my glasses.
Who steals
prescription glasses?
You don't have an old pair?
I broke 'em
playing basketball.
He was running from a bee.
Now if I want
to see anything,
I gotta wear these.
George, those are
prescription goggles?
What is there to see
in a health-club pool?
There's a lot of change
down there.
When I find that guy,
this much I vow:
Those glasses will be returned
to their rightful owner!
We're behind you, Aquaboy.
Godspeed.
What kind of
a sick, demented person
wants another
person's glasses?
Yeah, especially
those frames.
You know what
you ought to do?
Go see my friend Dwayne at
J&T Optical on Columbus Avenue.
He'll give you 30% off.
Pssh. Yeah, come on.
Hey, he just got me 30% off
on an air conditioner.
Really?
Retail is for suckers.
Wow. Uh...
All right,
what do I have to do?
You just gotta
mention my name.
That's it?
That's it. Click!
What about these?
They look good.
I liked the other one too.
I've liked about
five of them.
Well, it's a tough decision.
I have to wear these everyday.
[SIGHS]
I'm decidin' on a new face.
Come on, George.
Pick a face and go with it.
Now, those look good.
They're very bold.
Yes, they are bold.
Jerry, what do you think?
I think these women
would be pretty good-lookin'
if they weren't
wearing glasses.
Oh, hi there,
little doggy.
Do you mind
if I pet your dog?
It's okay with me.
[WHIMPERS]
Hi there,
little doggy.
[DOG BARKS]
[SCREAMS]
Hey, you can't have
that dog in here.
You okay?
Did he bite you?
[WHIMPERING]
Can you believe
that guy?
I'm okay
It's just a nip.
He just walked away!
And once again I'm standing
here like a little man.
Well, not
this time.
You! Dog man!
My leg looks pretty bad.
Let me take you over
to the emergency room.
Okay.
Hey, any luck?
Did you catch him?
Uh...no, no.
All right, I'm gonna take Elaine
over to the hospital.
Good, good. Do that.
What's the matter?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, nothing.
What is it?
I can't tell you.
Jerry, can we go?
Yeah, yeah,
in a second, in a second.
What do you mean,
you can't tell me?
I can't tell you.
Don't ask.
I'm asking.
Jerry,
my leg.
Yeah, yeah. Here.
Take care of it.
Come on, George. What is it?
I saw Amy making out
with your cousin Jeffrey.
What?
They were right outside.
Amy and Jeffrey?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes. Positive.
But you can't see.
There's no lenses
in those frames.
I know. I was squinting.
Okay, listen, Jerry, you just
catch up with me, okay?
You can just follow
the trail of blood.
We're gonna have
to talk about this later.
Thank you.
Taxi!
Excuse me.
What do you think of these?
Oh, we just got those in.
It's a very exciting new frame.
Yes, it is exciting!
All right, this is
gonna be my new face.
All right, do you have
a prescription?
Yeah.
Kramer.
What?
What about him?
You do know Kramer.
Yes.
Well, I'm mentionin' his name.
Cha-chik!
Why?
Because...
You know...
No, I don't know.
Look, I'm gonna need
a deposit on these.
Oh, come on.
Cousin Jeffrey?
It's not possible.
Why not? They could've met.
She loves the park, he works
for the Parks Department.
Oh...
Jerry, that is so ridiculous.
George didn't even
have his glasses on.
But he was squinting.
So what? Squinting doesn't make
that much of a difference.
Are you kidding?
I've seen him squint.
He can squint his way down
to, like, 20-30 vision.
Once we were driving
down from the Catskills,
and he lost his glasses,
he squinted his way
from Wurtsboro
down to the Tappan Zee Bridge.
He was spottin' raccoons
on the road.
Okay.
Okay? That's it?
I--? I don't need a shot?
[THICK ACCENT]
Not shot. Dog bite.
No, no, no.
I know I wasn't shot.
Do I need a shot?
Not shot. Dog bite.
Woof-woof, not bang-bang.
Ah, look at this. Cable's out.
Oh, that's okay.
We don't have to watch TV.
No, no, no.
No trouble at all.
It's the principle of the thing.
I like them to know that
I know what's going on,
that they're not...
getting away with anything.
Unh, I'm on hold.
So, what'd you do yesterday?
Yesterday?
Yeah. You remember yesterday.
Beautiful day,
good day to be...out.
I didn't do anything.
[LAUGHING]
Well, you must've done something.
Mmm...no, nothing really.
Didn't go out of the house?
Didn't take a walk on...
Columbus Avenue?
Well, I did go out
for a little while.
Well, your day's getting
more interesting already.
Oh. See?
Told me they'd be
back in a minute,
and they lied.
You can't trust anyone.
No, you can't.
Well, let's cut
the bull, sister!
You think I don't know
about you swappin' spit
with somebody yesterday
on Columbus Avenue?
What are you talking about?
Look, my friend saw you.
Saw me? With who?
You tell me.
There's nothing to tell.
There isn't?
No.
Oh.
All right.
Wanna get some pizza?
I had a feeling this was
too good to be true. Why?
I knew there had to be
another side to you.
No, no, there's no side.
There is a side, an ugly side.
No, no, no ugly side.
Look, I think
I'm gonna go.
Why?
It's really hot in here.
Uh, so are we gonna still
go out on Friday, though?
Yeah. When are you gettin'
an air conditioner?
I-it's comin'.
It's a Commando 8, 12,000 BTUs.
It's gonna be
like a meat locker in here.
I was an idiot
for listening to you.
Hey, I saw
what I saw.
Oh, everything was
going so well.
She hadn't seen
any flaws in me.
Now she sees a side.
What side?
A bad side, an ugly side.
Oh, so what?
So what?
I wasn't planning
on showing that side
for another six months.
Now you made me throw off
the whole learning curve.
Why don't you
just ask Jeffrey?
Oh, he'd just deny it.
There must be some way
to find out.
Amy said nothing happened.
You're gonna take
her word over mine?
I'm your best friend!
Yeah, but you're blind as a bat.
I was squinting!
Remember that drive
from Wurtsboro?
I was spottin'
those raccoons.
They were mailboxes,
you idiot.
I didn't have
the heart to tell ya.
Hey, look.
A dime.
Huh, Mercury head.
You mind?
No, keep it.
What happened?
You buzzed 5 minutes ago.
There was a dog
in front of the building,
and it spooked me.
I couldn't come in
until he left.
A little white dog?
Yeah.
Snowball?
You're afraid
of Snowball?
I'm afraid of dogs now.
He's like a squirrel.
Well, he frightened me.
Did you get the shot?
No. He said
I didn't need a shot.
You got bit
by a strange dog,
and you didn't get
a rabies shot?
Why, you think I should've?
Oh-ho!
You should go back
to the optical store
and ask Dwayne if he knows the
name of the owner of the dog.
All right, that's a good idea.
I'm gonna do that.
Ah.
The AC's on its way.
Ahem. Pardon me.
I went to see
your friend Dwayne,
there was no discount.
What?
That's right. No discount.
Well, did you
mention my name?
Yes, I mentioned your name.
And?
Pfft! Bupkis.
I don't believe this.
That guy owes me bigtime.
I got him off sugar!
Look, I'm gonna go down there
with you right now. Come on.
All right. Let me--
I'm gonna grab an apple.
All right.
Hey, Kramer.
Yeah.
[LAUGHING]
Elaine's afraid of Snowball.
Little Snowball?
He runs on batteries.
You know, George,
that's an onion.
Yes, it is.
He couldn't tell
an apple from an onion,
and he's your eyewitness.
I saw them makin' out.
You can believe it.
I don't know
what to believe.
You're eatin' onions,
you're spottin' dimes.
I don't know
what the hell is goin' on.
Look, all you gotta do
is get Amy and Jeffrey
together somewhere. That's it.
Hey, wait a second,
wait a second.
I'm goin' over to Jeffrey's
apartment tomorrow night
to pick up these
Paul Simon tickets.
I'm gonna
surprise Amy.
All I gotta do is
bring her with me.
And then when Jeffrey
opens the door,
it's Howdy Doody time.
Mmm. Right this way, Mr. Doody.
[TEARFULLY]
You'll see. I'm right.
Hey, Dwayney.
Oh, hello,
Kramer.
What is goin' on here?
What are you talking about?
I'm talkin' about
the 30% discount.
Um, excuse me.
A man came in here--
Elaine,
don't interrupt.
They're discounting
something.
Who said anything
about a discount?
Oh, how quickly we forget.
You owe me, buddy.
For what?
Whoop! Remember this?
What are you doing?
Six months ago you were eating
four of those for breakfast
and chasing it
with a Ring Ding.
And two Butterfingers
on the train!
Sound familiar?!
Put that away.
Remember that night I found you
at Dinky Doughnuts?
You were all hopped up
on cinnamon swirls!
They wouldn't
serve you anymore.
You wouldn't even have
any teeth
if it wasn't for me taking you
over to Joe's fruit stand
and stuffin' cantaloupe
down your throat,
but so much
for gratitude.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
All right! All right!
All right!
I'll give 'em the discount.
Just put that thing away.
But this squares us.
Could I just have the name--?
Out!
We'll see you,
Dwayne.
I don't know
what to tell you, Elton.
Uh-oh. Listen to this.
This is not good.
Listen to these symptoms
for rabies:
anxiety, irritability.
I've got those. I'm irritable.
Who picked these out?
I did.
They're ladies' glasses.
I mean, all you need is that
little chain around your neck,
so you can wear 'em
while you're playing canasta.
Well, Elaine was
supposed to help me.
Hey, I got bit by a dog!
I had to go to the hospital!
I was bleeding to death!
I can't solve every
little problem you have!
Hey, hey.
Oh.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Commando 8 has arrived!
I'll get the window.
12,000 BTUs of
raw cooling power, huh?
Ha, ha!
Yeah.
Installed.
That--?
That's it?
You don't have to
screw it in or anything?
No. Just plug it in, and
the Commando 8 does the rest.
I'll seal it up later,
all right?
Yeah. Just in time
for Amy.
Oh, yeah, when are you
gonna execute that plan?
Oh, God.
I've got such a headache.
Aw! That's another symptom.
Of what?
Rabies.
Oh, that's fatal.
You don't want that.
I know I don't want it!
I don't need you to tell me
what I don't want,
you stupid hipster doofus!
Hey, hey.
What is this?
What's goin' on here?
I'm sorry, Kramer.
I'm sorry.
No, it's all right.
I had a friend
who had rabies once.
May I have
one of those, madam?
Madam? What are you
callin' me madam for?
They're
ladies' glasses.
No, look. Here.
See, it's right here.
[CHUCKLES]
"Gloria Vanderbilt collection."
He sold me
ladies' glasses!
I...
I think I'm...
I'm having
trouble swallowing.
I-- I can't swallow.
She's got rabies, just like
my friend Bob Sacamano.
Look at that,
she's delirious.
She's foaming
at the mouth!
Is this gonna hurt?
Yes, very much.
What if Jeffrey's
not home?
Did you ever
think of that?
He'll be home.
It's Friday night.
Big night on
the Nature Channel.
Let me tell
you something.
There is no way
Cousin Jeffrey is dating Amy.
He looks like a horse.
He does look
like a horse.
Yeah, he's got
a real horse face.
[GASPS]
Hey, look at this.
It's the guy
with the dog!
Hey! Hey,
you down there!
Remember me?
I had to get shots
because of your stupid dog!
MAN:
Hey, who you callin' stupid?!
Hey, should we spit on him?
No, no, no. Come on.
Let's go get him.
♪ Oh, my papaya ♪
The air conditioner!
[HORNS HONKING]
[DOG BARKING]
[CRASH]
[DOG YELPS]
I think it got the dog!
Ahhh.
Ah, boy.
Excuse me.
Uh, I'm new here.
Uh, would you mind walking
me back to my locker?
Oh, uh, sure.
Why not?
Uh, there you go.
Hey, that's the guy.
What guy?
The guy that stole
my glasses.
This time I got him!
Could you pick it up
a little?
Where the hell
are we going?
Ah, phooey.
He's getting on a bus.
Damn.
Those are nice glasses.
I don't like 'em.
They pinch my nose.
Is that right?
Dwayne, my friend and I
would like to exchange frames.
Could you put his lenses
in my frames
and mine in his?
Yeah, we can do that.
[WHISPERS]
Excuse me.
And I'd like
a discount.
Why should I
give you a discount?
Listen, you're lucky I'm not
askin' for a whole refund.
[WHISPERS]
You gave me ladies' frames.
What's that
about ladies' frames?
Say, I'm trying
to track down
that lady that was
in here the other day.
The one that was
messing with my dog.
She's trying
to track you down.
Well, I would love
to talk with her.
Heh, heh.
She lives on
81st street?
No, that's Jerry.
Really?
You wouldn't happen to know
what apartment he's in?
Yeah. 5A.
Thanks a lot.
So, what are we
doing here?
Oh, you'll
find out.
I don't know.
You're acting very mysteriously.
Well, I'm very mysterious
by nature.
A lot of women find
that attractive.
I find it annoying.
Oh.
Hello.
Uncle Leo.
Come on in.
Uh, this is Amy.
Hello, Amy.
Uncle Leo,
what're you doing here?
Jeffrey went out
tonight.
Oh,
very convenient.
I'm supposed to tape
this nature show for him.
He loves
nature.
Botany, zoology.
You know, his botany teacher
from college
stays in close touch
with him.
They became friends.
Really?
That's
pretty rare.
I mean actual friends,
like equals.
They have dinner together,
they have discussions, they--
Uncle Leo,
did he leave
any tickets here for me?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'll get 'em.
Thank you.
What tickets?
To the Paul Simon
"Concert in the Park."
We're going to
the Paul Simon concert?
That's right, lady.
Ha-ha!
What a great surprise.
I thought
you'd like that.
Oh, so that's why you've been
acting so mysteriously.
Now you know.
That, and that alone,
is the reason.
You know Jeffrey's
favorite animal?
The leopard.
Why is that?
He likes the spots.
Oh, uh, here's--
Here's the tickets.
Thank you.
Oh, uh, he asked me
to give you a message.
He said that, uh,
he's very sorry,
and, uh, he hopes
you'll forgive him.
Ah-ha! So it's true.
You were makin' out
with him.
What are you talking about?
I don't know Jeffrey.
Oh, so this is why
you brought me up here.
Very convincing,
but it's not gonna
work this time.
What are you
talking about?
All he meant was
that he was sorry
that the seats
aren't very good.
Oh.
Wanna get
some pizza?
Boy, these really do
pinch the nose.
Tough luck.
A deal's a deal.
Oh, my God. It is them.
[WHINNIES]
I still don't know how
you spotted that dime.
I think you planted it.
Plus I got to pay that vet bill
for the stupid dog.
I don't know how
that guy got my name.
Yeah. Heh.
All right.
Boy, these really
do pinch.
I tell you, if I ever find
the son of a bitch
that stole my glasses...
But I want to know,
when did glasses
go from being this carefully
crafted medical apparatus
to just this mall impulse item?
"Honey, I'm going out
for a yogurt
and a pair of trifocals.
You need anything?"
It's always glasses
in about an hour.
"Well, how much are they?"
"75 bucks."
"Well, here's 72.
It's about 75, okay?"
What, you tryin'
to coordinate it
with the one-hour photo place,
is that the idea?
"Hurry up. Gimme the glasses.
My pictures are coming out
right now. I need to see 'em."
Then they have
those Woolworth glasses,
you know, that are like,
they're there.
They're there now.
No eye exam, you don't have any
idea what's wrong with the eyes,
and the glasses are made up.
They are ready and waiting
for you to just walk in,
"Thank you. Bye." And just walk
right into a wall. Bang.