I love these nature shows.
I watch any kind of nature show.
It's amazing
how you can always relate
to what they're
talking about.
You're watching
the African dung beetle
You're going, "Boy,
his life is a lot like mine."
You always root for
whichever animal's the star
of the show that week.
Like if it's the antelope,
and a lion's chasing
the antelope,
you go, "Run, antelope, run!
Use your speed! Get away!"
The next week it's the lion,
and then you go,
"Get the antelope!
Eat him! Bite his ass!
Trap him! Don't let him
use his speed!"
Well, did he bring it up
in the meeting?
Elaine,
see this T-shirt?
Six years I've had
this T-shirt.
It's my best one.
I call him...
Golden Boy.
Yeah-- I'm on the phone here.
Golden Boy's always the first
shirt I wear out of the laundry.
Here. Touch Golden Boy.
No, thanks.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll hold.
But see,
look at the collar.
It's fraying.
Golden Boy
is slowly dying.
Each wash brings him
one step closer.
That's what makes the T-shirt
such a tragic figure.
Why don't you just let
Golden Boy
soak in the sink
with some Woolite?
No!
The reason
he's the iron man
is because he goes out there
and he plays every game!
Wash, spin, rinse, spin!
You take that
away from him,
you break his spirit.
Yeah.
[GASPS]
What?
He is?!
Oh, that's fantastic!
I'm so excited!
Yes, I'm excited! Okay.
Okay, I'll be in soon.
Yeah, yeah! I'm coming!
I'm coming! Okay, bye.
Yuri Testikov,
the Russian writer!
The guy who's in the gulag?
Yeah! Pendant's
publishing his new book,
and I'm gonna be
working on it!
Lippman and I are gonna go
to the airport on Thursday
and pick him up
in a limousine!
You wanna borrow
Golden Boy?
Oh! Do you know
what this means?
It's like working
with Tolstoy.
I read an unbelievable thing
about Tolstoy the other day.
Did you know the original
title for War and Peace
was War,
What Is It Good For?
[SINGSONG-LIKE]
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, I'm not kidding,
Elaine. It's true.
His mistress
didn't like the title
and insisted that he change it
to War and Peace.
But it's a line
from that song!
That's where they
got it from.
Really?
I'm not joking.
[IMITATING JACK NICHOLSON]
You can't handle the truth!
What?
I'm working
on my Jack Nicholson.
You can't handle
the truth!
What is this,
your mail?
[NORMAL VOICE]
Yeah, I grabbed it on the way out.
I don't want my mother
reading it.
Ah, your alumni
magazine.
Your mother reads
your mail?
Yeah.
What, you mean,
like postcards and--?
No. Anything.
She doesn't open.
She'll open.
You've caught your mother
opening envelopes?
Yes.
What does she say?
[MIMICKING]
"I was curious."
Isn't that
against the law?
Maybe I can get her
locked up.
[GASPS]
Hey, Jerry, you're in
the alumni magazine!
Listen to this:
"Jerry Seinfeld
has appeared
"on David Letterman
and The Tonight Show,
"and he did a pilot
for NBC called Jerry
that was not
picked up."
Georgie, how come there's
not anything about you in here?
He can't handle
the truth.
All right. This
is too much fun.
I gotta get
back to work.
[SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Uh...
Sorry.
It's okay.
Yeah-- Oh!
Wait, wait.
Uh...
Maybe you could,
uh, use this.
Here.
It's an electronic
organizer.
What?
Uh, yeah. Uh--
Wha--?
Yeah, here.
Yeah.
[GASPS]
For phone numbers,
addresses.
Keep appointments,
everything.
Wow.
It's got an alarm
that beeps.
Oh, I can't believe this!
Kramer, I've been wanting
to get one of these things.
Are you sure that--
You sure you can't
use this thing? No.
I got all my appointments
right up here.
Where'd you get this?
Oh, the bank.
I opened up a new account.
Hey, did you see that whale
thing on TV last night?
No.
I am such a huge
whale fan.
These marine biologists
were showin'
how they communicate
with each other
with the squeaks
and the squeals.
What a fish.
It's a mammal.
Whatever.
Hey, new
tape recorder?
Yeah, I got it
from the bank.
Hey!
Hey.
Who wants to have
some fun?!
I do.
Are you just sayin'
you wanna have fun,
or do you really
wanna have fun?!
I really wanna have fun.
I'm just sayin'
I wanna have some fun.
Right now,
there are 600 Titleists
that I got from
the driving range
in the trunk
of my car.
Why don't we drive out
to Rockaway
and hit 'em
into the ocean!
Now, picture this.
We find a nice sweet spot
between the dunes.
We take out our drivers,
we tee up and--
Whoo!
That ball goes sailing up
into the sky,
holds there for a moment
and then--
Gulg!
You wanna get some lunch?
Yeah. Let me stop
by the cash machine,
and I'll meet you over
at the coffee shop.
Yeah,
I'm gonna get a paper.
Keep your head down.
Yeah.
Cash advance?
Yes.
No.
Balance inquiry?
Receipt?
No.
Processing.
I won.
Jerry?
Yeah.
It's Diane. Diane DeConn
from Queen's College.
Oh, Diane.
How are you?
Good.
How long has it been?
Since college.
Ah.
I've been seeing you on TV.
You're doing great.
Yeah, pluggin' along.
You know, I got
the alumni magazine.
Whatever happened
to your friend, George?
I notice I never see
his name in there.
Well, he's kind
of modest.
He was always such
a goof-off.
I mean, did he ever
get anywhere?
Sure.
Yeah? What field?
Marine biology.
George is
a marine biologist?
Yeah. Pretty damn
good one too.
[SCOFFS]
I can't believe it.
I-I would never
have thought.
Yeah. He's specializing
in whales.
He's working on lowering
the cholesterol level
in whales.
All that blubber.
It's quite unhealthy.
You know, it's the largest
mammal on earth,
but as George says,
they don't have to be.
Diane DeConn?
You saw Diane DeConn?
Somethin', huh?
How did she look?
She looked great.
Oh. Mm!
She asked about you.
She asked about me?
What did she say?
"How's George?"
George?
She said, George?
She remembered my name.
Diane DeConn
remembered my name!
She was the "it" girl.
Yeah, she asked
for your number.
I think she's gonna get
in touch with you.
Okay, I'm telling you
right now.
If you're kiddin' around,
I'm not gonna be able
to be your friend anymore.
I'm serious about that.
You got that?
I got no problem with that.
Good, because
if this is a lie,
if this is a joke,
if this is your idea
of some cute little game,
we're finished!
Expect a call.
Oh, my God,
he's not kidding.
Now,
I should tell you...
that at this point,
she's under the impression
that you're a, uh...
A what?
A marine biologist.
A marine biologist?
Yes.
Why am I
a marine biologist?
I may have mentioned it.
But I'm not
a marine biologist.
Yes, I know that.
So?
Why, you don't think
it's a good job?
I didn't even know
it was a job.
Oh, it's
a fascinating field.
Well, what if
she calls me?
What am I supposed
to say?
Algae.
Obviously plankton.
I don't know what else
I could tell ya, uh...
Oh, I-- I just got back from
a trip to the Galapagos Islands.
I was living with the turtles.
LIPPMAN:
We have got you in a very nice hotel.
I-- I don't know how
you like to work,
but, uh, I can arrange
for an office, if you like.
I work in hotel.
Is better.
[WHISPERS] The hotel.
Away from all your little
petty bickerings
and interference.
You know, Tolstoy used to write
in the village square.
The faces inspired him.
He did not need
inspiration.
God spoke
through his pen.
Oh, that is so true.
Yes.
Although, one wonders
if War and Peace
would have been
as highly acclaimed as it was
had it been published
under its original title,
War, What Is It
Good For?
What?
Yeah. Mr. Lippman, it was
his mistress who insisted
that he call it
War and Peace.
Elaine.
War, What Is It
Good For?
♪ Absolutely
Nothin' ♪
♪ Huh!
Say it again ♪
LIPPMAN:
Elaine.
It's a song--
They took it from Tolstoy.
LIPPMAN:
No. Elaine--
War, What Is It Good For?
[LOUD BEEPING]
It's just her sense of humor.
No, it's not.
That really is true.
What is that noise?
Yes, it is.
No, it's not.
That noise!
What is it that noise?
It's traveling up my spine
into my brain. Oh, um.
It's coming
from your purse.
Oh, it must be
my new organizer.
Yeah--
Testikov: That noise.
Turn it off.
Right, I think
it's this--
No, it's the button--
I cannot stand it!
It's the button
at the top. The top.
Will you turn it off?!
The one at the top.
I'm gonna work on that one.
Ah, give it to me!
JERRY:
I did it for you.
I don't know what you
had to tell her that for!
You put me in a very
difficult position.
Marine biologist.
I'm very uncomfortable
with this whole thing.
With all due respect, I would
think it's right up your alley.
Well, it's not up my alley.
It's one thing
if I make it up.
I know what I'm doin'.
I know my alleys.
You got me
in the Galapagos Islands
living with the turtles.
I don't know
where the hell I am!
Well, you came in
the other day
with all that
whale stuff,
the squeaking
and the squealing and--
Look, why couldn't you
make me an architect?
You know I always
wanted to pretend
that I was an architect.
Well, I'm-- I'm supposed
to see her tomorrow.
I'm gonna tell her
what's going on.
I mean, maybe she just
likes me for me.
Hey.
Hey, you want these?
I don't want 'em!
What?
I stink!
I can't play.
The ball is just
sitting there, Jerry,
and I can't hit it.
I only hit one good ball
that went way out there.
Well, what happened?
I have no concentration!
What's-- What's--
What's wrong with your--?
Sand. I can't get
rid of this sand.
Look, there's still
some in here!
It won't go away.
Look at that. I even got
sand in the pockets.
Hey, come on. You're gettin'
it all over the floor!
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Yeah.
Yes, it is.
Really?
Uh-- Could you
hold on a second?
Hey, listen to this:
Some woman found
an electronic organizer.
My name was in it. She wants me
to help track down the owner.
How'd she find it?
She's walkin' down the street,
and it hit her in the head.
So, I am walkin' along,
minding my own business,
when all of a sudden,
this thing comes flyin'
out of nowhere
and clonks me
right on the head.
Wow.
Yeah.
So, they took me
to the hospital. Yeah?
Yeah, and they put me
in this thing
that feels like a coffin
for 45 minutes.
You ever been in one
of those things?
You can go berserk in there!
You have insurance.
I wish.
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
[BEEPS LOUDLY]
What is with this thing?
I don't know.
It never shuts up.
So, anyway, you could see
why I would be interested
in finding this person.
Absolutely. You should not
have to pay for that.
[BEEPS]
Stop it.
Stop it!
Let me have a look
at this thing. You know,
somebody told me they saw
that thing come out
of a limousine.
Typical rich people
using the world for their
personal garbage can.
Boy, am I lucky
your name came up.
I just pushed a button.
I'd like to know what my name's
doin' in this creep's organizer.
Yeah.
Who do I know who
would have even been
in a limousine yesterday?
Oh-- Oh.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Great organizer
you gave me.
Oh, you liked it, huh?
It wouldn't stop beeping
in the car,
so Testikov threw it
out the window.
Oh.
I transferred everything in there.
I threw out my old book.
I'm lost now, Kramer.
What? What is it?
This sand.
It's everywhere.
Okay, I'll see ya later.
[WHIMPERS]
Oh, there you are.
There you are.
So?
So, what do you have
to say for yourself?
Why should I say anything
for myself?
War, What Is It
Good For?
Ah.
[CHUCKLES]
Who told you?
[CHUCKLES
SARCASTICALLY]
Yuri Testikov,
the Russian writer.
Hello-o-o.
[STAMPS FOOT]
You told Testikov...
that Tolstoy wanted
to name his book
War, What Is It
Good For?
Uh-huh.
And do you know
what happened?
Can I take a guess?
Oh, please.
Oh, I don't know.
He threw your organizer
out the window?
What? How do you
know that?
Because I know
who has it!
How did you find it?
The woman who got hit
in the head with it
found my name,
called me up and we met.
Where is it?
Give it to me.
I don't have it.
Why not?
She's not returning it
until she gets money
for the hospital bill.
But I didn't do it.
Testikov did it.
He should pay for it.
How much is Testikov gettin'
from Pendant for this book?
One million.
Well, that's a start.
Then, of course, with evolution,
the octopus lost the nostrils
and took on the more familiar
look that we know today.
Really?
Yeah.
But if you still
look closely,
you can see a little bump
where the nose used to be.
Heh, heh, heh.
Ha.
But enough about fish.
I can discuss
other things, you know.
Architecture.
JERRY:
You know what room Testikov's in?
Yeah, 308. Oh, I'm crazy
for doing this.
You want your organizer back,
don't you?
Why are you
so interested?
You wanna take her out?
Hey, when Superman
saves someone,
nobody asks if he's
tryin' to hit on her.
Well, you're not
Superman.
Lois Lane.
Ah... Listen, you got
the tape recorder?
Yeah, I got it.
You sure you
wanna do this?
Yeah, I gotta get
Testikov on tape.
If this woman ends up
in the New England
Journal of Medicine,
I'm not gonna pay for it.
Oh, here she comes.
Hi.
Elaine, this is Corinne.
Hello.
Hi.
You got the organizer?
[BEEPS]
We'll meet you back here
in 10 minutes,
hopefully with the money.
Your parents must be
so proud of you, George.
Oh, they're busting.
[CHUCKLES]
DIANE:
What are those people doing over there?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What?! Come in.
Come in.
Come in, Miss Benes!
That is, if you can
spare a minute
from your busy schedule.
Have you bring guests
for my entertainment?
Yes, this is
my friend, Jerry.
Um, he accompanied me,
you know--
Ahem-- Single women in a big
city can be dangerous, so--
Yeah, that's why
I wear these sneakers.
In case of
any trouble.
Zip! I'm gone.
Yeah, yeah. The sneakers.
All the Americans
with the sneakers.
You always running
from something.
Yeah, well, sit!
Stop running!
Two minutes. I give you
latest manuscript.
Oh, Rimsky.
Great, great book,
if I may say so, sir.
I almost read
the whole thing.
[BEEPING]
What?
If you can't turn
that thing off,
I'll have to ask you
to leave.
I'm waitin'
for two people.
Well, you can wait
for them outside.
Yeah, I guess I'd better.
I wouldn't wanna take
any attention away
from the hookers.
All right.
All right. Out. Out.
Whatever you say,
Crowell.
What's goin' on
over here?
There's a beached whale.
She's dying.
MAN:
Is anyone here a marine biologist?
TESTIKOV:
Here is latest draft.
I see you next week,
same time, same day.
On time, please.
Okay.
It was nice meeting you.
Yeah, a real
pleasure.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, by the way,
Mr. Testikov, um...
Do you remember
the other day
when we were
in the limo, and, uh,
my organizer started
making noise,
and you threw it
out the window?
How can I forget?
Well, um,
would you believe
that it actually hit
somebody in the head?
Right in the head.
Boing! Heh, heh.
[SQUEAKING]
What is that noise?
Uh, that's nothin'.
Um, and anyway, um--
What's going on, huh?
That noise!
No--
No, that's my purse.
That noise!
No, get--
Get off my purse!
It's a recorder! Huh!
No, that's a radio!
You are spying on me!
[WHISTLING]
[WHIZZING]
Aah!
CROWD: Come on!
MAN: Save the whale.
You gotta
do it!
Save the whale,
George...for me.
GEORGE:
So, I started to walk into the water.
I won't lie to you, boys.
I was terrified,
but I pressed on.
And as I made my way
past the breakers,
a strange calm came
over me.
I-- I don't know if it was
divine intervention
or the kinship
of all living things,
but I tell you, Jerry,
at that moment,
I was
a marine biologist.
George, I've just been
reading this thing in the paper.
It's unbelievable.
I know, I was
just telling the story.
Well, come on, George.
Finish the story.
The sea was angry
that day, my friends...
like an old man trying
to send back soup in a deli.
I got about 50 feet out
when suddenly,
the great beast
appeared before me.
I tell ya, he was 10 stories
high if he was a foot!
As if sensing my presence,
he let out a great bellow.
I said,
"Easy, big fella."
And then, as I watched
him struggling, I realized
that something was
obstructing its breathing.
From where I was standing,
I could see directly
into the eye
of the great fish.
Mammal.
Whatever.
Well, what did you do next?
Well, then,
from out of nowhere,
a huge tidal wave
lifted me,
tossed me like a cork,
and I found myself
right on top of him,
face-to-face
with the blowhole!
I-I-I could barely see from
the waves crashing down upon me,
but...I knew something
was there,
so I reached my hand
in, felt around,
and pulled out
the obstruction!
What is that,
a Titleist?
A hole in one, huh?
The crowd must
have gone wild.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Yes, Jerry, they were
all over me.
It was like Rocky I.
Diane came up to me,
threw her arms
around me,
kissed me.
We both had tears
streaming down our faces.
I never saw anyone
so beautiful.
It was at that moment
that I decided to tell her that
I was not
a marine biologist.
Wow. What did she say?
Told me to "go to hell,"
and I took the bus home.
All right. Let's go.
What, are you
in a bad mood?
Nah, I got my laundry back.
[GASPS]
Golden Boy?
He didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
This is
Golden Boy's son...
Baby Blue.
What's with you?
Sand.
It's everywhere!