How about that seedless
watermelon? What an invention.
Scientists are working on this.
I mean, other scientists
devote their lives
to fighting cancer,
AIDS, heart disease.
These guys go,
"No, I'm focusing on melon.
"Oh, sure, thousands of people
are dying needlessly,
"but this, ptooey.
"That's gotta stop.
[LAUGHTER & APPLAUSE]
"You ever try and pick
a wet one up off the floor?
"It's almost impossible.
I'm devoting my life to that."
So I guess if they can
get rid of the seeds,
the rind is going next.
What do we need that for?
Get rid of the rind.
They're not gonna stop
until they're making
in-the-ground,
ready-to-eat fruit cups
growing right out
of the ground.
So, what's her name?
Karen.
She nice?
Great.
So you like her?
I think so.
You don't know?
I can't tell anymore.
Well, do you
feel anything?
Feel? What's that?
All right.
Lemme ask you this.
When she comes over,
you cleanin' up a lot?
Yeah.
You straightenin' up,
or you cleanin'?
Cleaning.
You do the tub?
Yeah.
On your knees, Ajax,
hands scrubbin',
the whole deal?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I think
you're in love.
Tub is love?
Tub is love.
Huh.
So there you are.
You got a nice girl
and a clean apartment.
Yup.
Just one little problem.
Sexual?
Yeah.
Well...
I've never really felt
confident in, uh...
one particular aspect.
Below the equator?
Yeah.
Nobody does.
You know, nobody knows
what to do.
You just close your eyes,
you hope for the best.
I really think they're happy
if you just make an effort.
I-- I don't know.
Last time I got the tap.
You got the tap?
You know, you're goin' along,
you think everything's
all right,
and all of a sudden you,
You get that tap
on the shoulder.
You know, it's like, "Phweet!
All right, that's enough.
You're through."
The tap is tough.
It's like the manager comin' out
and askin' you for the ball.
Yeah.
Well, maybe she just wanted
to move on to other business.
No. No, this wasn't
moving on.
I got the hook.
I wish I could get
a lesson in that.
It's a very complicated area.
You could go crazy trying
to figure that place out.
It's a hazy mystery.
Anyway, I think
everything else is okay.
[LAUGHING]
Unless, of course, she's fakin'.
Who's fakin'?
Nothing.
Fakin' what?
Nobody's fakin'.
Oh! Orgasms?
She's not faking!
How do you know?
I know. I can tell.
It's one of my powers.
Why? Do you ever fake?
Of course.
Really?
You faked?
On occasion.
And the guy
never knows?
Nah.
How can he
not know that?
[SENSUALLY]
Because I was good.
I guess after
that many beers,
he's probably
a little groggy, anyway.
You didn't know.
What's that?
Are you saying...
I think I'll have
a piece of cake.
With me?
Well...
You faked with me?
Yeah.
You faked with me.
Yes.
No.
You faked it?
I faked it.
That whole thing,
the whole production,
it was all an act?
Not bad, huh?
What about
the breathing,
the panting, the moaning,
the screaming?
Fake, fake,
fake, fake.
I'm stunned.
I'm shocked.
How many times
did you do this?
Um...
All the time.
All the time!
Think I'll have
a chocolate malted here.
But-- But I'm so good.
I'm sure you are.
Jerry, listen,
it wasn't you.
I just didn't have 'em
back then.
She faked.
Maybe they've all
been faking.
I'm sure they're not.
Maybe Karen is faking.
She was
probably joking.
No, no.
It was no joke.
She didn't have any?
No, none.
She faked 'em all.
Faked 'em all.
Well, so she faked 'em.
So what?
Th-th-the woman had an orgasm
under false pretenses.
That-- That's sexual perjury.
You know, I heard her screaming
from my apartment.
She woke me up
a few times.
How did she do it?
She's like Meryl Streep,
this woman.
And I know how
to work the equipment.
I'm not unskilled.
I'm in the union.
I mean, if she at least told me,
maybe I could've
done something about it.
Yeah, I could've helped you out.
What could
you have done?
Well, I could've
given you some pointers.
I know how to press
those buttons, buddy.
Well, I'm feeling
very inadequate
about the whole thing.
Ahhh...
Don't "ahhh."
I'm supposed to do something
with her later.
I don't even think
I even wanna see her.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hello, Elaine.
So we havin'
dinner tonight?
Uh, I don't know.
I'm not really in the mood.
Why? What's wrong?
You're not still thinkin'
about this afternoon, are you?
What, the grilled cheese?
Nah, they always burn the toast.
No, the other thing.
Oh, that!
Well...
Oh.
Come on, Jerry. You're making
too much of a big deal about it.
I guess. So you wanna meet
at that place at 7:30?
Okay.
All right.
All right, see you later.
Bye.
Renee, can you
come here a second?
Let me ask you
something. Um...
Have you ever...you know...
faked it?
Yeah, sometimes.
Really, like when?
Like if we went
to a Broadway show,
if we had
really good seats.
Yeah, well.
Well, you know,
if it's enough already
and I just wanna
get some sleep.
I really don't feel
like seein' her.
You know, I've faked it.
What?
Yeah.
You faked it?
Wh-why would you do that?
Well, you know,
if it's enough already
and I just wanna
get some sleep.
Yeah, but why
would you--?
[MUMBLES]
Oh!
Bad peach?
It's terrible!
Did you get that at Joe's?
Yeah, of course I got it
at Joe's.
That's surprising.
His fruit's usually the best.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna return this.
You're returning
used fruit?
Jerry, this peach
is subpar.
So, what do you
want me to do?
I want restitution.
Restitution?
You want restitution?
Why should I give you
restitution?
Because it's no good.
Once I put that fruit out,
that's where it ends for me.
But it's still your fruit.
You gotta stand
behind your fruit.
Hey, I stand behind my fruit.
So?
Hey, you got a bad peach?
That's an act of God.
He makes the peaches.
I don't make the peaches.
I sell the peaches.
You got a problem,
you talk to him.
You know, this whole place
is going, vvvvp, downhill.
I could've come in here
last week with a bad plum,
but I let it go.
Well, I got a perfect solution
for you.
Take your business elsewhere.
Now you don't want my business.
No, I don't want your business.
And at this moment,
you're banned from the store.
You're banned!
[WHIMPERS]
But what am I gonna do for fruit?
Mmm.
Mmm, hm-hm-hm-hm-hm.
Mmm!
Whoo!
Ah, ha-ha.
You seem like you really
enjoyed your risotto.
[CHUCKLES]
You have a very contented air
over there.
You look very contented,
very satisfied.
Are you satisfied?
I'm very satisfied.
I'm-- I'm sure if
you weren't satisfied,
you would probably
say something, wouldn't you?
I probably would.
But then again,
I'm an enigma.
Hey, listen, um,
instead of the movie, uh,
maybe we'll go back
and, uh...
you know...
Ha-ha-ha-hoo!
Maybe.
So, uh...
y-you feel okay
about that whole thing,
uh, what we do...
in there.
You're generally okay
with everything in there.
Generally.
Do you, uh,
feel the way you feel
after the risotto?
Well, no.
I feel full
after the risotto.
Yeah. Full.
Mmm.
Oh, God. Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmmmm-mm!
Mmm!
Oh.
Whoo!
Satisfied?
Mmm.
Hey, you know what?
You wanna go see
that new Meryl Streep movie?
Meryl Streep?
You don't like her?
Eh, she's okay.
Come on, I love her, Jerry.
She's so authentic.
I really believe everything
is actually happening to her.
There's no acting there.
Yeah.
You don't want coffee
or anything, do you?
I really admire
actors, you know?
It's just such an incredible
skill to pull that off.
Yeah. Yeah.
Can we get off of this?
What's the matter?
Nothin'.
You're not still thinkin'
about that, are you?
[LAUGHING]
No, no.
Oh, good.
[LAUGHS]
Gimme another shot.
What?
Another shot.
I want another shot.
You mean...
Yes!
Ohhh, no,
I don't think so.
Come on!
One shot. I could do it,
I know I could do it!
Jerry, we're friends.
We can't do that.
It would ruin our friendship.
Oh, friendship.
Friendship, schmiendship.
No. That's important to me.
We won't ruin the friendship.
Yeah-- Yes, we will!
Elaine...
No, Jerry, it is
out of the question.
You know what sex does
to a friendship. It kills it.
Half-hour. Gimme a half-hour.
No!
Okay. Fifteen minutes.
I guarantee you, 15 minutes,
I can make it happen!
No!
You're worried I'll be able
to do it, aren't ya?
Wha--?
No, it doesn't matter.
Jerry, I don't care.
No. No, that's it. That's it.
You like havin' this over me.
You don't want me to do it.
That is so ridiculous.
Come on, Elaine!
No.
Elaine!
No!
[WHIMPERS]
[GROANS]
[CHUCKLES]
It's Jerry's fault.
Jerry?
Jerry and Elaine.
They made me nuts!
Oh, I don't care,
George, really.
It's all right.
So you feel okay?
Well...
it's not like
after the risotto.
JERRY:
Well, good night.
I still
don't understand
why we had to walk out
on that movie.
Oh, that Meryl Streep,
she's such a phony baloney.
Good night.
Thanks for a really
fabulous evening.
Oh, what,
you're upset?
Yes, I'm upset.
Can't you tell?
No, I can't.
Maybe you're faking.
I'm really, really sorry
I told you that.
I'm sorry too.
Well, stop being
such a baby.
You're a baby!
It's all
your fault!
You and Elaine,
all that orgasm talk!
She did have an orgasm,
she didn't have an orgasm.
Orgasm this! Orgasm that!
I got so focused on it!
I started to panic,
and poom! I lost it!
I tried everything.
I was talking to him.
"Please wake up.
Do something."
They're mysterious little
fellows, aren't they?
I hate 'em!
You know, it happens
to everybody.
Happened to Houdini,
and he could get out
of a trunk underwater
with his hands in chains.
But he had a problem with that.
The miracle
is that it ever happens.
It's like a magic trick.
Sometimes I think
it would be easier
to bend a spoon mentally
than to make
that transformation.
Hey.
Listen...
Uh, if I
give you money,
will you go out
and get me some fruit?
Why can't you get it?
Well, I-- I got banned
from the store.
I can't go back in there now.
What happened?
Well, we had a fight
over the peach, and, uh,
well, Joe doesn't want
my business.
Hey, is that a joke
about Houdini?
No.
I told you not to say anything.
Jerry, what am I
gonna do for fruit?
Well, you'll have to go
to the supermarket.
The supermarket?
It's impossible.
They don't have a decent piece
of fruit at the supermarket!
The apples are mealy,
the oranges are dry.
I don't know what's
goin' on with the papayas!
Look, Jerry, you gotta
go to Joe's!
You gotta get me some fruit!
Oh, so, what, am I gonna
buy all your fruit now?
Well, if Houdini couldn't do it,
what chance do I have?
[PHONE RINGS]
[STAMMERS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Patty.
Thanks for calling me back.
I just wanted to
ask you a question.
When we were going out,
did you have orgasms?
Okay.
Thanks. No, that's it.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Patty Lawrence had 'em!
All right, look, I'm gonna make
you a fruit list, all right?
Yeah.
Hello, Elaine?
Patty Lawrence had orgasms.
What do you think about that?
And I got calls in
to six other women.
And I'll bet you
they confirm an orgasm too.
So, what do you have to
say now, Elaine?
Hello?
Why do I feel like
I'm doin' somethin' wrong?
All right, now,
here's the list.
All this? It's too much.
What do you need
five mangoes for?
I like mangoes.
Avocado?
I don't know how
to pick out an avocado.
Well, they gotta
be soft.
How soft?
But not too soft.
See, better too hard
than too soft.
Well, I'm not going
through this every week,
I'll tell you that right now.
All right.
Now, what are these? Plums?
What is that?
Yeah. Now, get the ones
that are red on the inside.
Uh-uh. Well, how do I know
what they look like inside?
What do they look like
on the outside?
Oh! And get
some plantains.
Plantains?
Yes.
What the hell is a plantain?
Oh, it's part of
the banana family.
It's a delicacy.
You're not getting
any plantains.
[STAMMERS]
JERRY:
Hey, Joe.
How's it goin'?
Good. Just gettin'
some fruit for myself.
Uh, gotta have fruit
in the house.
I like it
as a snack.
Wholesome, natural,
chock-full of vitamins.
All right, let's see.
Mangoes.
Four plums with red
on the inside.
Avocado.
Ooh, just right.
And, uh...
three plantains
ought to do it.
All right, all right.
Just hold it right there!
What?
This fruit isn't for you.
Why, what're you talking about?
You think I don't know, huh?
Mangoes, plantains,
plums with the red
on the inside?
That's Kramer!
I can't buy mangoes
and plantains?
All right, get out!
You're making
a big mistake, Joe.
I'll tell you something else,
I don't want your business,
either.
Are you saying you're banning me
from the store?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
I'm banned?!
You're banned.
All right,
where do you want it?
Put it
over there.
Yes!
[GRUNTS]
This stuff is heavy.
What do you got?
Ooh, look at these.
Ooh, these mangoes
are beautiful.
[SNIFFS]
Oh, those are beautiful.
You did good, George.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All right,
I gotta get goin'.
What are you doin'?
I got a date with Karen.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Nothing happening down there.
You're thinkin' about it
too much.
You're puttin'
too much emphasis on it.
I knew this was gonna
happen someday.
It was inevitable.
I've known it ever since
I was a little kid.
I've been waitin' for it.
This mango's delicious!
Hey, that
reminds me.
I'm not getting' you guys
any more fruit.
That guy was eyeballin' me
the whole time.
He gave me the creeps.
All right, you owe me 28.60.
Gee, sorry.
I don't have any cash.
I only got hundreds.
You see, I--
All right, I knew it!
Oh, come on. Come on,
we're gonna pay you.
Here, have some mango.
I don't want any mango.
Come on, take some.
It's good.
Very good.
Juicy.
Yeah.
Ripe.
Mm.
Boy, this Joe's got
some terrific fruit.
Mmm.
What?
I feel like I got a B12 shot.
This is like
a taste explosion.
I told ya.
What is it?
I think it moved.
Oh, my God, I think it moved!
Yeah, give me the big piece.
I'll see you later!
Hi, George.
I'm back, baby!
I'm back!
Want some mango?
No, thanks.
Yeah.
Well, well.
If it isn't the first lady
of the American theater.
What brings you here?
Just gonna return some of your
things that were in my house.
Oh, and I've got
some things of yours here.
I know.
Well, I'll get them.
I'm waiting.
All right, then.
You got my fins?
Yeah, I got your fins.
Do you have my poker chips?
I got your poker chips.
You got my goggles?
They're next
to the fins.
You got my cards?
They're next to
the poker chips.
Okay.
All right.
Guess that just about...
does it.
I guess.
Okay, well...
see you around.
Yeah, see ya.
All right, let's go.
I'll give you half an hour.
What?!
Come on.
Are you serious?
Look, Jerry,
we have to have sex
to save the friendship.
Sex...
Well...
if we have to, we have to.
KAREN:
Mmm...
Oh, George.
Ohhh.
Please, it's not necessary.
Mmm, what's not necessary?
The little extra moan
you threw in there.
Laying it on a bit thick,
don't you think?
What're you talking about?
What am I talking about?
Come on.
[LAUGHING]
You don't think I bought all that.
Bought what?
No. You're very good.
Very good with the moanings
and the gyrations.
You really had me
goin' there for a minute.
You think I was faking?
Come on.
With the, "Oh, George!
Oh, George!"
Come on.
Not that I don't
appreciate the effort
that was put into
the performance.
[SIGHS]
I'd like you to leave.
What?
I said I would
like you to leave!
Come on, just get
your clothes on and get out.
But why?
Because I said so!
[THUMP]
I-- I can't find
my glasses.
Well, hurry up.
Lemme look
for my glasses.
Get out!
[WHIMPERING]
It's all George's fault.
All that talk about impotence,
it got to me.
And that orgasm stuff.
Orgasm this and orgasm that.
It's a lot of pressure!
Hey, you know,
I'm a little hungry.
You wouldn't happen to have
any of that mango left?
The female orgasm
is kind of like the Batcave.
Very few people
know where it is,
and, uh, if you're
lucky enough to see it,
you probably don't know
how you got there,
and you can't find
your way back after you leave.
[LAUGHTER & APPLAUSE]
There are two types
of female orgasm:
the real and the fake.
And, uh, I'll tell you
right now,
as a man, we don't know.
We do not know,
because to men,
sex is like
a car accident,
and determining
the female orgasm
is like being asked,
"What did you see after
the car went out of control?"
"Uh, I heard a lot
of screeching sounds.
"I-I remember I was facin'
the wrong way at one point.
And in the end,
my body was thrown clear."