You know,
doctor is supposed to be
such a prestigious occupation,
but it's really
one of the only jobs
where you have
to have your diploma
right up there on the wall.
It makes them seem
so insecure, doesn't it?
[SLACKER ACCENT]
"I really am a doctor, you know.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
If you think I'm not,
just check it out."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I mean, I don't know why
they need these little bits
of psychological leverage
over us all the time.
"Go in that little room,
"take your pants off,
wait 15 minutes,
then I'll give you my opinion."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I mean, after that, anybody
that comes in with pants on
seems like they know
what they're talking about.
In any difference of opinion,
pants always beats no pants.
Can I say
one word to you?
Lobster.
The lobster here
is unbelievable.
[CHUCKLES]
Ooh! A little
expensive.
Twenty-five dollars.
Yes, well, you know...
I'm not thinking
about the price.
You know, you're
the only woman
I've never thought
about the price.
Get the lobster.
I beg you to get
the lobster.
Go for it.
Go for the lobster!
George.
George, uh...
I think
we have to talk.
I think we have
a problem.
We do?
We can't keep seeing
each other.
Why?
[SNIFFLES]
Because it's over!
[SOBBING]
It's my parents, George.
The differences
in our religion...
Oh, George.
Can you
ever forgive me?
Uh, have you
decided yet?
[SOBBING]
Yes.
I'll have
the lobster.
Um...
You know, I'm--
I'm starting to think that...
maybe lobster
isn't the way to go.
What,
he asked you out?
Well, we started to talk,
and I told him that I jog.
And then he put
his hand on my heart.
On your heart?
Jerry, the man is a doctor.
Doctor.
He's a podiatrist.
So? Same thing.
Anyone can get into
podiatry school.
George got into
Really?
Sure.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Are you gonna be
stopping by later?
Yes, I'll be stopping.
Okay. I'll see you later.
See you later.
Well, we can't all be
dating podiatrists.
It's over.
What?
How'd you get in?
Kramer.
What's that?
Lobster.
Looks like a swan.
She says we can't
go out anymore.
Why?
'Cause I'm not
Latvian Orthodox!
Her parents won't let her
get involved with anyone
who isn't Latvian Orthodox!
Latvian Orthodox?
[GASPS]
Ooh! It is lobster.
Oh.
She's limiting herself
to Latvian Orthodox?
That's
too bad.
I know.
This was the only woman
I never lied to.
Well, that's
not entirely true.
Well, whatever.
Mmm.
This is delicious.
Mmm. Succulent.
Mmm.
She knew
I didn't have a job.
I lived at home.
Didn't seem
to bother her.
I think I could have
married this woman.
Why don't you just
ask her parents?
I can't.
I met them.
They're devout.
You know, in the cab
on the way over here, I...
I actually thought
about converting!
[CHUCKLES]
To Latvian
Orthodox?
Why not?
What do I care?
You know, it's not like
changin' toothpaste.
I think it
would be romantic.
Really?
Yeah,
it's like Edward VIII
abdicating the throne
to marry Mrs. Simpson.
Ohhh!
Like King Edward.
[SNAPPING]
Like King Edward,
Jerry.
Yeah, well...
King Edward
didn't live in Queens
with Frank
and Estelle Costanza.
You know what?
I could probably
do this.
What's the difference?
George, I was just
kidding around.
Oh, I wouldn't even
have to tell her.
I could surprise her!
George,
I wasn't serious!
How hard
could it be?
You make
a little contribution,
you have a ceremony.
[SNAPS]
I am gonna
think about this.
I am really gonna
I guess this one
is my fault.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Mmm.
That was nice.
Have you always been
such a good kisser?
Oh, I don't know.
Not always.
No?
No, I, uh...
I had to work at it.
When I was a kid,
the other kids
would be out playing.
I'd be up in my room,
practicing my kissing.
It was worth it.
I'll be right...back.
Where are you going?
Wash my hands.
They're sticky from the orange.
Meet you back here?
Right there.
Okay.
JERRY:
"Fungicide"?
Fungus?
Fungicide.
I mean,
what could she have?
I don't know.
Fungus.
Exactly.
So, what'd you say?
I said I was comin' down
with the flu or something,
and I had to go home.
I wanna know,
what were you doing
opening her medicine cabinet?
I didn't open it.
It was open.
I just nudged it
a little.
You were snoopin'.
I was not snooping.
I did not
break the seal.
There was
no breaking and entering.
I wouldn't do that.
I would.
I always open
medicine cabinets.
Well, I trust people
not to do that.
Big mistake.
Why don't you ask
that doctor what it is?
Oh, now he's a doctor?
Before he was
a podiatrist.
But that's what
podiatrists do.
They deal
in fungus.
They're knee-deep
This guy
knows fungus.
I am not goin' to
ask him about funguses.
"Fungi."
What?
Why do you want to accept
the Latvian Orthodox faith?
[CLEARS THROAT]
In this age of uncertainty
and confusion...
a man begins to ask himself
certain questions.
How can one even begin to put
into words something so, um...?
Enigmatic?
No.
Vast?
No, not vast. Um...
Well, whatever it is,
basically you like
the religion.
Yes.
Is there one
aspect of the faith
you find particularly
attractive?
I think the hats.
The hat conveys that--
That solemn religious look
you want in a faith.
Very pious.
Are you familiar
with Orthodox theology?
Well...
perhaps not to the extent
that you are,
but, uh...
Heh, heh.
But I, uh--
I know the basic plot, yeah.
Plot?
Yes, you know,
the flood and the, uh, lepers
and the commandments
and all that.
Well, it's obvious you are
sincere in your desire.
Oh, yes, I am, Father.
Incredibly sincere.
So, uh...
pksh, am I in?
The first step
would be
to familiarize yourself
with these texts.
Ah-ha.
You see, Father, I-I-I'm--
I'm incredibly anxious
to become a member.
Um...
don't you offer any kind
of an express conversion,
a quick change?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yes?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Father, there's a man
waiting in the chapel.
Well, you may
attend to it, Sister.
Oh, this is
George Costanza.
He is interested
in joining the church.
Are you?
Well, that's wonderful!
Well, good luck
to you.
Thank you.
Nice nun.
No, no. Sister Roberta
is not a nun.
She is what we call
a novice.
She won't be taking
her final vows
until next Thursday.
Ah.
May I help you?
Oh! Uh, yeah.
I'm, uh, here to pick up
my friend George Costanza.
Oh, well, he's in
with the Father.
Oh, yeah. Yeah...
I'm Sister Roberta.
Oh. Kramer. Yeah.
It's a pleasure.
Mine.
GEORGE:
I can't believe how easy it is!
I'm virtually
Orthodox.
All I have to do
is read a few books,
memorize a few prayers,
and I'm in the club.
That's all
there is to it.
By Christmas Day,
I will be
Brother Costanza.
And what is
Brother Costanza
planning on telling
Mother Costanza?
Brother Costanza will be
taking the vow of silence.
Oh!
Hey.
Oh, a slinky.
Whoom, whoom,
whoom.
Sister Roberta
gave it to me.
Why'd she
give you that?
Well, I think
she liked me.
What do you mean,
she liked you?
Liked me.
Kramer, they
like everybody.
They're
friendly people.
No, no, no.
I think I picked up
on a vibe.
Chk-chk-chk, chk, chk!
You picked up
on a vibe from a nun?
Yeah, yeah.
Jerry, I'm tellin' ya,
I have this power.
And I have
no control over it.
Yeah.
All right.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Oh! That's
my phone.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Just wanted to stop by
and see how you were feeling.
Oh, a little better.
[COUGHS]
Okay, well, if you need
anything, you let me know.
Okay.
All right.
Bye.
Story.
She's subletting
Carol's place for a month.
Yeah. She likes you!
Yeah. But there's
a problem.
I found a tube of a fungicide
in her medicine cabinet.
So?
So I don't know
what she's using it for.
Well, how do you
even know it's hers?
Maybe it belonged
to Carol.
Did you see her name
on the tube?
I didn't even think to look!
Well, take a look.
It might not even
belong to her. Yeah!
People always leave old things
in their medicine cabinets.
Yeah! I got this old
bottle of cough medicine.
I still have Brylcreem.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Could I use your bathroom?
My bathroom?
You sure you don't mind?
No, of course not.
People ask me medical questions
all the time.
Well, I mean, the question
isn't even for me, actually.
It's for a friend.
Elaine,
I'm used to it.
I'm a doctor.
[SCOFFS]
Well...
podiatrist.
Huh?
No, no.
I'm just saying you...
You didn't really
go to medical school,
you went to
podiatry school,
which I'm sure is very grueling
in its own way.
I went to podiatry school
because I like feet.
I chose to work
with feet.
I like feet too.
I-- I'm just saying...
Saying...what?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
How you doing
in there?
Uh, fine. All done.
Just lookin' for the soap.
No soap?
No, I don't see it.
[KNOCKS]
Here you go.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
ESTELLE:
George?
What're you doing
in there?
What? Nothing.
FRANK:
You've been in there an hour.
ESTELLE: You don't feel well?
I'm fine.
ESTELLE:
I wanna know what you're doing in there!
Nothing!
FRANK:
George, open the door.
No.
ESTELLE:
Georgie!
No!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey.
Good evening.
I hope I'm not
disturbing you,
but I found another toy
I thought you might like.
Okay, Latvius was the son
of which apostle?
And I'll need that
in the form of a question.
I don't know, I--
I can't believe they're
makin' me take this test.
Hey, did you talk
to the doctor?
No.
All right, the next time
you see him, show him this.
You took her medicine!
Well, not on purpose.
I-- I was...
I was hoping there'd be
a name on the tube.
When are you
seein' him again?
I don't know.
We got into
this whole thing
about how podiatrists
aren't real doctors.
How could you say that?
That's your fault!
You just
got me thinkin'.
I was merely speaking
extemporaneously.
I've got nothing
against the foot.
I'm pro-foot.
Me too.
Do you think I should
call him and apologize?
Yes! He's a doctor.
Wait a second.
What're you doin'?
What does it look
like I'm doin'?
"Matthew. Luke.
Paul."
What, you're cheating
on your conversion test?
I told ya.
What?
I told you she liked me.
Who?
Sister Roberta.
How do you know?
She told me.
She says she's
never had a man
stir up all these feelings
inside of her.
She's questionin'
her faith.
She's thinking
of leavin' the church!
Wow.
Aaargh!
All this power!
Look what I'm doin'!
I'm dangerous,
Jerry.
I'm very,
very dangerous!
I must say, George,
I was somewhat surprised
at the results of
your conversion test.
I don't recall
having seen
such an impressive performance!
You truly must be filled
with the spirit of the Lord.
Oh, I'm--
I'm full of it, Father.
Yes, yes.
[SPEAKING LATVIAN]
...Kramer...
Yes, yes, yes. I see.
I'm sorry.
Something has come up.
Oh. Oh, sure.
I understand.
Hey!
Hey. Yeah.
Um...
You wanted to see me, Father?
Yes.
Please, sit down.
Sister Roberta came
to see me yesterday--
I know what
this is about, Father.
I didn't do anything.
I just spoke to her innocently
for just a few minutes.
It's just that I...
I have this power.
Yes.
Kavorca.
Kavorca?
Mm-hmm.
It is a Latvian word
which means
"the lure of the animal."
I don't understand.
Women are drawn to you.
Yeah.
They would give anything
to be possessed by you.
Help me, Father.
Help me!
Yes, yes, yes.
I will help you.
Now, listen
very carefully.
I want you to buy
10 cloves of garlic,
three quarts of vinegar,
Mm-hmm.
six ounces...
JERRY:
What is that stench?
I got it.
Ah-ha!
Hey.
What the hell
is goin' on?
It stinks in here,
what are you doing?
I've got
the kavorca, Jerry.
The kavorca?
What is that?
The lure
of the animal.
I'm dangerous.
Well, what is this thing
around your neck?
The priests,
they're helping me.
I just bathed
in vinegar.
You know, you're funkifying
the whole building!
Keep away, Jerry.
Keep away.
Kramer.
Kramer!
George Costanza?
Estelle's son?
ESTELLE:
Latvian Orthodox?
Why are you
doing this?
For a woman.
A woman?
What, are you
out of your mind?
Why can't you do anything
like a normal person?
Wait.
Is this the group that goes
around mutilating squirrels?
No, it's
a regular religion.
I'm calling my lawyer.
It might not be too late
to get out of this.
I don't wanna
get out of it!
But, George,
you don't know
what you're saying.
You're under their control.
What, they
brainwashed you?!
No, no.
You're not performing
any rituals in this house!
Go back
to the psychiatrist.
I beg you.
And stay away
from those squirrels!
Oh, hi.
How you doin',
Jerry?
Good.
What's the matter?
I'm tired.
I hardly slept last night
with all the scratching.
Bonkers was going crazy.
Bonkers?
My cat.
He's got this weird
sort of skin condition.
It's some type of fungus.
I couldn't find
his medicine.
Oh, it's your cat!
What?
Oh...
nothing.
Are you ready,
my son?
Yes, faddah.
What did you say?
What?
I thought
you said "faddah."
I said "faddah."
I, uh...
I meant "Father."
Oh!
Just a little bit
nervous.
Of course!
How you doin'?
Get away from me,
you creep.
Yes, yes!
It worked!
Sister Roberta.
I still got time to catch her.
[ORGAN PLAYING SOLEMN MELODY]
[PRAYING IN LATVIAN]
Gotta get there.
Congratulations,
George.
Welcome to the faith.
Sister Roberta,
would you please offer
the final benediction?
I can't.
[CROWD GASPS]
I'm sorry.
It's a beautiful
religion,
but I am not
worthy of it.
I found something else.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Him.
MAN:
Kavorca!
WOMAN:
CROWD:
Kavorca! Kavorca!
You know, because
I love the foot.
I'm a big fan of the foot.
Well, it's my fault.
I got a little defensive.
And that pinkie toe!
Oh.
Come on!
How adorable is the pinkie toe?
[CHUCKLES]
It's my favorite toe.
Let's face it.
You get a bunion,
where you goin'?
You're not goin'
to the ear guy.
No, you're not.
[GIGGLES]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Would you excuse me?
I'll be right back.
Oh, uh, where's the bathroom?
Oh, it's right down here
to the left.
I will, uh, meet you
right back here?
Elaine, it's her cat!
Her cat has the fungus.
So I need the tube back.
PODIATRIST:
"Fungicide"?
Fungus?
ROBERTA:
Something's wrong.
I don't feel
the same lure.
You don't?
What have I...?
I must return to the church.
By the way, you really need
to take a bath. You stink.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah!
Once you put medicine
in your medicine cabinet,
you're never usin' it again.
Any medicine you're usin'
is on the sink.
It's not really even
a medicine cabinet.
It's really like
an ointment museum, isn't it?
It's like,
"Here's a salve from 1983,
some cream from the '70s."
But you wanna
keep it private,
because a medicine cabinet
is a place
that reveals our weaknesses,
and it could really
throw off the balance
between two people
that might be goin' out.
Somebody peeks in there, and,
"Oh, I see Mr. Perfect
needs tough actin' Tinactin.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Well, I guess
I'll be callin' the shots
in this relationship
from now on."
[♪]
You did that
for me?
Well, I didn't do it
for my mother.
I'm really
flattered.
Yeah.
But I just don't feel ready
to make a commitment yet.
Maybe when I get back
from Latvia.
Latvia?
[LAUGHS]
Yes!
I'm going to stay with some
relatives there for a year.
Isn't it great?
Ooh!
Enjoy, enjoy.
Oh, George.
You are so sweet.
Don't ever change.
Mmm-mwah!
I'd like a doggie bag
for this, please.