To me, government is basically
parents for adults.
Especially the IRS.
The IRS is like
Ward and June Cleaver,
and we're all
Wally and the Beaver.
And your accountant
is Eddie Haskell
showing you all these
neat tricks
to get away with stuff.
Which is fine
unless you get audited.
Then you don't want
some wise guy in a suit,
just standing there going:
"You have a very lovely office
here, sir."
Because jail
is the government's way
of sending you to your room.
And when you meet Whitey
and Lumpy in the joint,
there's really going to be
something wrong with the Beaver.
[♪]
So, does he like you?
What do you think?
Do you like him?
Yeah, yeah, I like him.
Definitely like him.
I like him a lot.
So, what's wrong
with him?
Nothing, and I've looked.
Well, I'm sure
you'll find something.
So, how'd you meet him?
In the office.
So, he's a writer?
Yeah.
Yeah, big surprise.
So, I was sitting
on the reception desk,
I was looking pretty hot,
I was wearing
my sling-back pumps.
What are those?
Ask your mother.
You live with her now,
don't you?
Anyway, so then this guy
comes up to me,
and he starts feeling
my jacket,
between his thumb
and his forefinger, like this.
So what'd you do?
I said,
"so, what do you think?"
and he said, "Gabardine?"
and I said, "yeah."
That was it.
Wow. Just felt
your material?
Yeah. Jake Jarmel.
Wow. Sounds like
a cool guy.
Sounds like a jerk.
"Felt your material,"
come on.
Jerry, where'd you get
that sweater?
Yeah, what do you think? I found
it in the back of my closet.
I think that's what
the back of closets are for.
Hey, that's Barry.
Look it. Barry.
Hey. Hi.
GEORGE:
Who's that?
That's Barry Prophet.
He's our accountant.
I don't know how you can let
this guy handle all your money.
Oh, he doesn't handle my money,
he handles Jerry's money.
He just does my taxes.
Hey, Barry.
How you doing?
This is my friend George.
Hi, what are you doing
in this neighborhood?
Nothing, really.
[SNIFFING]
You eat here?
Yeah. So, how's my money?
It's still green.
[SNIFFING]
What, you got a cold?
No, no.
Wow. Look at that ring.
Oh, you like that?
Say, uh, where's the bathroom?
Bathroom, uh?
Bathroom's right over there.
Great.
Did you see that?
See what?
Yes, I saw that.
What?
What was all that sniffing?
I don't know.
You don't think--?
Oh, no! Come on, Jerry.
He was definitely
sniffing.
I mean, what if--?
This guy's got all my money.
Plus I got some
of Kramer's money with him.
This guy can write checks
to himself,
right out of my account.
I have known this guy
since college,
He doesn't do drugs.
Then what was all that sniffing?
Maybe it's the cold weather.
Today's not cold.
All right.
I gotta get going,
My parents are expecting me.
Don't forget to wash your hands
before supper.
What do you need
all that ketchup for?
This is my ketchup.
I bought this ketchup,
just so I could have
as much as I wanted.
So I talked to
Phil Kassikoff today.
Phil Kassikoff?
Yeah. You know,
my friend the bra salesman.
He says they're looking
to maybe put somebody on,
so I got you an interview
next Friday with his boss.
Next Friday? What time?
2:00.
That's my whole afternoon.
I was gonna look for sneakers.
You can look for sneakers
the next day!
He doesn't know
anything about bras.
I know a little.
Besides,
what do you have to know?
Well, it wouldn't hurt
to go in
and be able to
discuss it intelligently.
Maybe you should take a look
at a few bras.
Where's your bra?
Give him a bra
to look at.
I'm not giving him a bra,
Why not?
because I don't need him
looking at my bras.
Fine. So he'll go
into the interview--
He wouldn't know
what he's talking about.
Do we have to...?
You don't even know
what they're made from.
They're made from Lycra spandex.
Get out of here.
Lycra spandex?
I think they are made
from Lycra spandex.
Do you wanna bet?
How much you wanna bet?
I'm not betting.
Take a look.
All right.
I'll get a bra.
I don't know what
the big problem is,
getting a bra.
She doesn't want to get a bra.
I'm not saying go to the library
and read the whole history,
but it wouldn't kill you
to know a little bit about it.
All right.
It wouldn't kill me.
How long does it take
to find a bra?
What's going on
in there?
You ask me to get
a pair of underwear,
I'm back
in two seconds.
You know about the cup sizes
and all?
They have different cups.
Yeah, I know
about the cups.
You got the "A."
the "B,"
the "C,"
the "D."
That's the biggest.
I know the "D" is the biggest.
I based my whole life on knowing
that the "D" is the biggest.
Here. Here's the bra.
Let me see it.
One hundred percent
Lycra spandex.
Let me see it.
I told you.
Here.
You think you know everything.
Huh. That's surprising.
All right, what else?
You got the cups in the front,
two loops in the back.
All right,
I guess that's about it.
I got it. Cups in the front,
loops in the back.
You got ketchup on it.
Sniffing?
What do you mean, sniff?
Sniffing
with his nose.
Jerry, he probably had a cold.
No, he didn't.
I asked him.
So what are you saying?
I don't know.
You know, what if--?
Drugs?
You think he's on drugs?
I don't know.
All I know is he was sniffing.
Listen, we went in
on a CD together.
I know.
And Newman gave you money too.
See, I didn't even meet
this guy.
You know. We trusted you.
Look, It doesn't necessarily
mean anything yet.
It just means he was sniffing.
Well, what else?
Was he nervous?
Did he use a lot of slang?
Did he use the word "man"?
No, he didn't use "man."
I mean, when he was leaving,
did he say, "I'm splittin'"?
No, but at one point,
he did use the bathroom.
You think that's a bad sign?
Yes, yes.
That's what they do.
They live
in the bathroom.
All right,
what are we gonna do?
We're gonna go get
our money back, right?
I don't know.
This sweater itches me.
You want it?
Yeah.
Hello? Hel--?
Well, you notice anything?
You have cleaned up
the whole apartment
and you're making dinner.
You're perfect!
You're a perfect man!
BOTH:
Ohhhhh.
Did anyone call?
You got a few messages,
I wrote them down.
Where are they?
Let's see. They are--
Here they are.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah. Ha.
I'll call you back.
Forget that.
[GASPS]
Myra had the baby!
Oh, my god!
That's wonderful!
Who called?
She did.
She did?
Oh, that's so great.
Where do you keep the corkscrew?
It's in the drawer,
on the right.
Hmm.
What?
Nah. It's nothing.
No, what is it?
It's nothing.
Tell me.
Well, I was just curious,
why you didn't use
an exclamation point.
What are you talking about?
Well, see right here?
You wrote,
"Myra had the baby,"
but you didn't use
an exclamation point.
So?
It's nothing.
Forget it. Forget it.
I just found it curious.
What's so curious
about it?
Well, I mean,
if one of your close friends
had a baby,
and I left you
a message about it,
I would use
an exclamation point.
Well, maybe I don't use
my exclamation points,
as haphazardly as you do.
You don't think that
someone having a baby
warrants an exclamation point?
Hey, look, I just
jotted down the message.
I didn't know
that I was required,
to capture the mood
of each caller.
I just thought that you'd be
a little more excited,
about a friend of mine
having a baby.
Okay, I'm excited.
I just don't happen to like
exclamation points.
Well, you know Jake,
you should learn to use 'em.
Like the way I'm talking
right now,
I would put
exclamation points at the ends,
of all these sentences!
On this one!
And on that one!
You can put one
on this one:
I'm leaving!
You're out of your mind,
you know that. Why?
It's an exclamation point.
It's a line
with a dot under it.
Well,
I felt it called for one.
"Called for one." You know, I
thought I'd heard of everything.
I never heard of a relationship
being affected by punctuation.
I find it very troubling
that he didn't use one.
George is right.
Didn't take you long.
Anything new
with that guy on drugs?
Oh, he's not on drugs.
Then why the sniffing?
Who walks around...sniffing?
All right, here.
You call him right now, okay?
See if he's sniffing
right now.
Good idea.
[RINGING]
Prophet and Goldstein.
Yes, I'd like to speak
with Barry Prophet, please.
I'm sorry,
he's out of town this week.
Out of town?
Yes.
He went to South America.
South America?
I'll call back.
Thank you.
He went to South America.
Yeeahh!
So what?
Who goes to South America?
People go to South America.
Yeah, and they come back
with things taped to their large intestine.
So because of a few bad apples,
you're going to impugn
an entire continent?
Yes, I'm impugning
a continent.
Well, I say we go
and get our money right now!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hello,
Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
So any news?
Yeah, he skipped out
and went to South America.
South America?
What kind of snow-blower
did you get us mixed up with?
Okay gentlemen, the fact remains
you still have no proof.
This is all speculation
and hearsay.
Wait, there's one way
to find out.
We set up a sting.
You know, like Abscam.
Like Abscam, Jerry.
Oh, what are you going to do?
You're going to put on
phony beards,
and dress up like Arab sheiks,
and sit around
in some hotel room?
I mean, come on.
Well, wait a second.
Maybe there is a way that
we could tempt him and find out.
I'm sure if we put
our three heads together,
we should come up
with something.
[♪]
What's today?
It's Thursday.
Really?
Feels like Tuesday.
Tuesday has no feeling.
Monday has a feel.
Friday has a feel.
Sunday has a feel.
I feel Tuesday and Wedn--
All right, shut up,
the both of you.
You're making me nervous.
Where is he already?
He should have been out of work by now.
You know,
this is kinda fun.
Yeah. Maybe we ought to become
private detectives.
Maybe you should.
Maybe I will.
Yeah, me too.
All right,
what are you gonna say to him?
I'm just gonna find out
if he's interested.
Hey, maybe I should go
in with him.
No, you stay here in the car.
Who made you leader?
All right, Newman.
One more peep out of you,
you're outta
the whole operation.
There he is.
He's going into that bar.
All right,
I'm going in.
Be careful,
Kramer.
I should have gone
in with him.
No, you stay here, in the car.
I may need you.
What do you need me
in the car for?
I might need you
to get me a soda.
I'll have a brewski,
Charlie.
The name's Mitch.
There's nothing like a cold one
after a long day, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. I've been known
to drink a beer or two.
But then again, I've been known
to do a lot of things.
Cigarette?
No, no.
I never touch 'em.
Well, I suck 'em down
like Coca-Cola.
[SNIFFING]
Well,
here's to feeling good
all the time.
[SNIFFING]
Looks like you got
yourself a little cold there,
huh, fella?
I don't think so.
Me neither.
You should try this new dental
floss, Glide. It's fantastic.
I use Dentotape.
You should try this.
I don't want to.
Not even once?
No.
You know,
you're an idiot.
Why, 'cause
I use Dentotape?
Right. Anyone who uses
Dentotape is an idiot.
South America?
Yeah, yeah.
That's a burgeoning
continent.
Well, they are expanding
their economic base.
Tell me about it.
Excuse me,
I gotta go to the bathroom.
I'm hip.
Hip to what?
To the whole scene.
[SNIFFS]
What scene?
The bathroom scene.
Listen, don't take
this personally,
but when I come back,
I'm sitting over there.
Whatever turns you on.
No, no, no.
I don't like it.
What do you mean
you don't like it?
How could you
not like it?
I like the thick tape.
BARRY:
Hey!
What kind of nut
are you?
So basically, George,
the job here is quite simple:
selling bras.
Well, that interests me very
much, very much indeed, sir.
Have you ever sold
a woman's line before?
No. But, um...
I have a very good
rapport with women.
Very good. Comfortable.
And from the first time
I laid eyes on a brassiere...
I was enthralled.
Hmm.
Tell me about it.
Well, I was 14 years old.
I was in my friend's bathroom.
His mother's brassiere
was hanging over the shower rod.
I picked it up,
I studied it,
I thought, "I like this."
I didn't know in what way
or what level,
but I knew I wanted
to be around brassieres.
That's an incredible story.
You have a remarkable passion
for brassieres.
They're more than just underwear
to me, Mr. Farkus.
Two cups in the front,
two loops in the back.
How do they do it?
Well, I think I can say,
barring
some unforeseen incident,
that you will have
a very bright future,
here at E.D. Granmont.
Thank you, Mr. Farkus.
Thank you very much indeed.
See you Monday, 9:00.
If you don't mind, sir,
I'll be here at 8.
Excellent.
So long, Mr. Farkus.
What do you think
you're you doing?
Nothing. Why?
Farkus,
get out here.
Uh, yes,
Ms. De Granmont?
Farkus,
who's this perverted
little weasel?
Uh, this is Costanza,
he's our new bra salesman.
He's supposed to start
on Monday.
If he's here on Monday,
you're not.
Take your pick.
Get out!
I'm terrible sorry,
Ms. De Granmont.
ELAINE:
You wanted to see me, Mr. Lippman?
I was just, uh, going over
the Jake Jarmel book.
I understand you worked with him
very closely on this.
Yes, ahem,
yes, I did.
Anyway, I was just reading
your final edit,
and, um,
there seems to be an inordinate
number of exclamation points.
Well, I felt the writing lacked
a certain emotion and intensity.
Ahh!
Hmm.
"It was a damp
and chilly afternoon,
so I decided to
put on my sweatshirt!"
Right. Well--
You put an exclamation
point after "sweatshirt."
That's correct.
I felt that the character
doesn't like to be c-c-chilly.
I see.
"I pulled the lever
on the machine,
"but the Clark bar
didn't come out!"
Again exclamation.
Well, you know
how frustrating that can be
when you keep putting quarters
and quarters into a machine,
and nothing comes out--
Get rid of
the exclamation points. Okay.
I hate exclamation points.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
I'm just-- I'll--
"Dear Barry,
consider this letter
"the official termination
of our relationship
effective immediately."
Exclamation point.
You still have no proof.
Elaine, he was sniffing
like crazy around me.
"I will expect all funds,
in the form of a cashier's
check, no later than the 18th."
Double exclamation point.
Will that take care
of ours too?
Yep. I'll give you yours
as soon as I get my money back.
You want me to mail it?
I'm on my way out anyway.
Yeah, thanks.
It'll be
my pleasure.
[GIGGLING]
See you later.
You know--?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey, Ralph!
What's up, fellas?
That'll be $14.30.
All right.
Mushrooms?
You got mushrooms, Jerry?
[SNIFFS]
What's the matter,
you got a cold?
No. Kramer,
what is this?
It's a sweater.
What is it made out of?
I don't know.
Jerry gave it to me.
It's mohair,
I think.
Mohair, it figures.
I'm allergic to mohair.
You mean,
you just started sniffing?
Yeah. Mohair does it
to me every time.
I was wearing that sweater
in the coffee shop,
when Barry came in.
Jerry, I was wearing it
in the bar.
The sweater!
The sweater made him sniff!
See, I told you he wasn't
a drug addict.
Oh, no, the letter!
Newman, it's got exclamation
points all over it.
Not to mention the picture
of him on the toilet.
The what?
After you.
Thank you.
Get your hands
off of me!
Johnny! Johnny!
What do you mean
you felt her material?
What, with your fingers,
like this?
So what?
What's so bad about that?
Who goes around feeling
people's material?
What can be gained by feeling
a person's material?
It's insanity!
Whatever happened to:
"My that's a lovely dress
you have on.
"May I have this dance?"
You know you are really lucky
Newman never mailed that letter.
Sorry I'm late.
I just came from a meeting
with my lawyer.
What is this?
It's a letter from your friend,
Barry Prophet's lawyer.
He's filing
chapter 11?
What's going on?
Why's he filing
chapter 11?
Bankruptcy.
Bankruptcy, as in
"I've taken your money
and spent it on drugs."
What do you mean?
I thought it was the sweater!
All right,
what about the money?
What about the money?
Apparently, if I'd dissolved
my relationship with him,
prior to his filing chapter 11,
I could have got the money back.
Which I would have done.
If a certain imbecile,
had been able to get
to a mailbox,
and mail a letter.
A pair of bear claws, please.
Nice.
Think so?
Yeah. What is it?
Half silk, half cotton,
half linen.
How can you go wrong?
[♪]
My accountant actually did take
a big chunk of money from me,
and use it to buy drugs.
And the thing that was hardest
for me to comprehend about this,
is the life choice
of drug abuse and accounting.
But actually, it makes sense.
Why would and athlete
or musician take drugs?
They have an interesting job.
But an accountant?
If ever a job required
some hallucinogenic support,
this is the job.
That should be
the legal defense.
You're in court:
"You're charged with possession
of illegal narcotics."
"But your honor,
I'm an accountant."
Bang! "Case closed.
"Bailiff, give this man his
peyote buttons and tequila back,
"for the drive home.
Sorry to bother you, sir,
terribly sorry."