You can always tell what was the
best year of your father's life
because they seem to freeze
that clothing style
and just ride it out to the end,
don't they?
And it's not like they don't
continue shopping,
it's just they somehow manage
to find new old clothes.
Every father is like
this fashion time capsule,
you know what I mean?
It's like they should be
on a pedestal
with someone next to 'em goin',
"This was 1965."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
To me, the worst thing
is shopping for pants.
I hate dressing and undressing
in that little room.
What men need is a place
to shop where you go in,
you check your pants
at the door,
and you just walk around
the store in your underwear.
That would be the best way.
Then you'd really have to lie
to the salesman.
"Need some help?"
"No, just getting some air."
How would you describe
the smell in this house?
Dandruff?
Yeah, that's part of it.
Kasha?
There's some kasha.
Yeah. Dandruff, kasha,
mothballs, cheap carpeting.
It's potpourri, really.
All right, let's go.
Come on.
What,
you're going?
Yeah. We shouldn't
have bowled that last game.
I'm gonna be late.
Hey. These aren't candies,
are they?
Did you use those?
These are guest soaps.
Well, I'm a guest.
Now my parents are gonna know
I had people over.
Not allowed
to have people over?
I can't have any parties
while they're out of town.
This is a party?
Not anymore.
Come on, get your ball.
We're leavin'.
Let's go, let's go.
Whoa!
Who put this cup
right on the new table?!
I was having coffee.
I put it on the coffee table.
But you didn't use a coaster!
Jerry, you left a stain.
Oh, boy, there's always one
at every party, huh?
Come on.
What's the big rush?
I'm having people over.
Who?
The girls for poker night.
You know, Joanne,
Renee, Winona--
Ah, ah, ah.
Winona's gonna be there?
Yeah. And she broke up
with the vitamin guy.
Really?
I'll put in a good word
for you.
Thanks. Because I would really--
[SCREAMS]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
I tell you,
this is not coming out.
Just put a coffee-table book
over it.
My parents don't read.
They're gonna wonder what
a book is doing on the table.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You know what would make
a great coffee-table book?
A coffee-table book
about coffee tables.
Get it?
Got it.
Come on, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Not so fast.
Jerry, you gotta take me
to get this thing refinished.
Now?
Yes, now.
It's gonna take a few days,
and my parents are
gonna be back.
I gotta have it back
before then.
Jerry, you promised you'd
get me home by 7.
All right, we'll take
the subway.
That'll get you home
in time.
Oh. The subway?
From Queens?
I'm gonna
get my coat.
I'm sorry, Elaine,
I'll make it up to you.
I need something to read
on the subway.
Here, read this.
TV Guide?
Like a history of coffee tables.
Celebrities and
their coffee tables.
It's a natural.
This is a story
that must be told.
Mm-hmm.
So you gonna talk
to your boss about it, huh?
Mm-hmm. First thing
in the morning.
Yes, indeed.
CONDUCTOR:
Next stop, Queensborough Plaza.
Oh. Queensborough Plaza.
This stop is famous
for its gyros.
You want one?
How are you gonna
get something
and get back
on the train in time?
Well, they got a stand
right out on the platform.
The gyros are cooked and wrapped
and ready to go.
Three dollars, no change.
You want one?
No thanks.
All right. But no bites.
Highlighter?
Excuse me?
To highlight the programs
you plan to watch.
Uh, look, really, I'm--
I'm just trying to read.
Fine, okay. It's just...
I've never seen a beautiful lady
reading...the Guide...
so far away
from the TV.
You must really like television.
KRAMER:
Hey!
Guess your boyfriend will have
to catch the next train.
He's not my boyfriend.
He's not?
Interesting.
Hey, maybe I should get
Elaine something.
Why?
Ah, you know,
I didn't drive her home,
plus I give her a gift
in front of Winona,
how does that hurt me?
Can't hurt you.
What about--?
What about this thing?
The Indian?
Yeah, you know,
kind of a peace offering.
It's cute.
Well, I can have the table
ready for you on Monday.
All right, but no later 'cause
my parents are coming back.
They left you home alone, huh?
Oh.
Okay, see?
On this particular Tuesday,
you could have watched
six hours of Lucy.
There's I Love Lucy...
The Lucy Show...
Here's Lucy.
Oh! Ha-ha. It's my stop.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Bye-bye.
Hey, miss, you forgot this!
They don't make these
anymore.
The work is all done by hand.
It takes years and years.
Sylvia!
For cryin' out loud,
you're 45 minutes late.
Yeah, yeah.
[GIGGLES]
Is that your car out there?
No, it's his.
Oh, nice.
You guys are obviously
from Manhattan?
Well, he is.
I-- I live around the corner.
Really? Hm.
I didn't think any cool guys
lived in this neighborhood.
Well, they do now.
The neighborhood's changing.
All right,
I'll take it.
Smart choice.
Wow, you bought the Indian?
Oh, you guys
have great taste.
Well,
we're collectors.
We, uh, see objects
of great beauty and, uh...
we must have them.
Bluffed you out, jack.
Pair of deuces.
Ohhh.
[ELAINE LAUGHS]
[KNOCKING]
Who is it?
It's Jerry.
What?
Jerry!
Surprise!
What is this?
Well, I felt bad about
this afternoon,
so I got you something.
Oh, you did.
Do you guys all know Jerry?
Hi, Jerry.
Yeah. Hi.
Hi. Hi, Winona.
Nice to see you again.
Elaine, is it
your birthday?
No.
I don't need a reason
to give gifts.
It's my nature.
I love to make people happy.
Oh, that is so sweet.
Ohhh.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Ta-da!
It's a cigar-store Indian.
Read the card.
That's very nice.
Thank you very much.
Read it out loud.
I-- I don't think so.
Jerr--
We had a little fight
this afternoon.
"Let's bury the hatchet.
We smokem peace pipe."
You know, it's late.
I really should go.
I, uh-- I don't blame you,
Winona. I--
♪ Hey-ya, ho-ah
Hey-ya, ho-ah ♪
♪ Ho-ah, ha
Hey-ya, ho-ya ♪
♪ Hey-ya, ho
Hey-ya, ho-ah ♪
Are you out of
your mind?
It's-- It's--
It's kitschy.
Winona is
a Native American.
She is?
You've got
very unusual taste.
I hope prune juice is all right.
It's the only thing I had
that was chilled.
Oh, that's fine.
I'm sorry about that lock
on the liquor cabinet.
The, uh-- The combination must
have just flown out of my head.
It's a mental block.
Ah. Is this your son
in the bubble bath?
No, that's me.
Oh.
You don't see
too many guys your age
who keep baby pictures
of themselves around.
[CHUCKLES]
I like it.
Consistent with the rest
of the house.
Yes, it is consistent.
I've, uh--
I've tried to maintain
a consistent feel
throughout the house.
What is this
we're listening to?
The Ray Conniff singers.
Mmmmm.
What's that smell?
Kasha?
It's a potpourri.
May I, uh...?
May I show you
the master bedroom?
WINONA:
Who is it?
Uh, Winona,
it's Jerry Seinfeld.
Yeah?
Um, listen, I really feel bad
about what happened. I-- I--
I'd really like to apologize.
Can I come up?
[SIGHS]
I'll come down.
I came by
to get my ball.
It's right
over there.
Oh. Yeah, thanks.
Yeah, it's got the magic grip.
How do you think I bowled
that 220 today, huh?
Yo.
Where did this come from?
Do you want it?
I can have this?
Ha. Yeah.
You wanna lug it uptown,
it's yours.
Oh, I'll lug.
It's just that it's
a very sensitive issue for me.
And well it should be.
I think if you spent any time
with me at all,
you'd see I'm very sensitive
to these matters as well.
You wouldn't be hungry
by any chance, would you?
I guess I could go for a bite.
Do you like Chinese food?
'Cause I once went to
a great Szechwan restaurant
in this neighborhood.
I don't remember the address.
Uh, excuse me.
You must know where
the Chinese restaurant is?
Why must I know?
Because I'm Chinese?
You think I know where all
the Chinese restaurants are?
Oh, ask honorable Chinaman
for "rocation" of restaurants.
No, I thought because
you're the mailman
you would know
the neighborhood.
Oh, hello, American Joe, which
way to hamburger/hot-dog stand?
I...
I didn't know--
It's late.
I should probably just go home.
I-I had no idea--
Hey, Jerry, look what I got!
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!
Looks pretty good.
Yeah, he did a good job.
Yeah, I don't think
they'll be able to tell.
You know, I don't get it.
You're not allowed to ask
a Chinese person
where a Chinese restaurant is?
I mean, aren't we all getting
a little too sensitive?
I mean, somebody asks me
which way is Israel,
I don't fly off the handle.
So, anyway, what's, uh--?
What's the status with, uh--?
She kinda calmed down.
I talked to her today.
In fact, I'm gonna
see her tonight.
Oh, great.
But I'm a little
uncomfortable.
I'm afraid of making
another mistake.
Ah, come on--
Hello, hello!
[FLATLY]
Oh. Hey. Your home. Hi.
Oh, Georgie!
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, the house
looks very nice.
Yeah, huh?
Where's the mail?
Hello, Jerry.
Hello.
So how was the trip?
Eh. Your father.
Is there anything wrong
with getting a receipt
at a toll booth?
I'm going upstairs.
This stack
should be bigger.
Where's the TV Guide?
What TV Guide?
I'm missing TV Guide
volume 41 number 31.
Uh, Elaine took it
to read on the subway.
Elaine took it?
I didn't know
she took it.
Ah, it's two weeks old.
How could you let her take
the TV Guide?!
He collects them.
You collect TV Guide?
The nerve of that woman
walking into my house,
stealing my collectibles.
ESTELLE:
Oh, my God!
This was
in our bed.
Wh--?
What is this?
A prophylactic rubber?
What is this doing
on my bed?!
I don't know. Uh...
I'll see you later.
You were having sex
on our bed?
Yes.
Who told you
you could have sex in our bed?
[WHINES]
Well, my bed is too small!
Your bed is too small?
I'm gone two weeks,
and you turn our house into...
Into Bourbon Street?
Where am I
going to sleep?
What're you talkin' about?
I can't sleep in there!
Of course, you can.
I can't.
I can't!
That's it.
You're grounded.
You can't ground me,
I'm a grown man.
You wanna live here...
you respect
the rules of our house.
You're grounded!
So...where are
we gonna go eat?
Oh, I thought we'd eat
at the Gentle Harvest.
Ooh, I love that place,
but it's usually so crowded.
Can we get a table?
Oh, don't worry.
I made reser--
You made what?
I, uh...
I, uh-- I arranged for
the appropriate accommodations.
Mm.
And then...
Knick tickets.
Floor seats.
Oh!
How did you get these?
Got 'em on the street
from the scal--
From who?
A, uh...
One of those guys.
What guys?
You know, the guys that, uh--
They sell the tickets
to the sold out events.
Oh.
Wait a second.
You got the Mark McEwen
TV Guide.
That's Al Roker.
Oh, well, they're both
chubby weathermen.
I get Dom DeLuise and
Paul Prudhomme mixed up too.
Could I have this?
Sure, take it.
Thanks.
JERRY:
So Winona had the TV Guide.
Told you
I'd make it up to you.
Ah. So, Mr. Costanza
was pretty mad, huh?
Yeah. You almost ruined
his life's work.
He collects these?
Yeah.
Wow.
All right, well, I will
personally go out to Queens
and deliver his Al Roker
TV Guide to him.
What'd you do
with the one you took?
I don't know.
[HUMMING I LOVE LUCY THEME]
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Hi.
Yeah, uh, Elaine,
what did, uh--?
What did he say, huh?
What did who say?
Your boss.
Didn't you tell him about
the coffee-table book?
Um...
Yeah, you didn't tell him,
did you?
Kramer, it is
such a dumb idea.
I would be--
Wait a minute, on the cover--
I would be embarrassed
to bring it up.
I thought it was
a pretty good idea.
It's about coffee tables,
it's on a coffee table.
Yeah, right, right.
And on the cover is
a built-in coaster.
Chk!
All right, I'm gonna go.
Where are
you goin'?
I'm gonna go
to the cigar stores.
I'm gonna see if
I can sell that Indian.
My Indian?
You know, I think
it's worth something.
It's kitschy. Chk!
How do you just
walk into a house
and take a TV Guide?
How does she expect
you to watch TV?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Am I just supposed to
turn it on
and wander aimlessly
around the dial?
Hello. Is Elaine home?
Elaine Benes?
Oh, she's my son's friend.
And she's not welcome
in this house.
Oh, 'cause I made her
this very special gift, okay.
It's-- It's a bouquet of paper
from her TV Guide.
That's my TV Guide!
Ripped to shreds.
She gave that to you?
Hey!
Is that the Twilight Zone
you're watching?
Yeah.
Oh, this is a good one.
CONDUCTOR:
Next stop, Queensborough Plaza.
ELAINE:
Mmm, gyro.
I like your place.
It's very unassuming.
Oh, why would I assume?
I never assume.
It leads to assumptions.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, by the way,
that TV Guide I gave you?
I need it back.
Why?
I'm doing a report
on minorities in the media,
and I wanted to use
that interview with Al Roker.
It's too late.
I gave it to Elaine.
She's already on her way
to give it to George's father.
Jerry, I really need it back.
I-it is mine.
You can't give something
and then take it back.
I mean,
what are you, a--? A...?
What?
A, uh...
A person that, uh...
A person that what?
Well, a person
that gives something,
and then they're dissatisfied,
and they wish they had never--
And?
Gi-given--
Given it to the person
that they originally gave it to.
You mean like...
an Indian giver?!
I'm sorry, I'm not familiar
with that term.
I like the special fall preview
issues the best.
Those...
I've been saving
those from the beginning.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
These are worth, like,
a lot of money.
Oh, hello, Elaine.
Hello.
MAN:
Elaine!
Hello.
You look scrumptious.
Why'd you take
my TV Guide?
I'm so sorry about that,
Mr. Costanza.
But look, look.
I brought you
another one.
I made this for you.
Oh.
Thank you.
What is this?
You got stains all over it.
What the hell'd you do?
Hey, you can't talk to her
like that.
I'll talk to her
any way I want!
Come on, Elaine, let's go.
My coffee table!
KRAMER:
I don't understand.
How can you have a cigar store
without an Indian?
It's unseemly.
I'll give you
a box of coronas for it.
Forget it.
E-excuse me, are--?
Are you, uh,
selling this Indian?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm just
redecorating my office
Uh-huh.
in a southwestern motif
and this would be perfect.
Give you $500 for it?
Giddyup.
Yeah?
Could you help me bring it up
to my office?
I'm right next door,
Pendant Publishing.
Giddyup again.
Mr. Lippman, I'm sorry.
I was in Queens and--
Oh.
Kramer.
Yeah, hi, Elaine.
What're you doing in here
with that?
Well, it's a...
business transaction.
Listen, the petty cash
just had 10s and 20s.
Go ahead, count it.
Yeah.
I'm sure
it's all here.
You know, I was just admiring
your coffee table
out there in the hall.
You like that, huh?
I had that custom made for me
in Santa Fe.
You mind if I use it
in my book?
What book?
Well, I'm doing
a coffee-table book on coffee tables.
About coffee tables?
Uh-huh.
That's fantastic.
Who's your publisher?
Well, I'm still
shopping it around.
Yeah?
You see...
this is the kind of idea
you should be coming in with.
What the hell do you do around
here all day, anyway?
Um, well, I read manuscripts--
God, that Indian really
completes the room.
Don't you think?
[SIGHS]
I know this coffee table.
It's George Costanza's.
It's mine.
I'm his mother.
Oh, I haven't seen George
for a while.
He must be working very hard.
George doesn't work.
He's a bum.
That's why he lives
at home with us.
He does?
I don't know why we didn't
think of this before.
We just could call TV Guide.
I don't know.
Well, it's gonna make
Mr. Costanza very happy.
I guess.
What's the matter?
What do you think
is the matter?
I've been assigned to work
on Kramer's coffee-table book.
It is a good idea,
Elaine.
CONDUCTOR:
Next stop, Queensborough Plaza.
Do you want a gyro?
I don't think so.
Elaine!
Ah, guess your boyfriend's gonna
have to catch the next train.
He's not my boyfriend.
He's not?
Interesting.
I was always excited as a kid
when that new TV Guide
would come.
Somehow when that front cover's
nice and flat,
it seems like there's good,
fresh TV shows in there.
Then as the week goes by,
you start to hate the TV.
All the shows stink.
Everything's gettin'
all crumpled and ripped
from being sat on,
thrown across the room.
TV Guide is always thrown,
never handed to another person.
It's the world's most thrown
reading material.
"Where's the TV Guide?
There it is."
You know, in the back
of the TV Guide,
they have a phone number,
95 cents a minute,
they'll give you the answers to
the TV Guide crossword puzzle.
My question is, if you can't do
the TV Guide crossword puzzle,
where are you comin' across
95 cents?