To me, the thing about
birthday parties
is that the first and last
party you have
are actually quite similar.
You know, you just
kind of sit there.
You're the least excited
person at the party.
You don't even really realize
that there is a party.
You don't know
what's going on.
Both birthday parties,
people have to help you
blow out the candles.
You can't do it.
You don't even know
why you're doing it.
What is this ritual?
What is going on?
It's also the only two
birthday parties
where other people
have to gather
your friends together for you.
Sometimes they're
not even your friends.
They make the judgment.
They bring them in,
sit 'em down, and they tell you:
"These are your friends.
"Tell them
thank you for coming
to my birthday party."
WOMAN:
These are great! Just great!
Really great!
Really,
really great!
Don't you think so,
Elaine?
Yeah.
Really great.
Oh, a coffee table book
about coffee tables.
How did you come up
with this idea?
It was there.
Oh, look at this one.
It's saying,
"I'm a coffee table.
"Put some coffee on me.
Oh, the hotter the better.
That's what I'm here for."
Ah, you know, actually, I've
got some work I've gotta do.
How about if the book came
with these little foldout legs
so the book itself
becomes a coffee table.
Oh, that is
a great idea!
Really,
really great!
ELAINE:
"Ohh!
"and that coffee table
is saying,
put some coffee on me!"
I'd like to put
some coffee on her.
Hot, scalding coffee
right in her face.
I swear! This is like
working with a contestant
from The Price Is Right.
[FAKE LAUGHING]
Yeah, that's
real interesting. Elaine...
listen, tell me if
you think this is funny.
"Men definitely hit the remote
more than women.
"Men don't care
what's on TV.
"Men only care
what else is on TV.
"Women wanna see
what the show is
"before they
change the channel
because men hunt
and women nest."
Yeah, it's funny.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Come on. That's gold!
Well, I don't know
about gold.
Oh, that's gold, baby.
Baby? What?
Are you doing George now?
Hey, I was saying "baby"
way before George.
Well, I don't know. Don't ask me
any more questions about jokes.
Jerry, it just puts
too much pressure on me.
This guy Leonard Christian's
gonna be there tomorrow.
Yeah?
Who's he?
A writer from
Entertainment Weekly.
I would like to have
a good show.
Danke schoön,
my little dumplings.
Hi.
Hey, how 'bout
that Toby, huh?
Yeah,
how about her?
Ooh, she's a package
full of energy.
Yeah, she's a package
full of something.
And that something
is life.
You gotta meet this gal.
She's brimming with positivity.
Oh, please.
Hey, are you performing
tomorrow?
Yeah.
Great.
I'm gonna bring Toby.
You better laugh.
I'm being reviewed by Leonard Christian.
She's a great laugher.
Right, Elaine?
Oh, yeah.
She's a great laugher, Jerry.
"Ha-ha!
Really, really great!"
Well, you wanna
sit with George?
He's coming with Robin.
The waitress
from the comedy club? Yeah.
What about her kid?
Is she bringing him too?
She's got a kid?
Yeah. You should see George
get along with this kid.
GEORGE:
Ow! What are you doing under there?
Hey, hey, stop that.
Don't eat that.
That's not food!
He's sucking down
Equal packets.
Do you think 25 kids
is too much?
Twenty-five kids
for his birthday party?
Don't put your tongue
on the floor!
He's putting his tongue
on the floor.
Here, here.
Have some more
sugar packets.
So what about
entertainment?
Should I get Barney?
BOY:
No Barney!
Maybe a clown.
How about Bozo?
BOY:
Who's Bozo?
Bozo the Clown.
That's who Bozo is.
When I was a kid, Bozo
the Clown was the clown.
George...
With the orange hair,
the ruffled clown shirt.
George...
A TV show.
Cartoons.
George!
Forget Bozo, George.
Bozo's out.
He's finished.
It's over for Bozo.
When I was a kid, we didn't
have these elaborate parties
with catered food
and entertainment.
I remember my seventh
birthday party.
Blow out the candles!
I said blow out
the damn candles!
Stop it, Frank!
You're killing him!
Blow out the candles!
Well, this time, you can
blow out the candles.
No. I have asthma.
Ow! Ben!
Ben!
Hi.
Hi, Toby.
How are you
doing today?
Fine.
How are you?
Oh, I'm great.
Just great.
Really great.
Oh, hey, did you hear
about Bob Rosen?
No.
He's going to Knopf. He is going
to be a vice president.
Knopf? Really?
Boy...
that means there's
an opening here for...
senior editor.
Has Lippman, uh,
hired anyone?
No. I hear he wants to
promote someone in-house.
Really?
Maybe it'll be you.
Oh, well...
You really deserve it.
I mean, you have
experience, seniority.
Lippman really
respects your opinion.
Well...
Well, it could be you.
No.
No, really.
Really?
You think so?
Sure.
Boy, wouldn't that
be exciting?
I mean, stranger things
have happened.
Wow! Me, a senior editor!
I'd like that.
You shouldn't
get your hopes up.
Oh, well...
It's a possibility.
Like you said, stranger
things have happened.
Thank you, Elaine.
Thank you.
JERRY:
Hey, Ronnie.
Hey.
Can I have
a club soda?
Going on tonight?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
You know,
Leonard Christian's here.
Yeah, I know.
Can I ask you something?
Are my nostrils
getting bigger?
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
Take a good look.
They seem
a little bigger?
I don't...
I don't know.
Is it possible
for nostrils to expand?
Oh, is this a bit?
Hey, I don't do bits.
I'm a prop comic.
Damn it. I can't
find my water gun.
I can't go on
without my water gun.
Hey, Jerry.
Hey!
Well, here's Toby.
Jerry.
This is so exciting.
Look.
I have goose bumps.
Touch.
TOBY:
Touch them.
Ahh! Ha-ha!
Oh, hey.
I've never been
to a comedy club before.
Really?
You know a lot of restaurants
are serving brewed decaf too.
[LAUGHING]
You are so funny!
You'll have a good time,
I swear.
He swears, like he thinks
I don't believe him.
I believe you.
Oh, he's so funny.
What about me?
What about you?
I'm only kidding.
You're funny too.
I love to laugh.
Good. Good.
So you up next?
Yeah. You guys
get a table.
So you have good seats.
We don't want some jerk
in front of us.
It'll be, like, "Hey, big-head,
move outta the way.
I didn't pay a cover charge
to stare at your bald spot."
All right,
have a good show.
Yeah.
Hey, we'll make sure
it's a great show.
Okay, good.
I'll see ya later.
Yeah.
Oh, he's so great!
This is so great!
I'm so excited!
Men definitely
hit the remote button
more than women.
Oh, really!
That is so true!
Yes, I... Yeah.
See, men don't care
what's on TV.
Men only care
what else is on TV.
Oh, yes, yes!
TOBY:
Right on! Right on!
See, women, uh...
Women really wanna see
what the show is
before they
change the channel.
TOBY:
Oh! That is so true!
Yes! Yes!
JERRY:
That's why...
men hunt
and women nest.
Boo! Boo!
Sssss!
TOBY:
Boo!
Uh, yeah, anyway,
Yeah, all right.
So, uh, anyway...
What was I talking about?
Hey.
Wh-what's the deal?
What was going on there?
I invite you down here.
I have an important show,
and she heckles me?
Look, she didn't
mean anything.
What's the matter with her?
Is she crazy?
She's just being
enthusiastic, that's all.
Hey, what is wrong
with you?
Me?
Nothing's
wrong with me.
You boo me!
You hiss!
You didn't stop blathering
throughout the whole set.
Oh, come on!
I thought you're a pro.
That's part
of the show.
No!
Not part of the show.
Booing and hissing
are not part of the show.
You boo puppets. You hiss
villains in silent movies.
Well, that's the way
I express myself.
How will you make it
if you can't take it?
Oh, I can take it.
Let's go.
Hey, man, good set.
Bozo?
No.
B-O-Z-O.
Sorry. I...
You've never heard
of Bozo the Clown?
No!
How could you not know
who Bozo the Clown is?
I don't know.
I just don't.
How can you call
yourself a clown
and not know
who Bozo is?
Hey, man, what are
you hassling me for?
This is just a gig.
It's not my life.
I don't know who Bozo is?
What, is he a clown?
What, are you
kidding me?
Well, what is he?
Yes, he's a clown!
What's the big deal?
There's millions of clowns.
All right.
Just forget it.
Me? You should
forget it.
You're living
in the past, man.
You're hung up on some
clown from the '60s, man!
All right.
Very good.
All right. Go fold your little
balloon animals, Eric.
"Eric."
Ha-ha. What kind of name
is that for a clown, huh?
Excuse me.
You must be
George.
I'm Robin's
mother.
Ohh.
You seem like such
a lovely young man.
Well, I do what I can.
Hi, Ma.
How's everything?
Oh, this is just
a wonderful party.
The burgers should be ready
in a minute.
Oh, great. Great.
[SNIFFING]
What's that smell?
Smoke?
Smoke...
Everybody...
I think I smell
some smoke back here.
Fire!
[EVERYONE SCREAMING]
It was an inferno in there!
An inferno!
MAN:
There he is! That's him!
WOMAN:
That's the coward that left us to die!
[YELLING]
I was trying
to lead the way.
We needed a leader.
Someone to lead
the way to safety.
But you yelled,
"Get out of my way."
Because...
as the leader,
if I die,
then...
all hope is lost!
Who would lead?
The clowns?
Huh?
Instead of
castigating me,
you should all
be thanking me.
What kind of a topsy-turvy
world do we live in where--
Where heroes are
cast as villains,
brave men
as cowards?
But I saw you push
the women and children
out of the way
in a mad panic.
I saw you knock them down!
And when you ran out,
you left everyone behind!
Seemingly.
To the untrained eye,
I can fully understand
how you got
that impression.
What looked
like pushing,
what looked like
knocking down,
was a safety
precaution.
In a fire,
you stay
close to the ground.
Am I right?
Well...
And when I ran
out that door,
I was not leaving
anyone behind!
Quite the contrary.
I risked my life,
making sure
that exit was clear.
Any other questions?
How do you live
with yourself?
It's not easy.
So, she doesn't wanna
see me anymore.
Did you knock
her over, too,
or just the kids?
No. Her too.
And her mother.
Really? Her mother?
Yeah.
I may have
stepped on her arm too.
You probably couldn't see
because of the smoke.
Yeah.
But it was
somebody's arm.
Mmm.
So you feel...
"women and children first"
in this day and age
is somewhat of
an antiquated notion.
To some degree, yeah.
So basically,
it's every man,
woman, child and invalid
for themselves.
In a manner
of speaking.
Yeah.
Well, it's honest.
She should be
commending me
for treating everyone
like equals.
Well, perhaps when she's
released from the burn center,
she'll see things
differently.
Perhaps.
So, what was the fire,
just some greasy hamburgers?
Yeah.
Eric, the clown, put it out
with his big shoe.
By the way,
did you see this?
No, what's that?
The Leonard Christian
article about my show.
Plus my gig in Miami
got canceled.
I betcha it's because
of the article.
Wow.
He really does
a number on you.
"Seinfeld froze like a deer
in the headlights
in the face of
incessant heckling."
I should've let her have it.
I held back because of Kramer.
You know what you
ought to do?
You should go to her office
and heckle her.
Yeah, right.
Like all the comedians say,
"What if I came to your work
and heckled you?"
Yeah, that'd be something.
I'm not kidding.
You should do it.
But wouldn't that be
the ultimate comedian's revenge?
I've always had a fantasy
about doing that.
Well, go ahead.
Do it.
Why can't I?
No reason.
You know what?
I think I'll do that.
She came down
to where I work.
I'll go down
to where she works.
This is unprecedented.
There's no precedent,
baby.
What, you're using
my "babies" now?
Hey, nice shoes.
What, do you wear
sandals to work?
It's always nice to walk
in a room and get the aroma of feet.
That's real conducive
to the work atmosphere.
I'm sure your coworkers
appreciate it.
Hey, let's go eat
in Toby's office.
Great idea. We can
check on her bunions.
You know, I have work
to do here. I'm very busy.
Oh, is this
disruptive?
You find it hard to work
with someone interrupting?
Well, how'd you like it
if I called security?
Security!
I don't know how you'll
make it in this business
if you can't take it.
Oh!
You gotta be tough.
Boo! Boo!
You know--
Hiss! Boo!
All right.
That's it.
Get out of my way!
What's going on?
What's happening here?
Toby!
Sss! Boo!
TOBY:
My pinkie toe!
KRAMER:
Toby!
Oh!
KRAMER:
What did you go up there to heckle her for?
Because she came down
to the club and heckled me.
I gave her a taste
of her own medicine.
Oh, yeah! You gave her
a taste of medicine, all right.
Well, I didn't want her
to have an accident.
What accident?
After he heckled Toby,
she got so upset,
she ran out
of the building,
and a street sweeper
ran over her foot
and severed
her pinkie toe.
That's
unbelievable!
Yeah. Then after
the ambulance left,
I found the toe.
So I put it in a Cracker Jack
box, filled it with ice
and took off
for the hospital.
You ran?
No. I jumped
on the bus.
I told the driver, "I got a toe
here, buddy. Step on it."
Holy cow!
Yeah, yeah.
Then, all of a sudden,
this guy pulls out a gun.
Well, I knew any delay's
gonna cost her her pinkie toe,
So I got out of the seat
and started walking towards him.
He says, "Where do you think
you're going, Cracker Jack?"
And I says, "Well, I got
a prize for you, buddy"
Plah! Plah! Keeyah!
Knocked him
out cold.
How could you
do that?
Yeah, then everybody
is screaming
because the driver,
he's passed out
because of all
the commotion.
The bus is
out of control!
So I grab him by the collar.
I take him out of the seat.
I get behind the wheel.
Now I'm driving the bus.
You're Batman.
Yeah. Yeah.
I am Batman.
Then the mugger,
he comes to,
and he starts
choking me,
So I'm fighting him off
with one hand,
and I kept driving the bus
with the other, ya know?
Then I managed
to open up the door,
and I kicked him out
the door with my foot
at the next stop.
You kept making
all the stops?
Well, people kept
ringing the bell!
Well, what
about the toe?
What happened
to the toe?
Well, I am happy to say
the little guy's back in place
at the end of the line.
You did all this
for a pinkie toe?
Well, it's a
valuable appendage.
So Kramer
found the toe,
and they
reattached it.
Really?
Yeah. Poor kid.
What an ordeal.
Right. And you know how
extremely sensitive she is.
She's gonna need
our full support.
Yeah, right.
Look who's here!
Toby.
Hey, it's Toby.
WOMAN:
How are you? How are you feeling?
Oh, I'll be okay.
WOMAN:
Are you sure?
I think so.
Toby, what can I do?
Can I get you something?
Oh, no. No, thank you.
Toby, please let us help.
We're family.
Oh, well, I could
use a cup of coffee.
JERRY:
She got the promotion?
Yep.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Because of her pinkie toe.
That's why.
Because Lippman felt
so sorry for her,
he didn't wanna
hurt her feelings.
Too bad.
Sure, the pinkie toe
is cute,
but I mean,
what is it?
It's useless.
It does nothing.
It's got that little nail
that's just impossible to cut.
What do we need it for?
Because that's the one
that goes "wee wee wee"
all the way home.
You just shut the--
Hey, Elaine.
Did you hear the good news?
Toby got promoted.
Yes, I heard,
Kramer.
I work there,
remember?
Yeah, and you know
what she told me?
She said her first
order of business
is to put my coffee table book
into the bookstores
as soon as possible.
Oh, wonderful!
You know, throughout this whole
thing, she always kept smiling.
Of course. She's deranged.
I went down
to the magazine.
I pleaded with him
to come see me again.
He's coming tonight
and writing another article.
I heard you went down
to somebody's office
and heckled them?
Damn right. We've been
lap dogs long enough.
How could you do that?
Everybody's talking about it.
It's about time one of us
drew a line in the sand.
Jerry,
you're like Rosa Parks.
You opened the door
for all of us.
I can't wait till the next time
somebody heckles me.
Yeah, well,
it won't be long.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Jerry Seinfeld!
Robin? Robin!
George, what is it?
I'm working.
Robin, listen to me.
The most amazing
thing has happened.
Kramer has
opened my eyes.
I think
I've changed.
What are you
talking about? Okay.
I mean, Bozo the Clown.
I mean, does he really need
"the Clown" in his title
as clown.
Bozo the Clown?
Are we gonna confuse him
with Bozo the district attorney?
Bozo the pope?
There's no other Bozo.
You'll see. Things
will be different now
if you'll just give me
one more chance.
L-listen, I-I gotta
think about this.
All right, but I'm
serious about this.
All right.
Hand it over, man!
That's why men hunt
and women nest.
GEORGE:
He's got a gun!
Get out of the way!
[SCREAMING]
George!
This is Ronnie Kaye!
The prop comic?
Oh, hi. I--
I didn't
recognize you.
What, did you...
You get a haircut?
Nostrils.
George,
could I have a word?
[♪]
I was in a hotel the other day,
and they have that fire map
on the back of the door.
I'm flattered they think
I have it together enough
to stand in a burning hotel
room memorizing directions.
"Hey, I'll go left
by the stair,
right by the candy machine."
I'd probably get lost,
have to go back to the room,
check the map again.
And they always tell you,
no matter what you do,
in a hotel fire,
do not panic.
Hey, I've got
four minutes to live.
I've never panicked
in my whole life.
It's my option.
Even if they find you,
you have a perfect excuse.
"Gee, I heard they saved you
swinging from the shower curtain
naked with the ice bucket
on your head. What happened?"
"Well, I panicked."
"That's understandable."