We never should have
landed a man on the moon.
It's a mistake.
Now everything is compared
to that one accomplishment.
Now we go, "I can't believe
they can land a man on the moon,
and taste my coffee!"
I think we all
would've been a lot happier
if we hadn't landed a man
on the moon. We'd go:
"They can't make a prescription
bottle top open easily?
"I'm not surprised they couldn't
land man on the moon.
Things make perfect sense
to me now."
Neil Armstrong should've said,
"That's one small step for man,
"one giant leap for every
whining, complaining S.O.B.
on the face of the earth."
[♪]
Hey, do you believe
I got Happy New Year-ed
today?
It's February.
I once got Happy New Year-ed
in March.
Disgusting.
It's pathetic.
Hey, is it cold out?
Really cold.
Scary-cold?
What's your definition
of scary-cold?
That.
What is that?
[LAUGHING]
What?
When did you
get that?
This week.
My father got a deal
from a friend of his.
It's Gore-Tex.
You know
about Gore-Tex?
You like saying Gore-Tex,
don't you?
Look at you.
You can't even turn around
in that thing.
Look at this.
Hey, George,
can you feel this?
Can you?
All right! All right!
Knock it off!
Come on, let's go.
We should stop off on the way
and get a bottle of wine
or something.
What for?
These people invited us
for dinner.
We have to bring
something.
Why?
Because it's rude
otherwise?
You mean,
just going there
because I'm invited,
that's rude?
Yes.
So you're telling me,
instead of them
being happy to see me,
they'll be upset because
I didn't bring anything.
You see
what I'm saying?
The fabric of society
is very complex, George.
I don't even
drink wine.
I drink Pepsi.
You can't bring
Pepsi.
Why not?
Because we're adults?
What,
you're telling me
that wine is better
than Pepsi?
[SNORTS]
No way wine is better
than Pepsi.
I tell ya, George,
I don't think we want
to walk in there
and put a big plastic
jug of Pepsi
in the middle
of the table.
I just don't like
the idea
that any time there's
a dinner invitation
there's this annoying
little chore to go with it.
You know,
you're getting to be
an annoying little chore
yourself.
All right, let's go.
Who's driving?
You are. I can't get
that thing in my car.
[♪]
Where's the heat
in this car?
Come on, Elaine.
Warm me up. It's cold.
Jerry, get off of me.
Just a little squeeze.
Get off!
Get off of me! No!
Hee, hee, hee!
You're pretty comfortable
up there, huh, bubble boy?
Oh, yeah. You wish
you had this coat.
I was just thinking.
The four of us
can't show up
with just one
bottle of wine.
Oh, here we go.
What?
Why don't we
get them a couch. [LAUGHS]
We'll rent a U-Haul,
bring them a nice sectional.
We should bring
some cake.
Will you stop off
at the bakery?
Just get some Ring Dings
from the liquor store.
Ring Dings?
They're better than anything
you'll get at a bakery.
Ooh, I like
Ring Dings.
George, you can't show up
at someone's house
with Ring Dings
and Pepsi.
Hey, your lights
are on!
It's a funeral
procession.
I got news
for you.
I show up with
Ring Dings and Pepsi,
I'd become the biggest hit
of the party.
People would say,
"Just between you and me,
I'm really excited about
the Ring Dings and the Pepsi."
What are we,
Europeans?
With the Beaujolais
and the chardonnay...
Oh. That's the bakery.
Stop here. Stop here. Okay.
Okay, let me out.
You, whatever
your name is.
Jerry.
Yeah. Jerry. Come with me.
So, we're gonna
get the wine.
We'll pick you up here
in 10 minutes?
Yeah.
All right.
[♪]
[ELAINE SNIFFS]
Mmm. I love
the smell of bakeries.
Oh, look. The black
and white cookie.
I love
the black-and-white.
Two races of flavor
living side by side
in harmony.
It's a wonderful
thing, isn't it?
You know, I often wonder
what you'll be like
when you're senile.
I'm looking
forward to it.
I think it'll be
a smooth transition for you.
Thank you.
Look at all this stuff.
What are we getting?
Chocolate babka.
That's their specialty.
Love that babka.
Yeah, yeah.
But when we get up
to the door,
you hold
the cake box.
Why?
I don't know.
Just standing there,
holding a box
by the little string...
You think
it's effeminate?
It's a tad dainty.
[GASPS]
Oh, we forgot
to pick a number.
See,
that's not fair.
We were here ahead
of all these people.
You think I should go
and ask her for hers?
Ah, no, forget it.
No, no, no.
It's not fair!
Just because
they have a ticket
doesn't mean they were
here first. We were here.
And we were ahead of them,
and them, and her.
Come on, let's just
go ask them. Come on.
Excuse me...
KRAMER [SIGHING]:
I'm not finding a spot here.
What do you
wanna do?
Just double-park.
No, no.
Why not?
I'll get a ticket.
Besides, what if somebody
wants to get out of here?
Are you kidding?
People get spaces this good,
they never give them up.
That's a fallacy.
All right,
I tell you what.
Why don't you go into the store.
I'll wait in the car.
Why don't you go into the store,
and I'll wait in the car.
Because
I've got the coat.
I can sit in the car
and not get cold.
So what? I'm gonna leave
the car heater running.
Does the heater even work?
No.
Hey, there's a spot,
right in front
of the liquor store!
You see?
I see.
You see?!
Ho, ho, ho!
[♪]
But we were here
ahead of you!
How do I know that?
Well, we saw you
come in.
Well, that's easy
for you to say.
Yeah, right. That's something
I do all the time.
I make up stories to get
ahead in lines at bakeries.
ATTENDANT:
Forty-six!
Wait-- Wait a second.
Are you
Barbara Benedict?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I don't--
I-- I know you.
I'm Elaine Benes.
Do you remember?
We met at Linda van Brak's
baby shower.
I'm on my way
over there right now.
Yeah, me too.
You're Jerry,
right? David.
Well, this is a little
awkward, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You know, we were
here ahead of you.
You're not getting
my number!
Oh, so you still
don't believe us!
Forty-seven!
That's us!
Oh, okay, fine.
Fine. Go ahead.
But listen.
As soon as I get there,
I'm gonna tell everyone
what a jerk you are.
I'll be there ahead of you,
and I'll be telling them
what a jerk you are!
I'll have
the chocolate babka.
You're lucky, Mrs. Benedict.
It's our last one.
[♪]
All right, what
are we getting?
It's hot in here.
Hm. What do you say
we get a Mouton Cadet?
What's that?
It's a Bordeaux.
Robust, bold,
very dry,
as opposed to a
Beaujolais,
which is richer
and fruitier.
All right, here's one.
Twelve dollars.
Twelve dollars?!
I knew we should've
gone to the bakery.
I guarantee you they're not
getting no $12 cake!
I'll pay you back later.
I don't have my wallet.
Why not?
'Cause I don't like
to carry my wallet.
My osteopath says
it's bad for my spine.
Throws my hips
off-kilter.
[MUTTERING]
Throws your hips off-kilter.
So where's
your money?
I never take it.
So, what do you do?
Oh, I get by.
[♪]
See you later.
See you later!
That's
the last babka.
They got the last
babka. I know!
They're going in first
with the last babka.
That was our babka.
You can't beat a babka!
We had that babka!
They're gonna be
heroes!
What are we gonna do now?
If we can't get
the babka,
the whole thing's
useless.
Well, how about
a carrot cake?
Carrot cake?
Why is that a cake?
You don't make carrots
into a cake. I'm sorry!
Black forest?
Too scary.
You're in the forest.
Ooh.
Hey, how about
a napoleon?
Napoleon?
Who's he
to have a cake?
He was a ruthless
warmonger!
Might as well
get a Mengele.
That was our babka!
We had that babka!
What's this one?
That? Cinnamon babka.
[GASPS]
Another babka?
There's chocolate,
and there's cinnamon.
Well, we gotta get
the cinnamon.
But they got
the chocolate.
We'll be going in
with lesser babka.
I beg your pardon?
Cinnamon takes a back seat
to no babka!
People love cinnamon!
It should be on tables
in restaurants
along with salt and pepper!
Anytime someone says,
"This is so good!
What's in this?",
the answer invariably
comes back: cinnamon,
cinnamon, again and again.
Lesser babka?
I think not.
Forty-nine!
I'll have
a cinnamon babka.
And a black-and-white
cookie for me.
Peace.
That'll be 13.05.
All right.
Here you go.
A hundred?
I can't change that.
You can't?
Ha-ha.
All right, let's go.
Wait a second.
I can get change.
Hey! Anybody got change
for a hundred?
Are you crazy?
You'll get us killed!
What?
Don't go shouting
we got a $100 bill!
People will be
jumping out of windows!
Go buy something,
and we'll get change.
I am not buying something
just to get change.
George, there's a newsstand
right over there. Come on.
What are we doing?
Just get some gum
or something.
Pack of gum.
Here you go.
What is it, a hundred?
I can't change a hundred.
Why not?
You got to buy
more that that.
Here.
Get a newspaper.
Newspaper.
Not enough.
Clark bar.
Keep going.
We're up to
2 dollars here!
George,
get a Penthouse Forum.
I'm not getting
a Penthouse Forum!
That'll make great
dinner-party conversation.
We'll read the letters
at the dinner table.
Oh, that's nice.
Ever read
one of these?
It's not real.
They're all made up!
Oh, it's real.
Hey, you know,
then there's an unusual
number of people
in this country
having sex
with amputees!
Penthouse Forum,
newspaper, gum,
Clark bar.
Six seventy-five.
Oh, great. All right,
with the wine,
I'm in
over $20 now!
[MAN YELLS
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Big coat! Big coat!
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's a new coat.
It's Gore-Tex.
You better be careful
with that thing.
You'll start a war.
Mm.
See, the key to eating
a black-and-white cookie
is you wanna get
some black
and some white
in each bite.
Nothing mixes better
than vanilla and chocolate.
And yet, still somehow
racial harmony eludes us.
If people would only
look to the cookie,
all our problems
would be solved.
Your views on race relations
are just fascinating.
You really should do
an op-ed piece for The Times.
Mm.
Look to the cookie,
Elaine.
Look to the cookie.
Oh, what is this?
What?
It's a hair.
Oh!
Oh, take it back.
Let's get another one.
We're late as it is.
I'll take it off.
No, get another one.
It'll take a second.
All right.
Excuse me--
Hey, hey.
I'm on line here.
No, we just
bought this.
Um, you sold us a cake
with a hair on it.
You have to
take a number.
We waited 15 minutes
for this!
You sell me a cake
with a hair on it,
and then you
want me to wait?
What are you doing?
You're gonna wait now?
I'm not gonna eat a cake
with a hair on it.
It was a little hair.
I took it off.
A little hair?
Do you think
that makes it better?
What if it's your hair?
What is wrong with my hair?
Nobody takes better care
of their hair than me.
You could serve dinner
on my head.
You use that
misty herbal rainwater crap
they sell in
the health food store.
I use Prell,
the hard stuff.
Hundred proof.
Takes your roots out!
Okay, fine.
We'll just wait till
she calls the number.
Maybe we should just
forget about the cake.
No!
I'm bringing cake!
[♪]
All right,
we got the wine.
Aren't we lucky?
We got wine.
Whoopee-whoa!
Imagine if we didn't
bring the wine.
We'd be shunned
by society.
Outcasts!
"Where's your wine?
Get out!"
"I know this is
gonna sound
"like a crazy fantasy,
"but every word
of this story is true.
"A few weeks ago,
"my girlfriend happened
to mentioned to me
how attractive she thought
our new neighbor Linda was."
Look-- Look at this.
Somebody double-parked
and blocked us in!
Does anybody know
whose car that is?
Maybe there's
a note on it.
Oh, brother.
No! No note!
Can you believe this?
"Of course,
I noticed her, too,
"with those ample breasts
and pouty lips.
I don't have to tell you,
she was a knockout."
I really cannot comprehend
how stupid people
can be sometimes!
Can you comprehend it?
No, I can't
comprehend it.
We can put
a man on the moon,
but we're still
basically very stupid.
This car's driver
could be a guy
that built the rocket.
See what I'm saying?
He could build the rocket,
but he's still stupid
for double-parking
and blocking somebody in.
You really understand my point
about building rockets
and double-parking.
On one hand
he's smart with rockets,
and on the other hand
he's dumb with parking.
It's cold out here,
huh?
Maybe it's
not even stupidity.
Maybe it's just
a blatant disregard
for basic human decency.
This is how
dictators start.
Think Mussolini
would circle the block
six times
looking for a spot?
How about Idi Amin, huh?
If I was running
for office,
I'd ask for the death penalty
for double-parkers!
If this is allowed to go on,
this is not a society.
This is anarchy!
Are those shoes
comfortable?
No, not really.
They look comfortable.
I know, that's why
I bought them,
but they're not comfortable.
[♪]
Why couldn't we
take the hair off and go?
No, that's out
of the question.
Why?
Because I had
a bad experience
with a hair
when I was younger.
What happened?
I'd rather not
talk about it.
You can't tell me?
All right.
I once found a hair
in my farina,
and I freaked out.
You found a hair
in your farina?
Yeah.
What happened?
I started screaming,
"There's a hair in my farina! There's a hair in my farina!"
And I ran
out of the house,
and I was running
and running.
I was little, but I could
run really fast.
I just kept running.
They found me
three hours later,
collapsed at
a construction site.
[COUGHING IN BACKGROUND]
Wow.
Whose hair was it?
My mother's.
Oh...
Fifty-eight.
Ooh, that's us.
Oh, good.
You sold us a hair
with a cake around it.
We'd like another one.
[COUGHING]
JERRY:
Oh, that's lovely.
That's what you want
to see, yeah.
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
Yeah, you wanna trade
your hair for some phlegm.
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
That's a good deal.
You win the pennant
with that trade:
hair for phlegm.
Here you are.
Okay. All right,
we got the cake now.
Where is George
and Kramer?
[CAR HORN HONKING]
KRAMER:
Hey, double-parker!
Show yourself!
Come on out!
I'm freezing!
[HONKING HORN]
We are really
late now.
We're in big trouble.
Big trouble.
Why?
You know...
Elaine.
What about her?
I'm a little
scared of her.
You're scared
of Elaine?
Yes!
Why?
Did you ever see her
lose her temper?
I was once late 'cause
I bought a Panama hat.
She grabbed it by the brim,
pulled it down so hard,
my head came right
through the top.
Let's go inside
the liquor store.
I'm freezing in here.
Why don't you
just wear a heavier coat.
I wanted to look good
for the party.
GEORGE:
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
That's great!
That's very nice!
We been waiting 20 minutes
for you people!
You think
you're Mussolini?
Back off, puffball,
it's not my car!
Wasn't talking to you.
KRAMER:
I'm going in.
Wait till I get my hands
on that George.
I am going to pull
that big hood
over his little head,
tie the strings
and suffocate him.
You remember
that Panama hat?
Ha!
That was nothing.
Huh? What?
What's the matter
with you?
I don't know.
I don't feel so good.
What's wrong?
My stomach.
I think it was
that cookie.
The black-and-white?
Yeah.
Not getting along?
I think I got David Duke
and Farrakhan down there.
Well, if we can't
look to the cookie,
where can we look?
I feel like
I'm gonna throw up.
Wait. What about
your vomit streak?
I know.
I haven't thrown up
since June 29, 1980.
Ow! Oh!
[GASPING]
Sorry.
Sorry?
You almost
took my toe off!
Why don't you watch
what you're doing,
you lunatic!
Oh, Jerry, I think
he broke my toe.
Wh-- Where
you going?
Fourteen years
down the drain.
You think chickens
have individual personalities?
[SHIVERING ]
I don't know.
If you had five chickens,
could you tell them apart
just by the way
they acted,
or would they all
just be walking around?
[CLUCKS LIKE CHICKEN]
If they have
individual personalities,
I'm not sure we should be
eating them.
What's the matter
with you?
[CHATTERS INCOHERENTLY]
Can I help you guys
with anything?
No, no.
We bought the wine
here before.
We're just waiting for some
double-parker to unblock us.
Well, wait outside.
This isn't a hangout.
But my friend here
has hypothermia!
Hypothermia.
All right, guys...
take it outside.
[BOTTLES CRASH]
You're paying for these.
How was it?
Good as it gets.
You know, that coat
was Gore-Tex.
It's worth a hell
of a lot more
than that cheap
chardonnay.
You know, I'm freezing?
I'm definitely freezing.
I can't stop shaking.
I'm cold too.
At least you got a coat.
Let's get
in the car.
Oh, my god.
That's Saddam Hussein,
the dictator!
I told you!
HUSSEIN:
I wouldn't walk around without a coat in this weather.
You'll catch your death
of cold. So long.
[♪]
Can I get you
anything else?
Oh, no, thanks.
How about a nice box
of scram?
Somebody double-parked!
We couldn't help it!
It might've been Saddam Hussein.
We're not sure.
He had a British accent,
though.
What-- What
happened to you?
Somebody put a cane
on my foot...
just like the one
I'm gonna put up your--
Hey, what happened
to your coat?
And what's that smell?
What, are you drunk?
I had to give it
to the liquor store guy.
What for?
I spilled
some chardonnay.
So, what
did you get?
Cinnamon babka.
Cinnamon?
Why didn't you
get chocolate?
George...
What?
[SHIVERING]
[♪]
[KNOCKING]
Here.
Here's your cake.
And your wine.
See ya.
[♪]
I heard a weatherman say
that 75 percent
of your body heat
is actually lost
through the top of the head,
which sounds like you
could go skiing naked
if you got a good hat.
But there's no hat
that makes a statement
quite like the hat
with the flaps.
The hat with the flaps
makes a statement
that no other hat makes.
This hat says to the world,
"I would rather have
the heat in my skull
than anything society
could possibly offer me."
In fact, I would say
if you're on trial
for a serious crime
and your lawyer recommends
the insanity defense,
this is the hat to wear.
Your lawyer should insist.
He should just go:
"Your Honor,
the defense rests."