Aren't mannequins an insult
to your imagination?
"You couldn't possibly
visualize a sweater,
so we'll show you on this
life-size, snotty puppet."
I guess when
they're finished with them,
they become
crash-test dummies.
That's the end of the line
for a mannequin.
"Whatever happened to Bob?"
"Have you seen
that new Volvo commercial?
He's got a bull's-eye
right in his face."
Mannequins are only used
for car accidents and fashion.
I guess these are
the two situations
that it's impossible for us
to imagine ourselves:
well-dressed
or getting killed.
I'm sure some
pro-mannequin organization,
doesn't even like you
to use the term mannequin.
"Hey, they're not mannequins.
They're the life-deprived."
AUDREY:
Mmm, that was really good.
Yeah.
Are you full?
Oh, no.
I've had just enough.
Ah, here we go.
Apple pie.
Best apple pie
in the city.
Mmm.
Delicious.
I'm not waiting
for you.
Take some.
No, thanks.
You're not gonna
have any?
No.
Do you not like
apple pie?
No. It's not that.
Well,
at least taste it.
No.
You won't even
taste it?
No.
Come on,
try it.
A little taste.
Come on.
She wouldn't
so much as taste it.
She say why?
No. She wouldn't
say anything.
She just kept
shaking her head like this:
Maybe she's diabetic.
No. She carries
Entenmann's doughnuts
in her purse.
Maybe you said something
that offended her.
The only thing
I can think of
is I told her
we should have
those moving walkways
all over the city.
Like at the airport?
Yeah.
That's a great idea!
Tell me about it.
We'd could be zipping
all over the place.
They could
at least try it.
They never
try anything!
What's the harm?
No harm!
I'm sorry.
There's no reason
for her
not to taste that pie.
Who wouldn't
taste the pie?
Audrey.
Dump her.
Well, I never broke up
with anyone for not tasting pie.
I once broke up with someone
for not offering me pie.
You did?
He could be eating
a hero, Jerry.
He wouldn't
offer me anything.
It's a sickness.
Well, I can't
walk anywhere now.
I'm just gonna
be wishing
there were
walkways.
GEORGE:
What are you doin'?
I got a pebble.
Well, I never heard of that
happening to a woman.
What the hell
does that mean?
Hey.
Oh, hey, Elaine!
What?
Go like this:
What? Why?
Do it. Do it.
But--
Like this.
Like...
Like this?
Oh, yeah!
It's you!
What's me?
There's a clothing store
downtown.
They got a mannequin
in there
that looks
exactly like Elaine.
Get out!
No, it's uncanny!
It's like they chopped off
your arms and legs,
dipped you in plastic,
then screwed you
all back together again,
and stuck you
on a pedestal.
It's really
quite exquisite.
Kramer,
what's the name
of the store
with the mannequin?
Rinitze.
Oh, yeah.
Uh...
May I help you?
It's this itch.
I was watching TV
without my shirt on,
and one of my couch cushions
didn't have any fabric on it.
Wait a minute.
Rinitze.
Don't they have
some really
cool suits in there?
Real boss.
I'm going
down there.
Yeah, wait.
I'm gonna go with you.
I gotta get
a new suit.
I got a second interview
with MacKenzie,
and I think
I'm really close.
They're taking me
out to lunch on Friday.
Let's go. Let's go.
All right. All right.
You gonna need this?
Keep it.
It looks
exactly like me.
It's like some pod
landed from another planet
and took your body.
Don't fall asleep,
Elaine.
What's going
on here?
How do you think
this happened?
Whoa.
Look at this.
This is
a beautiful suit, huh?
You think this could be
a coincidence, George?
Is that possible?
[EUROPEAN ACCENT]
You are perfect for that suit.
You think so?
Um,
excuse me.
Where did this
come from?
I don't know.
You really think
this looks okay on me?
Fabulous.
Perfect fit.
And it's
the last one we have.
I'm--
I'm sorry.
You can't tell me
where the mannequin
came from?
I told you,
I don't know.
Well, um, is there
somebody around here
I could talk to
who would know?
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
This mannequin looks
exactly like me.
Did you just
roll your eyes at him?
Because let me
tell you something.
If anybody should be
rolling their eyes,
it is me, at him,
about you.
I think maybe
you're flattering yourself.
That mannequin is wearing
a $1200 Gaultier dress.
What--
What are you saying,
that I'm not good enough
for this hideous dress?
Listen, Natasha.
I wouldn't be
caught dead
wearing your crummy
little Eurotrash rags.
I'll meet you
outside.
What is
her problem?
Ah, psh,
what can you do?
Um...
Is this
the price tag?
Yes.
Yes, hello.
Party's over.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
We're having
an unadvertised sale
starting Friday.
That suit
will be half-price.
So do you think you could
put the suit aside and hold it for me?
Oh, I'm afraid
I couldn't do that.
It wouldn't be fair
to the other customers.
Oh, yes,
of course.
And, uh, we have
to be fair.
So, I found out
who supplies the mannequins,
and I called him up.
Well, how did they
get your face?
I don't know.
They wouldn't tell me.
Jerry?
Jer-- Hello?
Um...excuse me.
I couldn't help
but notice
you offered her
a piece of your pie.
That's right.
And you waved it away.
Right.
Did you give her
a reason?
Yes. I was full.
You were full.
So, you gave a reason.
You didn't just
shake your head.
No. I'm not
a psycho.
Exactly.
You're not a psycho.
You've been very helpful.
Thank you very much.
Allow me to leave the tip.
Well, I think we've proven
who the psycho is.
We certainly have.
Hey, Elaine,
scratch my back.
No way.
Come on.
One lap around.
No.
It'll be
a funky adventure.
Kramer, forget it.
Forget it.
Jerry,
how about you?
I think
you know my policy.
I'm going home
to spatula.
I thought George
was meeting us here.
No, he's going downtown
to guard the suit.
He's guarding a suit?
Do you need some help
with that itch?
Madam, I pray
you're not toying with me.
Whoa.
Turn around.
Oh, all right.
Oh!
It fits you
perfectly.
You think so?
What is this?
Can't I leave this place
for a second?
[EUROPEAN ACCENT]
Can I help you?
I'm buying
this suit.
No-no-no-no. This suit
is not for sale.
Excuse me.
Do you work here?
No.
Then what the hell
business is it of yours?
Look, I'm doing you
a favor.
They're having
an unadvertised sale.
This suit is gonna be
half-price starting Monday.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This Monday?
Yes, yes.
Now, take off
those pants.
Actually, the unadvertised sale
starts on Friday.
Friday?
Thanks.
You know, honey,
for an unadvertised sale,
you're doing a lot
of yapping about it.
JERRY:
I can't believe your father owns this place.
So how are
the desserts here?
Everything
is delicious.
You've tasted them?
Mmm-hm. I think
almost all of them.
Hmm.
Oh, I see
they have apple pie.
Mmm-hmm.
You've had
the apple pie?
Many times.
Audrey, I gotta be
honest with you.
I'm a very
curious guy.
It's my nature.
I need to know things.
Not tasting the apple pie
the other day,
I can't get past it.
You obviously like pies.
You carry doughnuts
in you bag.
You're not averse
to pastry.
Surely you could see
how such a thing
would prey on my mind.
Can we drop this?
Why can't I know?
Oh, Poppie.
Sweetheart,
hello.
Poppie,
this is Jerry.
POPPIE:
Welcome.
Hello, Poppie.
Ah! Don't fill up
on the bread.
I'm making you
a very special dinner.
Very special.
The pies.
I'm going
to the bathroom.
You know.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Aha-ha, Jerry!
Tonight you in
for a real treat.
I'm personally gonna
prepare the dinner
for you and my Audrey.
Jerry,
you okay?
Huh?
Is anything
wrong?
No. Nothing.
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
I'll see you
tomorrow.
Hey.
These are
for you, Olive.
Thank you.
Ohhh!
Yeah, yeah.
Here it is.
Oh, wait till
you taste this.
Mmm.
Poppie,
this is perfect.
Well?
Jerry, have some.
You're not gonna
taste it?
Jerry.
So she thought I did it
to get back at her.
Why didn't you
just tell her?
I don't think
it's the kind of thing
you wanna hear
about your father.
But I'll tell you,
when he came
out of that bathroom,
and he was kneading
that dough,
it was a wild scene.
How could he
not have washed?
Even if you're
not gonna soap up,
at least pretend
for my benefit.
Turn the water on.
Do something.
Yeah, just like I do.
You know, a chef
who doesn't wash
is like a cop
who steals.
It's a cry for help.
He wants to get caught.
Well, I think Poppie's
got some problems.
There's a whole other thing
going on with Poppie.
So how'd you leave it?
We haven't spoken.
Hey.
Hey, George.
Well, I'm not gonna
need this anymore.
I got Olive.
Olive?
Yeah, my lady friend down at Monk's.
You guys ought to
see the way
she works her nails
across my back.
Ooh!
She's a maestro!
The crisscross,
the figure eight,
strummin'
the ol' banjo,
and this wild,
savage free-for-all
where anything
can happen.
Is that the time?
I gotta get downtown
and buy that suit.
The store opens
in 20 minutes.
Hey, is that Elaine
mannequin still there?
Yeah.
Yeah?
The last time
I saw her,
she was naked.
Yeah. And Poppie's
got problems.
Where is it?
where is it?
Well, look at this.
This doesn't
belong here.
Someone has made
a terrible mistake.
You bastard!
You hid the suit.
Hid?
I have no idea how this suit
got misplaced.
Nevertheless, I do believe
I shall purchase it.
I hope you rot
in that suit.
Look, I'm gonna
get you for this.
I don't know how,
but I am gonna get you.
You are gonna pay!
Oh, I'll pay.
Half-price.
Arrivederci,
my fellow 40-short.
ELAINE:
So, I made a little list
of people who might've
made the mannequin.
You know,
possible suspects.
Yeah, all right.
Go ahead.
Okay.
All right, well,
there's this blind guy
at a party I was at,
and he felt my face
for a really long time,
you know, to see
what I look like.
He almost put his finger
up my nose.
Okay, what else
you got?
Okay, I'm not
gonna tell you
the rest of the list.
Oh, because
I didn't think
the blind guy
did it?
Because you have
an attitude.
Oh!
Ooh!
Georgio!
Nice duds.
Huh?
You're telling me.
[PANTS SWOOSH]
[SWOOSHING]
So, what do you think?
Did you
hear something?
Yeah, like a swoosh.
Yeah.
It must be
the fabric.
It's-- It's rubbing
between your thighs
when you walk.
That's what's making
that swooshy sound.
[SWOOSHES]
I probably didn't hear it
on the way over
because of
the street noise.
[SWOOSHES]
This is no good!
I gotta meet these guys
from MacKenzie
for lunch
in half an hour!
So what?
What would they care?
This MacKenzie guy,
he's a bit of a nut.
Someone told me
he fired the last guy
because his nose whistled
when he breathed.
So you think you're not
gonna get the job
because your pants
make a noise?
Let's say it's comes down
to me and one other guy.
He's got a nice,
quiet suit,
and I'm whooshing
all over the place!
Who do you think
he's gonna hire?
You know, I think
all these interviews
are making you nuts.
Hey, Jerry, I saw
your girlfriend
was in here before.
Audrey?
Yup.
Sat down,
had herself a piece of pie.
What...
Was it apple?
What else?
This woman is bending my mind
into a pretzel!
Do I know you?
Hmm...
No, you don't.
Yeah!
You were wearing
a G-string
and one of those bras
with points.
The mannequin!
Oh, I gotta
see this thing.
[GASPS]
Boy, the resemblance
is uncanny.
You think you can pose me
however you want?
That's my ass
in your window!
It's our store
and our mannequin.
We can do whatever
we want with it.
No, you take that mannequin
down right now, or...
Or I am
pressing charges.
Yes.
This is my attorney.
Oh, yeah? What law
am I breaking?
Uh, well,
I believe there is
some legal
precedent, uh,
Winchell v. Mahoney.
Uh-huh.
Uh, the Charlie McCarthy
hearings.
Uh-huh.
Are you
taking this down?
I'm getting
the manager.
Jerry, get the car.
What are
you doing?
Just get
the car!
Elaine, as your
legal counsel,
I must advise
against this.
I don't know
about you,
but I'm getting
a hankering
for some
Doublemint gum.
All right,
I'm dropping you off
at work, right?
Where you goin'?
Poppie's.
Thanks for meeting me
down here, George.
My office
is out of control,
phones ringing,
people running
in and out--
Did you
hear something?
No, I didn't
hear anything.
Huh.
That's strange.
It's quieter
down here.
We can concentrate
without people
whooshing around.
That sound again.
You sure you didn't
hear anything?
No, can't say
as I did.
Kind of like
a...rustling.
Could be the leaves.
AUDREY:
That's right.
Poppie's on 77th.
Okay. We'll see you
at 8. Bye-bye.
Hello.
What are you
doing here?
So how was the pie?
What pie?
The apple pie
you had today at Monk's.
I'm very busy here.
Pretty good,
wasn't it?
I told you
you should've tasted it.
You better not let Poppie
see you here.
All right, I'm looking
for someone named Poppie.
Uh, who are you?
Board of Health. We've had
several complaints.
Oh, about the,
uh...
You Poppie?
Eh,
I'm Poppie.
Think you better
come with me.
What's
the problem?
What do they want
from Poppie?
Well, Poppie's
a little sloppy.
[LAUGHING]
You thought
I'd care
about your pants
whooshing?
Well,
you know.
I heard the last guy
got fired
because his nose
whistled.
No, no, no.
He got fired because
he wasn't a team player.
That's something we
don't joke about at MacKenzie.
You'll find we're
a team here, George.
We don't tolerate
dissent.
You wanna go your own way,
you're in the wrong place.
Oh, no problem there.
Conformity's
an obsession with me.
Chocolate
cream pie,
compliments
of the house.
Whoa! Hope you saved
room for dessert.
The chef said
that he made it
special for you.
Oh.
Mmm. Best pie
I've ever tasted.
Take a bite,
George.
Take a bite.
It's delicious.
I insist.
If you're one of us,
you'll take a bite.
So, you didn't
get the job.
No.
But I was the only one
at the table
that didn't get
violently ill.
Kramer, you can't keep
avoiding her like this.
You're gonna have
to say something.
What am I supposed
to say?
Tell her
you lost your itch.
What happened
to your itch?
I lost it two days ago.
I've been faking it
so I wouldn't
hurt her feelings.
Well, you should
tell her.
I'll let her down easy.
All right.
Well...
Hi, Olive.
No, no, no.
No more of that.
There's something
I have to tell you.
What?
Uh, well,
there's someone else.
Someone else?
Yeah, yeah.
Who is she?
Her.
Her?
Yeah. There she is.
That's my gal.
You're a liar.
I've seen her
in here before.
She's not
your girlfriend.
All right, now, Olive,
look, I'm sorry.
Well, why is she wearing
her underwear?
Uh, well,
it's a style, yeah.
Jerry, give me
the keys.
Yo.
Okay. Well, I guess
we're gonna
go for a drive now.
She, uh,
really loves that.
[♪]
Did you ever solve
the riddle of the pie?
No. That's one
for the ages.
But I think they're gonna be
putting Poppie away
for a long, long time.
You guys, you're not gonna
believe this.
I just got a letter
from a friend of mine
in Chicago
who was shopping,
and she said
she saw a mannequin
that looked just like me.
What if there are more?
Where are they
coming from?
Ricky, we've been getting
a tremendous response
to your TR-6 mannequin.
TR-6?
I prefer
to think of her as...
Elaine.