There's no way that
moving in with your parents,
is a sign that your life
is right on track.
There's no way that
you could fake this, even.
"Yeah, things are going great.
I met a terrific girl,
"I got a great job,
making a lot of money,
"and if everything
goes according to plan,
I'm going to be moving back
in with my parents soon."
It's like getting busted
on a parole violation,
and thrown back
into the slammer.
"In the opinion of the board,
you'd need further
rehabilitation, I'm afraid."
And you go back
into that little room of yours,
you feel so huge,
it's like you can take your bed
and just crush it in your hands.
You can hold your parents
between your fingers going,
"why was I so afraid of you
people when I was growing up?"
[♪]
GEORGE:
I can't believe this.
Oh, it won't be for that long.
How could I do this?
How can I move back in
with those people?
Please, tell me.
They're insane!
You know that.
Hey, my parents are just
as crazy as your parents.
How can you compare your parents
to my parents?
My father has never thrown
anything out, ever.
My father wears his sneakers
in the pool.
Sneakers!
My mother has never set foot
in a natural body of water.
Listen carefully.
My mother has
never laughed.
Ever.
Not a giggle,
not a chuckle,
not a tee-hee,
never went "ha!"
A smirk?
Maybe.
And I'm moving back
in there.
I told you I'd lend you
the money for the rent.
No, no, borrowing money
from a friend,
is like having sex.
It just completely changes
the relationship.
All right. I'm ready.
You know,
I still don't understand,
why do you want to move back in
with your parents?
I don't want to.
I'm out of money.
I got $714 in the bank.
Well, move in here.
What's that?
Why doesn't he just move
in here?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna move in with him,
He doesn't even let you
use the toilet.
You can move in with me
if you want.
Thank you.
I, uh--
That might not
work out.
Careful! Careful
with the suitcases.
We just painted.
Hello, Mrs. Costanza.
Hello, Kramer.
Close the door.
I gotta bring in
some more stuff.
More stuff?
How much is there?
There's more.
So, how are you, Jerry?
Fine Mrs. Costanza.
Hey, I got a terrific joke
for you.
Nah. Not interested.
No, no. It's really funny.
There's these two guys--
Tell it to the audience.
Here, I made
some bologna sandwiches.
Bologna? Nobody eats
bologna anymore.
What are you
talking about?
Have a sandwich.
No, thanks.
Oh, stop it.
You don't want one,
Kramer?
Uh, no, thanks.
I think you're all
a little touched in the head.
You're so worried
about your health?
You're young men.
I really don't eat it.
What am I going to do
with all these sandwiches?
Will you take them home,
give them to someone
in your building?
I don't know
if I feel comfortable,
handing out bologna sandwiches
in the building.
All right. That's it.
Anything else?
No. That's it.
[HORN HONKS]
I gotta go move the car.
Well, I guess we'll be going.
What? You going?
Yeah.
Well, what are you doing later?
Elaine and I are going out with
Kramer and his new girlfriend.
Really?
Yeah.
You can't believe this woman.
She's a low-talker,
you can't hear
what she's saying.
You're always going,
"excuse me, what?"
Maybe I'll meet you.
No, George.
We're going out to eat tonight,
with your father.
Oh.
Okay.
I'll talk to you later.
Yeah. Take it easy.
Oh, my God.
Okay, well, I had this idea
for a pizza place,
where you make
your own pie.
Right.
You remember that?
Yeah, well,
that was a good one.
[MURMURING]
What's that?
Excuse me?
[MURMURING]
Yeah.
You know that Leslie's
in the clothing business?
She's a designer.
In fact, she's come up
with a new one,
that's gonna be the big
new look in men's fashions.
It's, uh, like a puffy shirt.
[MURMURING]
Yeah, it's all puffy,
like the pirates used to wear.
Oh, a puffy shirt.
Puffy.
See, I think people
wanna look like pirates.
You know,
It's the right time for it,
be all puffy
and devil-may-care.
[MURMURING]
That's true.
I'll be right back.
Jerry's going to be on
the Today Show on Friday.
Yeah, that's right.
He's promoting
a benefit for Goodwill,
you know, they clothe the poor
and the homeless.
And the indigent.
Yeah. I do volunteer work
for them.
I set the whole thing up,
and I got Jerry to do it.
[MURMURING]
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yup.
[MURMURING]
Uh-huh.
Yup.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe you should take
a civil-service test.
I'm not taking
Look at this,
George.
You ever seen
a silver dollar?
Yes, I've seen
a silver dollar.
Why don't you want to take
a civil-service test?
To do what,
work in the post office?
Is that what you want me to do?
Would you believe,
when I was 18,
I had a silver dollar
collection?
I don't understand.
You get job security,
You get a paycheck
every week.
I'm a college graduate.
You want me to be a mailman?
You know, I couldn't bring
myself to spend one of these.
I got some kind of, uhh,
phobia.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I do know that I have
some kind of a talent,
something to offer.
I just don't know
what it is yet.
I bet that collection
would be worth
a lot of money today.
Oh, my God.
I don't like this waiter.
Look at him.
He sees us.
Doesn't wanna come over.
I need some air.
George,
where you going?
I got a lot
thinking to do.
Oh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
Look what you've done.
You've spilled my bag.
Here,
let me help you.
No, no. It's all right.
It's just that I'm here
with my parents,
and my mother wants me to take
a civil-service test.
To tell you the truth,
I don't even think I'd pass it.
Hmm.
What?
Your hands.
What about them?
They're quite exquisite.
They are?
Extraordinary.
Have you ever done
any hand modeling?
Hand modeling?
Here's my card.
Why don't you, uh,
give me a call?
I don't get it.
Me neither.
What is it?
I don't know.
They're hands.
This woman already signed me
up for a job.
Well, what about my hands?
I don't see how your hands are
any better than my hands.
What, are you kidding?
Knuckles are all
out of proportion,
you got hair over there--
Where do you get off comparing
your hands to my hands?
This is a one
in a million hand.
That's what comes from avoiding
manual labor your whole life.
This is it.
It's happened to me, Jerry.
I was sitting
in the restaurant,
the two nut-jobs
were talking,
I couldn't
take it anymore.
I get up from the table and
"bop," I bop into this woman.
It's just like in the movies.
Hey.
Hey, George.
[BUZZING]
Ow!
Aah!
Are you crazy?
What?
You could've
damaged my hands!
But it's just a toy!
George has become
a hand model.
A hand model?
Yes.
Really? Let me see
your hands.
You can look at them,
but do not touch them.
Let's see.
Oh, those are nice.
You know, I never
noticed this before.
They're smooth,
creamy,
delicate, yet masculine.
All right.
I gotta get going.
Oven mitts?
It's all I could find.
Would you mind getting the door?
Thank you very much.
You're not gonna believe
what's happening with Leslie.
You know, since you agreed
to wear the puffy shirt,
on the Today Show,
she's getting
all these orders,
from boutiques
and department stores.
Uh-huh.
Since I what?
Agreed to wear
the puffy shirt.
What are you
talking about?
When you said
that you would agree
to wear the puffy shirt
on the Today Show.
This?
I agreed to wear this?
Yeah, yeah.
When did I do that?
When we went to dinner
the other night.
What, are you crazy?
What were you
talking about,
when I went
to the bathroom?
I don't know.
I couldn't understand
a word she was saying,
I was just nodding.
There you go.
Where I go?
You mean, she was asking me
to wear this ridiculous shirt
on national TV,
and I said yes?
Yes, yes,
you said it.
But I didn't know
what she was talking about,
I couldn't hear her.
Well, she asked you.
I can't wear this
puffy shirt on TV.
I mean, look at it.
It looks ridiculous.
Well,
you gotta wear it now.
All those stores
are stocking it,
based on the condition
that you're gonna wear this
on the TV show.
The factory in New Jersey
is already making them.
They're making these?
Yes, yes.
This pirate trend that
she's come up with, Jerry,
this is gonna be the new look
for the 90's.
You're gonna be
the first pirate.
But I don't want
to be a pirate!
[♪]
MRS. COSTANZA:
I knew it.
I always knew you had
beautiful hands.
I used to tell people.
Frank, didn't I used to
talk about his hands?
Who the hell did you ever
mention his hands to?
I mentioned his hands
to plenty of people.
You never mentioned
them to me!
Hand me an emery board.
I always talk
about your hands,
how they're so soft
and milky white.
No, you never said
milky white.
I said milky white!
Scissor.
Don't hand them to me
with the point facing out!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
I'll try to be
more careful.
I hope so.
Georgie--
Oh.
Georgie, would you
like some JELL-O?
Why did you put
the bananas in there?
George likes
the bananas!
So let him
have bananas on the side!
All right, please!
Please, I cannot have
this constant bickering.
Stress is very damaging
to the epidermis.
Now, I have an important
photo session in the morning.
My hands have got to be
in tip-top shape.
So please,
keep the television down,
and the conversation
to a minimum.
But, Georgie,
what about the JELL-O?
I'll take it in my room.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Yeah, come in.
Just wanted to let you know,
he's got about five minutes.
Yep, yep.
Jerry! Five minutes!
Now that's
a great-looking shirt.
Aye, captain!
Yeah.
I'm glad I ironed it.
It's perfect.
Look at it.
It's fantastic.
Kramer, how am I
gonna wear this?
I can't wear this.
Hey, this looks better
than anything you own.
You know,
in two months time,
everybody's gonna be wearing
the pirate look.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi Kramer, guess what.
I just saw Bryant Gumbel.
He said he might help out
at the benefit.
Great.
What is that?
It's the puffy shirt.
Look at it.
What do you think?
Is it cool or what?
Why are you wearing this now?
Why am I wearing it now?
I'll tell you why
I'm wearing it now.
Because the low-talker asked
me to, that's why.
And I said yes.
Do you know why?
Because I couldn't hear her.
When did she--?
When did she ask you this?
When we were at dinner,
and Kramer went
to the bathroom.
I didn't hear anything--
Of course not.
Nobody hears anything
when this woman speaks!
Well, you can't wear that
on the show.
Elaine, you want to stuff it?
Wha--?
What? No.
Jerry, you are promoting
a benefit,
to clothe homeless-people.
You can't come out
dressed like that.
You're all puffed up.
You look like
the Count of Monte Cristo.
I have to wear it,
The woman has orders
for this shirt,
based on me
wearing it on TV!
They're producing them
as we speak.
Yeah, but you're supposed to be
a compassionate person,
that cares
about poor people.
You look like you're gonna
swing in on a chandelier.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Okay. Let's go.
Is that what
you're wearing?
I've never seen hands
like these before.
You're so soft
and milky white.
You know whose hands
they remind me of?
Ray McKigney.
Oh! Ray.
He was it.
Who was he?
The most exquisite hands
you've ever seen.
Oh, he had it all.
What happened
to him?
Tragic story,
I'm afraid.
He could've had
any woman in the world,
but none could match
the beauty of his own hand.
And that became
his one true love.
You mean, uh--?
Yes.
He was not
master of his domain.
But how--?
The muscles became
so strained with overuse,
that eventually the hand locked
into a deformed position,
and he was left with nothing
but a claw.
He traveled the world
seeking a cure:
acupuncturists,
herbalists,
swamis.
Nothing helped.
Towards the end,
his hands became so frozen,
he was unable
to manipulate utensils,
and was dependent
on cub scouts to feed him.
I hadn't seen
another pair of hands,
like Ray McKigney's,
until today.
You are his successor.
I, uh, only hope you have
a little more self-control.
You don't have to worry
about me.
I won a contest.
Okay,
let's get to work.
On Tuesday the 19th
here in New York,
there'll be a benefit
for the Goodwill Industries,
a used clothing organization,
that provides services
to the needy.
One of the performers will be
comedian Jerry Seinfeld.
Jerry, good morning.
Thank you, Brian.
And speaking of clothing,
that is a very, very
unusual shirt you have on.
Uh-huh, yeah.
You're all kind of puffed up.
Yes, it's a puffy shirt.
You look like a pirate.
Like a pirate.
Anyway, uh, you know,
we're hoping to raise
enough money--
You know, you know--
Look, I'm sorry,
it is just a very unusual shirt.
It could become
a whole new look for you.
You know, you could put
a patch over an eye,
You could kinda be
the pirate comedian--
Uh-huh, yeah.
You gonna be wearing
the puffy shirt at the--?
Look, it's not my shirt.
Whose shirt is--?
What's the difference?
I agreed to wear it.
It's a puffy shirt,
I feel ridiculous in it.
And I think it's the stupidest
shirt I've ever seen,
to be perfectly honest with you.
LESLIE:
You bastard!
Did you hear that?
That I heard.
All right.
A little to the left.
Little higher.
Good, Perfect.
Like that?
Just like that. Hold it.
Okay, let me get one more.
Good. That's it.
You're done.
That's it?
That's it.
And here's your check.
Thank you very much.
It was an honor.
Thank you.
It was great
working with you.
Your hands
are beautiful.
Oh.
Thank you very much.
You know, I was wondering,
if you're not doing
anything later,
maybe you'd
like to get together.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
You ruined me,
you ruined my career!
Just keep your voice down.
Everyone can hear you.
I don't give a damn!
You know, if you talked
this loud to begin with,
I wouldn't be in this costume
in the first place.
Hey, hey, you can't
believe this.
Look at this check.
They told me I had
the most beautiful hands
they've ever seen in their life,
except for this McKigney guy.
This great-looking girl
gave me her phone number.
I got it all!
I'm busting, Jerry. I'm busting!
Hey, I've never noticed
your hands before, let me see.
All right.
Yeah. Real nice.
Nice shirt.
Wh-what is this?
Is this what you wore
on the show?
Yeah.
Have you completely
lost your mind?
Who's dressing you?
You look like
a complete idiot.
I wouldn't wipe my--
Aah!
[GEORGE SCREAMING]
You ready?
Yeah.
Hot, hot!
Hot!
ELAINE:
I'm sorry.
This McKigney guy had
a few good years.
How could you forget
to turn off an iron?
I was excited because Jerry
was putting on the puffy shirt.
My whole life is ruined
because of the puffy shirt.
It didn't do
me any good either.
That benefit was the worst show
I ever did.
Some of those heckles
were really uncalled-for.
"Avast ye, matey"?
What the hell
does that mean?
"Twenty degrees over
the starboard side,
it's a Spanish galleon."
There's no comeback
for that.
Well, it got me fired
from the benefit committee.
You know, all those stores
canceled out on her.
She's finished.
We're finished.
Really?
What happened?
I just can't be with someone,
whose life is in
complete disarray.
What happened to
all the shirts?
They gave them
to Goodwill.
GEORGE:
Puffy shirt, puffy shirt!
Can you spare a little change,
for an old buccaneer?
You know, it's really not
a bad-looking shirt.
[♪]
Why do we always
have to say "excuse me,"
when we can't hear
what someone is saying?
Why are we so guilty?
"Excuse me. Pardon me.
I'm sorry."
Why can't just once, I go,
"Nope. Not loud enough"?
Why can't I do that?
[♪]
Just once I would like to have
the guts,
you know, to make that judgment.
Someone mumbles something
and you go,
"Your fault."
"I'm not sorry
because it's your fault."