Professional tennis. I don't
understand all the shushing.
Why're they always shushing?
"Shh! Shh!"
Don't the players know
that we're there?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Should we duck down
behind the seat
so they don't see us
watching them?
To me tennis is basically
just Ping-Pong,
and the players are standin'
on the table.
That's all it is.
And that goofy scoring.
You win one point,
all of a sudden you're up by 15.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Two points, 30-love.
Thirty-love.
Sounds like
an English call girl.
[ENGLISH ACCENT]
"That'll be 30, love.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"And could you be a little
quieter next time, please?
Shh!"
JERRY:
Are these seats unbelievable, or what?
GEORGE:
Yeah.
Hey, where's the sunblock?
Here.
Twenty-five? You don't
have anything higher?
What, are you on Mercury?
I need higher.
This has PABA in it.
I need PABA-free.
You got a problem
with PABA?
Yes, I have a problem
with PABA.
You don't even know
what PABA is.
I know enough
to stay away from it.
ANNOUNCER:
Thirty-love.
Going to Todd's party
this weekend?
I'll go if somebody
else drives. You?
Gwen really wants to go.
You're bringin' a date
to a party?
No good?
A party's
a bad date situation.
It doesn't matter
who you're with.
You could be with
J. Edgar Hoover.
You don't wanna sit
with him all night.
You wanna circulate!
[SNAPPING]
Ah-ah-oh!
Why'd you pick Hoover?
Was he that interesting
to talk to?
Well, I would think,
with the law enforcement
and the cross-dressing,
seems like
an interesting guy.
Yeah, I guess.
What can I do?
I gotta take her with me.
Todd introduced us.
I'm obligated.
That woman is
absolutely stunning.
Who, the Croat?
No, not the Croat.
The lineswoman.
That is the most beautiful
lineswoman I've ever seen.
Yeah, she's a BL.
BL?
LINESMAN:
Out!
Beautiful lineswoman.
All right, listen. I'm gonna
go to the concession stand
and get some real sunblock.
You want anything?
Jerry?
You know, I just heard
the Lexington line is out.
Oh!
You are kidding me.
How am I supposed to get
to this meeting?
Take a car service.
We have an account.
No, forget it.
I hate those.
Every time I've taken one,
the driver will not stop
talking to me.
No matter how disinterested
I seem,
he just keeps yakkin' away.
"Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah."
Why does everything always
have a social component?
You know, see, the stagecoach.
That would've been
a good situation for me
'cause I'm in the coach
and the driver's
way up there on the stage.
Well, you're not gonna
get a cab now.
Four-thirty on
a Friday afternoon?
Bring a magazine,
keep your head down.
Yeah, I guess
that could work.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
[PEOPLE CHATTING]
ANNOUNCER:
And that is it. Match to Miss Natalia Baudone.
[EXCITING THEME PLAYING]
ANNOUNCER 2:
Coming up next, men's singles.
But for now, let's stop
a minute and take a look
at our beautiful
tennis-center backdrop.
A beautiful but very hot day
Hey!
here in Flushing Meadows.
There's George!
Holy cow,
it's a scorcher.
Boy, I bet you that guy
could cover a lot of court.
Hey, buddy,
they got a new invention.
It's called a napkin.
[ANNOUNCER 2 LAUGHS]
We'll take a station break
and continue with more action.
Hee, hee, hee, hee!
Dag Hammarskjold Plaza, huh?
Pendant, uh, Publishing.
That's books, right?
Miss?
Pardon me?
Books,
that's what you do?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't
read much, myself.
Well, you know,
besides the paper.
Yeah, a lot of people
read to relax.
Not me.
You know what I do?
You know, I'm-- I'm havin'
a lot of trouble, um,
hearing you back here,
so...
[LOUDLY]
I said, "You know what I do when I wanna relax?"
The jumble.
Hey, do you make
a book of jumbles?
I'm gonna have to be
honest with you.
I'm going deaf.
Going deaf?
What?
Oh, I... I-I'm sorry.
It can be
very frustrating.
Hey, what about a hearing aid?
Am I fearing AIDS?
Oh, yeah, sure! Who isn't?
But, you know,
you gotta live your life.
Eh, no. No, no, no.
I-- I said that...
Eh, uh...
[LOUDLY]
Forget it.
I can't take my eyes
off this lineswoman.
The woman is
absolutely mesmerizing.
Boy, you are
really smitten.
I-- I gotta talk to her.
What do you think?
Cold? How you gonna do that?
You're not one of those guys.
I'm gonna psych myself
into it
like those people that just
walk across the hot coals.
But they're not
mocked and humiliated
when they get
to the other side.
I have to, I won't be able
to live with myself.
Wait a minute, Jerry.
There's a bigger issue here.
If you go through that wall
and become one of those guys,
I'll be left here on this side.
Take me with you.
I can't.
What're you gonna say?
I don't know. "Hi"?
[LAUGHING]
You think you're going to the other side with "hi"?
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
You're not gonna make it.
DISPATCH:
Base to 92. Come in.
Yeah, this is 92.
Yeah, after this, go back
to the city for a 6:00 pickup.
Rightio.
749 Bleeker.
The party's Hanks, Tom Hanks.
Tom Hanks!
After me you're
pickin' up Tom Hanks?
I love him!
So I guess your hearing
goes in and out, huh?
Yeah, it-- Yes, it d--
Yeah. Yeah,
you know what I think?
I think you made
that whole thing up.
No, no. No, no, I--
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know your type.
You're too good
to make conversation
with someone like me.
Oh, God forbid, you could
discuss the jumbles!
But to go so far as to
pretend you're almost deaf?
I mean, that is
truly disgusting, miss.
And Mr. Tom Hanks...
may I say, he too would be
disgusted by your behavior.
Excuse me.
Oh, that's nice.
That's right, ignore me.
That's real polite.
Yeah, nobody's even
talkin' to you.
Oh, you're
a big lineswoman.
Oh, like that's
some kind of a cool job.
I know your type. Think you're
too good for everyone.
But, you know,
it's women like you--
Oh, well!
What, are you deaf?
Bingo!
And you're saying
she's deaf?
I'm not sayin' she's deaf.
She's deaf.
Can't hear a thing.
And you're gonna
go out with her.
Yeah. Isn't
that something?
Hey.
Hi.
Yeah, you know,
I know how to sign. Really?
Yeah, when I was 8,
I had a deaf cousin
who lived with us for a year.
'Course, you know, I haven't
been able to do it in a while.
What is this about?
I met this deaf lineswoman
at the tennis match.
You are kidding.
That is amazing!
I just took a car service
from work.
And to get the driver
not to talk to me,
I pretended
I was goin' deaf.
Wow, good plan.
Ah, it didn't work.
He caught me hearing.
Oh.
All right, it's terrible,
but I'm not
a terrible person.
No. No.
No!
When I shoo squirrels away,
I always say, "Get out of here."
I never, ever
throw things at 'em,
and try to injure 'em
like other people.
That's nice.
Yeah!
And when I see freaks
in the street,
I never, ever stare at 'em.
And yet I'm careful
not to look away.
See? 'Cause I wanna make
the freaks feel comfortable.
That's nice
for the freaks.
Yeah. And I don't
poof up my hair
when I go to the movies
so people behind me can see.
Oh, God, I gotta make it up
to this guy.
I'm not gonna be able
to live with myself.
What can I do?
Why don't you get
him some tickets?
How 'bout your friend that
works at that ticket agency.
Yeah, Pete. He can get you
great tickets to something.
Really?
Like a rock concert.
Whatever you like.
Oh, great. Thanks, Kramer.
Yeah. Yeah. You got it.
Hey, Jerry,
do me a favor.
The next time you see
that lineswoman,
ask her how those ball boys
get those jobs.
I would love to be able
to do that.
Kramer, I think perhaps
you've overlooked
one of the key aspects
of this activity.
It's "ball boys,"
not "ball men."
There are no ball men.
Yeah, I think he's right.
I've never seen a ball man.
Well, there ought to
be ball men.
All right,
I'll talk to her.
You wanna be a ball man?
Go ahead, break
the ball barrier.
Yeah.
Hey!
Mmm. Hey, you know what?
A friend of mine from work
said that she saw George
at the tennis match
on TV yesterday.
Yeah! Yeah, me too!
He was at the snack bar
eating a hot-fudge sundae.
He had it
all over his face!
He's wearin' that chocolate
on his face like a beard.
And they got in there
really nice and tight,
and he's,
"Mmm. Mmmm!"
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I'm sorry, George.
But...
I-I don't understand.
Things were going so great.
Wha...?
What happened?
Something must've happened.
It's not you. It's me.
You're giving me
the "it's not you,
it's me" routine?
I invented
"it's not you, it's me."
Nobody tells me
it's them, not me.
If it's anybody,
it's me.
All right.
George, it's you.
You're damn right
it's me!
Look, I was just
trying to--
I know what you
were trying to do.
Nobody does it
better than me.
I'm sure you do it
very well.
[CHUCKLES]
Yes, well, unfortunately,
you'll never get the chance
to find out.
JERRY:
But I thought things were going great.
Yeah, so did I.
Did she say why?
No.
She tried to give me
the "it's not you,
it's me" routine.
But that's your routine.
Yeah!
Well...apparently
word's out.
Hey.
Hey! Georgie.
I saw you on TV yesterday.
Really? At the tennis match?
You were at the snack bar,
eatin' a hot-fudge sundae.
Ha, ha! Get outta here!
I didn't see any cameras there.
Oh, the camera was,
whoom, there.
And the announcers, they made
a couple of cracks about ya.
Cracks?
What were they saying?
That you had ice cream
all over your face.
They were talking about
how funny you looked.
Oh, my God.
Maybe Gwen saw it.
Maybe that's what did it.
Well, I tell ya,
it wasn't a pretty sight.
She must've seen me
eating it on TV!
So she sees you with hot fudge
on your face, and she ends it?
Do you really think
she's that superficial?
Why not? I would be.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Dad.
You saw him?
Really? With the ice cream?
All right,
I'll talk to you later.
GEORGE: What--?
Bye.
What, your parents saw me on TV?
Yeah.
This is a nightmare!
Kramer, how long was I on?
It felt like...
eight seconds.
One 1000, two 1000,
three 1000--
I heard you really
inhaled that thing.
Did anyone tape it?
Can we move on?
What?
He thinks Gwen
broke up with him
because she saw him
eatin' the ice cream on TV.
Ohhh, come on.
If she's that superficial,
you don't want her.
Yes, I do.
So I guess you're not going
to Todd's party on Friday.
Well, I can't now.
Gwen's gonna be there!
Well, she should be the one
that shouldn't go.
Well, if a couple breaks up
and they had plans to go
to a neutral place,
who withdraws?
What's the etiquette?
Excellent
question.
I mean, I think
she should withdraw.
She's the breaker,
he's the breakee.
He needs to get on
with his life.
I beg to differ.
Really?
He's the loser.
Ahhh.
She's the victor.
Ah-ha.
To the victor belong the spoils.
Mmm.
Well, I don't care.
I don't wanna go anyway.
I don't wanna fight
that traffic on Friday night.
Well, we can take
the car service from my office.
Really?
Yeah. They don't know.
All right, I'll see ya later.
Okay.
Hey, Georgie.
Yeah.
[MOCKINGLY]
"To the victor go the spoils."
What're you gonna do tonight?
I got a date with
Laura the lineswoman.
Oh.
Why?
[MUMBLES]
What're you doin'?
Oh, I was just gonna
wander the streets.
I don't wanna...
tag along with you
or anything.
Oh. Um...
You wanted to
come with us?
Psh. Jerry, please.
It's very nice, but, uh...
where would we be going?
So I've got ice cream
all over my face.
There were
no napkins there.
Whoever is responsible for
stocking that concession stand
cost me a relationship.
They never have napkins there.
Let's get the check.
Is this, uh,
considered signing?
Do you do this when you
ask for the check? Really?
I know a sign!
That's my first sign!
Uh-oh.
That couple is breaking up.
They're breaking up?
How do you know?
She reads lips.
What are they saying now?
"It's not you,
it's me."
Oh, my God.
I-- I just had
a great idea.
She could come
to the party tomorrow
and read Gwen's lips
for me.
What?
We bring her
to the party,
and she tells me
what Gwen is saying about me.
She's not a novelty act,
George,
where you hire her out
for weddings and bar mitzvahs.
Look, it's a skill,
just like juggling.
She probably enjoys
showing it off.
I don't know,
George.
I'm not sure
about this.
Would you ask her?
Just ask her.
If she says no,
case closed.
All right.
Uh, Laura...
George
was wondering--
Sure. I'll do it.
JERRY:
So I really had a good time.
Yeah, me too.
So you wanna go
to the party on Friday night?
Yeah.
All right. We're taking
a car service.
Okay.
So we'll swing by and pick you up.
How about 6?
Six is good.
You got a problem with 6?
What?
[DOOR SLAMS]
What?!
Okay, listen up, people.
There are plenty of you here,
but we've only got
two spots to fill.
So good luck.
Hey, pops...
isn't there a better way
to spend your twilight years?
Well, I may be old...
but I'm spry.
[CHUCKLES]
The tryout lasts
three and a half to four hours.
Are you up for it?
Oh, I'll be up for it, punk.
Yee-ee!
See, I was sayin' "six,"
but she thought
I was sayin' "sex."
We straightened
the whole thing out, though.
She confused "six" with "sex"?
Yeah.
Well, if she can't
tell "six" from "sex,"
how's she gonna lip read
from across the room?
Well, "six" and "sex"
are close.
It's two completely
different sounds.
"Ih" and "eh."
Ah.
It seems like a problem.
Well, I'm not dating
any other deaf women.
Hey.
Guess who's gonna be
the new ball man for the finals?
You're kidding!
Ah! Yeah.
Yeah, they said
they never saw
anybody go after balls
with such gusto.
Ooh, when is that
car service coming?
In five minutes.
Gonna pick us up.
Then we pick up Elaine.
Laura's gonna meet us there.
If this lip-reading thing
works tonight,
do you know how incredible
this is gonna be?
It's like having Superman
for your friend.
I know.
It's like x-ray vision.
If we could just
harness this power
and use it for
our own personal gain,
there'd be
no stopping us.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
I hear you got some lip reader
working for you.
Let me use her for one day!
Just one day!
Can't do it, Newman!
B-but, Jerry, we got--
We got this new supervisor down
at the post office.
He's workin'
behind this glass.
I know
they're talkin' about me.
They're gonna transfer me.
I know it!
Two hours. Gimme two hours.
It's not gonna happen!
[HUFFING]
[SNARLS]
All right.
All right,
you go ahead!
You go ahead,
you keep it secret.
But you remember this:
When you control the mail,
you control...
information.
Ha!
Uh, just pull over
right by that stop sign.
[LOUDLY]
Pardon me, sir?
I said, pull over
by the stop sign.
Oh, sorry.
You'll have to forgive me.
I can't hear a damn thing.
Went to a rock concert
last night at the Garden.
My seats were right up
against the speaker.
It's a heavy metal group...
Metalli-something.
Ca.
Huh?
What?
Ca.
Ah.
My ears are still ringin'.
Some woman's idea of a joke.
Ha, ha.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Hi.
Get out. Get out!
GEORGE: We'll never get there.
Go on!
KRAMER: Okay.
Hey!
Huh?
Shut the door.
Yeah, sure.
[TIRES SCREECH]
You know, the whole idea
of the car service
was so I wouldn't have to fight
the traffic on Friday night.
I know, I'm late.
But hey, now I know
two signs:
"check" and "late."
Hey, this is my friend
you helped become the first ball man.
Ah.
Congratulations.
Uh, ah. Ah.
Hm?
She doesn't know what
she's talking about.
Guys!
You made it.
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, Todd.
Sorry to hear about Gwen.
What? Why, did she say
something to you
about why she broke up
with me?
Oh, uh, no.
Tonight will be
the first chance
I've had to talk to her.
Really. Heh.
Look, George...
I'm friends with
both of you,
but I can't betray
her confidence
by telling you
anything.
I wouldn't
hear of it, Todd.
It's none of my business.
But you should try and find out
everything you possibly can.
In fact, I'll even stay
all the way over on
the other side of the room
just so there's no chance
of me overhearing anything.
You are so centered.
Hey...
I've grown up.
Oh, my God. There she is.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Go. Heh.
[WHISPERING]
Let's go, let's go!
What?
Huh? Let's go!
Wh-what're
they saying?
"Hi, Gwen." "Hi, Tide."
High tide?
"Hi, Todd."
KRAMER:
"You got something between your teeth."
Where?
No, that's what he said.
"That's interesting.
"I love carrots,
but I hate carrot soup.
And I hate peas,
but I love pea soup."
So do I, huh?
This is so wild.
Can I borrow her for a few hours
tomorrow afternoon?
No. If I lend her to you,
I have to lend her to everybody.
I don't envy you,
Todd.
This place is gonna
be a mess.
Well, maybe you can stick around
after everybody leaves,
and we can sweep together.
"Why don't
you stick around,
and we can
sleep together?"
What?!
"You want me to
sleep with you?"
I don't wanna sweep alone.
He says, "I don't
wanna sleep alone."
And she says...
Oh, boy.
"Love to."
All right, that's it!
So you get rid of me,
and now the two of you
are gonna sleep together?!
What?
You're crazy!
KRAMER:
"What? You're crazy!"
I heard
your whole conversation.
How?
"How?"
I can read lips!
You said,
"Let's sleep together."
No, I didn't. I said "sweep."
Let's sweep together.
GWEN & KRAMER:
You know like with a broom. Cleaning up!
Sweep?
GWEN & KRAMER:
Yes. Sweep.
Cut it.
George says, "Cut it."
Cut it!
KRAMER: George is saying--
Cut it.
Would you stop signing?!
What?!
They said "sweep together,"
you idiots,
not "sleep together"!
Look, I know
how to sign.
Ah! My eye! My eye!
This is really amazing,
getting to see Monica Seles
play in the finals.
I know, and in the first
tournament of her comeback.
Thus ends the great
ball-man experiment.
You with
the tennis center?
Yeah.
Hey, how about that ball man
injuring Monica Seles?
[CHUCKLES]
Wasn't that something?
I'm deaf.
Oh.
I've always been a big fan
of the little check move.
You know...
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[WHISPERING]
Can I get the check?
Check.
Unless the waiter's
not too sharp,
they gotta total it up.
[MOUTHS]
The check, I want the check.
Sometimes they come over,
"Do you want the check?"
"No, I wanna be pen pals.
"Can't you see
what I'm doing here?
I'm trying to be cool
and impress people."
[♪]