The whale's supposed to be
such an intelligent animal.
You know, you always hear about
how they can communicate
by song from miles away,
how extensive
their vocabulary is.
I would say, from the rate
we're pushing the whales
off the beach,
back into the ocean,
the words
"shore" and "close"
do not appear to be
in their vocabulary.
I'd tell the whales,
"Concentrate less on the singing,
"a little more
on the approaching
"Cuervo Beach
volleyball tournament,
if you wanna maintain
that brainy mammal image."
ELAINE [THINKING]:
Oh, I can't believe this.
What a dope!
Excuse me.
I-I'm sorry.
This is, uh-- This is
kind of embarrassing,
but there's no toilet paper
over here.
Are you talking
to me?
Yeah. I just
forgot to check,
so if you could
spare some...
No, I'm sorry.
What?
I can't spare it.
You can't
spare it?
No. There's not
enough to spare.
Well, I don't
need much.
Just three squares
will do it.
I'm sorry.
I don't have
three squares.
Now, if you
don't mind...
Three squares?
You can't spare
three squares?
No, I don't have
a square to spare.
I can't spare
a square!
Well, is it
two-ply?
Because if it's two-ply,
I'll take one ply.
One ply.
One puny little ply.
I'll take one
measly ply!
Look, I don't have a square,
and I don't have a ply!
No, no, don't go!
I beg you!
[SIGHS]
Mmm. I love this
artificial flavoring.
I like it
better than butter.
I think it's
more consistent.
You would not believe what
just happened to me
in the bathroom.
What?
Hey.
Hey, where's
my popcorn, babe?
What?
My popcorn.
You were supposed
to get me popcorn.
What, did you forget
about me, babe?
You would
not believe
what just happened to me
in the bathroom.
I mean, a person needs
a certain amount
of toilet paper
to be covered.
That's right.
I simply could not
spare it.
This woman just
didn't get it.
She kept
harassing me.
Three squares!
That's all I was
asking for.
Three squares!
She wouldn't stop.
"Help me!
Help me!"
She was insane.
I was
begging her.
"Please,
please!"
She was insane!
Who does she
think she is? How dare she.
Do you want me
to get the manager?
Too bad they don't
have those old ladies
walking around with
flashlights anymore. We'd flush her out.
I don't even know
what she looks like.
I wonder where
Elaine is sitting.
I really wanted you
to meet her.
She's supposed to
be here
with her new
boyfriend, Tony.
I wonder where
Jerry's sitting.
He's supposed to
be here tonight
with his
new girlfriend.
I'm dying to see
what she looks like.
Hey, you think if I
jumped off that balcony,
I'd get hurt?
Hey.
JERRY: Hey.
Hey, guy.
Can I use your phone
in your bedroom?
What's the matter
with yours?
Uh, my batteries
are dead.
It's not one of those
976 calls, is it?
Come on.
Let me use it.
Five minutes.
I'll pay you back, huh?
Why do you do that?
I am never going
to the movies again.
Hey, where were you last night?
I looked for you.
I looked for you too.
I was all the way
over on the side.
Oh, with, uh,
pretty boy...
Tony.
Ya.
Hey. Hey.
Right, okay.
Tony. Hey. Hey.
That's nice.
Listen.
Listen to this.
I am in the bathroom
right before
the movie starts,
Uh-huh.
and I'm in the stall,
and there's no toilet paper.
No what?
Toilet paper.
Oh. Whoa.
So I ask
this woman
in the stall
next to me for some,
and she refuses!
Ha, ha!
Well, maybe she
couldn't spare it.
A square?
Well, you know, sometimes
a square is everything.
A ply?
Elaine, you cannot
judge a person
in a situation
like that.
I mean,
it's like asking
for someone's canteen
in the desert!
Yeah.
It's battle conditions.
Yeah, well, I just hope
I run into her again, okay?
'Cause I will never
forget that flinty voice.
It is tattooed
in my brain.
If I hear it,
watch out.
So, listen, what happened
with Jane last night?
Oh...
Jane, she, uh...
She, uh...
The four of us are going out
Saturday, right?
That should be fun.
Yeah, that should be
real fun.
You know what?
It's getting late.
Can I call Tony?
Yeah.
WOMAN [SEXY VOICE]:
Then we'll get a cab
and we'll do it
in the back seat.
How's that, Andre?
Andre?
Oh.
KRAMER:
Well, what about the driver?
We might get
in an accident.
WOMAN:
So what.
KRAMER:
Well, that wouldn't be very good.
Hey, Andre,
get the hell off the phone!
Wait, what is
going on?
Who is Andre?
Kramer's Andre.
He's fooling around
with these 976 numbers.
Hey, I told ya,
I don't want you doing that
on my phone!
Jerry,
I'm telling you,
this phone sex thing
is hilarious!
Like this Erica woman.
Here, look.
You gotta call her.
What a voice
she uses.
Hey, you know,
it's weird
because that voice sounded
a little familiar to me.
You hungry?
Wanna go to Monk's?
No. I gotta go
downtown.
Wait, you're giving me
a lift home, right? Yeah.
So listen,
what happened
last night with Jane?
Oh, nothing.
She just, uh,
choked on a jujube.
Oh.
You know, I hate
to tell you this,
but it is time
to defrost your freezer.
I know. I just can't
bring myself to do it.
Meanwhile, that freezer
keeps getting
smaller and smaller.
Uh, don't wanna
keep Tony waiting.
Hey, you got
a problem with Tony?
Hunky...
Tony.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Okay, Jerry, I would
be going out with him
no matter what
he looked like.
Of course
you would.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, like you're
one to talk.
Elaine,
What?
it's different
for a man.
We're expected to be
superficial.
I'm not being
Elaine, he's a...
He's a male bimbo.
He's a mimbo.
He's not a mimbo.
He is an exciting,
charismatic man
who just happens to have
a perfect face.
And that's why you're
going out with him.
No, it is not.
You know, I think George
has a nonsexual crush on him.
I think he does too.
I mean, every time
I see him,
it's Tony this,
Tony that.
George is like a schoolgirl
around him.
Mm.
So I said, uh...
"Hey, dude,
you better step off."
Step off?
Yeah.
You said
"step off"?
Wow!
God, that is
too much!
Hey, uh,
hey, uh, Tony...
I, uh-- I just had
this brainstorm for us.
Can you guess
what it is?
No.
Bowling.
What do you say?
Bowling, huh?
Bowling's insane!
Bowling is crazy-time!
Bowling.
I don't think so,
George.
You get no rush
from bowling.
Rush?
You want a rush?
Drop a ball on your toe,
my friend!
Talk about a rush.
You'll be throbbing!
You'll see visions!
No, no, no, no.
I'm thinkin'...
rock climbing.
All right!
Rock climbing!
Just the two of us?
All right.
Hey, I'll make
some sandwiches.
What do you like,
tuna, peanut butter?
Whatever.
All right, all right.
I gotta buy some bread.
Yeah. You know,
I am definitely down
for some rock climbing.
Yeah, me too. I am down!
I am totally down!
Mark me down!
Cool. So, what do you say
we climb a rock...
mañana?
Uh...
mañana.
Uh, mañana might
be a problem.
I'm--
I'm supposed to, uh,
have a boil lanced
mañana, and, uh,
you know, I think they
charge me if I cancel
with only one
mañana's notice.
Hey, Kramer!
Hey, Tony.
Hey.
Hey, Georgie.
Kramer, my man,
what are you doing
mañana?
Mañana
I'm doing nada.
What do you say
you scale some rock with me and George?
Uh, Tony,
that'll be
too many sandwiches.
Come on, Kramer.
What do you say?
Kramer, it's pretty
dangerous up there.
I'm down.
Yes!
Yow!
I'll see ya.
All right, buddy.
Take it easy, Kramer.
You down, George?
What's wrong?
Oh, no,
I-I am down!
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha!
ELAINE:
Rock climbing?
Ha, ha.
Where do you
come off
going
rock climbing?
Rock climbing?
You need a boost
to climb into your bed.
All right.
Yeah, what is it
with you and Tony?
What are you, like,
his sidekick now?
Yeah.
That's right.
I like it.
He's such
a cool guy.
Cool guy?
What are you,
in eighth grade?
He's the first cool guy
I've ever been friends with
in my whole life.
You know,
it's a different world
when you're
with a cool guy.
He's not afraid
of anybody.
You should hear the way
he talks to waitresses.
He gets free pie!
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Nice move today.
What?
Horning in on
my rock climbing trip.
It's just supposed to be
me and Tony.
He asked me.
You put him
on the spot.
You know, I think that
you're in love with him.
What?
[SNORTS]
That's ridiculous!
No, no. I don't
think so.
You love him.
You better be careful on
those rocks tomorrow, buddy.
And you're not getting
any sandwiches, either!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
You're making
sandwiches?
Hello.
I don't know if there's gonna be
places to eat
up there. Who?
Hey, Elaine, does Tony
like peanut butter?
Hates it.
[SNAPS]
Good thing
I asked.
Who is it?
Oh, well,
she says Jane.
Yeah, so?
Well, that voice,
it's very familiar.
Throaty,
almost flinty.
Did you say flinty?
Yeah, yeah.
Flinty.
KRAMER:
Yodel-lay-hee-hoo!
Hello!
ECHO:
Hello, hello!
Hello!
Hey, George,
you hear that--?
Aah! Aah!
Let go of me!
Oh, God,
please get off me!
I don't wanna
die up here!
Please, please!
Please, stop moving.
That's all
I ask of you.
Aah! Kramer!
Kramer!
Hey!
George!
Let go of my leg!
Kramer--
Grab the rock!
What rock?
The rock
in front of you!
Oh!
All right!
Ah!
You've gotta relax.
Try to yodel.
Yodel.
Yodel-lay-hee-hoo!
[SINGING AND SOBBING]
That's it.
TONY:
George! Kramer!
Yeah?
Take the rope,
thread it through
the carabiner and knot it.
Then I'll climb up
to where you are.
All right. George,
you got it?
Yeah.
You got it,
George? Yeah.
All right,
take it.
TONY:
Hey, George,
you got anything
to eat, dude?
Yeah, I, uh...
I got
some sandwiches.
I got tuna
and salmon salad,
Tony,
because I know you don't
like peanut butter.
What?
[SLIDING SOUND]
TONY:
Dude... Aaaaaaaaah!
Aah!
ECHO:
Aah! Aah!
I've got oil
all over me.
Can I have
your napkin? What?
Your napkin.
I'm dripping.
Well, where's
your napkin?
I used it up.
Well,
I need mine.
Oh, God, look at the time.
I gotta get to work.
You know, I'd like to hear
about this job of yours.
I told you
already.
It's very boring.
You know, I think I had
a little too much garlic.
Can I have a piece
of some gum?
Ah, you're fine.
[BUZZER]
How's does
this thing work?
Just press it.
It's Elaine.
Oh, come on up.
Who is it?
It's Elaine.
Oh. Uh...
Is she coming up?
Yeah.
Ah. Huh.
Uh, you know, your breath
is a little garlicky.
You better take
some gum.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Have a couple pieces.
It's weak.
Weak gum. Okay.
Have some more.
For the road.
Isn't it
too much?
Nah. Trust me.
Believe me. Nah.
It's good. Yes.
Smells?
Yeah. Stinks.
Terrible.
Hi, Elaine.
Hi!
How are
you? Good.
This is Jane.
Elaine.
Hi.
Hi!
Nice to meet you,
finally.
It's so nice
to meet you.
I look forward
to Saturday night.
Yeah, me too.
Okay, so I'll see you
Saturday night.
Saturday night!
What is with
the gum?
I know. Big problem.
She puts, like, four pieces in her mouth.
It's ridiculous. I don't think
we can get together Saturday.
Because of the gum.
Well, it's too much.
It's embarrassing.
Why does have to
chew so many?
She's one of
these people
that always has
to be different.
She's in there.
I can hear her.
All right, who's
gonna tell her?
Uh, you tell her.
It was
ault. If you hadn't come along,
it wouldn't have happened!
I was the one
who was invited! Oh, yeah?
Well, look
who's here.
Hey!
Hey! What are you
doing here?
You're alive!
Yeah.
Did you have fun?
Well...
For a little while.
Yeah.
Where's Tony?
Oh.
Uh.
Kramer was supposed
to tie a knot--
Whoa, whoa,
ginga!
You were supposed
to tie the knot.
What, did something
happen?
Well...
Tony took a bit
of a tumble.
His face!
Did something happen
to his face?
Well, it all depends
on what you mean by...
"happen."
H-he's alive.
Yeah.
What happened
to his face?
Well...
You see,
he slipped
and landed
on a kind of a...
A rock.
Yeah.
The ambulance got there
very quickly.
It was
a big rock.
We rode with him all the way
to the hospital.
Yeah. I sang "99 Bottles
of Beer on the Wall."
Well, aside from that,
how'd he like the sandwiches?
So, what did
the doctor say?
They said, uh--
They said
I'm coming along.
Yeah.
But what else
did they say?
Well, let's see,
they said, uh...
"Tony, try to
keep it clean."
Right. Yeah.
No, I mean, um,
did they get into
stuff like, uh...
long, jagged scars
or gross deformities,
major skin grafts,
stuff like that?
Uh...I really
don't remember.
I was kind of out of it
the first couple of days.
I was on a lot
of medication.
You know, it was
kind of like a haze.
It was pretty cool.
Ha, ha.
But, um, you know,
in this medicated haze,
in this sort of
woozy state, um,
do you recall
the words
"radical reconstructive
surgery" being uttered?
I don't know.
Think, Tony, think.
I'm drawing a blank,
babe.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
Hi, Elaine.
Yeah.
This isn't a very
good time, George.
I-I just wanted to talk
to Tony for a minute.
Step off, George!
I don't wanna see you.
Me? Step off?
Yeah. Tony says you better
step off, George, so...
But why? It wasn't
my fault.
You asked me
for a sandwich. I--
I made such delicious
sandwiches, Elaine.
Just beat it, dude!
Here, Elaine, here.
It's Superman.
Tony, please.
Next time it'll
just be the two of us.
There won't be any
next time, George.
Oh.
Oh, Tony, don't.
Okay.
Step off, George,
okay?
Can you just
step off?
I just--
Step off.
Oh!
George, wait, wait.
Yes?
Would you throw
this trash out?
Ah, oh, I been waiting
a while for this.
You know, it's a shame
Tony got all banged up,
because we can't get
together on Saturday night.
Ah, that's too bad.
What a shame.
Yeah. It is.
It's a damn shame.
A damn shame!
Well, maybe when
he's feeling better.
Yeah. Without a doubt.
I'm down.
Whoo!
Oh, hey.
How you doing?
Hey, hey.
Jane, this is
my neighbor Kramer.
Oh, hey.
Hello, Kramer.
[EXHALES]
Well, hello,
Jane.
Jerry's told me
so much about you.
I feel like I know
you intimately.
Oh, I don't
think so.
We never met. I never
talked to you on the phone.
See you.
Where ya
going? Uptown. To the Y.
Oh, I'm going
uptown too.
You wanna
split a cab?
What about
the driver?
What are you
talking about?
All right,
I changed my mind.
I don't think
I'm gonna go now.
Oh. All right, well,
see you later.
Nice meeting you.
See you.
[EXHALES]
What's with you?
That's her!
Who?
Erica!
She's Erica!
You think she's Erica,
the phone-sex woman?
Jerry, that voice
is tattooed
on my brain.
It's her.
I'm telling you,
it's her!
You're crazy!
Am I?
Or am I so sane that
you just blew your mind?
It's impossible!
Is it?
Or is it so possible
that your head
is spinning like a top?
It can't be!
Can't it?
Or is your entire world
just crashing down
all around you?
All right.
That's enough.
Yeah!
He's supposed to get
the bandages off on Sunday.
What if?
What?
You know...
Oh. You're afraid he might
look like Zippy the Pinhead.
Yeah, I mean,
I mean,
what is my obligation
here?
You know,
we were just dating.
It was probably
gonna be over
in a couple of weeks
anyway.
Oh. I thought you didn't
care about his looks.
I lied.
Ah-ha.
Are you kidding?
He's a mimbo.
I know that.
But he's my mimbo,
you know,
and even if he is
a hideous freak,
maybe... Maybe I can
learn to love him,
and maybe in some
final irony,
I'll learn what love
really is.
You know, Jerry?
I'm sorry. I didn't get
most of that.
Uh, is that Kramer
over there?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Kramer.
Huh?
Hey.
It's all set.
What's all set?
Erica's gonna
meet me here.
Now we're gonna
find out the truth.
How'd you get her
to meet you?
We have a certain
chemistry.
Oh, my God!
Hi. Thought I'd
find you here.
Hello, Erica.
Erica? What are you
talking about?
How could you say things
like that over the phone?
What things?
What are you talking about?
Selling sexual pleasure
on the phone?
I sell paper goods,
you jerk.
Paper goods?
Excuse me. Do you have
a tissue?
No, I'm sorry.
I can't spare it.
There's just not
enough to spare.
Where's
the ladies' room?
Eh.
I have to go
to the bathroom too.
Oh, damn.
Something
wrong?
Yeah, there's no
toilet paper in here.
I usually check.
But would you mind?
I can't.
I don't have it.
I don't have
a square to spare.
I can't spare
a square.
Hey, wait a minute.
I know you!
That's right,
honey.
And I know you!
No! Wait!
No!
Here. Take it.
Thanks.
Don't call me
anymore.
[SEXY VOICE]
You either.
Now, of course, the thing
is extreme sports:
bungee jumping.
To me, if bungee jumping
as a sport,
so is being
a crash-test dummy.
Just leaning does not
make it a sport.
It's like a Wile E. Coyote
idea, isn't it?
The thing I wonder about
in skydiving
is why do they even
bother with the helmets?
Can you almost make it?
You might as well
wear a party hat.
What's the difference?
You jump out of a plane
20,000 feet in the air,
the chute doesn't open,
I got news for you.
The helmet is now
wearing you for protection.
Later on, the helmet's talking
to the other helmets, going,
"Boy, it's a good thing
he was there,
"or I would have hit
the ground directly."