The human fascination
with water is amazing.
We're constantly going
to beaches, pools,
lakes, rivers.
We're swimming.
We're snorkeling.
We're scuba-diving.
We bathe in it.
Our bodies are mostly water.
Everyone's carrying around
these bottles of water.
We can't get enough water,
unless it rains.
Then we're like,
"Oh, look, I'm soaked.
I am literally drenched."
For some reason,
we have a huge problem
with small, flying water.
It'll just stop us
right in our tracks.
"Oh! I felt a drop.
"We're gonna get
caught in it!
Everyone cover
your water bottles! Run!"
[♪]
KRAMER:
All right, get off at the next exit.
Kramer, I've driven
to East Hampton many times.
I know the exit.
I hear it's a great house.
Pool, sun deck...
Hoo-hoo. Yeah.
I'll be there.
You sure we're making
the right move?
We gotta see
the new baby anyway.
At least
it's in the Hamptons.
Didn't they
just have a baby?
That was two years
ago, remember?
[NASAL VOICE]
Jerry, you gotta see the baby.
Ya gotta see the baby!
Are they
just having babies
to get people
to visit them?
Hey, Jerry, you ever
wear silk underwear?
No.
Put that on
the top of your list.
Not for me. A little
too delightful.
Well, George and Jane should
be almost there by now.
Isn't it weird that
George and Jane haven't had sex,
but they're spending
a weekend together?
George is
pretty pleased.
It's like she signed
a letter of intent.
When's Rachel coming?
3:00 train.
Her father
is so religious.
I'm amazed he's letting
you see her again
after that Schindler's List
make-out session.
I brought him
some kishke.
What's that?
It's a stuffed
meat thing.
Israeli soldiers
carry it
in case they're captured
behind enemy lines.
They eat it,
and it kills them.
[LAUGHING]
[♪]
I never tasted
a cough medicine
I didn't love.
Me too.
I love cough medicine.
You see? We were
made for each other.
THINKING:
It's amazing. If I reach out and touch her breast now,
she'd throw me out of the car.
But at this
time tomorrow,
I could touch it
all I want.
What's
your favorite?
Pertussin.
Ever try it
with club soda?
No.
Oh, very refreshing.
Sex is like joining
a private club.
I'll be the same me tomorrow,
but suddenly
the "no trespassing" sign will be gone.
Are we almost there?
Yeah, about 10,
15 minutes.
But I have to stop
at a vegetable stand.
What for?
My mother loves
Hampton tomatoes.
She's nuts for
Can you
buy them later?
I really wanna
get some...sun.
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry.
Rub some lotion
on my back.
Who are you, Mrs. Robinson?
Come on,
and I'll rub some on you.
No, that's not
sweetening the deal.
Oh, come on!
[LAUGHS]
No.
When I was a kid,
I once found
$1.50 in change
at the bottom
of a pool.
You must
have been excited.
Yeah.
Hey, I gotta go
get those tomatoes.
Wanna go
for a ride?
I don't think so.
Okay. I'll, uh...
I'll see you later.
Anybody want
some tomatoes?
No, no.
No, thanks.
I'm gonna take a dip.
Go ahead.
And then there's Maude.
Look at my face.
Look at it.
Do you
see any lines?
No lines.
You know why?
One word: shade.
When will we
see this baby?
When is this
momentous event?
He's taking a nap
or something.
I wanna see if there
are any girls on the beach.
Elaine, wanna come?
No, thanks.
I got plenty
of girlfriends.
Well,
this is interesting.
What?
Jane's topless.
Yo-Yo Ma.
Boutros Boutros-Golly.
Nice rack.
Come on, you guys.
You can see the baby now.
Oh, uh,
in a minute, Carol.
We'll be right up.
This is weird,
wild stuff.
George hasn't even
seen her yet.
Why do you think we're
getting the sneak preview?
Maybe she's trying
to create a buzz.
What?
You know, get some good
word of mouth going.
Oh, here she comes.
Uh, ooh.
I'm thirsty.
Anyone want a drink?
No, thanks.
Uh, I'm good.
Uh, you can...
All right. Show's over.
I'm going to the beach.
Adam, Jerry and Elaine
are here.
ELAINE:
Where is the cute little snuggly baby?
Isn't he
gorgeous?
Oh, he's--
Eww...
Is he
gorgeous?
Uh, gorgeous, yes.
So very gorgeous.
Michael!
Shut the door.
You're letting bugs in!
[THE BEACH BOYS'
"WOULDN'T IT BE NICE" PLAYING]
♪ Wouldn't it be nice
If we were older ♪
♪ Then we wouldn't have
To wait so long ♪
♪ And wouldn't it be nice
To live together ♪
♪ In the kind of world
Where we belong ♪
♪ You know it's gonna make it
That much better ♪
♪ When we can say good night
And stay together ♪
♪ Oh, wouldn't it be nice ♪
[PANTING]
Is it me,
or was that
the ugliest baby
you have ever seen?
Oh... I couldn't look.
It was like
a Pekinese.
Boy, a little
too much chlorine
in that gene pool.
The thing is,
they'll never know.
No one's ever
gonna tell them.
Oh, you have to lie.
Oh, it's a must-lie
situation.
Yes. It's a must-lie
I don't think
we should tell George
we saw Jane topless.
No. I don't
think so.
Remind me
to tell Kramer too.
Oh.
Oh!
Lobster.
BEN:
This ointment should do it.
How are you
feeling, Adam?
Elaine!
This is our pediatrician,
Ben Pfeffer.
Hi.
Look at him,
Elaine.
How gorgeous is he,
I ask you?
How gorgeous?
Pretty gorgeous.
Elaine, do you
have kids?
Me? Oh, no,
but I'd love to have a baby.
I mean, I can't wait
to have a baby.
I'm just dying
A beautiful woman
like you should.
You're quite
breathtaking.
Breathtaking?
I'm breathtaking?
And he's
very particular.
Ben, you're staying
over tonight, right?
Uh...sure.
Uh--
I, uh...
I'm gonna go pick up
Rachel at the station.
Yeah. See ya.
Okay.
[WHISTLES]
Oh, just
look at him.
Yeah, he really
is breathtaking.
The train
was so crowded,
I had a seat
facing the wrong way.
I like that.
It's like going back in time.
Hey, Rachel.
Hi. I'm gonna go in
and get changed.
Okay.
What kind of greeting
was that?
She's got greeting
problems.
Yeah.
Boy, I love these
Hampton tomatoes.
You can eat them
like apples.
The tomato never really
took off as a hand fruit.
Well, the tomato's
an anomaly,
so successful
with the ketchup and the sauce,
but you can't
find a good one.
Hey, hey, hey!
Look at what I got!
Whoa!
Yeah!
Wow!
The K-Man!
You got lobster
for everybody?
Yeah,
and they're fresh!
Right out
of the ocean!
This is fantastic!
Man, what a weekend!
Swimming,
lobster for dinner.
I know. It's great.
I saw Jane topless.
You saw who what?
Yeah, I saw Jane topless.
Well, we all saw her.
All right.
You saw Jane
topless?
Well, when you went
for the tomatoes,
she lied out
topless.
You mean face-down
on her chest.
No.
Face-up
on her back?
Yeah.
Well, why'd she
do that?
Well, I guess
she was hot.
You mean she just
lay there topless?
No. She got up.
She walked around.
Yeah.
Walked around?
And you looked?
Of course! She's got
a great body, buddy.
I'm gonna go upstairs.
I'll be right back.
I can't believe
that you saw her before me!
Think of me
as a doctor.
Well, how good a look
did you get?
Well, what do you mean?
Well...
If she was a criminal
and you had to describe her
to a police sketch artist.
They'd pick her up
in about ten minutes.
Great. Great.
So any time you want,
you can just
visualize her naked.
I guess
that's true.
Stop it. Stop it.
This is not fair!
It's not fair.
I don't like
this situation, not one bit.
What do you want?
You wanna see Rachel naked?
Yes! Yes!
Yeah, right.
The punishment
should fit the crime.
You can see me naked.
I can offer ya that.
It's like
I'm Neil Armstrong.
I turn around
for a sip of Tang,
and you jump out first!
Nobody ever called me
"breathtaking" before.
I've never been called
"breathtaking" either.
I mean, if he thinks that
that baby is breathtaking,
then who's not breathtaking?
Maybe
he just said it
because the mother
was in the room.
Yeah. Right.
That's a possibility.
I have to find out.
How you gonna
do that?
I can be very clever.
I'm gonna take a swim.
Oh, me too.
I'll meet you down there.
Oh. Don't go in.
Rachel's getting
undressed.
Oh, okay.
Hey!
Oh, sorry.
Don't you knock?
I'm sorry. Uh...
It's not like
I'll see something
I've never seen before.
You might have.
I didn't.
You won't.
What do you want
anyway, George?
Yes, George.
I'm kind of
wondering myself.
What is it
that you want?
No, I was just wondering
if you guys, uh...
had any gum.
Oh!
So you were swimming
in the pool,
and you wanted
some gum.
Yes. Because
the water was cold,
and the, uh, chewing
warms me up.
We don't have any gum.
Okay.
Thanks anyway.
Strange man.
Wait till you get
to know him.
So where is
this baby anyway?
Oh. Check it out.
I guarantee
you've never seen anything
quite so objectionable.
[LAUGHS]
It's down the hall,
third door on your left.
Aah! Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
I thought this was the baby's room.
[CHUCKLING]
I'm really sorry.
I was in the pool!
[♪]
GEORGE:
Did she do it on purpose?
It was my fault.
I told her
the wrong door.
I was supposed to see her.
She wasn't supposed to see me.
Well, so what?
Well, ordinarily
I wouldn't mind.
But...
But what?
Well, I just got back
from swimming in the pool,
and the water was cold.
Oh.
You mean shrinkage.
Yes.
Significant shrinkage.
So you feel
you were shortchanged.
Yes.
I mean, if she
thinks that's me,
she's under a complete
misapprehension.
That was not me, Jerry.
That was not me.
Well, so what's
the difference?
What if she
talks with Jane?
She's not gonna
tell Jane. How do you know?
Women aren't like us.
They're worse!
They're much worse than us.
They talk about everything!
Couldn't you tell her
about the shrinkage?
No, I won't tell her
about your shrinkage.
Besides, I think women
know about shrinkage.
How do women know
about shrinkage?
Isn't it
common knowledge?
Oh, for...
Elaine!
Elaine.
What?
Do women know
about shrinkage?
What do you mean,
like laundry?
No.
Like when a man
goes swimming.
Afterwards...
It shrinks?
Like a frightened
turtle.
Why does it shrink?
It just does.
I don't know how
you guys walk around
with those things.
BEN:
Excellent lobster, Kramer.
Really good.
Rachel, aren't you
gonna have any?
Oh. Uh, no,
I can't.
I'm kosher.
We don't eat shellfish.
You mean you've
never tasted lobster?
No.
Wow.
You're so...
pious.
I really respect that.
You know,
when you die,
you're gonna get
some special attention.
[BABY CRIES]
Oh, the baby's crying.
I'll get him.
He can sit
with us.
No!
You don't
wanna do that.
You'll
be uncomfortable.
Yeah.
Finish eating.
The baby won't
have any fun here.
We're not fun
for a baby.
The lobsters
will scare him.
Grr. Grr.
I'm gonna
get him.
JERRY:
Oh.
See? Look at this.
Rachel.
My T-shirt
shrunk.
It used to be
much bigger,
and now it shrunk.
See, that's
what water does.
It shrinks things.
Really? Tell us
more, Mr. Science.
[GIGGLING]
What are you doing?
What are you laughing at?
It's nothing,
George.
It's very impolite
to tell secrets.
Are you talking about me?
What is it
with you?
Easy,
big fella.
So, Kramer, where'd you
get these lobsters?
At MacLeish's Fish Market?
No.
I got them
in the ocean.
The ocean?
What do you mean?
Well...
I found this rope,
and I kept
tugging on it.
All these lobsters
came up.
Those are commercial
lobster traps.
You can't take lobsters
from there.
That's against the law.
Hey, take it easy.
There are plenty of lobsters
in the ocean for everyone.
My father
was a lobsterman.
He got up
every morning at 4
and came home at night
stinking of brine.
He sent me
through law school
with the lobsters
he caught.
CAROL:
Here he is.
Aw...yaahh!
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Some night, huh?
Yeah.
I wish I had
my telescope.
Some dinner, huh?
Yeah.
Nothing like really
fresh-caught lobster.
Some house, huh?
It was built
by Mark Farbman.
He built a lot
of these homes here.
Some ugly baby,
huh?
What did you say?
I said, uh...
some...snuggly baby.
Yeah.
He is something.
Well, to tell you
the truth, Dr. Pfeffer,
I was--
I was surprised
to hear you use
a word like "breathtaking"
to describe a baby.
I mean, because you also
used it referring to me.
Well, you know,
Elaine,
sometimes you say
a thing like that
just to be nice.
You told her?
Yeah.
What's the big deal?
You don't understand
this organ.
It's very...
schizophrenic.
Anyway,
what's the difference?
You're the ones who are obsessed
with this stuff, not us.
I'm sure Jane doesn't care.
You're going back
to New York now?
Yeah. I have some things
to do tomorrow.
Uh-huh.
I think you spoke
to Rachel.
That's what
I think.
So what if I did?
She didn't say
something to you
about a certain something?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I think that you think
that a certain something
is not all it could be,
when, in fact, it is all
that it should be, and more.
I'm sure it is.
Look, you don't understand.
There was shrinkage!
You looking for this?
Aah!
Oh, Kramer.
You startled me.
Well...
I thought you might
wind up around here.
Yeah, well,
I couldn't
stop thinking
about the way everybody was
enjoying the lobster so much.
Well, I thought a little
taste couldn't hurt.
May I?
No, I'm afraid
I couldn't do that.
Why not?
Well, now,
it wouldn't be kosher.
Come on, Kramer.
I really wanna try it.
No, I'm sorry, honey.
Not on my watch.
Come on,
Kramer.
Ahh!
[CAR DRIVING]
I heard a car drive out.
What was that?
Oh, that's just Jane,
driving back to New York
in the middle of the night.
George.
Thanks so much
for making breakfast.
These are the best
scrambled eggs I've ever tasted.
I didn't know
you could cook.
Well, I'm just
expressing my gratitude
to our gracious host.
Yes, George. The whole
breakfast is breathtaking.
Good morning.
Hey. Morning.
Morning.
Kramer.
I wanna thank you again
for last night.
You really saved me.
What happened?
Well, I almost
tried the lobster.
But Kramer stopped me.
Well, I knew
you'd regret it
for the rest
of your life.
I would have.
Hey,
look at this guy.
A little
breakfast?
Yeah.
And you eat eggs,
don't you?
Yes, I do.
All right.
Thank you.
These are delicious.
Where did you learn
to make eggs like this?
These are so good.
Aw. Enjoying them?
Mm-hm.
Oh, good.
You know, you might
wanna try eating it
with one of these.
There's lobster
in these eggs?
Not that much.
They shrink in the water.
Well, I guess I gotta go too.
Well, this has turned out
to be one hell of a weekend.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
I'm sorry
to bother you,
but we're trying
to track down a lobster poacher
that cleaned out
one of the traps.
Wonder what's
going on.
Ah, I guess I should
go up and apologize.
There he is,
officer.
Yeah.
[RACHEL SCREAMS]
Don't you ever knock?
Why did Rachel
have to drive back
with Michael and Carol?
Hey, if you saw
me naked,
I wouldn't wanna ride
with you either.
I still can't believe
Michael finked on Kramer.
How is he gonna
pay off a $1000 fine?
They got some
sort of program.
What?
Hey, there's
a tomato stand.
Let's stop.
I can get some more.
Hey, isn't that
Michael's car?
There's Rachel.
Where?
Look at the work people will do
to get to the ocean.
They'll fight the traffic
and the heat
and the parking
and the hot sand,
trying to get
through the waves,
and the ironic thing is,
the ocean doesn't even
really want us in there.
That's what's surfing is.
Surfing is the ocean
throwing us out of itself.
You see?
We keep trying to paddle in.
And the ocean is saying,
"No, you don't."
The ocean is like a nightclub,
and the waves are bouncers
tossing us out.
The undertow's like
the really mean bouncer.
Instead of throwing you out,
they take you in back
and rough you up a little bit.
"Oh, you wanna come in?
How about coming in,
like, 25 miles?"