Of the places you go
all the time,
the dry cleaning relationship
is the most bizarre.
You give each other the same
thing over and over again.
He gives it to you.
You give it to him.
He gives it back to you.
It's like it's half his shirt,
in a way.
He has it as much as you do.
You ought to go shopping
with him.
"What do you think
of this shirt?"
"That would look good
with a light starch."
The only warning label people
respect is "dry-clean only."
Speed limits, lung cancer,
cigarette warnings--
Your very life is at stake.
People go,
"Ah, the hell with it!"
But dry-clean only?
"Don't put that in the wash!
It's dry-clean only!
Are you crazy?"
[♪]
MERYL:
Good morning.
How'd you sleep?
Hey, you are on the couch
tonight, young lady.
You were all over
my side.
I was not.
I was sleeping with one cheek
off the bed!
By the way, you're falling way
behind on the "I love you's."
No, no, 12-8.
No, it's 15-8.
I know
I can't beat you.
I try to stay
competitive.
Let's get
some breakfast.
Uh, let me
get a coat.
I think I'll try a sport jacket
and scarf thing.
You know,
like an unemployed actor.
Ahh. I haven't worn this one
in a long time.
Ooh, cashmere?
No, Gor-Tex.
It's new.
Look at this locket.
What the hell's this?
There's a picture
in here. Look.
Wow, this
is really old.
You don't know
whose it is?
No, I haven't
worn this jacket
since I had it
dry-cleaned.
Maybe we
should ask him.
We'll stop there.
What do you want
for breakfast?
Pancakes.
Come on, you know
I'm getting pancakes.
I don't know that!
We can't both get pancakes.
It's embarrassing.
It's one step from the couples
that dress alike.
I'll get
the short stack.
Ah, that's why
I love you.
15-9.
[LAUGHING]
Hey,
how ya doing?
We just got back
from breakfast.
The pancakes
were dynamite.
Hey, is that
my maple syrup?
Oh...
yeah.
You bring
your own syrup?
Got to.
You got a lot to learn
about pancakes.
[♪]
This is my wife.
She died
eight years ago.
I've been looking
all over for this.
It's a lucky thing
I put the jacket on.
But how did it
get in the pocket?
The chain is broken.
It must have slipped in
when I was, uh...
Oh, wow.
I turned my house upside down
looking for this!
It's all I have left
of her.
Oh, that's
so touching.
You know what
I'm gonna do for you?
I'm gonna give
you and your family
25 percent off all
your dry-cleaning.
Oh, come on!
What are ya talkin'--
It's silly.
Forget it.
Get outta here!
It's done.
All right.
Well, I guess
I get it, too,
because...
I'm his wife.
I didn't know
you were married.
Oh...yeah.
Uh, you've never met
my wife, uh, Meryl.
Meryl Seinfeld.
Yeah, sure.
You get the discount too.
You might
regret that.
The money my wife
spends on clothes--
I'm taking him
to the cleaners.
See her sense
of humor?
Come here.
I'm so nuts about you.
It was fun
being single,
but when you meet
a woman like this,
you don't walk
to get married, you run.
Ooh.
[♪]
Oh.
Hey.
Hi, Greg.
Haven't seen you
in a while. Yeah.
Today's the first day
I worked out
since the Central Park
Mini-Marathon.
You ran
the Mini-Marathon?
No, but I exercised
that day.
[LAUGHS]
Well, I gotta
take off.
Yeah, as an airline pilot,
you're one of the few people
who can say that
and mean it.
Um...
Do you have
the time?
Eleven-thirty.
Eleven-thirty?!
Wait, wait.
Ten-thirty. Sorry.
Oh. Oh.
You have to be
somewhere?
No.
Then what
are you doing?
I'm just waiting
for my friend, George.
We worked out
together.
Oh.
Well, it was
good seeing you.
Yeah, nice to see you
too.
Bye.
[♪]
Uh, would you,
um...
C-can I--
Pardon?
The syrup. Would you pass
the syrup?
Oh, you want to try
Can I get you
anything else?
Um. Yeah. My wife and I
will have some more coffee.
Okay.
And the check
for my husband.
To my beautiful wife.
Ahh. To my adoring
husband.
Adoring?
What about handsome?
I like "adoring."
Adoring's good for you.
What does it do for me?
Um, excuse me.
Where did you get that?
I-- Well, um--
We don't allow
any outside syrups,
jams or condiments
in the restaurant.
And if I catch you in here
with that again,
I will confiscate it.
Yeah, well, I--
I told my wife not to bring it.
KRAMER:
Really? Twenty-five percent off?
Well, do I get that too?
No. Just Meryl.
Why does she get it?
Because she's my wife.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
ELAINE:
Mah. Uh.
You know, I'm really enjoying
this marriage thing.
You think about each other.
You care about each other.
It's wonderful.
Plus I love saying
"my wife."
Once I started saying it,
I couldn't stop.
"My wife" this,
"my wife" that.
It's an amazing way
to begin a sentence.
"My wife has
an inner-ear infection."
See?
I like that.
Hey, will you
do me a favor?
Will you take my quilt
into the cleaners
so I can get
the discount too?
Oh, come on,
we're gonna do this?
I can't be taking
all your dry-cleaning in.
Just this one time.
It's expensive!
All right.
Hey.
Hi. Hey.
Hey, Elaine?
Yeah.
If neither of us
is married in ten years,
we get hitched.
Let's make it 50.
We're engaged.
I'm gonna get
my quilt.
All right.
Listen to this.
You remember that guy
at the health club?
The flyboy.
Yeah.
Hey, where's George?
I waited.
He didn't show up.
Anyway.
This guy gave me
an open-lip kiss.
Mm.
So?
We've always just pecked.
This one had a totally
different dynamic.
Really?
Yeah. His upper lip
landed flush
on my upper lip,
but his lower lip
landed well below my rim.
Ah-ha.
Moisture?
Definite moisture.
That's an open-lip kiss
all right.
Yeah.
I think he's giving me
a big signal.
Maybe he wants to change
our relationship. Wow.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
Oh, uh...
It's George.
Hey, what happened
to you?
Nothing.
A little problem.
Well, what was it?
I was waiting.
Can I come upstairs,
please?
Maybe he wants
to ask me out.
I don't know why you're
interested. He's a jerk.
Because he doesn't pay
any attention to me,
and, uh,
he ignores me.
Yeah, so?
I respect that.
Hmm.
What happened?
Nothing, I...
said it was
a little problem.
Yeah,
what was it?
Well, I was in the locker room
showering, and I...
I had to go, so...
Here we go.
Anyway, I think the guy
in the shower opposite saw me.
He even gave me a dirty look.
You went...
in the shower?
Yeah, so what?
I'm not the only one.
Do you go
in the shower?
No,
never.
Do you?
I take baths.
Well, what was I supposed to do?
Get outta the shower,
put on my bathrobe,
go all the way down
to the other end,
come all the way back?
Did you ever hear
of holding it in?
Oh, no. That's very bad
for the kidneys.
How do you know?
Medical journals!
Do the medical journals
mention anything
about standing in a pool
of someone else's urine?
[♪]
Hello.
Oh, hi, honey.
What are you
doing here?
Just thought I'd
drop off a few things.
Oh. Heh.
I must have been
in the incinerator room when you left.
Here ya go,
Marty.
Another quilt?
Huh?
Jerry!
Uncle Leo.
Hello!
Hello.
So if you or your wife
drop by on Wednesday,
it should be ready.
Your wife?
Yeah...
my wife.
What are you
talking about?
Uh...
I got married.
You got married?
I wasn't invited?
Nobody sends me
an invitation?
Well, it was...
sudden.
Are you ashamed
of your uncle?
Do I embarrass you?
No, no.
It was a small ceremony.
Haven't I always been
the good uncle?
Yes, yes,
you have.
Who told you when you went
to school that you print well?
You did,
you did.
When he was
younger
he had a beautiful
penmanship.
I used to encourage him
to print.
I'm a good printer.
I remember your "V."
It was like
a perfect triangle.
Oh! There's my bus.
There you go,
Jerry. Okay.
Hello! Wait!
Uncle Leo!
Uncle--
[♪]
GREG:
I'm glad you're here.
This can get really boring.
You know where I could get
some good olives?
I can find out.
Would ya?
Sure.
Oh, a project!
That's a definite signal.
You know,
by the way,
you look really great
in that leotard.
Oh...thanks.
That's no signal.
Who wouldn't like me
in this leotard?
I look amazing
in this leotard.
You know what's weird?
I think I had a dream
about you last night.
Okay, he open-lips me.
He dreams about me.
We have an olive project.
That's it,
I'm asking this guy out.
Um, you know,
Greg--
Can I have a sip
of your water?
Oh.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
You were saying?
Uh, it was nothing.
Forget it.
GREG:
See that guy right there?
Yeah.
You mean him?
I caught him urinating
in the shower.
I'm thinking about
turning him in too.
[♪]
Honey?
Could you get me
something to drink?
You're right there.
Come on, I'm sitting!
[LAUGHING AT TV]
Honey, what'd you do
with the can opener?
I didn't do anything
with it.
It was
here yesterday.
It's in the first drawer.
I'm looking in the first drawer.
It's not here.
Yes, it is.
Hey, I'm not stupid.
I'm looking.
There's no can opener.
Did I say you were stupid?
Well, wouldn't I have to be?
You tell me there's a can opener
in the drawer.
I'm looking in the drawer.
There's no can opener.
What other conclusion
could one reach?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Want me to go find it?
Yes.
I do.
You show me where there's
a can opener in that drawer.
Hello, I'm sorry.
I'm fighting with my wife.
Jerry,
we just heard.
What's going on?
Why the hell didn't
you tell us?
Listen, Mom--
It was in here yesterday.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Who is she?
When did this happen?
I told her you'd
get married.
She thought you'd
never do it.
Morty, you're
talking too loud.
I'm not talking loud.
You're hurting my eardrum.
You must have
done something with it.
I'm on the phone!
Is she there?
Can we talk to her? What's her name?
Mom, I'm not married.
What?
I'm not married!
I knew it.
I told you!
Uncle Leo said.
I'm just pretending to get
a discount on dry-cleaning.
A discount on dry-cleaning?
[CLATTERING]
Could you make
a little more noise?
I'll have to call you later.
Well, I give up.
Well, whoopee-whoo.
You got any coffee?
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Geez.
I'll get it.
Take it easy.
Why you so tired?
My quilt is still
at the cleaners.
Jerry, I can't sleep
without my quilt.
The other night
I was cold.
So last night, I turn up
the heat. It's too hot.
I open up a window.
It's too cold.
I can't get into
the zone.
What is that?
Huh?
That.
Oh.
I forgot.
[♪]
Hey, I'm sorry about
that can opener stuff.
Yeah. Me too.
I love you.
Love you.
Well, good night.
Good night.
GEORGE:
They could kick me out if he tells them.
So, what do you
want me to do?
Talk to him!
How can
I do that?
You said he gave you
an open-lipped kiss!
Yes, but then he wiped his hand
on the top of the bottle
when I offered him water.
That doesn't
mean anything.
Are you kidding?
It's significant.
If he was interested in me,
he'd want my germs.
He'd just crave
my germs.
She's right,
George.
Bottle wipe is big.
Well, what about
the open-lip kiss?
Bottle wipe supersedes it.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
All right, maybe
he's not interested,
but you still
know him.
Can't you just
ask him?
Yeah, George,
but if I ask him now,
I will have no chance
of going out with him.
Why?
I...
I don't know.
Uh-huh.
Ah-ha.
Could it be because
you don't want him to know
that you have a friend
who pees in the shower?
No, that's not it!
Oh,
I think it is.
That's exactly
what it is!
Why couldn't you
just wait?
I was there!
I saw a drain!
Since when is a drain
a toilet?
It's all pipes!
What's the difference?
Different pipes
go to different places!
You're gonna mix 'em up.
I'll call a plumber
right now!
Can we drop all
the pee-pipe stuff here?
Okay!
Okay, okay!
I will
talk to him.
Jerry, I think
that quilt is ready.
All right.
You gotta pick it up for me.
All right, but this
is the last time!
I'm so tired.
Boy, you don't
look good.
Huh? I don't?
No.
You look pale.
Pale?
Oh, my God!
I gotta meet
Anna's parents today.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Oh, hi, honey.
Yes, I told him.
I'll get it.
Whenever.
Okay.
Okay, I'm sorry.
[♪]
I'm sorry.
It's not ready yet.
Not ready?
It has to be ready.
What kind of a business
are you running here?
Who the hell are you?
It's not your quilt.
He's a very good
friend of mine,
like an older brother
to me.
When things
don't go right,
he takes it
personally.
Well, uh,
maybe tomorrow.
Maybe.
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
I'll see you later.
Where you going?
I gotta meet Anna's
parents today, remember?
I look terrible.
I'm going to hit
the tanning machines.
You know those things
are bad for you.
Hey, that's how
I maintain my glow.
I'm going home.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
How much would it cost
to clean this?
Oh...about $13.
Thirteen?
Uh-huh.
Well, I can't
afford that.
Oh.
Well, I'm sorry.
[SIGHS]
[♪]
Hi, Greg.
Hey, Elaine.
I'll be off in a second.
'Kay.
I got the machine
next, buddy.
Oh!
Ahh.
It's all yours.
What happened?
Did he bring it up?
Never mind that.
Look at the signal
I just got.
Signal.
What signal?
Look, he knew I'd use
the machine next.
He didn't
wipe his sweat off.
That's a gesture
of intimacy!
I'll tell you
what that is.
That's a violation
of club rules.
Now I got him.
And you're my witness.
Wait a second, George.
Listen! Listen!
He knew
what he was doing.
This was a signal.
A puddle of sweat's
a signal?
Yes.
It's a social thing.
What if he left a used Kleenex?
What's that, a Valentine?
Now, you tell him if he's
thinking of turning me in,
then I got the goods on him.
No, I won't be
a party to this.
So you'll let me
get suspended for shower urination?
Okay,
I'll talk to him,
but you're putting me
in a very difficult position.
[♪]
I can't let you do this.
I want to.
But it isn't right.
I can't.
Give me the clothes.
Jerry, please.
What about her?
Oh, the hell with her.
No.
I can't.
[GASPS]
No, Jerry. Please!
I'm not gonna let you
walk out of my life.
I can't fight you.
Do you want box or hanger?
Oh, you decide.
[♪]
You're really working up
quite a sweat today, huh?
Yeah.
GREG:
Oh, there's the manager.
Good. I'll talk to her
about that guy.
You know, we cannot have
people like that in here.
Are you sure
you want to do that?
Yeah. He's disgusting!
Besides, I'll take any chance
I can to talk to her.
You're interested in--
In her?
Very.
Ah.
Hm.
You know, uh...
I'm engaged.
Yep, I'm getting married
in 50 years.
Oh, good.
There he is.
I wanna be able
to point him out.
Uh, you know,
Greg,
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Why?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't it
a violation of club policy
to not wipe down a machine
after using it?
Oh, I see.
You're friends with
the urinator, aren't you?
Yeah, well...
At least he had a drain.
[SNORING]
MARTY:
There you go, Mrs. Seinfeld.
With your twenty-five
percent discount,
it comes
to $17.80.
Here you go.
Okay.
[LAUGHS]
Excuse me,
this isn't mine.
Oh, yes, it is.
Your husband
brought it in himself.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
[♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
That's him.
Okay.
Oh. Hi.
[♪]
You son of a bitch!
I'm sorry.
Who is she?
I wanna know who she is.
It doesn't matter.
I want a divorce.
A divorce?
Oh, so you can marry her
and give her the discount?
Yes, that's right.
What happened to us, Jerry?
I'll tell you what happened.
We got married.
I'm sorry. This is my fault.
I pushed it on you.
No. I just wasn't ready
for the responsibilities
of a pretend marriage.
Goodbye, Jerry.
Oh...
I forgot.
This is your maple syrup.
It's all right.
I want you to have it.
Okay. Thanks.
We'll always have pancakes.
Goodbye, Jerry.
[♪]
I thought you said
you was bringing
a white boy home.
I don't see a white boy.
I see a damn fool!
[♪]
To me,
the thing about marriage is,
I can't believe
how often it happens.
I mean, I like the idea of it,
but I can't believe
that many people
are meeting people
that they wanna see every single day,
every day, every day,
every day, every day?
That should happen, like,
three or four times
in the whole century.
Like any major investment,
you sign a marriage contract.
Here's your person.
If you're a man, the bride's
family pays for the wedding.
That's like getting cash back.
Till death do us part.
That's the extended
warranty program.
And you give her the ring.
That's the keys.
You slide it on,
start him up.
But you gotta try and make it
work, because remember:
Your value drops twenty percent
the minute you drive
each other off the lot.