The old-fashioned barbershop is,
unfortunately,
becoming a thing of the past.
Now, what went wrong?
Well, first of all,
he needs a $20,000 chair
to make a $3 tip.
I say cut back on the chair,
update the magazines.
Why do barbers
always display that license?
There's no laws in hair cutting.
But show customers
the back of their head.
That's the one law.
I don't want to see the back
of my head.
Why do I want to see something
that I won't see
at any other time?
When I buy pants,
two salesmen don't lift me up
by the legs and go:
"How do you like the crotch?"
If I wanted to see everything,
I would've been a fly.
[♪]
Well, George, we here at Sanalac
like to think of ourselves
as a fairly
progressive company.
We have a small, but
prestigious, group of clients.
Well, a lot of people
consider me, uh,
small and prestigious.
That's funny,
George.
You're very quick.
Ah, well.
I feel like I don't--
I don't have to explain
every little thing to you.
You understand
everything immediately.
I enjoy
understanding.
I want you
to have this job.
Of course--
Stu Zimmer
line two.
Great.
Thanks.
I've gotta
take this call.
Listen.
I'm really glad
that you came in.
"I want you
to have this job.
Of course..."
Wha... Yeah?
That's it.
What? What do you mean,
"That's it?"
He never finished
his sentence.
He got a call,
ended the interview.
"Of course,"
was the last thing?
Maybe he was going to say,
"Of course, I have to check
with my associates."
"I want you to have this job,
of course...
"the Board of Directors
is under indictment
and will be serving time."
"I want you to have this job,
of course...
sodomy is
a prerequisite."
Oh, all right.
Why don't you just
go ahead and call him?
Because he made a big deal
about how I understand
everything immediately.
That's what impressed him.
So if you call to ask
if you have the job,
you might lose the job.
And if I don't call--
You might have
the job,
but you'll never
know it.
Oh.
What kind
of company is it?
Rest stop supply.
Oh. Oh.
Good for you.
Hey. Yup, yup, yup.
Hey.
Shower?
Haircut.
I'm very happy
with this.
Who'd you use,
Gino?
Of course.
Wouldn't let that
butcher cut my hair.
What butcher?
The uncle: Enzo.
Jerry uses him.
I've been going to him
for 12 years.
I can't switch.
I'd hurt his feelings.
You never get
good haircuts.
You can get
a good one today.
It's Enzo's day off.
Gino's there all by himself.
Really?
Yeah, you know what? You should
get one for my bachelor auction.
What bachelor
auction?
Oh, it's this thing
where they auction off
dates with bachelors
for charity.
And you didn't
ask me to do it?
I could raise enough
money to cure polio.
I believe they've had a cure
for polio for quite some time.
Polio?
Will you go ahead?
You need a haircut.
Okay.
What are you
all dressed up for?
Had a job
interview.
Yeah? How'd it go?
Good.
Of course...
[ITALIAN ACCENT]
Ah, Jerry!
Oh. Hi, Enzo.
You come
for the haircut.
Uh, no.
Actually, I was--
It's my day off,
but I take care
of you anyway,
because you my favorite
customer. You been with me
for so long.
You're so loyal.
Well, uh,
if it's your day off--
Eh, what's
the difference?
It takes
ten minutes.
Well, it's...
Jerry, today I'm going to do
something special for you.
I don't wanna take
too much off.
Hey, who's
your barber, eh?
You tell the joke,
I cut the hair.
Gino, you've outdone
yourself this time.
This is the best haircut
I've ever had.
He massacred you!
I know.
You look like
you're five years-old.
What if I shampoo?
Sometimes a shampoo helps.
You gotta start
seeing somebody else.
Get out
of this relationship.
I can't.
He loves me.
He says I'm his
most loyal customer.
Plus, he's right there
on the corner.
I'd have to pass him
every day when I go by.
But,
you gotta do it.
I can't, I can't.
I'd break his heart.
Ah.
No way
my Gino did that.
It's an Enzo.
He was in the shop.
You told me he was off.
So what?
So I didn't want
to hurt his feelings.
You can't continue
seeing him.
You're
destroying yourself.
Aah!
I'm not gonna
let you.
Now, if you don't call him,
I will.
No, Kramer,
you can't do that.
No, I'm call Gino.
You'll see him.
We're gonna get
that haircut fixed up.
I don't want you
to call him.
All right. Gee.
You're crazy.
So, uh...
I still haven't heard
about that job.
Yeah,
that's tough one.
What are you gonna do?
I have an idea.
Yeah?
I show up.
What do you mean,
you show up?
I show up.
I pretend
I have the job.
The guy's
on vacation.
If I have the job,
it's fine.
If not, by the time
he comes back,
I'm ensconced.
Hmm. Not bad.
What's the worst
that could happen?
Well, you'd be embarrassed
and humiliated
in front of a large
group of people
and have to walk out
in shame with your tail
between your legs.
Yeah. So?
Yeah, I see what
you mean.
I forgot who
I was dealing with.
GEORGE:
Good morning.
Morning. Hi.
Nice to see ya.
How are ya?
Good morning.
How can I help you?
Uh, the name is
George Costanza.
Uh, I'm starting work
here today.
I was wondering
if you could, uh,
tell me where my office is?
I wasn't aware that uh--
Mike!
This is
George Costanza.
He's starting
here today.
Welcome aboard.
Thanks, Mike.
Nice to be aboard.
I didn't know know Mr. Tuttle
was finished interviewing.
Well, he was probably
just getting anxious to start his vacation.
He wants to find his office.
Oh, well, uh...
All right, let's see...
We've got two.
There's the big one
down the hall there,
and the small one over here.
I should ask Jack.
Oh, leave Jack
alone.
Jack's got
enough problems.
I'll just take
the small office.
Really?
Yes, I like to feel cozy.
I have a very small apartment.
I like to feel
tucked in, nestled in.
Love to be nestled.
All right.
It's 808, right down there.
Meanwhile, I'll get you
the Pensky file.
You can start
working on that.
Yes, of course.
The Pensky file.
Can't wait to sink
my teeth into that.
Wow, that Pensky.
Well,
we'll straighten him out.
[WHISTLING]
So, what do you do there
all day?
They gave me
the Pensky file.
Oh. So it's a nice
place to work?
You know,
I'm enjoying it very much.
I think my co-workers
are really taking to me.
We're like a family.
In fact,
yesterday was Grace's birthday.
She's such a sweet woman,
so we had a little party
with cake and champagne, and...
I made a toast.
What about
your boss,
who
interviewed you?
He'll be back
on Monday.
Hi.
Hey.
Hi. Hey.
How come
you're wearing a hat?
I got a haircut.
Oh, yeah?
Can I see it?
Nah, there's nothing
to see.
Come on,
let me see it.
Forget it.
Come on!
All right.
JERRY:
It's very good.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Did you...?
You can forget about me
going to that bachelor auction.
What? No.
Jerry, you have to go.
Ah, you know, Elaine, I'd do it
but I'm working that day.
Yeah, too bad.
This is the worst haircut
Jerry's ever had.
You gotta fix it.
[ITALIAN ACCENT]
Sure.
I fix.
But you gotta make sure
you no tell anybody.
He's a little crazy.
I don't know what he do if he
find out I touch Jerry's hair.
So, I love
that Edward Scissorhands!
That's the best movie
I ever seen.
Again with
the Edward Scissorhand?
How can you have a hand
like a scissor, eh?
Show me one person who's got
a hand like a scissor!
Hey,
it's a beautiful dream.
I love to be this man.
Did you ever think
about what you're going
to do on the toilet, hmm?
What are you going to
do on the toilet?
I'd like to have
shoehorn hands.
Hey.
Okay,
now listen to me.
I talked to Gino.
He's going to fix the haircut.
Oh, great! Then you can go
to the bachelor auction.
Yeah, but--?
Aah! No buts!
His apartment,
tonight, 8:00.
Can he fix it?
I don't know.
[♪]
Boy...
You got a beautiful
head of hair.
Well, thank you.
I bet Uncle Enzo,
he tell you that all the time.
Actually, Enzo hasn't
said that to me in a while.
Oh.
I don't think
Uncle Enzo realize
what a lucky barber
he is.
That's nice of you
to say.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Oh. Just a sec.
Yes?
It's your Uncle Enzo.
Oh. It's Uncle Enzo!
Quick! Go in there!
I'll clean up.
Come on up.
[♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Uncle Enzo,
what are you doing here?
I come to apologize.
Apologize?
I rented the movie
Edward Scissorhands.
That Johnny Depp,
he make me cry.
Oh. He make
me cry, too.
You want
something to drink?
Mmm.
Hey!
What's all this?
Nothing.
It's just hair.
You do haircut
in the apartment?
No.
Pizza man was here.
Maybe some fall off.
He's going bald.
It looks very familiar.
[♪]
In the one minute
that he worked on me,
I could tell
he was really good.
Yeah. Slow,
gentle, attentive.
Yeah.
Didn't I tell you?
But Enzo picked up
one of my hairs.
Yeah, so?
I think he knew.
No,
he doesn't know.
He knows my hair.
You're just
imagining things.
He doesn't know
a thing.
Come on.
Pull yourself together.
Okay, okay.
What happened?
It looks the same.
He didn't get to finish.
His uncle came in.
We almost got caught!
Jerry, the auction
is in a few hours.
Take the K-Man.
Yep.
You can still go.
What?
Are you kidding?
Look at him!
He's grotesque!
Ya think?
Do I think?
He's repugnant.
What would you wear?
Whatever it takes.
See, now, Newman
is a good customer.
Once I find a barber,
I stick with him.
I almost went
to barber school.
I always felt
I had a talent for it.
Not everybody like Newman.
So loyal.
NEWMAN:
Yeah, just the way that I was raised.
I'm special.
You know, I don't mind
if somebody's funny,
but I no like
the funny business.
I'm going to go out
for a little bit.
I'll be right back.
Take your time.
You happy
with the haircut?
Hm, it's okay.
A little crooked.
How you like a free haircut
for six months?
What's the catch?
You're gonna get me
a sample of Jerry's hair.
Hmm. That job sounds like
it might be worth...
a year's free haircuts.
And a comb.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Mr. Costanza, Mr. Pensky's
here to see you.
Mr. Pensky?
Of the Pensky file?
Costanza?
Arthur Pensky.
Mr. Pensky.
I, uh, I was just
working on your file.
I was, uh, transferring
the contents of the file
into this, uh, flexible
accordion-style folder to--
Where's Tuttle?
He's on vacation.
He was on vacation
the last time I dropped by.
Gimme my file.
Looks like you put
a lot of work into this.
In college, they used to call me
the Little Bulldog.
Yeah, you are Pensky material.
Would you ever consider
coming to work directly for me?
Really?
You are aware--
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Mr. Costanza?
Not now, Clarisse.
Mr. Pensky should know
they're towing his car.
Damn this city!
I am aware...
He knows about us.
How do you know?
Because I know.
He's crazy.
All morning, he looking at the
hair. He staring at the hair!
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who is it?
It's Newman.
He was in the shop
with Enzo.
He can't see
me here.
Go in the bedroom.
Use the fire escape.
What do you want?
Could I use
your bathroom?
What's wrong
with yours?
My toilet's clogged.
You can't unclog it?
No.
Did you ask Kramer? He's out.
Number one?
Yes, yes, yes.
May I go?
Go ahead.
I gotta go very badly.
Flush twice!
Thank you!
No.
Jackpot.
Heh-heh-heh.
I don't believe this.
There's no hair in this thing!
I've never seen a person
that didn't have at least
one hair in a brush.
Unbelievable.
Nothing!
Ah.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[SNIPPING SOUND]
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
See ya later.
What are you doing?
I'm watching
Edward Scissorhands.
Oh.
Could I watch a little?
It's my favorite movie.
Yeah, all right.
What? You want
something to drink?
No, no.
If you want to watch,
sit down.
You're making
me nervous.
I tell ya,
this...
Scissorhands
is a hell of a barber.
[SNIPS]
Gotta go!
Oh, gee, I--
I dropped a nickel.
Yeah.
See ya, Jerry.
[LAUGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Did you get it?
Heh-heh-heh.
Huh?
Eh?
Oh, you done good, Newman.
It was a cinch.
Where you going?
Io voglio vendetta!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Nine hundred...
Do I hear 1000?
Ladies, he is
a Harvard graduate.
A thousand!
A thousand.
Okay,
1000 once...
A thousand twice...
A thousand three times.
Sold! To the lucky lady
in the third row.
Congratulations.
Thank you
so much.
Okay, our next bachelor
is number, um...
[MUSIC PLAYING]
One twenty-four
on your program.
He--
[APPLAUSE]
He is, um...
He's a
high school graduate.
[MUMBLING]
Oh.
Equivalency.
A high school equivalency
program graduate.
Um, he's, um...
self-employed.
He's...
I don't know, 6'3",
190 pounds.
He likes, uh...
fruit.
And, uh, he just got
um...a haircut.
So...
K-Kramer! Oh!
Kramer! Oh!
Okay, um, why don't
we start the bidding?
Um...
Do I hear
five bucks?
I don't get
this Scissorhands.
Is he supposed to be
a superhero?
Like Green Lantern or somebody?
What's with this guy?
I'm just asking.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who is it?
Enzo Manganero!
Oh, my God!
[♪]
One second!
Go.
Go in the bedroom. Go.
It was you that was at Gino's
apartment the other night!
No, I wasn't there!
Don't lie!
I know it was you!
I get a sample of your hair.
I match them up!
Sample?
Newman!
Well, I was there,
but I was just
dropping off a book.
Don't, Jerry.
So! It's true!
Yes.
Is true.
I'm gonna kill the both of you!
[SNIPPING SOUND]
Mr. Tuttle!
You're back.
George.
I'm surprised
to find you here.
You are?
Oh, I thought
you would've taken
the larger office.
Oh.
Oh. Really?
I guess I didn't
make that clear
when I hired you.
Well...
So where's that Pensky file?
Let's see what
you've been up to all week.
Well, here it is.
What have you been
doing all week?
Well, you missed a lovely party
we had for Grace.
You haven't done
anything with this.
Well, bear in mind,
I am in the smaller office.
I'm beginning to wonder
if you understand anything.
You are aware
that, uh, Pensky
is interested in me.
You're not
Pensky material.
Really?
Well, we'll just see
about that.
Ta-ta!
Tut-tle.
[MEN SOBBING]
[♪]
[GASPS]
Jerry.
MR. PENSKY:
Gee, George.
I'm sorry I gave you
the wrong impression.
What I was
going to say was,
"Now, you are aware
"that our Board of Directors
"has been indicted.
"Myself included.
"And we're prohibited
"from doing business
until the investigation
is completed."
So, obviously, we would
have no use for you.
Obviously.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yes?
Excuse me,
but Mr. Costanza's car
is being towed.
So when you gonna
be able to go out?
Not for a while.