I don't even know
what is supposed to be
so attractive about fur.
Why does a man wanna see
a woman in fur?
Men want women to shave
their legs, shave their armpits,
pluck their eyebrows.
And then before we go out,
we dress them up like a bear?
To me the only reason
to wear fur
would be if you were trying
to sneak up on another animal.
Did you ever see
those tribal hunters
where they wear the fur,
and then they have
the other animal's head
on top of their head?
You know, I'm sure there's
a moose looking at that going,
"Yeah, that looks real good.
"Yeah, I'm gonna turn my back
on this goofball
"with the extra head
because there's nothing fishy
"going on there.
"I'll just keep drinking
from the stream.
I've seen a lot of
two-headed tigers with knees."
GEORGE: So I am actually
gonna have a secretary.
And, I get to do
the interview.
It's incredible.
Six months ago,
you were taking messages
for your mother.
Yeah, and now someone's gonna
be taking messages for me.
From your mother.
So this woman
you plan on hiring--
Is she gonna be
in the spokesmodel category?
Sure, I could go
the tomato route.
But, uh, I've given this
a lot of thought, Jerry.
All that frustration--
I'll never get any work done.
So I'm doing a complete 360.
I'm going for total
efficiency and ability.
That's a 180, George.
Whatever.
Hi, Willie.
Hey, Jerry.
I got this stuff
and my mother's fur for storage.
What are you doing with it?
Oh, she keeps it
in my apartment
for when she comes
up from Florida.
Hi.
Hey, Jerry.
You know my wife, Donna.
Yeah.
That's why I said hi.
Hey, nice jacket.
Thanks.
Hound's tooth.
Whoa, this is a beauty.
Great cut.
It's probably
very flattering.
Oh, yes. It really
accentuates my bust line.
WOMAN:
Well, I type about 90 words a minute.
I'm completely well-versed
in all the IBM
and Macintosh programs.
Well, Miss Coggins,
you're obviously qualified
for the job.
You have all the necessary
skills and experience.
But you're extremely attractive.
You're gorgeous,
and looking at you,
I can't even remember my name.
So I'm afraid
this is not gonna work out.
Thanks for coming.
You're luscious.
You're ravishing.
I would give up red meat just to
get a glimpse of you in a bra.
I'm terribly sorry.
Terribly sorry.
As you can see,
my references are impeccable.
I think I'd be
a real asset here.
My only concern is,
I do take care of my mother,
so will there be many
late nights?
I can't imagine.
Okay, so Barney's
is having this huge sale.
I try this dress on.
Stunning. Stunning.
I couldn't take my eyes
off myself.
Yeah.
Okay, so then
I put it on at home.
Looks like I'm carrying twins.
So you're saying store,
hotsy-totsy,
home, hotsy-notsy.
Yeah. Exactly.
Anyway, I gotta go
over there and return it.
I thought we're goin'
to the movies?
All right,
I'll try it on again.
You tell me what you think.
All right.
Hey, hey.
Hey, George.
Hey, Elaine.
I am telling you, Jerry.
Having a secretary
is incredible.
I don't know why
I didn't have one before.
Because you didn't
have a job?
Perhaps.
I walk in,
everything is organized:
messages, appointments.
And I can't tell you
how proud I am of myself
for going with Ada.
A lesser man
would have crumbled.
They would've gone
for the dish
and the sure-fire
sexual harassment suit.
It's a little--
All right.
You answered it
right there.
You got no waist
in that thing.
And your arms
look like something
hanging in
a kosher deli.
I said all right.
Well, what'd you buy it for?
Why did I buy it?
Because in the mirror
at Barney's,
I looked fabulous.
This woman
who was just walking by
said I looked like Demi Moore
in Indecent Proposal.
How fast was she walking?
De-mi?
I thought it was Dem-i.
No, I think it's De-mi.
Really?
I never heard of a se-mi
tractor-trailer.
Wait a minute.
I know what's going on here.
Skinny mirrors.
What?
Barney's has skinny mirrors.
They make you look,
like, 10 pounds lighter.
Oh, you're crazy.
Am I?
Do you think
I would have bought this dress
if I looked like this
at Barney's?
You know, I think she may
have something there.
Oh! Whoa.
What are you
all dressed up for?
I'm returning this dress
to Barney's.
Good idea.
Do it tomorrow.
We'll go to the movies.
Yeah, yeah,
okay.
Look, if you're going there,
maybe you could pick me up
some of this super hydrating--
It's a total protection
moisturizer with UVA.
Yeah.
Moisturizer?
That's girl stuff.
No, no, no. Look.
I'll tell you what.
They're having a sale, right?
Yeah?
I'll meet you down there.
We'll have lunch.
Well, we could.
Yeah, we'll get
to know each other.
We never get to spend
any time together.
Oh, sure, we have
our little group here--
And then, assuming
the strike is resolved,
on April 14th,
we play the Angels.
So let's clear a floor
at the Anaheim Hotel.
Anaheim Hotel.
You may wanna reconsider.
I believe they only have
room service until 10 p.m.,
and then it's only finger foods.
Ada, you're a wonder.
Okay, now, I projected
some of those figures for you
regarding the switch to canola
oil for the stadium popcorn,
and surprisingly, it will only
cost a half a cent more per bag,
so it is definitely doable.
Ada, I have to tell you.
I-- I have never met anybody
so...efficient.
Well, thank you.
I'm flattered.
I mean, you're just a marvel
of organization.
Well, I'm just doing my job.
It's like I'm--
I'm thinking of something,
and you're one
step ahead of me.
What can I say? I'm--
I'm good at what I do.
Do you, uh... Do you know what
I'm thinking about now?
Yes, I think I do.
Is it, uh...doable?
It's definitely doable.
JERRY:
Well, that was the worst.
I can't believe they made
the wife the killer.
Give me a break.
Hey, give us a break.
We haven't seen it yet.
Thanks a lot, big mouth.
You got a pen?
Yeah, I think I do.
I need something
to write on.
Well, all I got
is my dry-cleaning stub.
I just met Uma Thurman.
She's giving me
her telephone number.
Uma, Jerry. Uma!
Uma Thurman?
Really?
How'd you manage that?
Yeah, well, I-- I don't have
any time to talk now.
He's got the kavorca.
Hey, isn't that Willie,
my dry-cleaner?
Where?
He just went in.
You know, I--
I think he was wearing
my hound's tooth jacket.
What would he be doing
wearing your jacket?
It looked just like the jacket
I brought in to be dry-cleaned.
He complemented me on it.
Are you sure?
I got it.
Uma, Uma, Uma.
You are amazing.
Yeah. All right.
Taxi's on me.
[MOANING]
No, no, no, no.
A better way to reach the bra
would be to undo the jacket,
then go around
the back of the shirt.
Ada, you're incredible.
[MOANING & PANTING]
Oh!
Here, I wanna show
you something.
Hand me that pillow.
What?
Oh, my God!
Mr. Costanza!
Ada, ah! Ah! Ahh!
I'm giving you a raise!
So you're having sex.
Then all of a sudden
you just blurt out:
"I'm giving you a raise?"
Yeah.
Just a quick sidebar here.
Are you in any way authorized
to give raises?
Not that I'm aware of.
No.
So you're so grateful
to have sex,
you'll just shout out anything
that comes into your head?
I didn't think ahead.
Well, maybe she'll just think
it was bawdy talk.
I didn't say any other
bawdy things.
Maybe you could have sex
with her again
and then take it back.
All right. You know,
you're not any help at all here.
I don't know what the point is
of talking to you about it.
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, I guess the only
thing I can do
is to go into
George Steinbrenner's office
and tell him that
he has to give her a raise.
How long's
she been there?
Three days.
It's almost a week.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's a movie stub
from the 9:30 show.
George, I think
Willie the dry-cleaner's
been wearing my clothes.
ELAINE:
These mirrors are skinny mirrors.
This is false...
reflecting.
And I think that
the department of...
you know, whatever,
would be very interested
to know what's going on here.
Well, we're more than
happy to exchange it
for something else.
Okay, fine.
I did like that
little Calvin Klein number
right by the elevator.
You know, with the little--
I'll bring it
to your dressing room.
Okay. Thanks so much.
What are you
all dressed up for?
Well, Elaine, when you're
shopping on Madison Avenue,
you don't wanna skimp
on the swank.
I like your little bag.
Huh?
Oh, hey, look at this.
This is a super-hydrating,
triple-action moisturizer.
Wait until that Uma
smells this UVA.
Hey, Kramer.
Hey, Bania.
What's happening?
I'm looking for a new suit.
I can't find anything I like.
That's a nice suit.
Well, thank you.
Did you get that here?
No, no, no.
This is vintage.
They don't make
this stuff anymore.
You're telling me.
I sure am.
It's hard for me
to find pants that--
That don't make
you look high-waisted?
Yes.
Me too.
What size are you?
Uh, 42.
Forty-two?
That's what I am now.
I been working out.
I'm huge.
How'd you like to sell it?
Make me an offer.
One hundred bucks.
Surely you jest?
One seventy-five?
Look at the stitching.
This is old-world
craftsmanship.
Three hundred dollars.
Sold. Follow me into
the dressing room.
You'll throw the shirt in?
Bania, you're killing me.
Hey, that's the women's
dressing room.
There's nothing in there
that I haven't seen before.
Mr. Steinbrenner,
can I talk to you for a second?
Yes, yes, George.
Can you talk to me for a second?
Of course, you can.
I'm a very accessible man.
I just wanna say,
you're doing great work
on that canola oil stuff.
Well, you know,
to be honest, sir,
my new secretary, Ada,
came up with that one.
Ada? Ada. I like
that name, George.
She supports
her whole family.
Is that a fact,
George.
Yes. In fact, her mother's
in the hospital right now.
It's some kind of
diverticulitis.
I had a bout of that
myself one time.
It knocked me
right on my ass.
She can't even afford
to go out to lunch.
She-- She's been eating
in high school cafeterias.
She pretends to be a teacher.
Pathetic.
What does that cost her?
Like two and a quarter?
I was just thinking that--
She could really use
a raise.
[PHONE RINGS]
She'd be better off
making a sandwich at home
and bringing it in.
Hello?
George, will you
excuse me?
Psst. Hey!
Kramer?
What are you doing?
Listen. I need you to get me
some clothes.
What?
I just sold my suit
to Bania for a cool 300.
So go buy a new one.
At this place?
It would destroy
my whole profit margin.
So?
Listen.
Do me a favor.
Just call Jerry.
Tell him to bring me
some clothes.
Oh, God.
Hello, Willie.
Hey, Jerry.
You're dropping off?
No, but, uh, seen
any good movies lately?
You came by to ask that?
Yeah.
Specifically 9:30 shows.
Seen any good 9:30 shows
at the Paragon, Willie?
What are you getting at?
I saw you the other night
stepping out
with my hound's tooth jacket.
Jerry, that's a breach
of the dry-cleaner's code.
You need a code to tell you
not to wear people's clothes?
I wasn't wearing
your jacket.
Jerry, your imagining--
Am I imagining this?
Found that little cutie
in the pocket.
Jerry, I--
Yeah, well, now that we
understand each other,
I'll be taking
my business elsewhere.
And I want my mother's
fur coat back too.
Jerry, come on.
Now.
Now?
Yeah, I want that coat.
Well, I--
Where's the ticket?
Oh, Kramer.
Wait-- Wait a minute.
You mean to tell me
that you don't have a ticket
for the coat?
No, not on me.
Well, I-- I need to see
that ticket.
Why? I got my cleaning
before without a ticket.
Yeah, but this is different.
Those fur storage
warehouses are huge.
You can't get anything
without a number.
All right.
I'll be back.
Yeah, it looks good here,
but what does that mean?
So, uh, do you want it?
I don't know.
I have to think about it.
I need a non-partisan mirror.
ADA:
I can't thank you enough, Mr. Costanza.
I'm so grateful.
Yes, well, I sat down
with Mr. Steinbrenner.
I told him you have been
doing great work.
I said that you deserved a raise
and if you didn't get it,
that I was leaving.
It was just so generous.
Oh, well, don't worry about it.
He's got plenty of money.
Oh, I know.
But 25,000?
So you got
a $25,000-a-year raise?
Yes.
Oh, I tell you.
Mr. Steinbrenner was--
You know, you're--
You're making more than I am.
I am?
A secretary cannot make
more than her boss.
Well, apparently they can.
Oh, this is insanity.
I'm not this hippy.
Hey. Hey, what do you
think of this?
You'll never pull it off.
Hey, what's going on in there?
Excuse me. Could you tell me
where I could find,
like, women's
moisturizer lotions?
This woman's been in there
for over an hour.
Excuse me, miss.
Is everything okay in there?
KRAMER:
Yeah.
Kramer?
Jerry.
You got my clothes?
What clothes?
Didn't Elaine
call you?
No.
Well, what are you
doing here?
What am I doing here?
You're in the women's
dressing room.
I need that ticket stub
back so I can get
my mother's fur coat out.
Oh, the stub.
Yeah. I left it
in my-- My pants.
Where are your pants?
Well-- I sold them
to Bania.
What? You sold your pants
to Bania?
Let me in.
Why did you sell
your pants to Bania?
I had Uma Thurman's number
written on that stub.
I lost Uma's number.
Where are your clothes?
I told you.
I sold them to Bania.
You mean what you were wearing?
Yeah.
How'd you expect
to get out of here?
Well, I didn't
think ahead.
This isn't gonna work
for me.
So if you could show me
something else.
No.
No?
No, because you're
taking that one.
I am?
Yes.
You wore it outside.
That's preposterous.
I suppose that salt stain came
from all the snow in the store.
Shall I wrap it,
or will you wear it out?
No, you can wrap it.
Kramer, you still in there?
JERRY:
Elaine?
Jerry?
Where's Kramer?
KRAMER:
Bania?
Kramer?
JERRY:
I'm going out.
Jerry.
Bania.
Kramer, I want my money back
for this suit.
Your nancy-boy cream leaked
all over the pocket.
Suits ruined.
Well, you're not getting
any money back.
Jerry, come back.
Excuse me.
Uma's number's
on that ticket.
Never mind Uma. I need to get
my mother's fur coat back.
Why don't you just give him
the money for the suit.
I'm not gonna give him
$300 now for a suit
with moisturizer cream
all over it.
I got an idea.
What?
I can't believe
I'm gonna do this.
JERRY: Can I talk to you
for a second?
How's everything going?
Pretty good.
Yeah.
Well, see,
the thing of it is,
I'm in a bit
of an awkward position here
because I don't wanna get
between you two guys,
but...I need
a dry-cleaning ticket
that's in the pocket
of those pants.
Well, all you gotta do is tell
Kramer to give me my money back
and you'll get your ticket.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
Well, uh, tell you what
I will do, Bania.
You give me the ticket,
and, uh, I will take you out
for a nice dinner.
Can we go back to Mendy's?
You wanna go to Mendy's,
I'll take you to Mendy's.
Twice.
I wanna go twice.
All right, let's
be reasonable, Bania.
I'm taking you out
for a nice dinner.
All I want is a ticket
from that pocket.
I think that's
a pretty good deal.
Two Mendy's.
All right.
Just give me the ticket.
There you go.
Ohh!
But, Mr. Steinbrenner,
how can I be expected to perform
my job properly,
knowing that my subordinate
is making more money than I am?
With all due respect, sir,
it's out of whack.
Uh-huh. I understand
what you're saying.
I know what it's like
to be financially strapped.
When I was a young man,
I used to hitchhike
to work.
One time I got picked up
by a bakery truck.
You think that stuff
smells good?
Try being cooped up in the back
of one of those babies.
I couldn't look at a doughnut
for the next two years.
Well, not that I was ever
one for the sweets.
Sure, I like a cupcake now
and then like everybody else.
You know, I like it when
they have a little cream
on the inside.
It's a surprise. That's good.
Plus the chocolate ones
are good too.
Sometimes, I just can't
even make up my mind.
A lot of times,
I'll mix the two together,
make a vanilla fudge.
Let me in.
It's me.
Here.
You don't know what
this is costing me.
All right.
Nice work.
Where's Uma's number?
The moisturizer smudged out
the phone number.
The dry-cleaning number's
gone too.
It must have been
the botanical extracts.
Give me that.
Hey, Bania.
The dinner's off.
The ticket's no good.
The numbers are all smudged out.
You trying to get
out of Mendy's?
You can't do that.
The ticket is worthless.
You promised me.
Hey. Isn't that
my mother's fur coat?
No, it's not.
It is.
Give me that back.
[CLAMORING]
Do you think the dry-cleaner's
your own personal closet?
Hey, Donna. Think you can get
the salt stain out of this?
Let me see.
Piece of cake.
Bring it in.
What size is it?
Mmm. This soup
is great.
Yeah, it's very good.
I told you Mendy's had
the best pea soup.
The best, Jerry, the best.
Are you enjoying it?
Yeah. I'm having
a wonderful time.
Wait until you try
the swordfish.
You know, Jerry,
I was thinking.
For our next meal, do you think
we should come here,
or should we go someplace else?
You know,
it has its pros and cons.
On the one hand, here,
you're guaranteed a great meal.
On the other hand--
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
This would be good,
but it would be the same.
But if we go someplace else,
it would be different,
but it might not be as good.
It's a gamble.
I get it.
Yeah. Well, let's hurry up
and eat.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm meeting a woman for a drink.
Oh, and who might that be?
Some woman named Uma.
I got her number off that ticket
before it was smudged.
Hope she's good-looking.
If you are a waiter
or a waitress
and you ever see me
in a restaurant,
I'm telling you right now,
I don't wanna hear
about the specials.
I don't wanna know
I'm sick of the specials.
I hate the specials.
My feeling is, if the specials
were so special,
they'd be on the menu.
You know what's
special about them?
They don't know
if anybody likes it.
They always have those overly
creative descriptions
of the specials, too, you know.
The veal is
lightly slapped...
and then sequestered
in a one-bedroom suite,
with a white wine intravenous.