[♪]
Oh, hi.
A hundred episodes.
That's a lot.
During the course of which
George, Elaine, Kramer, and I
have had many experiences,
both positive and negative.
Well, mostly negative.
There have been
some relationships
that haven't worked out.
Ambitions that were
unfulfilled.
Hopes dashed.
Some property damage.
Hurt feelings.
I know one guy got deported.
Physical injury and...
all right,
maybe even a death or two.
But we've persevered,
because we're people.
Real TV people.
And for 30 minutes a week,
that's pretty important to us.
So if you're joining us late,
here's some highlights
from what's happened so far.
Why don't they have salsa
on the table?
What do you need salsa for?
Salsa is now the number-one
condiment in America.
Do you know why?
Because people like
to say "salsa."
Excuse me.
Do you have any salsa?
We need more salsa.
Where's the salsa? No salsa?
You know, it must be
impossible for a Spanish person
to order seltzer
and not get salsa.
I wanted seltzer, not salsa.
Don't you know the difference
between seltzer and salsa?
You have the seltzer
after the salsa.
See? This should be the show.
This is the show.
What?
This. Just talkin'.
Yeah. Right.
No, I'm really serious.
I think that's a good idea.
Just talking?
Well, what's the show about?
It's about nothing.
What's that red dot
on your sweater?
Hey, didn't we come in
over there?
I thought we came in
over there.
I'm out.
What?
Yeah, I'm out.
I'm out of the contest.
No story?
No, forget the story.
But we gotta have a story.
Who says you gotta
have a story?
[PLAYING SLOW, ELEGANT MELODY]
[LAUGHS]
Four.
Seinfeld.
Four?
That will be five,
ten minutes.
Boy, do you smell
something?
Do I smell something?
What am I,
hard of smelling?
What is it?
I think it's BO.
And who's on the show?
Who are the characters?
I could be a character.
You?
Yeah, you base
a character on a me.
It's come to my attention
that you
and the cleaning woman
have engaged in
sexual intercourse
on the desk
in your office.
Who said that?
She did.
Was that wrong?
Should I not
have done that?
I tell you, I gotta plead
ignorance on this thing,
because if anyone had said
anything to me at all
when I first started here,
that that sort of thing
was frowned upon...
And who else is on the show?
Elaine could be a character.
I wonder what happened
to my fiancé?
I know he's
here somewhere.
I have lost my fiancé,
the poor baby.
[LAUGHS]
[AUSTRALIAN ACCENT]
Maybe the dingo ate your baby.
What?
The dingo ate your baby!
Kramer.
Now, he's a character.
[LAUGHS] Yeah.
The bus is outta control!
So I grab him
by the collar,
I take him out of the seat,
I get behind the wheel,
now I'm drivin' the bus.
You're Batman.
Yeah, yeah. I am Batman.
Then the mugger, he comes to,
and he starts chokin' me!
So I'm fightin' him off
with one hand,
and I kept drivin' the bus
with the other, you know.
Then I managed
to open up the door,
and I kicked him out the door,
you know, with my foot,
you know, at the next stop!
You kept makin'
all the stops?
Well, people kept ringin'
the bell!
So everybody I know
is a character on the show?
Right.
My wallet's gone!
Jerry!
Uncle Leo.
Hello!
How could you?
How could I what?
You were making out
during Schindler's List?
How long does it take
to find a bra?
What's goin' on
in there?!
You ask me to get
a pair of underwear,
I'm back
in two seconds.
You know about
the, uh, cup sizes and all?
They have different cups.
Yeah. I-I know about the cups.
You got the A...
B...
the C...
the D...
That's the biggest.
I go out for a quart of milk.
I come home
and find my son
treating his body
like it was an amusement park.
I'm a United States
postal worker.
Aren't those the guys
that always go crazy
and come back with a gun
and shoot everybody?
Sometimes.
Why is that?
Because the mail
never stops.
Every day it piles up
more and more and more,
and you gotta get it out.
But the more you get out,
the more it keeps coming in.
Then the bar-code
reader breaks,
and it's Publishers
Clearing House day!
All right,
all right.
So you're sayin',
I go into NBC
and tell them I got this idea
for a show about nothing?
We go in to NBC.
We?
Since when are you a writer?
What writer?
We're talkin' about a sitcom.
You wanna go with me to NBC?
Yeah. I think we really got
somethin' here.
What do we got?
An idea.
What idea?
An idea for the show.
I still don't know
what the idea is.
It's about nothing.
Right.
Everybody's doing
something.
We'll do nothing.
Let's go do something.
I don't wanna sit around here.
Okay.
Wanna go get something to eat?
Where do you
wanna go?
I don't care.
I'm not hungry.
We could go to one of
those cappuccino places.
They let you just sit there.
What are we gonna do there?
Talk?
We could talk.
I'll go if I don't have
to talk.
Then we'll just sit there.
Oh, wow. That's
the astronaut pen.
I heard about that.
Where did you get it?
Oh, it was a gift.
Oh, 'cause a lot of times
I write in bed,
and I have to turn and lean on
my elbow to make the pen work.
Take the pen.
Oh, no.
Go ahead.
I couldn't.
Come on. Take the pen.
I can't take it.
Do me a personal favor.
I'm not comfortable.
Take the pen!
I cannot take it.
Are you sure?
I'm positive!
Take the pen.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Gee! Boy.
Jack, what are you doing?
Stop it.
Jack,
we should go.
It was nice
meeting you.
Mmm.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks again,
Jack.
Come on!
This?
I agreed to wear this?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, when did I do that?
When we went to dinner
the other night.
What are you, crazy?
What were you talkin' about
when I went to the bathroom?
I don't know.
I couldn't understand
a word she was saying.
I was just nodding.
Pow! There you go.
Where I go?
You mean she was asking me
to wear this ridiculous shirt
on national TV and I said yes?
Yes.
Yes, you said it.
But I didn't know
what she was talking about.
I couldn't hear her.
Well, she asked you.
I-I can't wear this
puffy shirt on TV.
I mean, look at it.
It looks ridiculous.
Well, you gotta wear it now.
This pirate trend that
she's come up with, Jerry,
this is gonna be
the new look for the '90s.
You're gonna be
the first pirate.
But I don't wanna
be a pirate.
I don't understand.
Do you have my reservation?
Yes, we do.
Unfortunately,
we ran out of cars.
But the reservation
keeps the car here.
That's why you have
the reservation.
I know why
we have reservations.
I don't think you do.
If you did, I'd have a car.
So you know how to take
the reservation.
You just don't know how
to hold the reservation.
And that's really
the most important part
of the reservation,
the holding.
Anybody can just take 'em.
I think I can sum up the show
for you with one word.
Nothing!
Nothing?
What does that mean?
What did you do today?
I got up and came to work.
There's a show.
That's a show.
How is that a show?
Well, uh, m-maybe
something happens to you
on the way to work.
No. No. No!
Nothing happens!
Well, something happens.
Well, why am I watching it?
Because it's on TV.
Not yet.
[♪]
I'm telling you,
she's good-looking.
What about the body?
What kinda body?
Good body.
Nice body.
How nice?
Nice.
Just nice?
Pretty nice.
Really good?
Really, very nice and good.
What about person--?
Good personality.
Funny.
Bright.
Smarter than me? I don't want
anyone smarter than me.
How could she be
smarter than you?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, no, he's a really, really funny guy.
What does he look like?
Pardon?
Um...
Well, he's got a lot of
character in his face.
Um, he's short.
Um, he's stocky.
He's fat.
Is that what you're saying?
That he's fat?
Powerful.
He is so powerful!
He can lift 100 pounds
right up over his head.
And, um...
What else? What else?
Oh. R-- Um...
Er-- Well...
He's-- He's kind of,
just kind of...ungh,
losing his hair.
He's bald?!
No!
No, no, no.
He's not bald.
He's balding.
So he will be bald.
Yeah.
Thick, lustrous hair
is very important to me.
"Thick, lustrous hair
is very important to me."
Is that what you said?
Yeah, that's right.
Just clarifying.
Lemme ask you this.
If you stick your hand
in the hair,
is it easy to get it out?
Do you wanna be able
to get it out,
or do you wanna not be able
to get it out?
I'd like to be able
to get it out.
I think you'll get it out.
What about the skin?
I need a good cheek.
I like a good cheek.
She's got a fine cheek.
Is there a pinkish hue?
A pinkish hue?
Yes. A rosy glow.
There's a hue.
She's got great eyebrows.
Women kill to have
her eyebrows.
Who cares about eyebrows?
Look at you.
Why don't you do something
with your life?!
Sit around here all day.
You contribute nothing
to society.
The alarm didn't go off,
it's 9:15!
You're gonna miss the plane,
[GROGGILY]
9:15?
Yeah, 9:15!
Eh, we'll never make it.
I'll leave tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Are you crazy?!
No. Now, now.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
You get dressed.
How could I be with
someone like you?
Wouldn't respect myself.
Put your pants on.
I'll go tomorrow
or the next day.
No, you have your ticket.
You have to go now.
We'll never make it.
Don't say that.
Well, it takes 45 minutes
to get--
It takes 45 minutes
to get there,
that will only leave me
5 minutes to get to the plane.
Shut up and pack!
I take it all back,
every word!
I love you!
It's not you. It's me.
You're giving me
the "it's not you,
it's me" routine?
I invented
"it's not you, it's me."
Nobody tells me
it's them, not me.
If it's anybody, it's me.
All right.
George, it's you.
You're damn right it's me.
Elaine...
Hm?
you don't know the first thing
about first base.
Oh. Well, I know something
about gettin' to first base.
And I know you'll
never be there.
The way I figure it,
I've already been there.
I plan on rounding second
tonight at around 11:00.
[LAUGHS]
Well, uh...
I'd watch the third-base coach
if I were you,
'cause I don't think
he's wavin' you in.
I guess things changed for me
on Tuesday night.
Tuesday night?
What happened
I saw your act.
My act? Wh-what does that
have to do with anything?
To be honest, it...
just didn't make it for me.
It was just so much fluff.
So, what're you saying?
You didn't like my act?
So that's it?
I can't be with someone
if I don't respect what they do.
You're a cashier.
You don't know my name,
do you?
Yes, I do.
What is it?
It rhymes with
a female body part.
What is it?
Mulva?
I think you're really sick.
I'm not sick.
You said much sicker
things than me.
I'm leaving.
So, where were we?
I was just leaving.
Right.
You were leaving.
I can't believe you sent
a woman into the sauna to do that.
That was an accident.
I think you're both
mentally ill.
Ohhh...
And by the way...
they're real,
and they're spectacular.
Why shouldn't we be able
to do that once in a while
if we want to?
I know!
I mean, really,
what is the big deal?
We go in there,
we're in there
for a while,
and then we come back
out here.
That's not complicated.
It's almost stupid
if we didn't.
It's moronic!
Absurd!
Of course...
I guess, maybe, some little
problems could arise.
Ah, you know,
there are always a few.
I mean, if anything happened,
and we couldn't be friends
the way we are now...
that would really be bad.
Devastating.
Because this...
is very good.
And that would be good.
That would be good too.
The idea is to combine
the this...
and the that...
but this cannot
be disturbed.
Yeah. We-- We--
We just wanna take this...
and...
add that.
But of course,
we have to figure out a way
to avoid the things that cause
the little problems.
Mmm.
Maybe some rules or something.
Huh.
For example...
now, I call you
whenever I am inclined
and vice versa.
Right.
But if we did that,
we might feel...
a certain obligation to call.
Oh-- Well, why should that be?
Oh! I have an idea.
I have an idea.
No calls the day after that.
Beautiful.
Let's make it a rule.
All right, sir.
Now, here's
another little rule.
Yeah.
When we see each other now,
we retire
to our separate quarters.
But sometimes, when people
get involved with that,
they feel...
pressure to...
sleep over...
when that is not really sleep.
Sleep is separate from that,
and I don't see
why sleep got all tied up
and connected...
with that.
Okay. Okay.
Rule number two:
spending the night is optional.
Well, now we're gettin'
somewhere.
I slept with Elaine
last night.
Oxygen.
I need some oxygen.
I thought you'd like that.
Oh, this is huge.
I know.
All right.
Okay. Let's go. Details.
No, I can't give details.
No details?
I'm not in the mood.
You asked me here
to have lunch,
tell me you slept with Elaine,
and then say you're not
in the mood for details.
Now, you listen to me.
I want details,
and I want them right now.
I don't have a job.
I have no place to go.
You're not in the mood?
Well, you get in the mood!
I was at
the unemployment office,
and I told them I was
very close
to getting a job
with Vandelay Industries.
and I gave them
your phone number.
So now,
when the phone rings,
you have to answer
"Vandelay Industries."
I'm Vandelay Industries?
Right.
What is that?
You're in latex.
Latex.
Yes.
And what do I do with latex?
I don't know.
You manufacture it.
Right here,
in this little apartment?
And what do I say about you?
You're considering hiring me
for your latex salesman.
I'm gonna hire you
as my latex salesman?
Right.
[LAUGHS]
I don't think so.
Man, I'm tellin' you
this pizza idea
is really gonna happen.
This is the thing
where you go,
and you have to make
your own pizza?
Yeah. We give you the dough.
You smash it. You pound it.
You fling it
up in the air.
And then you get to
put your sauce,
and you get to sprinkle
your cheese, and then...
you slide it
into the oven!
You know, you have to know
how to do that.
You can't have people
shoving their arms
into a 600-degree oven.
It's all supervised.
Oh, well.
Tolstoy used to write
in the village square.
The faces inspired him.
Although, one wonders
if War and Peace
would have been as highly
acclaimed as it was
had it been published
under it's original title,
War: What Is It Good For?
What?
Yeah, Mr. Lippman.
It was his mistress who
insisted that he call it War and Peace.
Elaine.
War: What Is It Good For?
♪ Absolutely nothin'
Huh! ♪
If I see her, what do I say
that I'm doing here?
Well, you came to see me.
I work in the building.
What do you do?
I'm an architect.
You're an architect?
I'm not?
I don't see architecture
coming from you.
We'll make our choice
in a few days,
and we'll let you know.
I have no chance, do I?
No.
You know I always wanted
to pretend
that I was an architect.
What do you do?
I'm an architect.
Have you designed
any buildings in New York?
Have you seen the new addition
to the Guggenheim?
You did that?
Yep, yep.
You know, it didn't take
very long either.
The beauty of my book is,
if you don't have
a coffee table,
it turns into a coffee table.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
Isn't that fabulous?
Look at this!
What-delay industries?
No.
GEORGE:
"Vandelay," say "Vandelay."
No. No, you're
way, way, way off.
What?
"Vandelay"!
Say--!
Vandelay Industries.
No problem.
And you wanna be
my latex salesman.
I think Superman probably has
a very good sense of humor.
I never heard him
say anything really funny.
He's got super strength,
super speed.
I'm sure he's got super humor.
Either you're born with
a sense of humor, or you're not.
It's not gonna change.
Even if you go from
the red sun of Krypton
all the way to the yellow sun
of the Earth.
Why?
Why would that
one area of his mind
not be affected by
the yellow sun of the Earth?
I don't know,
but he ain't funny.
What's today.
It's Thursday.
Really?
It feels like Tuesday.
Tuesday has no feel.
Monday has a feel.
Friday has a feel.
Sunday has a feel.
I feel Tuesday and Wednesday.
All right, shut up
the both of you.
You double dipped the chip.
Double dipped?
Wh-what are you
talkin' about?
You dipped the chip,
you took a bite...
and you dipped again.
So?
That's like putting your whole
mouth right in the dip.
Look.
From now on,
when you take a chip,
just take one dip
and end it!
Could I offer you
something to drink?
Okay, yeah.
I'll have a--
Do you have
a decaf cappuccino?
I don't think we have that.
Well, that's a little strange.
Uh, why does that surprise
you?
Well, it's...
It's a very popular drink.
This is an office.
That's true.
Magellan?
You like Magellan?
Oh, yeah.
My favorite explorer.
Around the world.
Come on.
Who do you like?
I like de Soto.
De Soto? What did he do?
Discovered the Mississippi.
Oh, yeah, like they wouldn't
have found that anyway.
I was talkin' to this guy,
you know,
and I just happened to throw
my purse on the sofa,
and my diaphragm goes
flying out.
So I just froze,
you know.
Ahhh!
Staring at my diaphragm,
you know.
It's just lying there.
So then this woman,
the one who sold me
this hair thing,
she grabbed it
before the guy noticed.
So I mean,
big deal, right?
So I carry around
my diaphragm.
Who doesn't?
I mean, like
it's a big, big secret
that women carry around
their diaphragms.
You never know when
you're gonna need it, right?
[SIGHS]
I hate Keith Hernandez.
Hate him.
I despise him.
Why?
NEWMAN: Why?
I'll tell you why.
Let me tell her.
You can't tell her.
You always tell it.
All right, tell it.
Ah, you just tell it.
June 14th, 1987.
Mets-Phillies.
We're enjoying
a beautiful afternoon
in the right-field stands
when a crucial
Hernandez error
opens the door to
a five-run Phillies 9th.
Cost the Mets the game.
Our day was ruined.
There was a lot of people,
you know.
They were waiting by
the players parking lot.
Now, we're comin'
down the ramp.
Newman was in front of me.
Hernandez was coming
toward us.
As he passes us,
Newman turns and says,
"Nice game,
pretty boy."
Hernandez continued past us
up the ramp.
Then, a second later,
something happened
that changed us
in a very deep and profound
way from that day forward.
What was it?
He spit on us.
Then I screamed out,
"I'm hit!"
Then I turned,
and the spit ricocheted
off him and it hit me.
Wow.
What a story.
Unfortunately,
the immutable laws of physics
contradict the whole premise
of your account.
Allow me to reconstruct this,
if I may, for Miss Benes,
as I've heard this story
a number of times.
Newman, Kramer,
if you'll indulge me.
According to your story,
Hernandez passes you
and starts walking up the ramp.
Mm-hmm.
Then, you say, you were struck...
...on the right temple.
The spit then proceeds
to ricochet off the temple,
striking Newman between
the third and the forth rib.
The spit then came
off the rib,
made a right turn,
hitting Newman
in the right wrist,
causing him to drop
his baseball cap.
The spit then splashed
off the wrist,
pauses in midair,
mind you...
makes a left turn,
and lands on
Newman's left thigh.
That is one magic loogie.
Story is the foundation
of all entertainment.
And people really have to care
about the characters.
Yeah. Forget about care. Love.
They have to love
the characters.
Now get the hell out
of my house.
Quiet!
You shut up.
As of now, you're banned
from the store. You're banned!
It's a pizza the moment you
put your fists in the dough.
I have a hair on my tongue.
Can't get it off.
You know how much I hate that?
Soup's not a meal.
You're supposed
to buy me a meal.
Yeah, well, just keep out
of my business, you big ape.
Who you callin'
"big ape"?
I'm calling you an ape.
Yeah, come on.
All right.
Break it up, break it up.
Come on, you two.
Just cut it out now.
But you put on a pair of shoes
when you walk
into the New York
Public Library, fella.
We had a funny guy
with us in Korea.
A tail gunner.
They blew his brains out
all over the Pacific.
There's nothin' funny
about that.
We will annex Poland
by the spring at any cost!
And our stock will rise high!
You may think
you're an idiot,
but with all due respect,
I'm a much bigger idiot
than you are.
Listen.
Don't insult me, my friend.
Remember who you're
talking to.
No one's a bigger idiot
than me.
Am I a hipster doofus?
No.
Said I'm not good-lookin'
enough for her.
Not good-looking.
Jerry, look at me.
Look at my face, huh.
Am I beautiful?
George, am I beautiful?
You're very attractive.
Yeah!
Is it possible
I'm not as attractive
as I think I am?
We're not gay.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
No, of course not.
I mean, it's fine if that's
who you are. Absolutely.
I mean,I have many gay friends
My father's gay.
Look, I--
I know what I heard.
Heard?
It was a joke.
Look, you wanna have
sex right now?
Do you wanna have
sex with me right now?
Let's go!
Come on!
Let's go, baby!
Hey, come on.
Let's go.
I thought we were
gonna take a steam.
No, I don't want any steam.
No. No steam.
Well, I don't wanna sit
there naked all by myself.
You fake?
On occasion.
And the guy never knows?
No.
How could he not know that?
[SENSUALLY]
Because I was good.
I guess after
that many beers,
he's probably
a little groggy anyway.
[ALL LAUGH]
Well...
you didn't know.
What's that?
You didn't know.
Are you saying--?
Ahem, I think I'll have
a piece of cake.
With me?
Well...
You faked with me?
Yeah.
Yes.
No.
You faked it.
I faked it.
That whole thing,
the whole production,
it was all an act.
Not bad, huh?
What about the breathing,
the panting, the moaning,
the screaming?
Fake, fake, fake, fake.
I'm disturbed.
I'm depressed.
I'm inadequate.
I got it all!
Can't you see what's happened?
I've become George.
Don't say that.
It's true.
I'm George.
I'm George!
Tuna on toast, coleslaw,
cup of coffee.
Yeah.
No, no.
No, wait a minute.
I always have
tuna on toast.
Nothing's every worked out
for me with tuna on toast.
I want the complete opposite
of tuna on toast.
Chicken salad on rye...
untoasted...
with a side of potato salad...
and a cup of tea! Ha-ha!
Well, there's no telling
what can happen from this.
You know, chicken salad's
not the opposite of tuna.
Salmon's the opposite of tuna,
'cause salmon swim
against the current,
and the tuna swim with it.
Good for the tuna.
Uh, George.
You know that woman
just looked at you.
GEORGE:
So what?
What am I supposed to do?
Go talk to her.
Elaine...
bald men with no jobs
and no money
who live with their parents
don't approach strange women.
Well, here's your chance
to try the opposite.
Instead of tuna salad
and being intimidated by women,
chicken salad
and goin' right up to 'em.
Yeah, I should do
the opposite, I should.
If every instinct
you have is wrong,
then the opposite
would have to be right.
Yes.
I will do the opposite.
I used to sit here
and do nothing
and regret it
for the rest of the day.
So now I will do the opposite,
and I will do something.
Excuse me,
uh, I couldn't help
but notice
that you were looking
in my direction.
Oh, yes, I was.
You just ordered
the same exact lunch as me.
My name is George.
I'm unemployed,
and I live with my parents.
I'm Victoria. Hi.
Boy, these pretzels
are makin' me thirsty!
These pretzels
are makin' me thirsty.
These pretzels...
are making me thirsty!
Boy, I'm really startin'
to dislike the Drake.
Hate the Drake.
[SNEEZES]
You are soooo good-lookin'.
You can't believe her,
she's one of these low talkers.
You know,
because he's a high talker.
He's nice.
Bit of a close talker.
How 'bout you, Jerry?
I'm swamped.
Are you sure?
You could examine
the artwork up close.
ELAINE:
I don't have a square to spare.
I can't spare a square.
I need hands.
I have no hands.
[WHISPERING]
Newman! Newman! Newman!
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
So you're still master
of your domain.
Yes. Master of my domain.
I am king of the county.
Lord of the manor.
I'm queen of the castle.
You mean...shrinkage?
Yes.
Significant shrinkage.
So you feel you were
shortchanged.
Yes.
If she thinks that's me,
she's under
a complete misapprehension.
So, what's the difference?
What if she discusses it
with Jane?
Oh, she's not gonna tell Jane.
Couldn't you tell her
about the shrinkage factor?
No, I'm not gonna tell her
about your shrinkage.
Besides, I... I think women
know about shrinkage.
How do women know
about shrinkage?
Isn't it common knowledge?
Aw...
Elaine!
Get-- Come--
What?
Do women know
about shrinkage?
What do you mean,
like laundry?
No.
Like when a man goes
swimming...afterwards...
It shrinks?
Like a frightened turtle.
Why does it shrink?
It just does.
I don't know how you guys walk
around with those things.
GEORGE:
Um, about the script.
The script.
Now, I've read this thing
three times.
And every time I read it...
What?
Excuse me for a second.
W-would you like
a Pepto-Bismol?
I keep 'em
in my wallet.
Do you think he liked it?
[RETCHING]
I'm not sure.
Yeah!
[SINGING OPERATICALLY
IN ITALIAN]
Waaaaaaah!
The air conditioner!
[DOG BARKING, YELPS]
My mother caught me.
Caught you? Doin' what?
You know...
I was alone...
You mean--?
Uh-huh.
[LAUGHS]
She caught you?
Where?
I stopped by the house
to drop the car off,
and I went inside
for a few minutes.
Nobody was there.
They're supposed
to be working.
My mother had
a Glamour magazine.
I started leafing
through it.
Glamour?
[LAUGHS]
So one thing
led to another.
So, what did she do?
First she screams, "George,
what are you doing?! My God!"
Then it looked like
she was gonna faint.
She started clutchin'
the wall, tryin' to hang onto it.
I didn't know whether
to try and keep her from fallin' or zip up.
What did you do?
I zipped up.
So, she fell?
Yeah.
Well, I couldn't run
over there the way I was.
No, I guess you couldn't
have done that.
I wouldn't think so.
So, she fell,
and then she starts screaming,
"My back, my back!"
So I picked her up,
I took her to the hospital.
[LAUGHS]
Oh. How is she?
She's in traction.
I'm sorry.
It's not funny, Elaine.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's serious.
Her back went out, she's gotta
be there for a couple of days.
Glamour?
[LAUGHS]
I'll tell you this though.
I am never doing...
that again.
What?
You mean, in your mother's
house, or all together?
All together.
Oh, gimme a break.
Yeah, right.
What? You don't
think I can?
No chance.
You think
you could?
Well, I know I could
hold out longer than you.
Care to make it
interesting?
Sure. How much?
Hundred dollars.
You're on.
Wait a second.
Count me in on this.
You?
Yeah.
You'll be out before
we get the check.
I wanna be
in on this too.
Oh, no.
No. No, no.
Not a level playing field.
Why?
It's a whole different thing.
What? Why?
Because you're a woman.
So what?
It's easier for a woman
not to do it than a man.
We have to do it.
It's part of our lifestyle.
It's like, uh, shaving.
Oh, that is such bologna.
I shave my legs.
Not every day.
All right,
you want to be in?
Yeah.
You gotta give us odds.
At least two to one.
You gotta put up $200.
No, $1000.
No, I'll put up $150.
All right.
You're in for $150.
Okay, $150.
All right, now.
How we gonna monitor this?
Well, obviously we all
know each other very well.
I'm sure
we'll all feel comfortable
within the confines
of the honor system.
All right. Come on.
ALL:
Yeah!
Fire!
[ALL SCREAMING]
We have sacrificed
everything,
all for the sake
of our little...
bubble boy.
Excuse me.
Oh, no. Here.
It's amazing how many
beautiful women live in New York.
Well, you're as pretty
as any of them.
Just need a nose job.
♪ Yankee bean ♪
♪ I like my Yankee beans ♪
In fact, I hate anyone
that ever had a pony
when they were growin' up.
I had a pony.
Well, I...didn't, uh...
When I was a little girl
in Poland,
we all had ponies.
My sister had pony.
My cousin had pony.
So, what's wrong with that?
Nothing, nothing at all.
He was a beautiful pony.
And I loved him.
Well, I'm sure you did.
Who wouldn't love a pony?
Who wouldn't love a person
that had a pony?
You.
You said so.
That's
my father's cabin.
I just realized,
you never gave me back
the change from the tolls.
So you heard
that I was in a car accident
and then decided to stop off
for some Jujyfruit?
Well...
the counter, ahem,
was right there.
I didn't know
she had a pony.
Who figures an immigrant's
gonna have a pony?
I mean, in all
the pictures I saw
of immigrants on boats
comin' into New York Harbor...
I never saw one of them
sittin' on a pony.
But why would anyone
come here if they had a pony?
Who leaves a country
packed with ponies
to come to
a non-pony country?
It doesn't make sense.
Now we'll open
the peritoneal cavity,
exposing the body's
internal organs.
What are you eating?
Junior Mints.
You want one?
No.
I can't see.
Psst!
Could you get...?
Where'd you get those?
In the machine.
Do you want one?
No.
Here.
Take one.
I don't want one.
No, they're good.
Take one.
I don't want any.
Just take one.
No, Kramer.
Stop it.
[SPLAT]
It's a Junior Mint.
Drake's Coffee Cake.
Snapple?
No, thanks.
PEZ?
Uh, no.
Do you have a box
of Jujyfruits?
Clark Bar.
I love Yoo-hoo.
Ooh, Chunkys.
Chocolate babka.
It's Gore-Tex.
Ooh, cashmere?
No, Gore-Tex.
Who's gonna turn down
a Junior Mint?
It's chocolate,
it's peppermint.
It's delicious!
That's true.
It's very refreshing!
What's goin' on
over here?
There's a beached whale.
She's dying.
MAN:
Is anyone here a marine biologist?
GEORGE:
The sea was angry that day, my friends.
Like an old man trying to
send back soup in a deli.
I got about 50 feet out,
when suddenly...
the great beast appeared
before me.
I tell you, he was 10 stories
high if he was a foot.
As if sensing my presence,
he let out a great bellow.
I said, "Easy, big fella."
And then... as I watched him
struggling, I realized
that something was
obstructing its breathing.
From where I was standing,
I could see directly into
the eye of the great fish.
Mammal.
Whatever.
Well, what did
you do next?
Well, then,
from out of nowhere,
a huge tidal wave lifted me,
tossed me like a cork,
and I found myself
right on top of him,
face-to-face
with the blowhole!
I-- I could barely see
from the waves
crashing down upon me,
but I knew
something was there.
So I reached my hand in,
felt around,
and pulled out
the obstruction!
What is that,
a Titleist?
A hole in one, huh?
So we go in to NBC.
We tell 'em we got an idea
for a show about nothing.
Exactly.
They say,
"What's your show about?"
I say, "nothing."
There you go.
I think you may have
something here.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Look, why don't you two just
go to the movies by yourself?
I'm not in the mood.
Well, me either.
I'm goin' to Sky Burger.
So you're not goin'?
You don't need us.
Well, I can't go
to a bad movie by myself.
What, am I gonna make
sarcastic remarks to strangers?
Oh, I guess
I'll just go to my uncle's.
Should we tell him
we're leaving?
What for?
Let's just get outta here.
Seinfeld, four!