The thing I admire most
about the Chinese
is that they're hanging
in there with the chopsticks.
Because, if you think about it,
you know they've seen
the fork by now.
I'm sure they've seen the spoon.
They're going,
"Yah...they're okay.
We're gonna stay
with the sticks."
I mean, I don't know
how they missed it.
Thousands of years ago,
a Chinese farmer gets up,
has his breakfast
with the chopstick,
goes out and works all day
in the field with a shovel.
Hello?
Shovel?
Not going out there
plowing 40 acres
with a couple of pool cues.
Good shave today.
Don't worry, Jerry,
I can manage these bags.
Really, I'm fine.
I think I'll let my side burns
grow in a little.
Can we rest here a second?
Yeah, I guess.
So, how's Noreen?
She got a new
boyfriend: Paul.
Already?
That was fast.
I assume he's not
a high talker?
No, but he has
the worst habit.
Whenever he answers the phone,
he won't put Noreen right on.
You go through, like,
10 minutes of chitchat.
A long talker.
Yes.
He is so boring
that now, whenever he answers
the phone, I just hang up.
All right, let's move it out.
Hey, isn't that
George's father?
ELAINE:
Oh, yeah, it is.
Should we say hello?
I've never seen him
in Manhattan before. It's weird.
It's so out of context.
That man he's with...
Is he wearing a cape?
I believe he is
wearing a cape.
Why is Mr. Costanza
with a man in a cape?
Well, it is good cape
weather, cool, breezy.
Why a cape?
Who wears a cape?
Where do you even
get a cape?
You're right.
It is strange.
In fact, let's cross to
the other side of the street.
Cover me.
Just plop it
on the counter there.
Oh, I got a message.
GEORGE:
Hey. It's George.
I got nothing to say.
[BEEPS]
That sounds urgent.
Let me call him back.
Hello?
Who is this?
Donna Chang?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must have dialed
the wrong number.
Donna Chang?
I should've talked.
I love Chinese women.
Isn't that a little racist?
If I like their race,
how can that be racist?
Hello? Is this
Donna Chang again?
Yes, I am calling George.
Oh, the lines are crossed.
You're getting his calls.
Well, what do you know?
So listen...
I'm going through
this stuff like water.
Who you talking to?
He's on with
a Chinese woman.
Ooh, ooh, I dig
Asian women.
You got a comfort
problem there?
No, I think these
Jockeys shrunk.
I thought you wore
silk underwear?
No... Well, you know,
I wore them for about a month,
but I couldn't
stick with it.
I need the secure
packaging of Jockeys.
My boys need a house.
That's nice.
Kramer, you know, if you
ever want to have kids,
you shouldn't wear briefs.
Boxers are better
for your sperm count.
Sperm count?
Well, how many sperm
should I have?
A lot.
JERRY:
I got a date.
With the Chinese
woman?
She knew who I was.
She saw me
at a club one time.
My first date ever
with the Pacific Rim.
I'm very excited.
Jerry, you ever have
your sperm count checked?
No, why should I?
I wear boxers.
You ever get
a woman pregnant?
I'm sorry, Kramer, those records
are permanently sealed.
What would you say if I told you
I never impregnated a woman.
Really?
You never slipped one fast past
the goalie in all these years?
I'm surprised. You've slept
with a lot of women.
A lot of women!
You think maybe I'm...depleted?
I'm sure you're not
totally depleted.
Yeah, but what if I am?
I'm the last male Kramer.
We're facing extinction.
Go to a fertility clinic.
Have your sperm count checked.
Yeah, but then I'd have to--
Well, you know...
Into a cup,
in the middle of the day.
Does that conflict
with your regular schedule?
All right, I'm gonna
try Noreen again.
I am very excited
about this date.
We're going
to Hunan Balcony.
She's Chinese, so you
suggest Chinese food?
She suggested it.
I thought Chinese
don't eat Chinese.
She's very
assimilated.
MAN'S VOICE:
Hello?
Paul again?
You can't get one ring past him.
Hey, hey, you don't
call me back?
I tried. Your line's crossed
with a Chinese woman.
Huh?
George, we saw your father
on the street before.
What's he doing
in the city today?
You didn't ask him?
You didn't say hello?
Well, he was
with someone.
A man...in a cape.
Why was he wearing a cape?
Was my father wearing a cape?
No. Jacket and tie,
no cape.
Huh.
Cape.
What was a man with a cape
doing with my father?
What was my father doing
with a man in a cape?
Why a cape?
The results of
your sperm test are in.
Oh?
Are you planning
to start a family?
Yes, I would like to very much.
I'm low, aren't I?
I can feel it.
Yes, I'm afraid
you're a little low.
Oh, man.
It's over.
The Kramer name is finished.
I'm never
gonna procreate, huh?
That's not necessarily true.
There are measures you can take
to improve your fertility.
What? What? You tell me.
I'll do anything.
C'mon, Doc, tell me.
First thing, you should
wear boxer shorts.
All the time?
All the time.
You have to get off
Jockeys right away.
But I've always
worn Jockeys.
ELAINE:
Hi, Paul. It's Elaine calling.
Yeah, I'm calling from
a car phone,
So I don't really
have time to talk.
Is-- Is, uh, Noreen there?
Oh, she's not?
Okay, great.
Well, you can just
tell her I called, then--
Well, yes, it has been
unseasonably cool lately.
Okay, well, look, I'm pulling up
to the building now,
so I'm gonna--
Yeah, I do too.
Um, look, Paul, the car seems
to be running out of gas.
I'm gonna have to
get off the phone.
Let me know when everyone
has arrived, sir.
Yes, I will.
Do you mind?
No, go ahead.
I secondhand smoke
two packs a day.
Jerry?
Excuse me?
Hi. Sorry
I'm late.
Who are you?
I'm Donna Chang.
What do you mean?
I mean I'm Donna Chang.
You're Donna Chang?
Did you think I was Chinese?
Oh, no, because of the Chang?
Actually, the family name
wasn't originally Chang.
I didn't think so.
Used to be Changstein.
ELAINE:
She's not Chinese?
No, not Chinese.
Not even Asian.
So, what is she?
Well, she's...like you.
Oh, how disappointed
you must have been.
It's false
advertising, see?
And the thing is,
I think she likes
people thinking
she's Chinese.
She suggests
Chinese food.
She always introduces
herself as Donna Chang.
So then why are you
seeing her again?
Well, she is a woman.
I spoke to Paul and Noreen.
They might be breaking up.
Really?
Well, maybe.
Wouldn't it be funny if
Paul and Noreen broke up
because you kept
hanging up on him?
What do you mean?
You know, if Paul thought
it was some guy hanging up
because he was having
an affair with Noreen.
Here, take
my Jockey shorts.
Whoa!
Get outta here!
You gotta help me. I have
to get off Jockey shorts.
Low sperm count?
Very low.
C'mon, Jerry,
take them.
No, no, I don't
want them.
Jerry, you gotta
help me.
If I have one pair in
my house, I'll wear them!
Look, I don't
want them.
All it takes is one pair!
I won't be able to sleep
if those are in the house.
These boxers!
How do you wear
these things?
They're bagging up.
they're rising here.
And there's nothing
holding me in place.
I'm flipping!
I'm flopping!
What am I gonna do?
Jerry, I'm going crazy
in these things.
Well, I'm gonna
have to move now.
FRANK:
You know what I like about Manhattan?
There's no mosquitoes.
Plenty of mosquitoes.
Queens is full of mosquitoes.
So, Dad--
Gnats, too,
if I'm not mistaken.
Dad, I heard you were
in the city the other day.
Your mother has to tell
you every move I make?
Jerry and Elaine saw you.
They didn't say hello?
They were in a rush.
They couldn't
just say hello?!
Ahh, the hell with them.
They said you were with some guy
who was wearing a cape.
Elaine, I could see
not saying hello.
She's very...
what's the word?
Supercilious.
So, Dad--
How could Jerry
not say hello?!
Did they uncross
the lines yet?
No, they can't
find the problem.
It's really
getting ridicurous.
Did you say "ridicurous"?
Ridiculous.
I thought you said...
ridicurous.
What are you
doing here?
Oh, I wanted to talk to you.
Sorry, I didn't know
you had company.
Oh, no, no.
Hi, I'm George.
Oh! Hi,
I'm Donna Chang.
I just spoke
to your mother before.
You spoke to my mother?
She was trying
to call you, but--
The rines are crossed?
Did you say "the rines
are crossed?"
Did I?
George, she's so sweet.
We talked for an hour.
Anyway, I'm really sorry.
Sorry?
Why sorry?
What do you have
to be sorry about?
Well, she told me she and your
father are getting divorced.
ELAINE:
Boy, divorce.
That's really too bad.
Yeah.
It's a shame his parents didn't
get divorced 30 years ago.
He could have been normal.
GEORGE:
Oh, my God.
You know what
I just realized?
If they get divorced
and live in two separate places,
that's twice as many visits.
I never thought of that.
Imagine if I have to see them
both on the same day.
It's like running
a double marathon.
Hey, Georgie, did you have any
idea that anything was wrong?
Have you ever spent
any time with these people?
You know what this
has to do with?
What?
The man in the cape.
I bet you he is
mixed up in this.
I don't trust men in capes.
You can't cast
aspersions on someone
just because
they're wearing a cape.
Superman wore a cape.
And I'll be dammed
if I'm gonna stand here
and let you say
something bad about him.
All right.
Superman's
the exception.
Oh, hey, Elaine.
I just heard Noreen
and Paul are breaking up.
I want you to put in
a good word for me.
I've always had
a thing for Noreen.
No, Kramer,
you don't understand.
This could be my fault.
Well, if she's available now,
I'm not gonna let her slip
through my fingers this time.
Looks like you've adjusted
to the boxers.
Well, I wouldn't
go as far as that.
You went back to the Jockeys?
Wrong again.
Oh, no.
What? What?
Don't you see
what's going on here?
No boxers,
no Jockeys.
Ohhh.
The only thing between him and
us is a thin layer of gabardine.
Kramer, say it isn't so.
Oh, it be so.
I'm out there, Jerry, and I'm
loving every minute of it!
Don't you need
a little help?
Surprisingly, no.
I'm free.
I'm unfettered.
I feel like a naked, innocent
boy roaming the countryside.
So you guys are trying
to work it out? That's great.
Yeah, well,
we're trying.
He just went insane
there for a while.
He went insane?
Believe it or not, Paul was
convinced I was having an affair
because somebody
kept calling and hanging up
whenever he answered.
What kind of sick person calls
and hangs up over and over?
Well...I don't know about sick.
I mean, maybe it was somebody
who didn't want to talk
to whoever was answering,
because whoever was answering
was always making boring
chitchat and was completely
oblivious to the fact
that the person who was calling
didn't want to speak to them.
I can't believe
that was you.
I'm really sorry,
Noreen.
So, you thought
he was boring?
Hey, Noreen,
don't go by me.
JERRY:
What are you doing to this woman?
This is the second relationship
you've ruined for her
in a few weeks.
I know.
You ruin her relationship
with the high talker.
I got confused.
They sound
exactly the same.
So she breaks up with him,
somehow picks up
the pieces of her life.
Miraculously, meets a new guy.
You bust that up.
And then,
just as their reconciling,
you announce to the world:
"He's boring."
I didn't know
she'd take it so seriously.
Apparently, you have tremendous
influence over this woman.
Anything you say, she does.
[BUZZ]
Yeah.
DONNA:
It's Donna Chang.
Come on up.
I guess I just
didn't realize it.
Well, let's look back at your
history with this woman, okay?
Okay.
First, you encouraged her
to join the Army.
She did.
She was lost.
Then you suggest
she goes AWOL.
She did.
Well, she didn't seem
to be having so much fun.
You better never tell this woman
to jump off the Brooklyn Bridge.
If I have this much
influence over her,
why don't I just
call her and tell her
to get back together
with him. That's all.
Hey.
Miss Changstein!
This is Elaine.
Hi, how are you?
Hello.
Guess what?
Mrs. Costanza called me.
They're not getting divorced.
Why?
What happened?
Well, she was trying to call
George last night.
She got me. We spoke
for an hour, and she changed her mind.
Wow, that's amazing.
She wants to meet me.
She invited me over
for dinner.
She said you
should come too.
Tonight?
Yeah.
I just remembered.
I'm gonna have to cancel
my acupuncture class.
All right, let me
just say one thing.
There is no way that this
is gonna happen, you hear me?
No way! Because if you think
I'm going to two Thanksgivings,
you're out of your mind!
We're not getting divorced.
Your mother changed her mind.
You did? That's good.
That's very good.
I'm very glad
to hear that.
We worked it out.
So let me ask you a question.
Who was the man in the cape?
He was my lawyer.
Your lawyer wears a cape?
Yeah.
So what?
Who wears a cape?
He's very independent.
Doesn't follow the trends.
He looks ridiculous
in that thing.
You have no eye for fashion!
I have no
eye for fashion?!
All right, come on.
Let's not fight.
All right, all right.
Georgie's right.
So, what made you
change your mind?
It was that
Chinese woman.
I'm curious, what did
you tell Mrs. Costanza
that changed her mind?
Mentioned a few bits
of wisdom from Confucius.
Confucius, huh?
Yeah.
You know,
you're not Chinese.
Hey, I heard the good news.
Jerry, how come you didn't
say hello to me the other day?
Oh, Elaine was in a rush.
I knew it was Elaine!
You must be Estelle.
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Donna Chang.
You're not Chinese.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yello.
Paul?
Elaine.
Kramer?
Yeah.
What are you doing there?
Well, isn't it obvious?
Ugh. Is Noreen there?
Yes, she is.
Well, can I talk to her?
Oh, why?
Am I too boring?
All right, would you
just put her on?
Well, I feel it would
be best you didn't talk
to Noreen for a while.
You feel?
That's right.
She and I have had
a very long talk.
And I was appalled to learn
of the destructive influence
you've had over her life
these many years.
What, are you insane?
From now on, I'll be calling
the shots around here.
Oh-ho-ho! And what are you
gonna tell her?
Well, I've encouraged her
to go back into the Army.
There she'll get
the structure and discipline
she needs right now.
And she'll have
qualified officers
telling her what to do.
Kramer, you have got
to let me talk to her.
Can't help you, kid.
You're not Chinese?
No.
I thought
you were Chinese.
I'm from Long Island.
Long Island?
I thought I was getting
advice from a Chinese woman.
I'm sorry.
Well, then...
That changes everything.
What?
She's not Chinese.
I was duped!
So what? She still
gave you advice.
What's the difference
if she's not Chinese?
I'm not taking advice
from some girl from Long Island!
Wait a minute. Now,
you're getting a divorce
because she's from Long Island?
You want a divorce,
you got one!
You know, you might wanna think
about changing your name.
So ever since she started
dating Kramer,
she won't even talk to me.
Well, Noreen listened to you
like George's mother
listened to the Chinese.
You know, everybody
listens to the Chinese.
Look at the fortune cookie.
You couldn't get away with that
in any other restaurant.
Yeah, no one's reading any
rolled up messages in a knish.
Well, it had to happen.
I knew it.
I predicted it.
I saw both of them today.
What a disaster.
I'm running
all over Queens.
First, I saw my mother.
We had lunch together.
I never had lunch
with my mother before.
It's like a date.
Then we drive down to
Q Gardens. Tons of traffic.
I see my father.
We played Clue.
All day with this.
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry, guess what!
The Kramer name might live on!
Noreen's late!
She's late!
[♪]
Who are you?
I'm Frank Costanza's lawyer.
[♪]