Now, I was thinking
the other day about hair
and that the weird thing
about it is that
people will touch
other people's hair.
You will actually kiss another
human being right on the head.
But if one of those hairs
should somehow be able
to get out of that skull
and go off on its own,
it is now the vilest,
most disgusting thing
that you can encounter.
The same hair.
People freak out.
"There was a hair
in the egg salad."
GEORGE:
Say it's Saturday night in Spain.
They go out dancing.
Think they do the flamenco?
I would think.
So you could a woman
for a date,
ask her if she's free
for dinner and a flamenco.
You don't flamenco
on the first date.
I wish the flamenco
was popular here.
Yeah? Would you do it?
Yes, I think I would.
[PHONE RINGS]
Well, I knew you had
an affinity for it,
because it's the dance
of a very proud people.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Nana.
What?
Oh, all right.
Okay, don't worry about.
Okay, I'll see you later.
All right, bye.
I have to go over
to my grandmother's.
What for?
I have to open a bottle
of ketchup for her.
So, what, no lunch?
No, we have time.
Oh. How's she doing?
Starting to slip a little.
Sometimes she has trouble
distinguishing between
the past and the present.
Yeah.
You know, there's got to be
an easier way to open ketchup.
They should make it in a tube.
Like toothpaste?
Yeah.
There's a
squeeze ketchup.
I've seen
squeeze mustard.
I've never seen
squeeze ketchup.
Well, if they make
squeeze mustard,
doesn't it stand to reason
that they make squeeze ketchup?
Not necessarily.
Mustard lends itself
to the squeeze.
I really don't see
the difference.
Oh, there's
a difference.
Subtle.
It's subtle.
Hey, uh, isn't Elaine
supposed to meet us?
Yeah, there she is.
Uh-oh.
What?
Oh, she's with
her friend Wendy.
Wendy?
Is that the physical
therapist?
Yeah, I'm on a kiss-hello
program with her.
Really?
Yeah, every time I see her,
I gotta kiss hello.
I just did it once
on her birthday.
Somehow it mushroomed.
Now I dread seeing her
because of it.
BOTH:
Hey.
You know, I'm down
to one kiss hello.
My aunt Celia.
Well, that's
fortunate.
I really
admire that.
Really?
I never heard you say
you admired me for anything.
No, I told you I admire
your hearing.
Oh, don't slough
that off.
You have great
hearing.
JERRY: Hi.
Hi.
Did you ever meet George?
Wendy.
You're a physical
therapist, right?
Yes.
You know, I got this
little swelling here.
You know,
it's kind of tender.
What do you make of that?
George.
Have you tried heat
and ice on it?
Oh, that-- That really seems
like a lot of trouble.
You could come
by my office later.
I could work on it
for you a little.
Oh. Okay.
Here, let me give you
my card.
Oh, thank you.
Well, I'll see you
guys later.
Nice meeting you.
Bye, Elaine.
Bye, Wendy.
I'm sorry.
Bye, Jerry.
Bye.
What did you do
that for?
What?
Ask about your arm.
I still don't see why I can't
ask her about my arm?
She's a physical therapist.
She doesn't want to have to deal
with that outside of the office.
Why not?
Because it is what she does.
I love these people.
You can't ask them questions.
They're so mentally gifted
that we mustn't disturb
the delicate genius
unless it's in the confines
of an office.
When huge sums of money
are involved,
then the delicate genius
can be disturbed.
George, you got a little
something right here.
People think they're
so important.
Well, I'm going on record
right now.
That was my last kiss hello.
I'm getting off
the kiss program with her.
Why?
Well, you know, frankly,
outside of a sexual
relationship,
I don't see the point to it.
I'm not thrilled with all
the handshaking either.
But one step at a time.
What are you getting?
And what's with that hairdo,
by the way?
Oh, yeah. I know.
It's not very flattering.
She looks like something out of
an old high school yearbook.
You should say something to her.
Oh, I could never say
anything to her about that.
Yeah, Kramer's the only
person who could say
something like that.
Yeah.
Well, just tell Kramer
to tell her.
No, if you tell him to do it,
he'll never do it.
What you have to do
is introduce him,
and then he'll just
come out with it.
Yes. Yes.
You're right.
That's right.
I'll bring her over
to meet Kramer.
ALL:
Hi.
Hello, boys and girls.
Yeah. Hey, listen.
I need a picture
of you, buddy.
What for?
Well, I'm putting
everybody's picture up
in the lobby of our building.
Why?
So everyone will know
everybody's name.
See, people are gonna be
a lot friendlier.
I don't want my picture
plastered up in the lobby.
Imagine walking by
someone on the floor
and you say "Hey, Carl,"
and he says "Hey, Jerry."
See, that's the kind of society
I want to live in.
Kramer, I don't want to stop
and talk with everyone
every time I go
in the building.
I just want to nod
and be on my way.
You know, your eyeliner
is smudged a little.
Why do you wear so much
eye makeup?
Yeah.
This is gonna
work out just fine.
LEO:
Ma, again with the ketchup.
Don't they have them in
the plastic squeeze containers?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Jerry!
Hello!
Hello, Uncle Leo!
What are you doing here?
Nana called me to open
the ketchup bottle.
Yeah, me too.
Hello, Jerry.
Hi, Nana.
Aren't you gonna
kiss her hello?
Yes, yes.
Of course.
Well, here's the bottle.
I'll do it.
I got it.
Give it to me.
Will you stop it.
Jerry, will you give me
the bottle.
Uncle Leo.
All right.
Take it.
You should let Buddy open it.
Buddy?
He lived next door to us
45 years ago.
Leo, did you give Helen the $50?
What $50?
Your father won $1000
at the track last week,
and he gave you 100,
and you were supposed to give
$50 to your sister.
Ma,
Dad died in 1962.
Believe me, I don't owe
your mother $50.
[CHUCKLING]
I'm just not getting
any hot water.
Believe me, I know
there's nothing worse than
when your shower's not working.
I'll take care of it soon, Jer.
Thanks, Julio.
All right.
Oh, hey.
Hey, hello.
What's going on here?
Uh, nothing, nothing.
Well, what are you doing?
I-- I need a pen.
What for?
Well, I'm making out my will.
Oh, I got a big slice
of dough for you, buddy.
And you too, Elaine.
I haven't forgotten you.
You're looking for a picture
of me, aren't you?
You got that straight.
I told you, forget it.
Oh, come on, Jerry.
If everybody knew everybody,
we wouldn't have the problems
we have in the world today.
I mean, you don't rob somebody
if you know their name.
You're robbing me.
All right, I'm gonna get
your picture,
and you're gonna participate
in my program.
Uh, um--
Are you going home?
Yeah.
Can--? Can you come back
in about five minutes?
Why?
No reason.
Just wanna see you again.
Yeah.
So?
Are you sure Wendy's coming?
Yeah, she'll be here any second.
This will be a very
interesting experiment
to see if Kramer
says something.
You sure you want to
go through with this?
Listen, Jerry,
she never dates,
and I know it's because
of her hair.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Mom.
Yeah, I was at Nana's yesterday.
I had to help her open
a ketchup bottle.
Hey, Ma, let me ask
you a question.
Do you remember
when you were a kid...
your father winning,
like, $1000 at the track?
Really?
Did you know he gave
Uncle Leo $100
and he was supposed to
give you 50?
How do I know?
Because Nana doesn't know
what year it is,
and she thinks
this just happened.
Well, I think you should.
Okay. Bye.
Do you know what the interest
on that $50 comes to
over 53 years?
Oh, Morty, please.
$663.45
And that's figuring
conservatively
at 5 percent interest
over 53 years,
compounded quarterly.
Or if you put it into
a 10-year T-bill--
Morty, will you stop it.
Well, he's not getting away
with this.
[BUZZER RINGS]
Yeah?
It's Wendy.
Come on up.
Well, this is it.
Should I go get Kramer?
No, he'll come in.
Wow, this is gonna be
my first opportunity
to not kiss her hello.
What is the big deal
about putting your lips
on somebody's face?
It's the obligation.
You know, as soon as
this person comes in,
you know you have to do this.
I mean, if you could,
say, touch a breast
as part of the kiss hello,
then I think could see
the value in it a little better.
How about
an intercourse hello?
How would that be?
Elaine, now you're being
ridiculous.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
That's her.
Wait. Wait.
What?
Okay. Go, go, go.
Hi, Wendy.
Hi.
Oh, hi, Jerry.
Would you like
something to drink?
Sure.
There you go.
Ah, thanks.
Oh, look at that.
I'm almost out of
Klondike bars.
So how's everything going?
Oh, okay. Your friend George
came by the office
the other day.
Then yesterday,
he canceled on me.
Oh, yeah, he had to take
his mother to the chiropodist.
[DOOR CLOSES IN HALL]
Oh, did you hear that?
That must be Kramer.
Hey, Jerry!
Come on.
That's not fair.
I told you
I was gonna get it.
No, come on.
Give me the picture.
No, no, no, no, no.
All right. Fine.
Put my picture up.
What do I care?
Uh, Kramer?
Kramer, I'd like you
to meet my friend, Wendy.
Oh, hello.
Hi.
You know, I really like
that hairdo.
Thank you.
I actually was thinking
it might be time for a change.
Oh, you were?
Oh, no.
You don't want to do that.
No.
Nobody wears it like that.
No, Kramer, if she wants
to change her hair--
No, you'd be a damn fool
to change it.
It's very becoming.
Oh, well... Oh!
[CHUCKLES]
So who's that friend of yours,
that guy that came in?
Oh, Kramer.
Yeah.
Does he have a girlfriend?
You want to go out with him?
Well, why not?
Well, it's just that--
That-- I don't know.
Well, is there anything
wrong with him?
Elaine?
I'm just thinking
about the question.
You know, my arm feels
a lot better.
That Wendy really knows
her stuff.
She is super.
Same time tomorrow?
Yeah, same time.
There you go.
Oh, uh...
you owe 150.
What for?
Well, you canceled on Tuesday,
and our policy is 24 hours'
notice for all cancellations.
Well, I-- I couldn't come.
I had to drive my mother
to the chiropodist.
What's the problem?
Are you aware I'm being charged
for Tuesday's appointment?
I had to take my mother
to the chiropodist.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's our policy.
Oh, you have a policy!
The delicate genius
has a policy!
So will you be here tomorrow?
Well, it's less than 24 hours,
so I guess I have to.
Hey! So, what do you think?
You like it?
Oh, my God.
Look at that picture.
That's terrible.
You can't put
that picture up.
Well, it's not
a beauty contest.
It's just a way for people
to get to know one another.
Hi, Cosmo.
Hey...Steve.
Now, you see?
Hey, Kramer.
My friend Wendy wants
to go out with you.
Well, how do you do?
Hello...Jerry.
Oh, hello, uh...
Mary.
You know, I have seen you
so many times,
and now we can finally
talk to each other.
See? What was I
telling you?
Isn't this nice?
Eh...
Jerry, you know, could you
help me with a package?
Oh, sure, yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
You see, that's just
what I need,
more kissing.
[SNICKERS]
What is so funny?
Nothing. Nothing.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Ma.
What?
Oh, Ma.
He didn't.
He couldn't?
All right.
I will.
Okay. Bye.
Uncle Leo put Nana
in a home.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe to keep her quiet.
Hi, Jerry.
Hi, Joan.
How you doing?
Pretty good.
Just pretty good?
Not great?
Okay. Great.
Are you happy?
Oh, I'm delighted.
Okay. Have a nice day.
You too.
Hi, Jerry.
Hi, Louise.
Hey.
Oh, well, thank you very much.
For what?
For putting my picture
up on that wall.
I'm like Richard Dawson
down there now.
Every person I see
engages me
in this long, boring,
tedious conversation.
I can't even get out
of the building.
You should be thanking me
for liberating you
from your world of
loneliness and isolation.
Now you're part
of a family.
Family?
Yeah.
You think I want another family?
My father's demanding
my uncle pay interest
on $50 he was supposed to
give my mother in 1941,
and my uncle put
my Nana in a home
to try and shut her up.
And I'll tell you another thing,
Cosmo, Kramer,
whatever you want
to be called,
the kissing thing is over.
There's no more kissing,
and I don't care
what the consequences are.
Oh, hi, Mr. Costanza.
We were trying
to get in touch with you.
Wendy can't make
her appointment.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
What do you mean?
She had some personal affairs
she had to attend to.
I left a message
on your machine.
You didn't get it?
When did you leave
the message?
A few hours ago.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I require 24 hours notice
for a cancellation.
Now, as I see it,
you owe me $75.
Look, Mr. Costanza--
Will that be cash or check?
I am really glad
I took the day off.
Oh, yeah, there's nothing
better than skiing.
Yeah. God, I hope my clients
weren't too upset.
Oh, the hell with them.
What are you stopping
here for?
I'm dropping
you off.
Oh, no.
I'm three more blocks.
Yeah, but if I take you
right to your door,
then I have to go
all the way around
Central Park West
back to Columbus--
You know,
it's all one way.
But it's only
three blocks.
Right. It's only
All right. Well...
She'd driven me 120 miles,
then all of a sudden,
three blocks from my door,
she decides this trip is over.
Isn't that strange?
Yes. It's very strange.
Very strange.
I've never heard of
anything like this.
I mean, it's almost as if
I was hitchhiking,
and she said "Well this is
as far as I can take you."
If you were hitchhiking,
you'd never get in a car
with someone with
a hairdo like that.
I had to carry my skis
and my boots and my poles.
I think I pinched a nerve
in my shoulder.
You should have her
work on it for you.
Yeah. All right.
I gotta go.
Hi, Jerry.
Hi, Mary.
Uh, listen.
I've decided I can't
kiss hello anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing personal.
It makes me
a little uncomfortable,
and I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Oh--
Hi, Jerry.
Hi, Louise. I was
just telling Mary
how I'm not gonna
be doing
the kiss-hello thing
anymore.
I'm sorry.
I just can't do it.
It's nothing personal.
It's just that I'm not
really able to do it--
Thank you
for your cooperation.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
HELEN: Jerry?
Hi, Mom.
What's happening with
Uncle Leo? Is he paying?
Well, he said no.
He said we have no proof.
No proof?
We'll get him.
He's a crook.
Sooner or later he'll slip up.
Anyway, I want you to go
check on Nana at the home.
Okay, I will.
Do you realize,
an above average
performing growth mutual fund
for 53 years...
What's up?
I gotta go visit my Nana
in the nursing home.
Oh.
Hey, Kramer.
Look at this.
Look at my picture.
I've been defaced.
Don't you worry, buddy.
I made double prints.
Hey. Hi, Cosmo.
Oh, hey, Jack.
How you doing?
Hi, Jack.
Hey, Julio,
I was wondering,
could you get to that shower
today, you think?
Oh, I see. When you need
something done,
then you're very friendly
to people, huh?
No, no.
That's not true.
Well, I think it is.
It's a big building, Seinfeld.
Maybe I'll get to it someday.
After I take care of the people
that are civil to each other.
NURSE:
Yeah, she's upstairs, playing cards.
You know, she really
doesn't belong here.
My uncle put her here
because he's trying to prove
he doesn't owe my mother $50.
Well, she seems very happy.
She met an old friend who used
to live next door to her.
Buddy?
Yes, that's his name.
He's right over there.
WENDY:
I'm sorry.
I don't owe you anything.
I had some personal
business that day.
Oh, I see. So your time
is more valuable than mine.
Is that it?
You're a delicate genius.
A delicate genius?
Elaine.
George.
Good luck.
What's going on?
Wendy, I injured my shoulder
Wednesday when--
When you dropped me off
and I had to carry
my skis and my boots
and my poles and everything
all the way home.
I'm having trouble
lifting my arm.
Do you think you could
give me some treatment?
Oh, sure.
You have insurance, right?
Insurance?
You're charging me?
Wednesday?
That's your personal business?
Skiing?!
Oh, sure, let people suffer
while you're shooshing
all over a mountain!
How did you hear that?
I hear everything.
All right, why don't you two
just take
your business elsewhere.
Ho-ho!
That is a good idea.
Come on, George.
Yeah. Let's go.
And you know,
you might want to do
something about that hair.
Why? What's wrong
with my hair?
I think it's a little
old-fashioned, don't you?
Tell her.
She's right.
So you were with him
that day at the track.
Oh, yeah.
He won $1000.
His son was there too.
Leo?
Yeah, that's it.
Leo.
Oh, what an obnoxious
little kid.
He used to steal
my soda bottles
and cash them in
for the deposit.
Is that so?
And after your grandfather
hit the daily double,
he give him $100 and told him
to give 50 to his sister.
His sister? Well, I say
he should give it to me
for all the bottles
he took.
Well, that's
very interesting.
Uncle Leo.
I just met an old
acquaintance of yours.
You remember Buddy.
He just told me
quite a story
about you and Grandpa
at the track.
Wait a second--
You're busted.
Hey, Steve,
how you doing?
Hey, Jeff,
what's happening?
Mary?
Oh, Mary.
Give us a kiss.
Don't be like that, Mary.
Come on.
I made a mistake.
Look, why don't you do
everybody a favor
and just get out
of this building.
Nobody wants you here.
Nobody!
JEFF:
Hi, Mary.
Hi, Jeff.
How are you?
Hi, Steve.
Hey, let's go
get some coffee.
Oh, that'd be great.
Great idea.
I gotta go down to
the corner, but...
Oh, Paul.
Could you hold that door?
Hey, could I use your shower?
What, again?
You took one this morning.
Well, I got a date.
Come on. Please?
I know, but, you know,
I got a little problem.
Wendy here?
No, no.
She changed her hair style.
It's terrible.
No, we're done.
I'll go get
some more beer.
Oh, yeah, yeah, great.
And get some of those
blue corn chips.
Hey.
Hi, Cosmo.
Hi.
Ooh. I like that.
Who was that?
Stephanie, 2G.
Oh, man.
Looks like you got quite
a few people in here.
Yeah, well, you know
I'd invite you in,
but, uh, you know...
Oh, I understand.