I've always wondered why
baseball is so associated
with sex.
"He's playing the field."
"Oh, He scored."
"He didn't get to first base."
"I struck out."
"Why?"
"She wanted a diamond."
It's always baseball,
always baseball.
As far as baseball goes,
I prefer the fat umpires.
I feel if you're on the field
and you're not in the game,
you should be in the worst
physical condition
a human being can
possibly be in.
They should be allowed to eat
during the game.
We're a little too into sports
in this country.
I think we got to throttle back.
You know what I mean?
People come home
from these games:
"We won, we won!"
No, they won.
You watched.
GEORGE:
Okay, Danny take a swing.
No, no, no.
You're not opening up
your shoulder.
Really?
No, not really.
I'm just saying
this to you,
'cause I like
to hear myself talk.
Yes, really!
All right,
all right.
What are you
all sweating for?
It's hot in this uniform.
Hot?
What is this?
What is what?
This uniform,
what's it made from?
I don't know.
Cotton?
No, this is not cotton.
Here, let me see.
What are you doing?
I wanna see the label.
Will you stop it?
Of course.
Polyester.
So?
I can't believe you're not
playing in cotton.
This is what they give us.
You know, they used to make
leisure suits
out of this fabric?
You really think
cotton is better?
Of course.
All right,
maybe I'll say something
to Buck.
Catch you later.
Hey, don't embarrass me
today.
I got some friends
in the stands, huh?
[CROWD CHEERING]
MAN:
Hot dogs here.
Yankee franks!
Oh, you want one?
Yeah.
I'll get it.
That's all right.
I got it.
Jerry.
Elaine, stop it.
Just because
I'm not working
doesn't mean I don't have
any money.
Yo, dogs, two.
I'm sorry.
ANNOUNCER:
Your attention, please.
New York Yankees
would like to welcome
Miss Connecticut,
Miss Rhode Island
and Miss North Dakota.
All of whom will be competing
in the Miss America pageant
this weekend in Atlantic City.
Now, there's a career path
you may have overlooked.
Ooh, I gotta check
my machine.
I'm waitin' to hear
about an interview.
Doubleday is looking
for somebody
to replace
Jackie Onassis.
Oh, she worked
at Doubleday?
Yes, she was
an editor.
Oh, right,
just like you. Yeah.
Could you move
your feet? Yeah.
WOMAN:
Sit down!
Hey, down in front!
Hang on, I'm going.
[GIGGLING]
Hot dog?
No, thanks.
I'm watching
my weight. Oh.
I'm watching my height.
My doctor doesn't want me
to get any taller.
So you're Miss, uh--
Rhode Island.
Oh.
I was almost Mr. Coffee.
They felt I was
a little too relaxed.
GEORGE:
Miss Rhode Island?
Jeez, when are you
seeing her?
Tonight.
I have to call.
She's staying
in a hotel.
You're incredible.
Get this: I'm working
in Atlantic City this weekend.
She's gonna be down there
for the pageant.
What if she becomes
Miss America?
You could be dating
Miss America, Jerry.
The only bad thing is
we have to go out
with a chaperone.
Chaperone?
What, are you kidding?
No, it's part
of the contest rules.
What does the chaperone do?
I don't know.
She just sits there.
Can she talk?
I'm not sure
if she's allowed to talk.
Are you calling?
Yeah.
♪ There she is
Miss-- ♪
Yes, room 417, please.
Karen Hanson.
Hey, did you know
the Yankees don't wear
cotton jerseys?
Of course,
they're polyester.
Well, what is that?
That's a crime.
You know how hot
those things get?
They should be
wearing cotton.
Why do they wear
polyester?
I don't know.
That's all gonna change.
You're gonna do something
about it?
Why shouldn't I?
No reason.
Of course, Jackie O
was a great lady.
Oh!
Those are going to be some tough shoes to fill.
Mm-hm.
Everybody loved her.
She had such...grace.
Yes.
Aaaaaah!
Grace.
Not many people have grace.
Well, you know,
grace is a tough one.
I like to think I have
a little grace.
Not as much as Jackie--
You can't have
a little grace.
You either have grace
or you...don't.
Okay, fine.
I have...no grace.
And you can't acquire grace.
Well, I-- I have no intention
of getting grace.
Grace isn't something you can
pick up at the market.
All right, all right, look.
I don't have grace.
I don't want grace.
I don't even say grace, okay?
Thank you
for coming in.
Yeah, yeah, right.
We'll make our choice
in a few days,
and we'll let you know.
I have no chance, do I?
No.
Thanks.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
WOMAN:
Justin Pitt to see you.
Justin Pitt?
He was a very close friend
of Mrs. Onassis's.
Mrs. Onassis's.
That's hard to pronounce.
Excuse me?
Nothing, nothing.
Mrs. Landis,
there's something wrong
with this copying machine.
It's all coming out slanted.
Now, I don't know if this
is your department or not.
Justin Pitt,
this is Elaine Benes.
Charmed.
I was a great admirer
of Mrs. Onasth--
Sus-- Ses.
Hello, Karen?
Hi, it's
Jerry Seinfeld.
Oh, that's very sweet
of you.
You know, you better
be careful.
You don't wanna get
too congenial.
They'll slap that
Miss Congeniality on you.
You'll congenial yourself
right out of the contest.
So, what time you wanna
get together later?
What?
So what? We don't need
the chaperone.
The chaperone can't make it.
Oh, you're not gonna
get disqualified.
So we're not going?
Come on--
Hold on a minute.
Hey, what are you
doing tonight?
Nothing.
I'm going out with one of
the Miss America contestants.
You wanna go?
What state?
Rhode Island.
They're never in contention.
How do you know?
Because I've seen every
Miss America pageant
since I was 6.
Look, do you want to go or not?
I'll buy you dinner.
Giddy up.
I think I got someone.
The resemblance is uncanny.
Even the brown eyes.
Well, a lot of people have
brown eyes.
No, there's something else.
An indefinable quality.
Grace?
Grace, yes.
You think I have grace?
Some grace, yes.
Just some?
Well, you don't want
too much grace,
or you won't be able
to stand.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, Mr. Pitt.
Elaine,
I want you to come
and work for me
as my personal assistant.
Now, I'll pay you the same
as Pendant,
but I would need you
to start right away.
Hey, Buck, talk to you
for a second?
Sure, George.
How's everything going?
Everything okay?
Well, you know,
all of a sudden
there's a problem with
Tartabull's swing but--
Listen, Buck, obviously
I don't need to talk to you
about the importance of
player morale,
but I've been talking to
some of the guys.
And some of them--
I don't wanna mention
any names--
But some of them
are not too happy
with the polyester uniforms.
How so?
Well, they get very hot
in the polyester.
You know, it's not
a natural fiber.
I think they would
prefer cotton.
Cotton, huh?
Cotton breathes.
It's much softer.
Imagine playing games
and your team is five degrees
cooler than the other team.
Don't you think that would be
an advantage?
They're cooler.
They're more comfortable.
They're happier.
They're gonna play better.
Maybe you got
something there, George.
Oh, I've got something.
Hmm, cotton uniforms?
JERRY:
Congratulations.
Yeah, and the best part is
I still get to
look for work
in publishing.
Now, what is it
that you do exactly?
I attend to his
personal affairs.
Like what?
Well, like tomorrow,
for example, I--
I have to buy him some socks.
Really?
Socks?
Yeah.
White ones. Like the ones
you wear with sneakers.
Hey, maybe you can pick me
up some underwear.
Ahh. So?
What do you think?
Does this work?
Listen, tonight, after
we finish eating?
You make like you got
something else to do,
and just recede into the night,
if you know what I mean.
No way.
What?
Look, if you think
I'm just gonna step aside
and do nothing
while you defile this woman,
you're crazy.
I'm not going to defile her.
That's right.
Because I'm gonna see
it doesn't happen.
Look, Jerry, these girls
are Miss America contestants.
It's every little girl's dream.
And I'm not gonna let you
trample that dream
and make a mockery of everything
the pageant stands for.
But--
Ahhh!
No buts.
Those are my rules.
But wait a minute--
If you wanna go out and have
some good, wholesome fun
with a nice girl,
I'll help you out.
If you're looking for
something more than that,
you got the wrong guy, buddy.
It's just--
Ahhh!
BOTH:
If you were Miss America,
what would you do
to make the world
a better place?
As Miss America,
I would try and bring
an end to world hunger.
If every person
sacrificed one meal a week,
there would be enough
to feed the whole world.
That's a hell of a plan.
Listen--
What advice would you give
young people?
All right, Kramer--
This is important stuff.
She's gotta be able to answer
these questions.
She's not gonna have time
to think out there,
with millions of people
watching her.
Any hesitation
could cost her the crown.
You know, poise counts.
You really know a lot
about this, don't you?
Oh, yeah. Last year, Miss Texas
should have won easily,
but she lost points
in the swimsuit competition.
What could she have done?
Tape her breasts together.
What else?
Take you, for example.
Now, you're very attractive,
but you got a big waist.
Hey, come on.
No, it's okay.
Go on.
Well, I'd recommend
a waist cincher.
Really?
Oh, yeah, just:
Suck you in.
All right,
I'll be right back.
So, what's your talent?
Magic.
Mmm.
I'm thinking of a number
from one to 10.
Six.
No. Five.
But you were close.
ANNOUNCER 1:
And the Yankees take the field.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Is it my imagination,
or do the Yankees look
a little different tonight?
I can't put my finger
on it.
Well, from what
I understand,
they've switched
to cotton uniforms.
They say
it's softer--
Well, it is
a natural fiber.
KRAMER:
What color is your evening?
I'm wearing this red--
Stop right there.
No good?
Disaster.
Why?
Well, you got brown eyes.
You wanna wear a green dress.
That makes sense.
Well, here we are.
Kramer,
would you consider
being my personal consultant
for the pageant?
Okay.
But if I'm going to do this,
we play by my rules,
or we don't play at all.
I'm in your hands.
Well...
Oh, good night, Jerry.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, Kenneth
will take you home.
KRAMER:
♪ There she is ♪
♪ Miss Amer-- ♪
JERRY:
Oh, shut the @#%! up.
Hey.
Well, if it isn't
Mr. Blackwell?
Oh, come on.
And that waist cincher.
That was the topper.
Oh, you're pooh-poohing?
Yes, I pooh-pooh.
Well, let me tell you
something.
I'm taking this kid
to the top.
To the top, Jerry.
We're going for the crown,
and you can't stop her!
I don't wanna stop her.
You can't stop her, Jerry!
I've seen them come and go,
but this kid has got something.
Yeah, so do you.
Well, did you see it?
See what?
The uniforms.
Did you see how they played?
Listen to these comments.
"Wade Boggs:
"'What a fabric.
Finally, we can breathe.'
"Louis Polonia:
"'Cotton is king.'
"Paul O'Neill:
'I never dreamed anything
could be so soft and fluffy.'"
Boy, they really sound
comfortable.
Hey, where you going?
I'm working
in Atlantic City.
Really?
You're not working this weekend.
Why don't you come down.
Atlantic City?
Yes.
Yes, I will go
to Atlantic City.
I'm in.
I'm down.
You know what?
Maybe Elaine wants to go too.
Let me call her.
She's at Mr. Pitt's.
I think I got the number.
ELAINE:
So, what do you think?
No!
You don't like them?
No, I don't like them.
What's wrong?
They're too tight.
Too tight?
There's no elastic.
You need to pull too much.
I think they look good.
They're cutting off
the circulation.
All right, well,
I'll just take them back.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hi, Mr. Pitt.
Is Elaine there?
It's for you.
Me? Sorry.
Hello?
Hey, Elaine.
It's me.
Jerry?
Yeah, we're going
to Atlantic City.
Really?
When?
Today.
Right now.
You in?
Um--
Um, one second.
Hang on. Hang on.
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Pitt?
Would it be all right
if I got you the socks tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Yes.
I was hoping
for my new socks today.
Well, it's just one more day.
I'm sorry, I must
have them today.
I can't go.
Why not?
Because I have to return
the socks
and get different ones.
Elaine!
I gotta go.
No.
All right, watch me.
Turn, back, head up.
Shoulders back.
Posture.
See? Posture.
Yes, I see. Okay.
All right. Let's try a few
more questions, all right?
If you were Miss America
and the U.S. was on the brink
of a nuclear war,
and the only way
the conflict could be averted
was if you agreed to sleep
with the enemy's leader,
what would you do?
Kramer, are these questions
really that important--
Yes, they're important.
If you stumble, if you hesitate,
you can kiss the crown goodbye.
Now, if I told you once,
I've told you 1000 times!
Poise counts!
It's just as important
as the others.
Swimsuit, evening wear,
talent, poise!
Hey.
How was the show?
Good.
How was roulette?
I won 50 bucks.
Wow, this is great.
Too bad Elaine's not here.
Yeah, all she had to do was
buy Mr. Pitt a pair of socks.
It's good, but--
But what?
Ultimately, I don't think
they'll stay up.
No, no, they'll stay up.
For a while, yes,
but not in the long run.
That's why I got you
the tighter ones.
Forget about those.
Why do you keep
mentioning those?
What do you want?
I want a decent sock
that's comfortable,
that will stay on my foot!
[DOVES COOING]
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
It sounds like pigeons
or something.
Well, I can't sleep
with that noise.
Me either.
Is there anything you can do
to shut them up?
Wait a second.
This will scare them off.
[DOVES SCREECHING]
Mm!
Well, good night,
Ollie.
Good night, Stan.
What is it?
My doves!
They're dead.
I trained those birds
for eight years.
How am I supposed to do
my magic act now?
How did this happen?
They like it outside,
so I kept them in the cage
on the terrace,
and then I found them dead
in a pool of water.
How did this happen?
It must have been an accident.
Accident?
This was no accident.
These doves were murdered.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Well, that's it.
She's out of the pageant.
What? Why?
What happened?
Her birds are dead.
Birds?
Yeah, birds.
She's got these trained doves.
She does this magic act.
That was her talent
for the pageant.
You know what I think, Jerry?
I think somebody murdered
those doves.
Somebody wanted her out
of that contest bad.
Somebody who was just eaten up
with jealousy,
somebody who couldn't stand
to have the spotlight
taken off of them!
What are you looking at?
Oh, that. We, uh--
We had to leave that
outside last night
because the water was making
the room too cold.
That's, uh--
You killed them,
didn't you?
No, you don't understand.
It's not what you think.
It was an accident.
Don't think you won,
because you haven't.
This kid is a fighter!
If you think I'm gonna
let a couple of dead birds
get in our way,
you're crazy!
Kramer, you've gotta
explain to her--
What was that all about?
Oh, it was just Kramer.
Apparently, I killed
Miss Rhode Island's doves
with the bucket of water
last night.
Oh.
[APPLAUSE]
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, that was Miss Texas.
Wasn't she wonderful?
And now, continuing
with the talent portion
of the competition--
Okay, this is it.
How you feeling?
I'm a little nervous.
There's nothing to be
nervous about.
But I've never sung before
in my life.
And now, let's welcome
Karen Ann Hanson,
Miss Rhode Island.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ It's a most unusual day ♪
♪ Feel like throwing
My worries away ♪
♪ And if I want to sing
Throw my heart in the ring ♪
[OFF-KEY]
♪ It's a most unusual day... ♪
[KAREN SINGING ON TV]
I heard those doves
were really incredible.
That's a shame.
♪ ...And a feeling
Of spring in the air ♪
It's like watching
an animal get tortured.
Hey, hey, Yankee game.
Oh, great.
All right.
ANNOUNCER 1:
And the Yankees take the field.
ANNOUNCER 2:
And what is with the Yankees?
They look like they're
having trouble running.
They can't move.
It's their uniforms.
They're too tight.
They've shrunk. They're
running like penguins.
Forget this game.
Oh, my God.
Mattingly just
split his pants.
That's a shame.
♪ ...My heart won't behave
In the usual way ♪
♪ Well, there's only one thing
To say... ♪
Poise, poise.
♪ It's a most unusual ♪
♪ Most unusual ♪
♪ Most unusual day ♪
The Miss America pageant seems
like a really tough contest.
You know, you gotta come out
there in the bathing suit
and the dress shoes.
They got that
"sanitized for your protection"
toilet seat thing
hanging off them, you know.
Plus, they gotta wear
all the other outfits.
I don't know why.
The bathing suit is the contest.
You win the bathing suit,
you win.
What is the formalwear?
Everybody looks good in formalwear.
It's dark,
it covers everything.
That's why we have
weddings in it.
I mean, if we had weddings
in bathing suits,
a lot of ceremonies
wouldn't be able to get past:
"If anyone sees any reason why
these two people
should not be
joined together--"
About 80 hands go up.