Car names are so stupid,
aren't they?
No baron has ever owned
a LeBaron.
Or the Ford LTD.
LTD. Limited.
It's a limited edition.
What do they make,
50 million of those?
Yes, it's limited
to the number we can sell.
Or when they try and mangle
a positive word into a car name.
You know how they'll do that?
The Integra.
Oh, integrity?
No. Integra.
The Supra or the Impreza.
Yeah, well, I hope
it's not a "lemona," huh?
Or you'll be hearing
from my "lawya."
So George, you sure I can't
show you any other cars?
Heh, heh.
I don't think so, Vic.
Done my homework.
'89 Volvo.
That's the car for me.
It's the one I want.
I got a LeBaron
convertible right here.
Heh, heh. N.I.
Not interested.
It's got a few more
miles on it,
but the previous owner
was Jon Voight.
Jon Voight?
Okay, Tim.
You're welcome.
Was that Tim Whatley?
Yes, it was.
He wanted your address.
You, my friend,
are going to be invited
to his night-before-Thanksgiving
party.
[EXHALES]
You know he's got that great
apartment on 77th Street,
and they overlook where they
inflate all those huge balloons
for the Macy's
Thanksgiving Day parade.
I have always had
a big crush on Tim Whatley.
Why can't
he ask me out?
Oh, he's a dentist. You don't
want to go out with a dentist.
Why?
He'll always be criticizing
your brushing technique.
It'll drive you crazy.
Away from the gums.
Uh.
[JANGLING]
New car!
Oh!
Hey!
Did you get
the Volvo?
No, I decided to go
with an '89 LeBaron.
A LeBaron?
I thought Consumer said
Volvo was the car.
What consumer?
I'm the consumer.
Ah.
Seems like a strange choice.
Well, maybe so.
But it, uh, was good enough
for Mr. Jon Voight.
Jon Voight?
The actor?
That's right.
He just happened to be
the previous owner
of the, uh, vehicle.
You bought a car because
it belonged to Jon Voight?
No. No.
I think "yes, yes."
You like the idea
of telling people
you're driving
Jon Voight's car.
All right, maybe I do.
So what?
I've never even
seen him in a car.
I mean,
look at his movies.
No cars.
Deliverance,
canoe.
Midnight Cowboy,
boots.
Runaway Train,
runaway train.
Hey.
Jerry, you know that shoe repair
place at the end of the block?
If they don't get some business,
they're gonna have to shut down
and make way for one of those
gourmet coffee or cookie stores.
I like coffee.
I like cookies.
KRAMER:
Of course you do.
And you know why?
Because you're
a bunch of yuppies.
It's your "go, go"
corporate-takeover lifestyles
that are driving out
these mom-and-pop stores
and destroying the fabric
of this neighborhood.
What's so great about
a mom-and-pop store?
Let me tell
you something.
If my mom and pop ran a store,
I wouldn't shop there.
Hey, Bucambo, they've been in
the neighborhood for 48 years.
Now, come on, Jerry.
You gotta have a pair of shoes
in need of a cobbler.
I really don't wear the kind of
shoes that have to be cobbled.
Well, what
about sneakers?
You know, they'll clean them.
They do complete detailing.
All right.
Take 'em.
Yeah, yeah.
POP:
Kramer, without you, we'd be out of business.
These sneakers,
they belong to my neighbor,
Jerry Seinfeld,
the comedian.
So many sneakers.
He's got a Peter Pan complex.
They'll be ready
a week from Thursday.
Oh, well, no rush.
Uh-oh.
MOM:
What's the matter?
I keep getting
these nosebleeds.
Lie down.
And put your
head back.
Oh, yeah.
[THUD]
Oh!
Hey, what's with
your ceiling?
What?
You got wires sticking
out every which way.
That looks dangerous.
You should call
an electrician.
You know, in the 48 years
we've been here,
I don't think we've ever
called an electrician.
Yeah, well, you should.
This place could blow
any minute.
[BIG-BAND MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO]
Elaine?
Yes, Mr. Pitt?
Have you gotten all the salt
off those pretzels yet?
No. I'm still
working on it.
What in blazes are
you listening to?
Artie Shaw.
"Honeysuckle Jump."
ANNOUNCER [ON RADIO]:
That was Artie Shaw. "Honeysuckle Jump."
Elaine, how did you
know that?
My father used to have a huge
collection of big-band records.
ANNOUNCER:
Congratulations to our listener Wayne Hopper
for identifying it. And by
doing so, he becomes our
seventh person to man
the WFBB-sponsored
Woody Woodpecker balloon in the
Macy's Thanksgiving Day parade.
There are only
three spots left.
We're going to take
a little break now.
When we come back,
you'll have three more chances
to win a spot holding a rope
under Woody Woodpecker.
Could you identify the next
song? Could you? Could you?
Mr. Pitt, why would you want
to hold one of the ropes
from the Woody Woodpecker
balloon?
My father was
a stern man.
He forbade us to participate
in any activities
that he thought were
associated with the common man.
The Thanksgiving Day parade
was first on the list.
All right. Okay.
I'll do the best I can.
ANNOUNCER: All right,
here we go for the next
spot under the balloon.
If you know the name of this
next song, call 555-BAND.
[SONG PLAYS]
Well, Elaine? Do you know it?
What song is it?
Will you shut up?
I can't hear!
I'm sorry!
Oh!
I've got it!
It's
"Next Stop, Pottersville."
Goody!
Yes, yes, yes!
"Next Stop, Pottersville"!
"Next Stop--"!
You are a genius!
You are gonna
love this car,
even if you don't
like Jon Voight.
I like Jon Voight.
It just seems like kind of
a strange reason to buy a car
because he might
have driven it.
What do you mean,
might?
You don't think
he really owned this car?
I don't know.
Why would the guy make up
something like that?
Of all the names
he could pick,
why settle
on Jon Voight?
Don't you see?
That's the genius of it.
If he had said
Liam Neeson,
you'd know
he's making it up.
Liam Neeson?
You're comparing Liam Neeson
with Jon Voight.
Jerry, we're talking
about Joe Buck.
If you can play Joe Buck,
Oskar Schindler's a cakewalk.
Oh, look at this.
I stepped in gum.
Whoa, whoa!
You're not getting in my car
with gummy shoes.
All right.
I'll change my shoes.
Liam Neeson.
You know
he's not American.
Let me get a clean pair.
♪ Everybody's talkin' at me ♪
♪ I can't hear a word
They're sayin' ♪
♪ Just drivin' round
In Jon Voight's car ♪
JERRY:
Kramer!
[DOOR SLAMS IN HALL]
Hey.
Where's all my sneakers?
You said take 'em.
Not all of them!
Well, obviously,
there was a miscommunication.
Obviously.
So, what am I
supposed to wear?
Jerry, I left you
a pair right here.
Where?
Come on.
You're not
looking.
Here.
There.
Put on those.
I can't wear these.
Well, why not?
They're
uncomfortable.
Come on, here.
Try 'em on.
Oh...
Where did you get those?
I worked a club
in Dallas one time,
and they couldn't
afford to pay me,
so they gave me these.
Oh, I can't wear these.
They look ridiculous.
You look
like a cowboy, huh!
I don't wanna be a cowboy!
KRAMER:
Oh, stop it.
You know that friend of yours,
Tim the dentist?
I got an invitation
to his Thanksgiving Eve party.
Yeah?
I got one too. Yeah?
Oh, yeah?
Huh.
What?
No.
Nothing.
What is it?
No, it's just that, uh,
I didn't get one.
You didn't get one?
Ah, but he
called me up
and he asked for yours
and Elaine's addresses.
I'm sure that means
I'm invited.
Not necessarily.
Hey, why would
you call someone up
and ask them for
two addresses
if you're not invited
to the party.
That's the genius of it.
I'm calling Elaine.
See if she can find out
anything from Tim Whatley.
Hey, I got Jon Voight's
LeBaron.
Boss.
POP:
Four thousand dollars!
We can't
afford that.
Well, I'm afraid you're gonna
have to do something about it
because it's in violation
of the building code.
Otherwise, they're
gonna close you up.
Well... Well, supposing
we can't pay for it?
Then I have
to report you.
Otherwise,
I lose my license.
Sorry.
Forty-eight years, Mom.
And now we have to close.
All because of that idiot
and his bloody nose.
Afternoon, Mom.
Afternoon, Pop.
You know you got a crack
in the sidewalk out there?
Now, you ought to
get that fixed.
[GEORGE HUMMING
"EVERYBODY'S TALKIN'"]
So?
Come on.
Put the top up.
It's November.
I feel alive,
Jerry.
Let's check out
the glove box.
A pencil.
Hey, you don't think...?
Sure. That's
Jon Voight's pencil.
With Jon Voight's
teeth marks.
Whoo!
Owner's manual.
You know what?
This car was owned
by Jon Voight.
You see?
I told you.
Except Jon is spelled
with an "h."
J-O-H-N.
So?
Doesn't Jon Voight
spell his name J-O-N?
[ENGINE IDLING]
So, what are you saying?
Nothing.
I'm sure Jon probably
misspelled his own name.
I know sometimes
I spell Jerry with a G.
And an I.
[LAUGHING]
Get out
of the car!
What?
That's right. You heard me.
Get out.
You are ruining this
whole experience for me.
Oh, look.
There's Gregory Peck's
bicycle.
Get out!
And Barbara Mandrell's
skateboard.
Get out!
Hey, cowboy.
Where's your horse?
MAN: Yeah, you
better run.
GEORGE:
Did they take anything?
No. They didn't
even touch me.
I tripped because of these
stupid cowboy boots.
Well, anyway, again,
I'm sorry about throwing
you out of the car.
You really seemed
to enjoy it.
It was kind of fun.
You know, maybe his name
really is J-O-H-N,
but he changed it to
J-O-N for show business.
Well, you know, J-O-N
is a lot zippier.
Yeah, that's possible.
How would you find out
something like that?
Wait a minute.
What am I thinking?
I've got the entire Yankee
organization at my disposal.
He'll dispose
of it.
That's right.
See you later.
So, Jerome, I did a little
snooping around for you.
Oh, what'd you
find out, Lois?
Well, I talked
to Tim Whatley.
Yeah?
And I asked him,
"Should Jerry bring anything?"
Subtle.
Mm.
And he said, "Why would
Jerry bring anything?"
All right, but let me
ask you this question.
What?
Which word did
he emphasize?
Did he say, "Why would
Jerry bring anything?"
Or "Why would Jerry
bring anything?"
Did he emphasize
"Jerry" or "bring"?
I think he
emphasized "would."
You know what?
The hell with this party.
I don't even want
to go to begin with.
Hey.
Hey. So where's
my sneakers?
That's what
I want to know.
What do you mean?
I saw Mom and Pop
this morning,
but when I went by the store
on my way home,
the place was empty.
Everything
is gone.
Mom and Pop--
Pfft.
--vanished.
So all my sneakers
are gone?
I'm afraid so.
And that's just
the tip of the iceberg.
I've been asking around.
They didn't even
have any kids.
Mom and Pop aren't
even a Mom and Pop?
It was all an act, Jerry.
They conned us,
and they scored bigtime.
So Mom and Pop's plan was
to move into the neighborhood,
establish trust...
for 48 years...
and then run off
with Jerry's sneakers?
Apparently.
All right.
That's enough of this.
Where you going?
I gotta go to
the Dixieland Deli
to pick up Mr. Pitt's
security pass for the parade.
Why does he want to hold a rope
underneath Woody Woodpecker
in the Thanksgiving Day
parade?
He finds his laugh
intoxicating.
[IMITATES WOODY WOODPECKER]
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
So, George,
what kind of promotional events
are we talking about?
Well, I think we need more
special days at the stadium.
You know, like, uh...
Joe Pepitone Day.
Mm-hm.
Or, uh...
[KNOCKS]
...Jon Voight Day.
Jon Voight?
The actor?
[SNAPS]
[SIGHS]
I make a motion that we have
no more of these meetings
that have been initiated
by George Costanza.
I suppose if I had suggested
Liam Neeson Day,
you'd all be
patting me on the back.
I guessed Stan Herman's
"Boomtown Blues."
What did you guess?
Um, it was
"Next Stop, Pottersville."
[EVERYONE GROANS]
Everybody knew that.
I knew that.
Do you know when they're
giving out the passes?
After the music.
[DIXIELAND JAZZ PLAYS]
Aw, man.
Taxi!
Hey!
Jon Voight!
Hey, listen.
Can I ask
you something?
Listen. Listen.
Do you--?
Wait!
Argh!
JERRY: No Jon Voight Day, huh?
No.
Now I'll always have
this doubt about the car.
What, your jaw
still hurts?
Yeah, it's
all swollen.
I think I may have chipped
a tooth when I fell yesterday.
You should have somebody
take a look at it.
I'm calling dentists
all day here.
There's nobody working
the day before Thanksgiving.
You going to the party?
No. I don't know
if I'm invited.
There's going to be
a lot of dentists there.
Yeah, you're right.
I mean, you don't want
to suffer all weekend.
Yeah, I gotta see a dentist.
This is killing me.
Well, I'll take
a chance.
We'll go together.
Maybe I'll just
meet you there.
You don't want
to go with me?
Jerry, for all I know,
this guy went out of his way
to not invite you.
How am I gonna feel
if I show up
with an uninvited,
unwelcome intruder?
The way I feel when
I go places with you?
Hey.
So did you find
my sneakers yet? No.
But I did run into somebody
you might be interested in.
A Mr. Jon Voight,
the actor.
Jon Voight!
Are you kidding me?
Did you talk to him?
Well, he was a little
standoffish.
You didn't ask him
about the car?
No, I couldn't.
His cab pulled away,
but he did, however, make
an impression on me. Look.
What?
His tooth marks.
He bit me.
Jon Voight
bit you?
What is he,
a vampire?
No, it's justifiable.
He thought I was
going for his wallet.
He left perfect imprints.
That he did.
Now, you've got that pencil
with the bite marks on it?
We get a trained eye
to match 'em up,
and we'll see whether you're
driving Jon Voight's car.
Oh, please.
Wait a minute.
Wait, it's not
that stupid.
No, it's stupid.
Why?
Why is it
impossible?
They're both
bite marks.
You're gonna show up
at that party
with a chewed-up pencil
and Kramer's gnarled arm?
It's worth a shot.
Yeah.
So, Kramer, you want to go
to the party together?
Jerry, look, come on,
I'm an invited guest.
I can't be aiding and abetting
some party crasher.
[MUTTERING]
Excuse me.
Uh, dentist? Dentist?
Dentist?
Are you a dentist?
You a dentist?
GEORGE:
These are the balloons?
Big deal. All I see
is Woody Woodpecker.
You've got a problem
with Woody Woodpecker?
Yeah.
What is he, some sort
of an instigator?
That's right.
He's a troublemaker.
Hey, Elaine, did you
get my message?
[SHOUTING]
What?
I can't hear
a word you're saying.
I was stuck at
the Dixieland Deli all day.
My head is still ringing.
Where's Tim?
What is that,
the Empire State Building?
What?
I can't hear you!
Elaine, would you
marry me?
I told you,
I can't hear a word.
All right.
Forget it.
Hey, Tim.
Hey.
How you doing,
George?
Kramer,
how you doing?
Watch--
Watch the arm.
Tim, we don't want to bother
you. We know you're busy.
It's okay.
What is it?
Let me show
you something.
Take at look
at this--
All right, Tim.
I'm gonna get going.
Oh! Let me take down
your number.
Hey, is that
Jerry Seinfeld?
Hey, he didn't
come with us.
Uh, Tim,
the pencil.
Jerry!
Hey, Tim.
Jerry. I didn't think
you'd show.
Did you say,
"Jerry, I didn't
think you'd show,"
or "Jerry, I didn't
think you'd show"?
Elaine, hi!
Whoo!
Tim.
Well, I'm really
glad you came.
What?
I'm really glad you came.
Uh-huh.
Uh, listen, Elaine,
I've been wanting to ask you...
would you like go out
with me New Year's Eve?
Nn-nn.
Oh. Thanks.
What?
Let me ask
you something.
Could you tell if teeth marks
on somebody's arm
matched teeth marks
on a pencil?
It's possible.
Roll up
your sleeve.
Somebody bit you?
Well, not just someone.
Jon Voight.
Jon Voight bit you?
Yeah, yeah.
The pencil.
Hey, hey!
Get the pencil
out of your mouth!
You're destroying
Jon Voight's teeth marks.
That's Jon Voight's pencil?
That's right.
And I got his whole
car downstairs.
Are you the one who bought
his LeBaron convertible?
Yes!
Yes, I'm the one. Hey!
So you know
Jon Voight?
Yes, yes!
I went to dental school
with him.
Jon Voight, the actor?
Y-- No.
The periodontist.
MAN:
Can't this wait until Monday?
Come by my office.
Just a quick peek.
I'm in agony.
All right.
Sit down.
It's this one
here in the back.
[FABRIC TEARING,
AIR HISSING]
[CROWD SCREAMING OUTSIDE]
KRAMER:
Oh! You popped Woody Woodpecker!
Hey, who invited
you anyway?
You're a troublemaker.
[NERVOUSLY IMITATING
WOODY WOODPECKER LAUGH]
ANNOUNCER:
Katie, looks like Woody Woodpecker
is running out of air.
In fact, he's collapsing.
Those kids look
pretty disappointed.
Especially that big kid
up in the front.
How old is he?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
MAN: Is this Jerry Seinfeld?
Yes, it is.
You don't know me, but a really
strange thing happened.
I was at a garage sale,
and this old couple sold me
a used pair of sneakers
they claimed belonged
to Jerry Seinfeld, the comedian.
Could I have the address
to that garage sale?
Okay, thank you
very much.
I found Mom and Pop.
They're selling my sneakers.
Where are they?
Parsippany, New Jersey!
Let's go.
My car's
in the shop.
How are we getting
to Parsippany?
Oh.
Jerry, these nosebleeds
are starting again.
Maybe we should get
you to a hospital.
I ain't going
to no Bellevue.
Look at me,
I'm falling apart here.
["EVERYBODY'S TALKIN'" PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
The marching band is a perfect
example of taking something bad,
and making it difficult too.
I mean, why does the band
have to march?
We're not moving.
Maybe if they'd hold still,
we can all leave.
Is that why they do it?
People try and get away.
No, you don't.
I'm right with you.
Right with you, buddy.
The human urge to wave at
total strangers just moving by
is very strong, isn't it?
Parades and ocean liners
and those little trains that
go through amusement parks.
It's always that bittersweet,
kind of hello-goodbye
combination wave, isn't it?
Just:
I've never seen these people
before in my life,
and they're leaving.