And, you know, these
pest control companies.
They call themselves
exterminators,
but they can't really do it.
The best they can do
is get the bugs
to go to somebody else's house.
They just relocate them.
You know what I mean?
They're bug realtors
is what they are.
Uh, I think you'll
be happy here.
There's a lot of crumbs,
not much light.
They usually sleep
through the night.
You'll really have your run
the place most of the time.
Nobody really cares
about killing insects.
Even the animal rights
people don't care.
You could probably walk into
an animal rights organization
meeting and hear a speech
like "The only way to stop
"the cruelty of the scientific
testing on animals--
"ahh, got him--
is to boycott these companies."
Anyway, it's funny.
Paula and I actually met
because of Elaine.
Elaine is in my drawing class
at the New School.
I went down there
one day to see--
The nude model.
If Elaine wanted
to go get some coffee.
You know, I once went out
with a nude model.
Never let me see her naked.
Hundreds of people see her naked
every week, except me.
Needless to say,
it was quite vexing.
[LAUGHING]
Are you through?
Yeah.
So anyway, I started
to compliment Elaine
on her sketches, and it
turns out they're Paula's.
George, I just
like to doodle.
Oh, dropped
my napkin.
Jerry.
What?
What are you doing?
She had those nuts
in her mouth.
She just spit them out.
[SPITS]
Ugh!
You ate these?
Y-you sucked
on these
and then put them
on the plate?
I didn't know you were
gonna eat them.
Still.
I'm sorry you
find me so repulsive.
No. No, I don't.
I mean,
don't be silly.
Yeah.
It's just...
Well. Ahem.
If you'll excuse me,
I think I'll just go to the ladies' room.
I'll join you.
Oh, man, did you see that?
I ate discarded food.
Well, I've done that.
Yeah, but with you,
it's intentional.
Haven't you kissed her?
Yeah, but this
is different.
This is like, you know,
semi-digested foodstuff.
You know, next stop
is the stomach.
And you can
take it from there.
Ah, excuse me
one second.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, that's gonna
make a big difference.
Hey, this is dating.
You can't leave
anything to chance.
You think Shelly's upset
that I made such a big deal
about the pecans?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Yeah.
Thanks.
No problem.
Well, Jerry, I guess
we should get going.
Oh, boy.
Well, it was very nice
meeting you, Shelly.
And Jerry, be careful.
There's a lot
of nuts out there.
Alrighty. Do you
have everything?
Oh, can you
grab my purse.
Yeah.
Yeah. So?
Don't you see
what this is?
Yeah, it's a doodle.
Yeah. A doodle of me.
Look at the size
of the nose, the ears.
All my features
are distorted.
Oh, it's an affectionate
caricature.
I'm grotesque.
I look like a troll.
It's just a drawing.
Don't you see
what this says?
How could you
possibly like somebody
if you think
they look like this?
[ANGRILY]:
Hello!
What is with him?
Usual.
Huh.
So you know what?
My friend Judy recommended
me for a job at Viking Press.
Hey, good for you.
Yeah. But get this.
Viking has a deal
with the Plaza Hotel.
They've got a two-bedroom suite
there for out-of-town clients.
So guess what I did?
Oh, come on.
You told them you're
from out of town
just so you could
stay in a hotel room?
I know, I know, Jerry.
But it's the Plaza.
I've never stayed there.
It'll be like
a little vacation.
Well, be sure to catch
a Broadway show
while you're in town.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, listen. I used your
parents' address in Florida.
Oh. They're coming into town
tomorrow, by the way.
Hey. What's this?
Don't ask.
What is it?
A drawing of Mr. Magoo?
No, it's George.
[LAUGHING]
It is!
Are you enjoying
yourself?
I'm sorry.
You see?
Listen...when is your
next drawing class?
Tomorrow.
All right. I want you
to do me a favor.
What?
I want you to find out
if she likes me.
Find out if
she likes you?
What are you,
in high school?
George, come on.
Can't you just, like,
talk to her yourself?
But then she's gonna
know that I like her
more than she likes me.
You know, my parents are coming
in, and I've gotta clean up.
So if you and Potsie
are done scheming...
Well, they're in.
What's in?
The Mackinaw peaches,
Jerry.
The Mackinaw peaches!
JERRY: Ah.
Right. The one's
from Oregon
that are only ripe
for two weeks a year.
Yeah. Yeah, I split
a case with Newman.
I wait all year for this.
Oh. This is
fantastic. Mm.
Makes your
taste buds come alive.
It's like having
a circus in your mouth.
Take a taste.
I don't want to.
Just take a taste.
Come on, jus--
I don't want it!
You don't want it!
I am not gonna
taste your peach.
I ate someone's
pecan last night.
I'm not gonna
eat your peach.
Jerry, this is
a miracle of nature
that exists
for a brief period.
It's like
the aurora borealis.
Mmm. Mmm.
Yeah.
Holy cow, what is this?
What?
I think I got
flea bites.
Flea bites?
Yeah. Look at this.
My ankle's all bitten up.
You got a dog?
No.
Well, that is
strange.
How can I have fleas?
Don't sweat it, buddy.
I used to have fleas.
What did you do
about them?
What do you mean?
Hey, Jerry!
Hey!
How you doing?
Kramer.
Hi, Jerry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Jerry, I'm your mother.
Now, what is it?
Mom, Dad...I have fleas.
ELAINE:
Hey, Paula.
I hear you've been
going out with George Costanza.
How did you know?
Everybody knows.
You know, George
told me he thinks
you're totally cute
and everything.
He said that?
Yep.
Do you like George?
Yeah. He's cool.
No, I mean...do you like him
or do you "like him" like him?
"Like" like.
Looks aren't that
important to me, you know?
Ms. Benes...
are you chewing gum?
I'm sorry.
Yep. They're in your
bedroom too, Mr. Seinfeld.
You got a full-blown
outbreak of fleas on your hands.
I don't get it.
How did this happen?
I don't have a dog.
I don't explain them,
Mr. Seinfeld.
I just exterminate them.
I don't
understand this.
I'm gonna have to
seal the place up
for 48 hours and fog it.
That's the only way
to get rid of them.
Nobody can be in here
for 48 hours?
I got my parents
in town.
Well, unless you
wanna kill them...
they can't stay in here.
This stuff is pretty toxic.
I'll go get my stuff.
It's in the truck.
Okay.
How you doing?
Hi.
Bug guy.
Why do you have
a bug guy?
I have fleas.
Ugh! Fleas?
How did you get fleas?
I don't know.
But everyone's
gotta clear out
of the apartment
for two days.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do with my parents.
They'll never let me
pay for a hotel.
And if they go someplace
on their own,
I'm sure it'll be
some awful dump.
Wait a second. Have you
checked into the Plaza yet?
No.
Oh, no.
Come on,
come on, come on.
No, no, no, no, no!
Come on! Come on!
All right!
Good.
[BUZZ]
Yeah?
GEORGE:
Yeah. Good.
Well, what about you?
Where are you gonna stay?
I don't know.
I'm gonna ask Shelly.
But she still might be
upset about the masticated pecan incident.
Hey, I found out from
Paula. She likes George.
I bet he'll
be relieved.
Yeah. When he's dead,
he'll be relieved.
Oh, by the way, Viking Press
sent a Fed Ex for you
to my parents.
They brought it with them.
Yeah, that's just
some stuff about the company.
Hey. Hey, did you
talk to Paula?
Yeah.
So, what did she say?
She likes you.
She said she liked me.
You're kidding?
She said that?
Yeah.
Those were her exact words?
"I like George."
Yep.
Ha-ha!
How do you like that?
Jerry, How do you
like that?
You see. I get myself
into a tizzy.
I'm all worked up.
And for what?
For nothing.
She said looks weren't even
that important to her.
You see--
What?
Uh-oh.
She said--
She said looks aren't
that important to her?
Let me rephrase that.
She thinks I'm ugly.
I knew it.
Well, see, the thing of it is.
You know, there's a lot
of ugly people out there walking
around, but they don't know
they're ugly, because
nobody actually tells them.
So, what's your point?
I don't know.
Okay.
The point, George,
is she likes you.
Oh, so what.
I'd rather she hate me
and thought I was good-looking.
Then at least I could get
somebody else.
What is this?
Why am I itching?
That would be
the fleas.
Hey.
Hey, how do you like this? Ha-ha.
Oh, my God.
Morty, let's go.
This is too nice.
Hey. This is the kind
of room Sinatra stays in.
Hey.
Look, macadamia nuts.
Macadamia nuts?
Yeah, you know
what these cost?
They're like
80 cents a nut.
Jerry, are you sure
this is all right?
Yeah, it's all
taken care of.
MORTY:
Hey! They got a phone in the john here!
Judy?
Hey!
Hi. Thank you so much for
recommending me to Viking Press.
It is my pleasure.
Just make sure
you give that manuscript a good read.
Manuscript?
Yeah, I'm sure they FedExed
you a manuscript.
They want to see
that you can read
an unpublished work
and give insightful criticism.
Oh.
Read it twice
if you have to.
This is a big step
in your career.
Yeah. I gotta go.
Hey, what about
lunch?
I gotta go.
Thank God I found you.
Oh, hey!
Do you still have
that FedEx?
Yeah, I got it.
It's in the apartment.
But we can't go in there.
It's being fumigated.
No, I'll take
my chances.
Come on.
JERRY:
You see.
Jerry, I need
that FedEx right now.
I told you
to take it.
I didn't know that it was
a manuscript that I had to read.
Well, you can't
go in there.
It's like a gas
chamber in there.
Hey.
I left a Mackinaw peach
in your refrigerator.
Kramer, they're fumigating.
There's toxic gas in there.
Toxic gas?
Oh, you'll be fine.
You were there a few minutes?
An hour and a half!
I was reading a manuscript.
I just couldn't put it down.
My manuscript?
How do you feel?
Now that you mention it,
a little woozy.
Kramer, you've got to
go back in there and grab my manuscript.
I'm not going
back in there.
All right.
Well, then, where is it?
Well, I left it
on the coffee table.
What are
you doing?
I'm going in.
Didn't you see
the sign on the door?
Well, I thought it was
so your parents wouldn't walk in
while you were
with a girl.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[GASPS FOR AIR]
It's not on
any table, Kramer.
Where is it?
Well, I don't know.
I was in the bathroom,
the kitchen.
Okay.
Bathroom, kitchen.
Could you get me
a soda?
Jerry...I had
some milk.
I made a sandwich.
I gotta get out
of the building.
[GASPS FOR AIR]
I couldn't find
it anywhere.
How did you get fleas, anyway?
I don't know.
Who could have been
in my apartment?
I looked everywhere.
Even under the couch.
But all I could find were
these stupid Chunky wrappers--
Wait a second.
Did you say
Chunky wrappers?
Yeah.
Let me see those.
Oh, I know the chunky
that left these Chunkys.
Newman!
Got him!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
JERRY:
Newman!
Open the door, Newman!
I know you're in there!
Hello, Jerry.
What a pleasant
surprise.
There's nothing
pleasant about it.
Let's just
cut the crap.
You gave me fleas.
I know it,
and you know it.
Fleas?
[LAUGHING]
That's preposterous.
How could I give you fleas?
Now, if you don't mind--
Oh, but I do.
There's probably fleas
crawling all over your little snack bar.
So you have fleas.
Maybe you keep your house
in a state of disrepair.
Maybe you live
in squalor.
You know, Newman...
the thing about fleas
is that they irritate
the skin...
and they start to
itch.
Oh, maybe you can hold out
five seconds or 10.
Maybe 15 or 20.
[STRAINED BREATHING]
But after awhile...
[COUGHS]
...no matter how much
willpower
a person may have,
it won't matter.
Because they're crawling--
Crawling on your skin.
Up your legs,
up your spine, up your back.
All right!
I've got them!
I'm ripe with fleas!
Ooh. Oh. Oh,
that feels good.
Hey, this guy charges
100 bucks an hour,
but I'm telling you,
he's worth every penny. Oh!
I'm next.
Hey, Leo, get this.
I'm watching
four movies at once.
Pay-per-view.
I love these nuts.
This champagne's
gone flat.
Nana.
[LAUGHS]
Let the chambermaid
clean it up.
Hello.
What's
the matter?
Well, I spoke to Elaine--
Hey, look.
No shave.
No. Why should that make
any difference to you?
It doesn't.
Of course not.
You don't care
what I look like.
That's right.
I don't.
I suppose I could
just pull this out
and walk around like this,
and you wouldn't care.
Not a whit.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
I suppose we could
go to Lincoln Center,
and I could wear
sneakers and jeans
and that would be fine too.
You could wear
sweatpants.
I could?
You could drape yourself
in velvet for all I care.
Velvet?
ELAINE:
Did you read the whole thing?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. So, what's it about?
Well, it's--
It's a story
about love,
deception, greed,
lust and...unbridled
enthusiasm.
Unbridled enthusiasm?
Well, that's what led to
Billy Mumphrey's downfall.
Oh, boy.
You see, Elaine, Billy
was a simple country boy.
You might say, a cockeyed
optimist who got himself
mixed up in the high-stakes
game of world diplomacy
and international intrigue.
Oh, my God.
Well, here we go.
Could I have a Scotch
on the rocks?
May I?
Yeah, go ahead.
All right.
What is this?
What? What do
you mean?
I can't taste this.
What are you
talking about?
This food.
It has no taste.
Nothing.
I'm getting nothing!
It must be the toxic gas
from the fumigation.
What?
JERRY:
Hey, thanks for letting me stay here.
Well, I don't keep
pecans in the house,
so I didn't think
there would be a problem.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, damn.
What's the matter?
I forgot my toothbrush.
Oh, no problem.
You can use mine.
Yours?
You know what?
I think I'll brush later.
Brush now.
Sure.
Newman. Newman, let me have
a bite of your Mackinaw.
What for?
You got your own.
Oh, Come on. Come on.
I need to taste it.
Nothing.
I can't evening taste
the Mackinaw.
Well, that's a shame.
Wait all year and
I can't even taste it.
You can't taste them?
Why waste them?
Why not give them all to me?
ELAINE:
It's a story about
love...deception...
greed...lust...
and...unbridled
enthusiasm.
Unbridled enthusiasm?
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
That's...what led to,
uh...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Billy Mumphrey's
downfall.
Hmm. Interesting take.
So you believe that had
he not been so enthusiastic,
he could have
averted disaster.
Y-Yes. Yes.
That's right.
You see, Billy Mumphrey
was a simple country boy.
Some might say a cockeyed
optimist who got caught up
in the dirty game
of world diplomacy
and international intrigue.
So it was more a question
of attitude than politics?
Yes. Yes,
Mr. Mandel.
Hey! Under Siege
is on again.
Who's up for it?
No more nuts.
[GROANS]
Oh, my God.
What the hell
is this?
Don't tell me.
Velvet?
It's the real deal.
She's seen you in this thing?
That's right.
We just had sex.
You know, Jerry...
I've been searching
for someone
a long time.
Well, the search is over.
And now the search for
the right psychiatrist begins.
[SNAPS]
So, uh, what's with
the suitcase?
Uh, she threw me out.
Why?
I wouldn't use
her toothbrush.
So where you staying?
Well, I guess I'm stuck
with the Velvet Fog.
MR. MANDEL:
Three hours of
massage time,
12 in-room movies,
including several
adult features,
five shoeshines
and $400 worth of snacks.
Not to mention
the damage to the room.
Mr. Mandel,
you don't understand.
My friend had fleas.
I ran into the gas.
It could have killed me.
My-- My other friend
couldn't taste his peaches.
They're only good
for two weeks.
I think you've
read one too many Billy Mumphrey stories.
Good day, Ms. Benes.
Okay.
Good day.
Hi, George.
Hi.
This is fantastic.
Have you ever had
a Mackinaw peach?
Oh, yeah, I love those.
Well, too bad.
It's all done.
[GAGS]
Yes.
Yes, it's back.
I can taste again.
What's the date today?
Uh, 15th.
15th! Yes. Last day
for the Mackinaws.
I can still make it.
Wait. Newman.
Newman, what--
Sorry. Last one.
But if you want
to suck the pit.
[LAUGHING]
[MOCK LAUGHING]
Look...Beauford,
it's the mailman.
[BARKING]
You remember
the mailman, don't you?
Kramer!
Kramer, don't!
Get him!
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hello?
Is anybody her--
Oh.
They said they were
sending over an Asian woman.
Oh, my God.
[♪]