Buying shoes is one of
the great shopping challenges.
Ever seen someone put on
a new pair of shoes?
They turn into a zombie once
they start walking around.
"Yeah, these are pretty good."
Then they have that little
1-foot-high mirror there.
What is that? To see what
cats will think of my shoes?
What is that angle?
Bum passed out on the curb.
"Hey, what do you
think of these?
I just got them. I've seen
them from that angle myself."
GEORGE:
That guy was amazing.
He could dunk.
And he was my height.
What was
his name again?
Jimmy.
Jimmy. Right.
JERRY:
I don't know how you could forget.
He kept referring to himself
in the third person.
"Jimmy's under the boards.
"Jimmy's in the open.
Jimmy makes the shot."
Ah, you're just mad
because we beat you.
Jerry, it's my fault.
I couldn't make a shot.
These losses
stay with me.
They fester, Jerry.
No, this is
gonna plague me.
Oh, mama!
Ow!
Hey! Jimmy!
Gee!
Great game!
Oh, yeah. Jimmy
played pretty good.
Hey, you know,
I felt like we had a synergy out there.
You know, like we were
really helping each other.
Hey, what do you got there?
These?
Yeah.
These are Jimmy's
training shoes.
Yeah. I've seen
these things.
What are they--?
They make your legs stronger?
Oh, yeah.
Jimmy couldn't jump
at all before he got these.
Jimmy...was like you.
Huh.
They're plyometric.
GEORGE:
Plyometric?
Yeah. They isolate
the muscles.
The muscle has
to grow or die.
Where you get them?
Jimmy sells them.
You sell them?
Oh, yeah. But Jimmy's
all out right now.
Moving to Manhattan...
set Jimmy back a bit.
Hey, listen. Let me
give you my card.
It's got my
home number on it.
I want to buy the first pair
when the next shipment comes in.
All right.
All right, Jimmy, good talking to you.
Jimmy will
see you around.
What day is today?
Oh, Tuesday.
Damn it. I shouldn't have
worked out today.
Mr. Wilhelm called
a big meeting.
I'm going to be sweating
the whole time.
Why?
You took a shower.
It wouldn't take.
Ten minutes from now
I'll be sweating all over again.
I can feel it.
I'm a human heat pump.
Well, you ought to
take cold showers.
Cold showers?
They're for psychotics.
Well, I take them.
They give me a whoosh.
All right.
I'll see you guys later.
So, what?
Are you heading home?
No. Got a dental
appointment.
Oh, what?
Tim Whatley?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got a checkup Thursday.
How do you
like that.
You know, you really
shouldn't brush 24 hours
before seeing
the dentist.
[SPITS]
I think that's eat
24 hours before surgery.
Oh, no. You've got
to eat before surgery.
You need
your strength.
MR. WILHELM:
I called this meeting because we have a problem.
For the last few months,
someone has been stealing
equipment
from the club.
Until recently,
it's been little things:
bases, batting
helmets, donuts.
But...two nights ago,
they pulled a big one.
They took a pitching machine,
a batting cage,
the infield tarp and all of
Mr. Steinbrenner's vitamins.
Now, we have reason
to believe it's an inside job.
So if anybody here knows
anything about it,
I recommend strongly
that...you come forward.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Dr. Whatley's running
a little late.
If you'd like to
take a seat, I'll call you when he's ready.
All right.
ELAINE:
Oh, okay.
Right. Thanks,
Mr. Pitt.
Okay. Goodbye.
Hey. You want to go see
the Velvet Fog?
The Velvet Fog?
Yeah, Mel Tormé.
That's his nickname.
What the hell is
a Velvet Fog?
Do you want to go or not?
Well, where is it?
He's performing
at this AMCA benefit.
AMCA?
Able Mentally
Challenged Adults.
I can't watch a man
sing a song.
What, are you crazy?
They get all emotional.
They sway.
It's embarrassing.
Well, what am I
gonna do for a date?
Oh, do you know that, um--
That blond guy
who's always on the Exercycle
at the health club?
I don't think so.
You know, he's really
handsome, with those--
Elaine, I really don't...
pay much attention
to men's faces.
You can't find
beauty in a man?
No. I find them
repugnant and unappealing.
Hey.
To wit.
What?
No, Elaine and I
were just discussing
whether or not I could admit
a man is attractive.
Hmm. Oh, I'll tell you
who's an attractive man.
George Will.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he has
a clean look.
Scrubbed
and shampooed.
He's smart.
No, no, I don't find
him all that bright.
So you got
any cavities?
Just one.
Yeah?
Gotta go back.
Oh, but get this.
Elaine, you will
appreciate this. What?
I'm sitting in
Tim Whatley's waiting room.
He's got a Penthouse
right out on the table.
Penthouse?
Yeah. What is that?
I mean, isn't that sick?
I'd be embarrassed
to have that in my apartment.
So, what's wrong
with that?
He's a doctor.
I mean, it's supposed to be,
like, a sterile environment.
So did you, uh,
take a look?
Of course. But that's got
nothing to do with it.
Well, I'll tell you.
I'm looking forward
to my appointment on Thursday.
I might even get there
a few minutes early.
[GASPS]
Hey.
Hey, listen.
Do either of you guys
know that blond guy
whose always on the Exercycle
at the health club?
You know, he's just
really handsome?
I, uh--
I wouldn't know.
You know, just admitting
a man is handsome
doesn't necessarily
make you a homosexual.
It doesn't help.
All right.
Never mind.
I'll see you.
Hey.
You know those shoes
that Jimmy had?
I cut a deal
with him.
We're gonna import
a case of them together.
Why are you doing that for?
You got a job.
There's a lot of
money in this.
He's got a proven
sales method.
Yeah? What's that?
He jumps.
Jimmy's got a backer.
Jimmy's jumping
for dollars.
Jimmy and George
are gonna get rich.
Will you stop with the Jimmys?
Hey, what is this?
Kung Pao.
Hot.
Ooh. Kung Pao!
ELAINE:
Look at me.
Come on. I'm stretching
right in front of you.
Hey, a smile.
Ha. We made contact.
All right.
One more stretch
and then go talk to him.
You know...Jimmy is
pretty sweet on you.
Oh. Ha!
He is?
Oh, yeah. Jimmy's
been watching you.
You're just
Jimmy's type.
Oh. Really?
Jimmy's new in town.
Jimmy, uh, doesn't
really know anyone.
Oh, well. I'd like
to get to know him.
Jimmy would like to
get to know you.
[GASPS]
You think Jimmy
likes Mel Tormé?
Jimmy loves the Velvet Fog.
[SCREAMS]
TIM:
Hey, Kramer.
Well, you're looking
sharp there, Tim.
Yeah, well.
I do what I can.
How have you been?
Oh, fine, good.
Yeah. I've just
been occupying myself
with some of your, uh,
reading material.
So, what will it be?
Novocain?
Oh, yes.
Yes, indeed.
Why don't we just
clear a path first. Yeah.
You remember
Mr. Thirsty.
[SUCTIONING]
Ah. You too
with these?
Yeah, I'm onboard.
So, what did Tim say?
[SLURRED SPEECH]
Well, he said I gotta cut out the Skittles.
Looks like he gave you
some Novocain.
Oh, I'm loaded.
What about the Penthouse?
Did you ask?
Well, he said that, you know,
it helps his patients
relax a little bit.
And he's got
a new policy.
Adults only.
Adults only?
Yeah.
What the hell is
going on over there?
You know, it's great.
You know? No kids allowed.
You don't have to
watch your language.
You find a need to use a lot
of obscenities at the dentist?
Heh-heh.
When they pull that needle out,
I let the expletives fly.
Hey, come on.
Watch it.
You're drooling
all over the floor.
How much Novocain
did that guy give you?
I can't hold the water.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Jimmy.
Jimmy's ready.
Jimmy's got some
new moves. Go, Jimmy.
Check Jimmy out.
Oh!
Jimmy's down!
[GROANS]
MAN:
It's pretty bad, man.
He's gonna be
in traction.
Jimmy might have
a compound fracture.
Jimmy's going into shock.
Why weren't you careful
with your drool?
Hey, I'm doing
the best I can.
Why are you taking it
so personally?
Because if he can't jump,
there goes my sneaker business?
Well, I said I'm sorry!
Jimmy's gonna
get you, Kramer.
Jimmy holds grudges.
Let Jimmy go!
You know I can't
feel anything.
[SLURRING]
Hey, taxi!
Taxi!
Okay.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
You've got it.
He's got it.
Oh.
Please. Go ahead.
No, no.
You were here first.
No, please. I insist.
I'll grab the next one.
Let's share.
We share,
all right?
Yes. Let's.
That's a great idea.
Oh.
Oh!
MAN:
My name is
Arnold Deensfrei.
[SLOWLY]
What is your name?
Cosmo Kramer.
It's nice to meet you.
Very nice to
meet you, Cosmo.
Are you heading home?
Yeah, heading home.
Mm. Good for you.
You're really
independent.
Well, you're not doing
too bad yourself.
Yeah!
[CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
Anyway...Jimmy, uh,
couldn't be here today.
So he asked me to
fill in for him.
And...I'm sure that
you'll be impressed
at what can be
accomplished after only
a few short days
of training.
Heh-heh.
Here we go.
[STRAINING]
KRAMER:
The Velvet Fog.
What about
the Velvet Fog?
Well...he's singing
at a benefit.
And I'm gonna be
sitting at his table.
Oh. I'm going
to that.
I'm a guest
of honor.
What are you
talking about?
Well, this afternoon
I shared a cab with this...Deensfrei.
Yeah, yeah.
Arnold Deensfrei.
He runs the AMCA.
Well, okay.
That's the guy.
He's organizing
the dinner.
I know that.
But why are you going?
Well, because
we hit it off.
And he was very impressed
with what I do.
What you do?
You don't do anything.
Well, apparently I do
something, because I'm sitting
at the head table
with Mr. Mel Tormé!
[SIGHS]
What are those?
Oh, these are my
vertical-leap training shoes.
Wait a second.
Were you wearing
those shoes in the cab?
Yeah, yeah. Right after
I left the Y.
Don't you see
what happened here?
He couldn't talk.
He's wearing these shoes.
He's drooling.
What?
He thinks you're
mentally challenged.
Well...
You know...
What happens when
you show up?
He'll see that
you're not.
Not necessarily--
I know.
Cheryl, would you ready
the nitrous oxide, please?
[INHALES]
[STRANGLED VOICE]
It's good.
Where's Jennifer today?
Oh, she's over at
Dr. Seisman's office.
Yeah, we find it fun
to swap now and then.
Mm-hm.
You just...take some deep
breaths and...try to relax.
[CHAIR HUMS]
Woo!
[PHONE RINGS]
Oh, man!
Ah!
This is George.
Oh, Sport's Wholesalers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thanks for calling me back.
No, no, I still got
the shoes. Lots of them.
Yeah. This is beautiful
athletic gear.
Oh. I'm sorry. I've got
to call you right back.
Yeah. All right.
Mr. Wilhelm.
So, George...have
you heard anything
about the missing
equipment?
No, no. Not a thing.
You know, George, there's
nothing I hate more than a liar.
Well, there's...no room
for someone like that
in this organization.
Are you feeling
all right, George?
Yeah, fine.
You look a little warm.
It's the chicken.
You're a terrible liar, George.
Look at you.
You're a wreck.
You're sweating bullets.
It's the Kung Pao.
Hm.
George likes
his chicken spicy.
ELAINE:
Maybe you were
still under the gas.
Maybe you were hallucinating
you were coming out,
but you were still
under the gas.
I don't think so.
I think they were
getting dressed.
And not only that.
My shirt was out.
Your shirt was out?
I think so.
Well, what kind
of a shirt was it?
You know, like
a tennis shirt.
Oh. You don't
tuck those in.
Sometimes I tuck them.
Sometimes I don't.
Well, were you tucked?
I think I was tucked.
All right.
Well, say you were.
I mean, what do you think
could have happened?
I don't know!
But I was spitting out
and rinsing
like there was
no tomorrow.
Ugh.
Is this guy a dentists
or Caligula?
What are you getting?
I don't think I'm hungry.
Okay. So you were violated
by two people
while you were under the gas.
So what?
You're single.
I'm damaged goods now.
Join the club.
Did you ever call
that guy from the health club?
Oh, yeah. Jimmy.
Jimmy?
Mm-hmm.
That's the guy?
Yeah.
I can't believe
you're going out with him.
Why?
I don't know.
He's so strange.
How so?
Didn't you ever noticed
he always refers to himself
in the third person.
Jimmy can dunk.
Jimmy's new in town.
Jimmy will see you later.
No, no, wait a minute.
That's not him.
That's the guy who
gave me Jimmy's number.
That's Jimmy.
That's the way he talks.
I'm gonna go see
Mel Tormé with him?
Jimmy's gonna put
the moves on Elaine.
So, I have to go see
Steinbrenner later.
Mr. Wilhelm told him that
I was the one responsible
for stealing
all the merchandise.
Why?
Because when he questioned me
about it, I was sweating
from the Kung Pao.
I don't know how
you could eat that spicy chicken.
George likes
spicy chicken.
What's that?
I like spicy chicken.
No, no. You said,
"George likes spicy chicken."
No, I didn't.
Yes. You said,
"George likes spicy chicken."
You're turning
into Jimmy.
George is getting
upset!
So, what did you want
to see Jimmy about?
Well...Jimmy...
[LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY]
about tonight.
There's been a little
misunderstanding.
Ha.
Jimmy doesn't like
misunderstandings.
Yeah. Well,
what happened was--
Jimmy and misunderstandings
kind of clash.
You know, I've never heard
anyone talk the way you do.
It's very unusual.
Well, Jimmy's
very unusual.
Well, anyway...see when I made
the date, I thought that Jimmy--
Hey, look. Hank's
got a new boyfriend.
Jimmy's not threatened
by Hank's sexuality.
Jimmy's happy for Hank.
Elaine once tried
to convert one.
But Elaine's not gonna
go through that again.
I'm gonna go and try
and find some candy.
You want some?
Yeah.
What kind?
I don't care.
Hey, Jimmy.
Hi, Elaine.
Elaine got a new dress.
Jimmy likes it.
[BOTH LAUGH]
There's no candy
around here.
Hey, Jimmy.
Well...look
who's here? Whoa.
That's the guy
who sidelined Jimmy.
What?
That's the guy
who took the bread
out of Jimmy's mouth.
Jimmy's out of work
because of you.
Oh!
Jimmy wants a piece
of Kramer! Come on, now!
Get your hands
off Jimmy!
Jimmy's gonna
get you, Kramer!
Hands off Jimmy!
Don't touch Jimmy!
Let go
of Jimmy!
[SLURRING]
Is my lip swollen?
Guy's got
a problem.
No, no. I've been living
alone a long time now.
Well, I think
that's the tops.
[MUMBLING]
Okay.
[KNOCKS]
You wanted to see me,
Mr. Steinbrenner?
Yes, George, come in.
George, I've been
your biggest supporter here.
And that's why I was
disappointed to hear
that you've been
pilfering the equipment.
George would never
do anything like that.
No, why would I?
I own it.
Right.
So, what are you saying?
Why would George steal
from the Yankees?
He wouldn't.
Of course not.
Exactly.
I don't really know what
the hell is going on here?
Sir?
Nothing.
Well, I think it's about
time for George's lunch.
Yes, it is.
All right. Let's see.
What do I have today?
Oh, darn it.
It's ham and cheese again.
And she forgot
the fancy mustard.
I told her I like
that fancy mustard.
You know, you could put
that fancy mustard on a shoe,
and it would taste
pretty good to me.
She made up for it
with a cupcake though. Hey, look at this.
You know, I've got a new system
of eating these things, George.
I use to peel off
the chocolate.
Now, I turn it upside down.
I eat the cake first and save...
MEL TORMÉ:
Ladies and gentlemen...
I wanna dedicate this song
to a very courageous young man.
♪ When you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world
Smiles with you ♪
♪ When you're laughing ♪
♪ The sun comes
Shining through ♪
♪ But when you're crying ♪
♪ You bring on the rain ♪
♪ So stop that sighing ♪
♪ Be happy again ♪
♪ Keep on smiling ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world
Smiles with you ♪
♪ The whole world ♪
♪ Smiles ♪
♪ With ♪
BOTH:
♪ You ♪
Hey.
Got the new Penthouse.
Ah. Where's
my Mr. Goodbar?
Yeah. Here you are.
Oh, here. Listen.
"Dear Penthouse,
"I'd like to tell you about
an experience I recently had.
"As an avid reader,
I've always wondered
BOTH:
"if the letters are true.
"I'm a dentist.
"And one afternoon
my hygienist and I decided
"to have a little fun
with one of our patients.
"Of course, none of
our patients had any idea
"exactly what
we were up to.
I was still wondering
whether or not..."
[♪]