Monkeys are really the end
of the line in the pet world.
I think when you're at the
monkey level of pet ownership,
have a kid. I mean, come on.
I mean, you're so close.
If you need a pet that can
roller skate and smoke cigars,
it's time to think
about a family.
Monkeys, of course, were the
first astronauts in the '60s,
which, I'm sure, made perfect
sense in the monkey brain.
"I feel that is the next
logical step for me
"because I've been workin'
"with the Italian guy
and the crank organ,
and I think I'm ready to handle
the maximum reentry G-forces."
Take toilet paper,
for example.
Do you realize
that toilet paper
has not changed
in my lifetime?
It's just paper
on a cardboard roll.
That's it.
And in 10,000 years,
it will still be
exactly the same,
because, really,
what else can they do?
Yeah, that's true.
There really has been
no development in toilet paper.
And, I mean, everything else
has changed.
[CHUCKLES]
But toilet paper
is exactly the same,
and will be so
until we're dead.
Yeah, you're right,
George.
What else can they do?
It's just paper
on a roll, that's it,
and that's all
it will ever be.
Wow.
You find this interesting,
don't you?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Oh, thanks very much.
The soup was really good.
What are ya
tellin' him for?
What?
He's the busboy. You think
he cares about the soup?
Yeah, well, wouldn't he want
the soup to be good?
Elaine, it's all this guy can do
to keep from killin' himself.
Come on.
You think he's back there,
talkin' to the chef, goin',
"Hey, they like the soup!
Keep it up!"
Hey, isn't that
Alec Berg?
Yep.
Alec Berg.
He's got a good
John Houseman name.
Yeah.
[SNOOTILY]
Alec Berg.
Mr. Berg.
I can't stand him.
He is so pretentious.
John Houseman?
No, Alec Berg.
Elaine!
Hi!
Hi.
Jerry.
Hi, Alec.
Hey, did you hear
about Gary Fogel? Yeah.
You gonna go
to the funeral on Friday?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, did I see you on TV
at the Ranger game?
Are those your seats,
right behind the glass?
Those are them, yeah.
Season tickets.
Uh, you know, unfortunately,
I can't go tonight.
So they're available
if you'd like to use them.
Oh, I'd love to.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
You just call my secretary.
She'll arrange everything.
Gee, thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Ah, it's my pleasure.
Be good.
Okay.
You know, I actually might
not use them on Friday either,
so...I'll let you know.
All right.
Thanks again.
Thank you very much.
Really, thank you.
JERRY:
Well, what about these nitwits
that get on a plane
with nothin' to read?
Ya know who
these people are? Who?
These are the people
that wanna talk to you.
They've got nothing else to do,
why not disturb you?
I will never understand people.
They're the worst.
♪ Something's up ♪
[GASPS]
♪ There's something
In the air ♪
Well, what is with you?
Well...
I think this is it.
What's it?
I saw Siena again.
Siena?
Yeah, he's dating a crayon.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
We discussed toilet paper.
Toilet paper?
Yep, yep,
I told her how toilet paper
hasn't changed in my lifetime
and probably wouldn't change
for the next 50,000 years,
and she was fascinated.
Fascinated!
What are you
talkin' about?
Yeah.
Toilet paper's
changed.
It's softer.
Softer.
More sheets per role.
Sheets.
A wide variety
of colors. Colors.
All right. Okay. Fine, fine.
It's changed.
It's not really the point.
Anyway, uh...
I'm thinkin'
of makin' a big move.
What?
I might...tell her
that I love her.
Oh, my.
Ooh.
I, uh-- I came
this close last night,
and then I just--
I just chickened out.
Well...
that's a big move,
Georgie-boy.
Are you confident in
the "I love you" return?
Fifty-fifty.
'Cause if you don't
get that return...
that's a pretty big matzo ball
hangin' out there.
Well... I've just
gotta say it once.
Everybody else gets to say it.
Wh-wh-why can't I say it?
What?
You've never said it?
Once, to a dog.
He licked himself
and left the room.
Well, so it wasn't a total loss.
Hey.
Hey! I forgot
to tell ya!
I got tickets to the
Rangers/Devils playoff tonight.
Oh, I'm there.
Monongahela!
What about you, George?
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Can't do it. Can't do it.
Sorry, got a date.
So? So?
No, no, no,
if you must know, I...
I would rather
be with her than...
Than go to the game.
Ooh!
Well, she must be a very
special lady, huh, George?
Ha!
Yeah.
Well, what do I do
with the extra ticket?
Oh, hey! Can I bring
David Puddy?
He's a big Devils fan.
Sure, fine with me.
Hey, by the way,
if anybody wants
an inside tour of the zoo,
Sienna works there as a trainer.
So she works at the zoo?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like Dian Fossey, huh?
You know,
she's the only person
that's ever been accepted
into gorilla society.
And you know,
once those gorillas accept you,
you got it made
in the shade.
ELAINE:
Hey, so how long have you been a Devils fan?
PUDDY:
Since I was a kid. I'm from Jersey.
Yeah? Well, we're gonna
kick your butts tonight.
Ain't no way, man.
Yes.
We're primed.
All right, you almost ready?
'Cause Jerry and Kramer are
gonna be here any second.
What the--?
So what do ya think?
What is that?
I painted my face.
You painted your face?
Yeah.
Why?
Oh, you know,
support the team.
Well, ya can't walk around
like that.
Why not?
Because...
it's insane?
They gotta know you're there.
This is the playoffs.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Yah!
Hey.
Hi.
Dave's, um...
painted his face.
Oh. Yeah, yeah,
that's cool.
You gotta support
your team, huh?
Okay, ready to go?
Let's get it on!
All right! Go, Devils!
Go, Devils!
Let's go, Devils!
Come on!
[ORGAN PLAYING FESTIVE MELODY]
You stink, Messier!
We're gonna get you,
Messy Ass!
Will you sit down?
Hey, man, I'm just tryin'
to support the team.
David, will you sit down? You're
disturbing everybody. Sit down.
Oh, yeah. 'Cause
you're a Rangers fan,
and you know I'm messin'
with their heads.
Yeah! Let's go!
[SIREN BLARING]
ANNOUNCER [OVER RADIO]:
Devils' goal!
Stephane Richer scores
from just inside the blue line.
And the Devils take--
[RADIO SILENCES]
Well, you know I could
have actually gone to that.
So why didn't you?
Well, didn't wanna
break our date.
Oh. Well...
Because I...
I love you.
You know? I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
[GUFFAWS]
We took it to ya.
You couldn't get it
outta your zone all night.
We were aggressive.
We didn't let you penetrate!
Yeah, all right.
That's enough outta you.
There's still three more games
left in this series, my friend,
and it's far from being over.
Very far from being over.
Watch out!
Hey, what are ya doin'?
Watch where you're drivin', man!
Don't mess
with the Devil, buddy!
We're number one.
We beat anybody.
We're the Devils!
The Devils!
[HISSES]
El diablo.
Dios mío...
!¡El diablo!
JERRY:
"I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat."
Yep.
Big matzo ball.
Huge matzo ball.
Those damn "I love you" returns.
Well, it's all over,
I slipped up.
Oh, you don't know.
You know how fast
these things deteriorate
when there's an "I love you"
outta the bag?
You can't have a relationship
where one person says,
"I love you,"
and the other one says,
"I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat."
Unless you're married.
I mean, now she thinks I'm one
of these guys that loves her.
Nobody wants to be with somebody
that loves them.
No, people hate that.
You want somebody
who doesn't like ya.
Ideally.
Look, I am never saying
"I love you" again
unless they say it first.
Matzo ball soup.
That would be me.
Hey, Jerry?
You're a smart guy, right?
No question about it.
All right.
I was supposed to go
on this special tour today
with George's girlfriend.
At the zoo?
Yeah, but...
before I met up with her,
I stopped to look
at the monkeys,
when all of a sudden,
I am hit in the face
with a banana peel.
I turn and look,
and there is this monkey
really laughin' it up!
Then someone tells me
that he did it.
Well, I pick up
the banana peel,
and I wait for that monkey
to turn around,
and then I...whack...
let him have it.
Kramer, you threw a banana peel
at a monkey?
Well, he started it!
It's a monkey, Kramer.
Well, he pushed my buttons.
I couldn't help it, Jerry!
Well, I still think it's wrong.
All right, all right, fine.
Take the monkey's side,
all right, go ahead.
I'm not takin' anyone's side!
I know
what happened, Jerry.
Oh!
Did you call Alec Berg and thank
him for the hockey tickets?
No.
Oh, Jerry, what are you
waiting for?
What am I gonna
call him for?
I thanked him five times
when he gave them to me.
No, no, no! You gotta call him
the next day.
It's common courtesy.
No, I don't believe in it.
I'm takin' a stand against
all this over-thanking.
Jerry, good manners
are the glue of society.
Hey, if I knew I had to give him
8 million thank-yous,
I wouldn't have taken
the tickets in the first place.
You know what this
is gonna do?
He's gonna be upset
because you didn't call,
we won't get
Friday night tickets.
Ah, you're outta your mind.
Where are you going?
I gotta get a suit cleaned.
I have a funeral on Friday.
Who died?
Remember the guy
who pretended he had cancer
so I would buy him the toupee?
So he actually had it?
No, car accident.
He was trying to adjust
his toupee while he was driving,
and he lost control of the car.
[ORGAN PLAYING SOLEMN MELODY
That poor priest.
He was just visiting
from El Salvador.
Now he's gone completely loco.
The one Puddy screamed at
in the car?
Yeah.
He thinks he saw the devil.
He won't leave his room
in the church basement.
Well, that's what you get
for gettin' mixed up
with a face painter.
I mean, what compels
a seemingly normal human being
to do something like that?
[IMITATES PUDDY]
Gotta support the team.
[WOMEN SOBBING]
You know, I really hate
my clothes.
Mmm.
I open up my closet,
there's just nothing.
Nothing.
I hate everything I have.
I really hate it.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
I mean at this point, it's...
It's like I can wear something
three or four times, that's it.
It's getting to be
a terrible problem for me.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Alec.
Did you see that?
What kind of a hello
was that?
MAN: Oh, Mr. Kramer.
KRAMER: Yes.
Thanks for coming.
So, uh...
what did you wanna
see me about?
Well, Mr. Kramer,
to get right to it...
we're having a bit
of a problem with Barry.
Barry?
The chimpanzee.
Oh. Well, uh...
what's the problem?
Well, he's not functioning
the way he normally does.
He seems depressed.
He's lost his appetite.
He's even curtailed
his auto-erotic activities.
And we think this is
directly related
to the altercation he had
with you, the other day.
So? So, what do you
want me to do?
Well, frankly...
we'd like you to apologize.
Yeah, well, he started it.
Mr. Kramer,
he's an innocent primate.
So am I!
What about my feelings?
Don't my feelings
count for anything?
Oh, only the poor
monkey's important.
Everything has to be done
for the monkey.
Look, I'm sorry. I, uh...
Hey, uh,
that's okay, um...
Well, I've got to go feed
the marmoset.
You know,
George really likes you.
I don't...
Oh, she doesn't hear too well
out of her left ear.
Oh.
JERRY:
I mean, do you think it's possible
that he's mad at me
because he didn't get
the day-after thank-you?
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
You were at
a funeral, right?
Yeah.
Well, people never give
a good hello at a funeral.
I mean, they go like this.
That's the biggest.
Yeah, yeah, that's
kind of what he gave me.
Yeah, they can't go,
"Hey, you look fabulous!"
Hey.
Well, I just spoke
to your girlfriend.
Girlfriend, yeah, right.
Anyway, she asked me
to apologize to Barry.
Barry?
The monkey.
Well?
Nothin' doin'.
Jerry, I didn't
do anything.
It's the monkey that should
be apologizing to me.
Yeah, well, I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Well, I'm sorry.
Well, George, I tried to put
the good word in for you
with Sienna,
but I don't think she heard me.
Ya know...left ear?
What?
Yeah, her boss told me
that she can't hear very well
out of her left ear.
What, you didn't know that?
Oh, my God.
What?
She probably never heard it.
Don't you see what this means?
It-it-it's like the whole thing
never happened.
It's like when Superman reversed
the rotation of the Earth
to save Lois Lane!
Well, are you
gonna say it again?
That's the question, Jimmy.
I'm gonna do it.
What?
After what you
just went through.
I thought you said
you'd never say it again.
I'd like to say it
once to someone
that can actually
hear it!
GEORGE:
Yeah!
What? What's goin' on?
Oh, he's gonna talk
into her other ear.
Oh.
All right, well, listen,
I almost forgot to ask you.
What happened at the funeral?
Now, did you talk to Alec Berg?
Yeah, yeah, I saw him.
So he's gonna give you
the hockey tickets, huh?
Uh, not exactly.
He's mad, isn't he?
See, I knew it. Huh?
I don't know if he's mad.
All right, what happened
when you saw him?
Well, I didn't really
get a good hello.
But, see, I was at a funeral.
Ah-ha.
See, so I don't know
if I got a funeral hello,
or he was mad 'cause he didn't
get his day-after thank-you.
See, I told ya, Jerry,
I told ya!
What do ya want me to do?
I want you to get on this phone
and give him his thank-you.
No.
No, I can't.
Jerry, this is the way
society functions.
Aren't you a part
of society?
Because if you don't wanna
be a part of society,
why don't you just
get in your car
and move to the East Side!
Look, we got five hours
before the game.
I am betting
it was a funeral hello.
He knows we're here,
he knows the number,
he knows we want to go.
There's plenty of time for him
to call and give us the tickets.
You stubborn, stupid, silly man!
PUDDY:
Hey, great dip, you make this?
No, it's from
the store.
Oh.
How come people don't have
dip for dinner?
Why's it only a snack? Why can't
it be a meal, ya know?
I don't understand
stuff like that.
[CROWD CHEERING OVER TV]
David...
David, I think
we oughta talk.
All right, that's cool.
David, I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
You gotta be kiddin'.
How come?
Well, you see, David...
you're a face-painter.
Yeah, that's right.
Well...it's...
It's not that
I don't like you,
but, um...
well, to be perfectly honest,
I'm just havin' some trouble
getting past the face-painting.
Well, all right, so you don't
like the face-painting.
I just won't paint
it anymore.
Yeah, b--
But you like
the face-painting.
Well, I don't need
to do it,
it's not like
a habit or anything.
Oh.
You mean you'd...
You'd stop it for me.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh.
That's so...
That's so sweet!
Yeah. Come here.
All right, I gotta go home
and get changed before the game.
I'll be back, we'll make out.
Sienna...
I love you.
Yeah, I know.
I heard you the first time.
Yeah.
Just confirming.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Mom.
No, I was expecting
somebody else.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I can't talk now.
I gotta keep the line clear,
I'll call you later.
Yes, I know,
I have call-waiting,
but I don't trust it
in an emergency. Goodbye.
KRAMER:
Anyway, I, uh...
I just wanna say
that I'm sorry.
I, uh...
I lost my temper,
and I probably shouldn't have.
I took it out on you, and...
Look, if I've caused you
any problems
as a result of my behavior,
well, then, I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Even though you know, Barry,
between me and you,
we both know
that you started it.
I mean who's kidding who?
But they tell me
that you're very upset,
and God forbid I should disturb
the very important monkey.
I'm just hoping
we can put this behind us.
Let's just move on
with our lives, okay?
So no hard feelings?
What is that?
That's the letter D.
Why is the letter D
painted on your chest?
At the game tonight,
me and these five other guys
are going to take our shirts off
and spell out "Devils."
But you said no more painting.
No, I said no more
face painting.
And, as you can see,
this is not my face.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, did he call?
No.
Oh, come on, Jerry.
Come on!
This is stupid.
It's 6:00!
It's all over.
Just pick up the phone
and thank him!
All right!
Hello, Alec?
Hi, it's Jerry Seinfeld.
You know, you've got
a great John Houseman name.
[SNOOTILY]
Alec Berg.
Did you hand in your assignment,
Mr. Berg?
Uh, what can I do
for you, Jerry?
Well, Alec, the reason I called
is I-I just wanted to, um....
thank you for the tickets
from the other night.
I wish you'd called me earlier.
I could've given you
my tickets for tonight.
You already gave
them away?
Yeah. But you know what,
I have got a friend, uh,
he's got a couple of seats,
if, uh...
you don't mind nose-bleed,
they're yours.
No, we just wanna go.
There is one
little catch, though.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Hey, great game, huh?
Let's go, Devils!
Let's go! Stand up!
Come on! Do it!
Do it!
Come on! D! D!
E.
V.
I!
L!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
Ajá, bueno.
Hello, Father.
!¡Ah!
!¡La Madona!
La Madre del Cristo.
Yo estoy listo.