Loyalty to any one sports team
is pretty hard to justify.
Because the players
are always changing,
the team can move
to another city.
You're actually rooting
for the clothes
when you get right down to it.
I mean, you are standing
and cheering and yelling
for your clothes to beat
the clothes from another city.
Fans will be so in love
with a player,
but if he goes to another team,
they boo him.
This is the same human being
in a different shirt.
They hate him now.
"Boo!
"Different shirt.
Booooo."
Sure you don't
want the tickets?
No thanks.
I can't believe
I'm having trouble
getting rid of
Super Bowl tickets.
I'm telling you, skip the
Drakes' wedding. Go to the game.
I can't. The Drake put me
in the wedding party.
Well, who schedules his wedding
on Super Bowl Sunday?
Maybe he didn't know.
Lemme see.
I can't believe you
got these for free.
What--? Row F?
Row F.
In front of the Gs.
Hobnobbing with the Ds and Es.
What about Kramer or Elaine?
They don't want them?
I asked.
Elaine laughed at me.
Kramer's only interested
in Canadian football.
Well, wish
I could help you.
Come on. Take 'em.
You could take Bonnie.
You payin' my hotel
and airfare to Miami?
What do you think?
So in order to use these,
I gotta spend, like, 1500 bucks.
This is a bill for $1500.
Plus, she'd ask about
the sleeping arrangements.
I find those sleeping-
arrangement conversations
depressing.
Yeah.
Sleeping arrangements.
So you haven't, uh...?
Oh, no, no, no.
I haven't even seen
her apartment yet.
Tomorrow is the first night.
Ah-ha.
Hey, hey, hey.
Is that Tim Whatley?
The dentist?
Yeah. Is he still
mad at you
for crashing
his Thanksgiving party?
Oh, no. I explained
the whole thing to him.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
I blamed it on you.
[SNEEZES]
Hi, Tim.
Hey, Jerry.
George.
What are you up to?
Oh, just a couple gals out on
the town, shoppin' and gabbin'.
I'm gettin'
a makeover.
Hey. How'd you like
to go to the Super Bowl?
What?
Are you kidding?
Here.
Two tickets.
Have a good time.
Whoa, how can
I thank you?
I tell you what, I'll take
you to dinner sometime.
Ever been to Mendy's?
No. No, no. No, no.
No dinner.
JERRY:
Tim, you didn't
have to get me
a thank-you gift.
I know.
It's a label maker.
The Label Baby Junior.
Yeah, I hear they're good.
Well, label me thankful.
Okay. Well, you enjoy
those tickets.
Bye-bye.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Yeah?
KRAMER: Gah!
Come in.
Hey, where can I
put this?
What is it?
It's Risk, Jerry,
the game
of world conquest.
All right,
that's perfect.
Kramer, why do you have to--?
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
Will he take it?
I gotta go to work?
Take what?
The board, Jerry.
We been playing
at Newman's for six hours,
but he's gotta go.
So why don't you
leave it at Newman's?
I wanted to.
He won't let me.
We have to put the board
in a neutral place
where no one
will tamper with it.
So that's here?
Yes, yes.
You're like Switzerland.
I don't wanna
be Switzerland.
Jerry, Newman and I
are engaged in an epic struggle
for world domination.
It's winner take all.
People cannot be trusted.
Don't look at me.
Oh, I'm lookin'
right at you, big daddy.
All right,
soldier boys.
Let's fall out.
So you're
gonna look after it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stay strong, buddy.
Yeah, yeah.
Watch it good.
Hey, hi.
Hey. Hey!
Hey.
Oh, is that a label maker?
Yes, it is.
I got it as a gift.
It's a Label Baby Junior.
Mmm...
Love the Label Baby, baby.
You know those things
make great gifts.
I just got one of those
for Tim Whatley for Christmas.
Tim Whatley?
Yeah. Who sent you that one?
One Tim Whatley.
No. My Tim Whatley?
The same. He sent it
as a thank you
for my Super Bowl
tickets.
I think this is
the same one I gave him.
He recycled this gift.
He's a re-gifter.
Or...maybe he liked
your gift so much
he decided to get me
the same thing.
Perhaps it's an homage.
Yeah, perhaps.
How did he react
when you gave it to him?
Um, he said,
"Oh, a label maker.
How about that?"
He repeated the name
of the gift?
Yeah. So?
If you repeat
the name of the gift,
you can't possibly like it.
What do you mean?
Like when someone
opens something up
and they go,
"Oh, tube socks."
What are you gonna
do about it?
I don't know. I guess
I'll just get invited up
to his apartment and...
see if he's got a label maker.
Why'd you get him
a gift anyway?
He did some dental work for me
and didn't charge me,
so I thought I'd get him
a Christmas present.
If you're getting him anything
for his birthday, I'm a large.
Well, here we are.
This is the place.
Wow!
You like it?
I love it.
This is fantastic.
Look at this couch.
Is this velvet?
Are you a velvet fan?
A fan?
I would drape myself in velvet
if it was socially acceptable.
Look at this,
hardwood floors.
[LAUGHS]
Aren't they great?
Oh, Scott, hi.
This is George.
George this is Scott,
my roommate.
Hey.
Here. Check out
this view.
If you lean out this window,
you can see the river.
So Scott's your roommate, huh?
Yes.
Well, I'm sure
I've mentioned him.
No, I don't think
you mentioned him.
He's a great guy.
You'll really like him.
I'm sure I will.
JERRY:
Male roommate?
Yes, a male roommate.
And this is a problem?
It's a huge problem, Jerry.
The hardest part about
having sex with a woman
is getting her
to come back to your place.
He's already got that.
Well, maybe he's--
No, believe me, he's not.
So he's
an eligible receiver.
[SNAPS]
She's confiding in him
about our dates.
You always like the person
you talk to about the date
more than the date.
It's just a matter of time
until they realize,
"Hey! We could have sex."
What's stopping 'em?
Exactly.
You know how they get animals
to reproduce in captivity?
They just put 'em
in the same cage.
What does he look like?
Oh, that's the worst part of it.
He looks just like me.
He looks like you, and he's
workin' from the inside?
I look like me, and I'm
workin' from the outside.
Who do you think's in
the better position?
Not you.
This bizarre Harrad Experiment
must end!
We'll take
a check, please.
I gotta find a way to work
this out. I love that apartment.
It's so cozy.
I'm ensconced in velvet.
If it was socially acceptable--
I know, you would
drape yourself in velvet.
I've said that before?
Many times.
You love velvet.
You wanna live in velvet.
Everything with the velvet.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Guess what.
I saw Newman talkin'
to the super.
So what?
The super has keys
to your apartment.
Don't you see
what's goin' on?
Newman is plannin'
a sneak-attack.
Oh, maybe he's got
no hot water.
Yeah.
All right. Fine.
You sit there, and you watch,
while Newman
takes over the world.
But he'd be a horrible leader.
And you know
who's gonna suffer?
The little people.
You and George.
JERRY: Are you through?
KRAMER: All right, all right.
Oh! I talked to
Arthur Jobania.
Yeah, the Drakes' wedding,
that's off.
The wedding's off?
What happened?
The Drake, he found out
that the wedding's
on the same day
as the Super Bowl.
So he wanted to postpone it.
They got in a big argument,
and...
Ka-pow! It's over.
GEORGE:
The wedding is off.
Now you can go
to the Super Bowl.
I can't call Tim Whatley
and ask for the tickets back.
You just gave them
to him two days ago.
He's gotta give you
a grace period.
Are you even vaguely familiar
with the concept of giving?
There's no grace period.
Well, didn't he re-gift
the label maker?
Possibly.
Well, if he can re-gift,
why can't you de-gift?
You may have a point.
I have a point.
All right, I'll call him.
Good. What's that?
Oh, it's Risk.
It's a game of world domination
bein' played by two guys who can
barely run their own lives.
Hello, Tim.
Yeah, hi, it's
Jerry Seinfeld.
Hey, remember those
tickets I gave you?
Well, it turns out
I can use them.
Oh, you do?
I understand.
Okay. Bye.
He already made plans.
He can't change 'em.
Well, they're his tickets.
He can do what he wants
with them.
Thanks.
All right. I gotta
go to Bonnie's.
What are you gonna do
about the roommate?
I gotta try and figure out
a way to switch places with him.
It's like
a Siegfried & Roy trick.
Well, the pickle breath
is a good start.
Hello, Jerry.
May I come in?
What do you want?
[GRUNTING]
Nothing.
Just being neighborly.
You wanna hang out,
shoot the breeze?
I'm not lettin'
you cheat, Newman.
You're not gettin'
anywhere near that board.
Jerry,
I'm a little insulted.
You're not a little
anything, Newman.
So just pack it up
and move it outta here.
All right.
Oh, uh, by the way.
What are you doing
for the Super Bowl?
I don't know. Watch it
on TV, I guess. Why?
Well, if you watch closely
enough, you just might see me.
I'll be the one
waving to the camera
from my seat
on the 40-yard line.
You're going?
Yes, I am. A guy on
my mail route just
got a couple of tickets,
and he offered one to me.
What's his name?
Tim Whatley.
That's my ticket.
Is it? Oh, well,
if only you'd known,
you could have saved some time
and given it directly to me.
[CACKLES]
Newman.
GEORGE:
What a movie.
Good choice.
Thank Scott.
He recommended it.
Oh, Scott,
Scott, Scott.
He's really great
isn't he?
Yes, he is.
Let me ask you something.
[CLEARS THROAT]
When you're comin' out of the
shower and you put your robe on,
do you cinch it real tight?
Are you concerned about that?
George.
Do you hold the neck
together with one hand,
or you just letting it
flap in the breeze?
George, you're
being ridiculous.
What's the massage
situation?
What do you mean?
Is there any work
being done?
Is there any rubbing, touching?
Finger manipulation
on the other person?
And if so,
who's makin' the request?
George, would you just stop?
Say you go to the bathroom
at 2:00 in the morning.
What's the outfit?
I mean, are you dressin' up,
or is it...come as you are?
George, what is
wrong with you?
I tell you what's wrong...
a grown woman
with a male roommate!
It's unnatural.
It's an abomination.
Hey.
How you doin'?
I'm good.
Are you gonna need
the bathroom
'cause I'm gonna
jump in the shower.
No. Just throw my bras
out of the way.
Well, this is
my building.
Yes, it is.
This was fun, you know.
Yeah.
So, I...
guess I'll talk to you.
Aren't you gonna
invite me upstairs?
Upstairs? You--?
You wanna go upstairs?
I would love to go upstairs.
Wow.
Elaine, you are
something else.
No one could ever put
a label on you, huh?
We'll see.
JERRY:
Newman.
He's goin' with Newman.
How does Tim Whatley
even know Newman?
Newman's his mailman.
Who goes to the Super Bowl
with their mailman?
Who goes anywhere with Newman?
Well...
he's merry.
He is merry.
I'll give him that.
What's this plant for?
Oh, I had a little tiff with
Bonnie about the roommate.
Oh. Well, the cactus
will smooth things over.
Hey.
Guess what.
♪ I'm going to the Super Bowl
With Tim Whatley ♪
[HUMMING]
What?
We went out last night,
and he offered me a ticket.
What about the label maker?
Oh. Well...
Wait a minute.
That's my ticket.
You didn't even wanna go.
It was totally
out of the blue.
We went upstairs
to his apartment,
you know, to look
for the label maker--
So how did you get up there?
Did you say you had
to use the bathroom?
No.
Then how'd you get up there?
I said, "Do you wanna
go upstairs?"
Oh!
And there's your ticket.
What?
That's why you're going
to the Super Bowl.
Why?
You go out with
a guy one time.
You ask him to go upstairs
like you're Mae West?
Of course he's gonna try and
get you alone for the weekend.
You mean, just because
I asked him to go upstairs
he thinks
he's goin' downtown?
Obviously.
You're crazy!
Well, what happened
when you got upstairs?
As soon as we walked in, he got
a call from one of his patients
with an impacted molar or
something, so he had to leave.
I didn't get a chance
to look for the label maker.
Yeah, well, I don't
trust this guy.
I think he re-gifted,
and then he de-gifted.
And now he's using
an upstairs invite
as a springboard
to a Super Bowl sex romp.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm watching your door.
My door?
Yeah, from my peephole.
Fisheye. Sees all.
[DISCS CLATTER]
What was that?
Newman!
Open it. Open it.
Open it.
Damn!
The bedroom.
KRAMER:
Get him!
I see ya, Newman!
I see ya!
I'm taking the Congo
as a penalty!
ELAINE:
I've got a confession to make.
Oh? What's that?
I've got Super Bowl fever.
Oh, yeah, me too.
Yeah.
S-so where are we staying?
Oh, the Ambassador.
Oh.
Big room?
It's a regular room,
but it's right downtown.
Downtown?
Right downtown.
So, what do they have there?
A couple of beds?
Why? Are you
bringing someone else?
No, but...
don't you think
there should be two beds?
There's two of us.
[GIGGLES]
[CHUCKLES]
BONNIE:
Oh, a cactus.
They don't need any water,
so you don't have to keep
takin' 'em to the bathroom.
Well...
look who's here.
I asked Scott to move out.
Oh.
Ohhh.
JERRY:
So she kicked him out of the apartment?
That's right.
It's just me and her.
Wow. She rearranged
her whole life for you.
Yeah, I guess she did.
He's gone.
Now I'm the man.
That's not a good role for you.
No, it's not.
You unwittingly made
a major commitment.
That's a lot of pressure.
Oh, my God.
You wanted to be
ensconced in velvet.
You're buried.
I had
the perfect situation here.
He was shouldering
half the load.
He was shouldering.
I couldn't leave
well enough alone.
Where you goin'?
I gotta go help her
tape up all his boxes
and get 'em ready
for shipping.
Oh. Well, here.
Take Whatley's
label maker.
I don't wanna
see it again.
Thanks.
[POPS MOUTH]
Yeah.
I am takin' over
South America,
and there ain't nothin'
you can do about it.
So too bad about that Super Bowl
ticket, huh, Newman.
Yeah. I just hope
Tim Whatley's electric bills
don't suddenly get lost
in the mail,
or it could be
lights out for him.
Thanks for having
me over, guys.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Oh, hey, Jerry.
Ah, Tim Whatley.
Out scalping?
Oh, you see. Now, I've
been thinking a lot
about what happened,
and I feel horrible.
Listen. I want to give
you a ticket back.
Are you serious?
What about Elaine?
Oh, Elaine, yeah.
Well...
things just didn't work out like
I thought they would.
Ah.
Hey, isn't this
Kramer's car?
Hey, Cosmo!
They're towing your car!
What?
Not my car!
Aah!
They're towing my car!
What are you doin'?
I'm takin' the board with me.
Hey!
KRAMER:
That's my--!
[KRAMER YELLING]
Wait a minute!
So, I guess I'll see you
at the game.
Yeah. See you there.
Okay. Good.
Hi, George.
Where--? What happened?
Where's--?
Where's all the stuff?
It's gone.
It was all his.
Is this a label maker?
But the table,
the stereo, the VCR, the...
The velvet couch!!
Where's the velvet?
They were his.
Besides, we don't need
any of those things.
We have each other.
NEWMAN:
Are you, um, sure you know where the impound yard is?
Oh, stop stalling.
Come on.
I can't think.
It's all this noise.
Or is it because I've built
a stronghold around Greenland,
I've driven you
out of Western Europe,
and I've left you
teetering on the brink
of complete annihilation?
I'm not beaten yet.
I still have armies
in the Ukraine.
KRAMER:
Yeah? The Ukraine.
You know what
the Ukraine is?
It's a sitting duck.
A road apple, Newman.
The Ukraine is weak.
It's feeble.
I think it's time to put
the hurt on the Ukraine.
I come from Ukraine.
You not say Ukraine weak.
Well, we're playing
a game here, pal.
Ukraine is game to you?
How about I take your
little board and smash!
Ahh!
Hello, Tim.
Oh!
[CHUCKLES]
Elaine, hi.
Don't worry, Tim.
I didn't come by
to yell at you.
for that at all.
I just came by to pick up
my label maker.
I gave you a label maker,
and now I would like
to have it back.
But you gave it to me.
Ah! But you gave me a ticket
to the Super Bowl.
Hand it over, Whatley.
Uh...okay.
[SCOFFS]
You don't have
the label maker, do you?
Uh, no.
I knew it!
You're a re-gifter!
Oh, yeah. Some gift.
That thing didn't
work at all.
What?
You put a label on something,
then ten minutes later,
it would peel right off.
It was the worst gift
I ever got.
Well, I bought it for you
because...
you were so nice to me for not
charging me for the dental work.
The way you worked on
my filling, you were so...
So gentle and so caring.
And so sensitive.
Oh, Elaine.
Oh!
JERRY:
H...G...F.
Seat 4.
One...
two...
three...
Per--
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
Tim couldn't make it.
He's in love.
Oh.
Isn't that wonderful?
Oh, it's enchanting.
Here's the TV.
I know you wanted
to watch the Super Bowl.
Do you, uh...
at least have some towels
we could sit on?
It's, like, a four-hour game.
George,
Scott's gonna drop by.
He said he never
got his boxes.
I'll get the towels.
GEORGE:
How am I gonna get out of this?
Think, Costanza. Think!
Here we are.
Hey...
You know, Bonnie, I...
I just had a pretty wild idea.
What is it?
Well, I, uh...
I'm not sure how you
pronounce it or anything,
but I, uh...
I believe it's ménage à trois?
What?
Hi.
Scott!
Remember what we talked
about the other day?
George is into it.
Oh, really?
[♪]
Great streak of luck
I'm havin'.
First, Kramer almost
beats me at Risk,
but I narrowly escaped,
and then Tim Whatley gives
me the Super Bowl ticket.
Can you move over at all?
And then-- Then just
as I'm about to go,
these boxes show up at
the post office with no labels.
No labels, Jerry.
You know what that means?
Freebies!
I got this great mini TV
and a VCR.
Oh, it's unbelievable.
An inch.
Can you move over
an inch?
Aw, come on.