The big new accessory
with eyeglasses
seems to be that strap
that connects in the back
so you can take 'em on and off.
Which I don't get, because
I thought if you have glasses,
isn't that because
you need to wear glasses?
You need glasses.
Isn't that what they say?
I mean, an eye doctor
doesn't say,
"Would you care
for some glasses?"
When people have crutches,
they don't have like a little
chain attached to their belt,
so they can just let go of them
every now and then.
Why not get a toupee
with a rubber band
for when you're water-skiing?
The thing could just...
Hey, George.
Gary?
Where the hell
have you been?
I've been leaving you
phone messages for months.
I know. I've been
pretty busy.
Oh, busy.
Don't give me busy.
Who's not busy?
I'm busy. We're all busy.
Everybody's busy.
All right, tell me,
what's kept you so busy?
Mostly chemotherapy.
Hey, I'll see ya.
Hey, pig!
[ENGINE STARTS]
Hey, hey, hey!
JERRY:
So you called the cop a pig?
I was yelling
at the litterbug.
I mean,
this is my town.
You don't throw trash
on the streets of my town.
So didn't you explain
that to the cop?
No, I fled the scene.
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, uh...
What?
Kramer, I, uh,
need to talk
to Jerry privately.
Oh.
What about?
Kramer.
Oh, come on, George.
You can share it
with me, huh?
Hey, you're
hurting me!
You gonna share it
with me next time, huh?
I swear! I swear!
All right, all right.
I'm looking forward to it.
All right, I got news.
You ready?
[SIGHS]
Gary Fogel had cancer.
Oh, yeah, I knew.
You knew?
How did you know?
He told me
a few months ago.
Why did he tell you
and not me?
I don't know.
How are you closer
to him than me?
So is he okay?
Oh, yeah,
he's fine, fine.
He was in bad shape
for a while, though.
Huh. Really? How bad?
Was he on his deathbed?
No, he was on
his regular bed.
So why didn't you tell me?
He swore me to secrecy.
So?
It's not like
you're not my wife.
Well, I still think you
should've told me.
Believe me, you were
better off not knowing.
It's not easy to deal
with someone
in a situation like this.
I was so nice to him,
I almost made myself sick.
Well, I want to talk
to him about this!
That's right.
You let him have it.
Who is he not to tell you about
his life-threatening illness?
That's what I'm saying.
His illness is your business.
If not mine, whose?
If not now, when?
Were you just
talking about me?
No, an old friend
of ours, Gary.
Oh, the guy with cancer?
You told her?!
She's not your wife!
If I'd told you,
you would've given it away.
You don't think
I can keep a secret?
No, but he would've
read your face.
You don't trust my poker face?
Do you ever win
at poker?
No.
Hey.
Oh. I just saw
your old boyfriend on TV.
Jake Jarmel?
Yeah.
I really liked those glasses
he was wearing.
Where'd he get those?
Why? You don't
wear glasses.
I know, but I need a new look.
I'm stagnating.
I have to say,
as a glasses-wearer,
I take exception
to that.
That's like me
buying a wheelchair
to cruise around in.
Yeah, I've considered that.
Uh, look, how do I get
in touch with this guy?
Well, he's having a two-day
book signing at Walden's.
You know, we had
a really bad breakup.
The Jujyfruits?
[SNIFFLES]
Yeah, the Jujyfruits.
Okay, K-Man.
Enjoy the book.
Thank you.
Listen, Jake,
where did you get
those eyeglass frames?
I can't tell you that.
You don't know
where you got them?
Yes, I do, but I don't want
anyone else to have them.
Well, that's peculiar.
There's that woman that
never talks to anybody.
GARY:
Really.
Every day she comes in, she sits
at that table and reads.
Never talks to anybody.
Oh, I spoke
to Debby Biblow.
She said to say hi.
Really?
You know, Gary, I really have
to say, I'm a little bit hurt
that you didn't decide
to confide in me.
Well, frankly,
you can't keep a secret.
You know, you get two pair,
the whole table knows.
Well, I still think
it was wrong.
All right, well,
I'm sorry.
I guess I was just
thinking of myself.
Yes!
So I called the litterbug
a pig, not you.
I like policemen.
I wanted to be a policeman.
Yeah, so why
didn't you?
I'm scared of being shot.
Mr. Kramer,
let me tell you a story.
In 1979, I ticketed
a brown Dodge Diplomat
for parking
in a church zone.
That fine
was never paid.
And since then,
that scofflaw
has piled up
more parking tickets
than anyone
in New York City.
For 16 years,
I pursued him,
only to see him
give me the slip
time and time again.
I've never got
a clean look at his face,
but he's become
my white whale.
Mr. Kramer,
that day was yesterday!
But thanks to you,
I don't know if I'll ever
get that chance again.
I like that eye patch.
All right.
I'm gonna move my car.
My meter's up.
You can't park
in this city.
Hey, George,
listen,
you know that
company I work for?
They own that parking lot
around the corner.
That's a Kinney lot?
Yeah. And there's
a space opening up, and...
I-I could get it for you.
You'd just have to
pay the tax on it.
It'd be, like, 50 a month.
Fifty bucks a month?
That's incredible.
Okay! Thanks!
All right, I got lunch,
all right?
Still owe me a secret.
All right, listen.
There is something I haven't
told you, all right. Yeah?
Yeah, but you can't tell Jerry.
What do you think,
I tell Jerry everything?
It's not like
he's my wife.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, well...
The thing is,
I've been livin' a lie.
Just one?
I'm livin', like, 20.
[CHUCKLES]
What's yours?
Well, I...
[CHUCKLES]
I never actually had cancer.
[LAUGHS]
I'll see ya.
ELAINE:
So he refused
to tell you where
he got the glasses?
Flat out refused.
Yeah, isn't that
just like him?
You know, he has to be
the only one who has them.
Yeah, tell me about it,
soul sister.
Anyway, I told Jake
that you said hi.
What?!
You told Jake
I said hi?
Yeah.
I can't believe you did that.
Why did you tell him I said hi?
I never said hi.
When did I say hi?
I never heard her say hi.
Well, it's
common courtesy.
No! No, Kramer,
you don't understand.
He made the last
contact between us.
I had the upper hand in
the post break-up relationship.
If he thinks that I said hi,
then I lose the upper hand.
It's like a game of tag.
Where you goin'?
Nowhere.
You're going to the bookstore
to see Jake Jarmel, aren't you?
So, what if I do?
Listen, if you're
going there,
maybe you can get him to tell
you where he got those glasses.
KRAMER:
Elaine!
Hey.
How'd it go
with Gary?
Fine.
Really.
Yup.
You look like something's
on your mind.
No, nothing.
I'm fine.
So that's your
poker face.
My regular face.
No, it isn't.
I've seen your regular face.
That is not it.
What're you sayin'?
All right, George.
Come on, what do you got?
Got nothin'.
What do you got,
a pair of bullets?
What are you
talkin' about?
Two pair?
Three of a kind?
Will you stop it?
Oh, my God, you got a flush!
You're holdin'
a flush!
I don't have a flush.
A full house?
You got a full house?
Turn 'em over, George!
I wanna see 'em!
Come on, I'm callin'!
What do you got?
Gary Fogel never had cancer!
ELAINE:
So you see,
Kramer took it upon himself
to say hi to you from me
when, in fact,
it was an unauthorized hi.
You didn't say hi.
That's what I'm saying.
That's what you
came to tell me.
Correct.
You never said hi.
You still like me,
don't you?
Correct-- What's that?
Hey, I have been trying to get
this book signed all day.
How can you say
that I still love you
when I didn't even
say hi to you?
Elaine, coming down here to say
that you didn't say hi
is more of a gesture
than if you did say hi.
[SCOFFS]
Jake...
Uh, er...
The doctors thought
he had cancer,
but the surgery revealed
he never actually had it.
So, what was wrong
with him?
Nothing.
He's been lying to me
for two months?
That's right.
What kind of
person is this?
There's only one other person
who might be able to do this,
and that's you.
Well...
I don't even think
you could do it.
I could do it.
Yeah, I guess you could.
Pfft. Come on.
Did you know he was so worried
about losing more hair
if he had to get
chemo treatments,
I bought him
an unlimited gift certificate
at the Hair Team For Men,
just to put his mind at ease?
You did that?
Yeah.
Oh, I can't wait
to talk to this guy.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
You can't say anything!
Why not?
Because he'll know
I told you.
He's giving me a parking spot
around the corner
for practically nothing.
You're telling me, because
you're getting free parking,
I gotta pretend this guy
had cancer when he didn't?
Yeah.
Well, I don't like it.
I don't like it one bit.
I'm supposed
to see him tomorrow.
Well, you have to maintain
the same disposition too.
You can't start acting
differently.
You have to be nice.
Why didn't he tell me?
Because you were
being so nice.
I don't think
I can be that nice.
You be nice!
Gary?
What do you think?
Check it out.
Is that from
my gift certificate?
Yeah, buddy.
You really came through for me.
You've been so nice.
Yeah, well, I'm glad you
could take advantage.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what
I'm thinkin' of doin'?
I'm gettin' rid
of all my fillings
'cause that mercury's toxic.
Let me see
your fillings.
I don't think so.
Oh, come on.
Open up,
let me take a look.
GEORGE:
You be nice!
He's giving me
a parking space.
Parking space...
Well, what do
you know?
Hey, lookie there.
You're loaded!
Okay.
Hey, look who's
over there.
Miss Cool Toes.
[CHUCKLES]
Check this out, Jack.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Look at you.
Wh-what's this?
It's an eye patch.
You look like
a pirate.
I wanna be
This is Gary.
How you doing?
How are you?
Whoo.
Well, I tell you,
there's only one problem--
Can't see on
your right side?
No, it's, uh...
It's itchy.
Ah.
DEBBY:
Nice car.
Yeah.
Once belonged
to Jon Voight.
Really?
Really.
[CHUCKLES]
So, um, what made you just...
call me out of the blue
like that?
Oh, well, uh...
Gary told me
you said hi.
I didn't say hi.
You didn't?
N-no.
I told him to send
you my regards.
I didn't say hi.
Regards?
Yeah. Regards.
Anyway, I admit I was dumb
to go to the bookstore
to tell him
I didn't say hi,
but he didn't have
to act so smug.
Oh, I hate smugness.
Don't you hate smugness?
Smugness is not
a good quality.
Oh, my God.
That man over there.
I think he's wearing glasses
that look just like Jake's.
Pull over.
Stop the car.
[HORN HONKS]
Here, here.
I think I've got a way
of getting back
at my ex-boyfriend.
Good.
Revenge
is very good.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Excuse me, sir? Sir?
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, if you don't
mind my asking,
could you tell me where
you got your glasses?
Malaysia.
Malaysia?
Yeah.
Um, look, I know
this'll sound odd,
but can I buy them
from you?
Actually, I was gonna
buy a new pair.
Oh.
But I can barely
see without these.
Come on.
Well...
these were expensive.
Let's start
the bidding.
So you didn't think
this was a date.
N-no.
Not really.
Why? Is it a date?
I thought
it was a date.
No, it's not a date.
What about the regards?
Regards don't mean anything.
I mean, it's not like I said hi.
I mean,
the fact is...
Oh, I shouldn't say anything.
No. Tell me.
Can you keep a secret?
Me?
Oh, yeah.
I never had feelings for Gary
until he got sick.
But he was so brave
and gained such a wonderful
perspective on life,
I fell in love
with him.
Oh, yeah, he's got
some perspective there.
Hey, do you know
what the whip does?
What whip?
The whip. In the Senate
and the House.
Well, you know, in the old days,
when the senators didn't vote
the way that the party leaders
wanted 'em to,
they whipped them.
[STERNLY]
You better vote the way we want you to,
or there's gonna be big trouble.
[IMITATES WHIP CRACKING]
Hyah!
She won't talk
to anyone, huh?
Oh, no.
She won't say
a word to anybody.
Well, she's talkin'
a blue streak now, Jack.
Well, well.
The white whale.
Look at this. There's no
place to park around here.
I don't know why they even
sell cars in Manhattan.
Don't complain. At least
you have your health.
George, watch out
for that man!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR CRASHES]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, get back here!
Newman.
The white whale.
GEORGE:
Can you believe he sold his glasses on the street?
Can you believe someone
would lie about chemotherapy
to get a wig?
Would you do that?
No. Definitely not.
I'm pretty sure I wouldn't.
And you know
what else?
He picked up that woman
in the coffee shop.
The one who sits
by herself?
Yeah.
How did he do that?
Because he was brimming
with confidence from the toupee.
Really!
And Debby told me that
she fell in love with him
because he has
all this perspective.
She thinks a guy who lies about
a life-threatening illness
so he can get some phony hair
has perspective?
He picked her up?
Walked right
over to her table.
Wow.
Jake, Jake.
Take a look.
Ah! See, you're not
the only one who has them.
I have them too.
Where did you get those?
Malaysia. I was in the area.
Ooh!
Kramer.
Just drive.
All right.
Now, you listen,
and you listen good.
I know who you are.
You're the scofflaw.
[CHUCKLES]
What are you
talkin' about?
Don't play dumb!
It's me, Cosmo.
All right, so it's me.
So what?
You don't think
I know how you're feeling
every second of the day,
looking over
your shoulder
to see if someone's
comin' up from behind,
sitting alone at night,
knowing they could
be closing in?
I can't sleep, I tell you.
I can't sleep.
Of course you can't,
you poor sap.
Now, why didn't you tell me?
I couldn't.
I couldn't tell anyone.
So you've been living
this secret by yourself?
It's been awful.
[SOBBING]
I wanted
to tell somebody.
Help me, Kramer.
Help me!
All right,
I'm gonna help you.
I'll try some on
and see how they look.
It's just hair.
You ever see what that thing
looks like in the back?
You got your natural
little curls on the bottom,
and then that big phony mat
coming down on top of it.
Well, some of them
look good.
The ones that look good,
you don't even know about.
What if you get involved
with a woman?
How you gonna tell her?
The way they make
them these days,
I'll never have
to tell her.
So you keep it a secret
your whole life?
Then at your funeral,
the mortician comes out,
"Here, Mrs. Costanza.
I thought you might want this."
Ah!
LIPPMAN:
Oh, it's no secret
that it's my dream to have
my own publishing house.
And if this Jake Jarmel book
does,
you know, what I think
it's gonna do,
if I can get this whole thing
off the ground, then, you know,
I think I'll have
something for you.
Oh, Mr. Lippman.
[BOTH LAUGH]
That is so exciting.
I mean, you have no idea
how sick I am
of running around town
looking for socks. Yeah.
By the way, those are
great glasses.
Oh, really, you like 'em?
Mm-hmm.
Very unusual.
Well, you know what?
What?
You can have 'em.
Oh, no, no.
No, no! Go to that
place on the corner.
They'll change
the prescription in an hour.
Take 'em.
Really?
I have no use
for them anymore.
I could use a new pair
of reading glasses.
They're from Malaysia.
Oh, yeah?
Oh! Fabulous.
WOMAN:
Well, Mr. Newman,
in all my years
on the bench,
I have never come across
anything quite like this.
I have given this matter
some very serious consideration,
and I've decided
that what's best for the city,
and possibly
for yourself,
is for you
to keep your car in a garage
convenient
to your home.
[SOBBING]
I can't afford that.
Afford it, you will,
Mr. Newman,
or this court will see
that your car is impounded
and sold at auction.
Oh, don't you worry,
Your Honor.
He's in my custody.
GEORGE:
Well? What do you think?
I really can't say.
No, say.
I want you to say.
It's not good,
okay?
It's not good.
You look...
stupid.
I'm sorry.
You have to realize,
this has not been
custom-fitted to his scalp.
I really think this
looks pretty good.
Why don't you get
a pair of white shoes,
move down to Miami Beach, and
get the whole thing over with?
Well, maybe you could
show me something else.
As I said,
it'll be different
once we design something
specifically for you.
But I don't think your friend
here is being very helpful.
Oh, hey.
I'm being helpful.
I am the only one
being helpful.
No, I don't think
you're helpful!
I think you're
being disruptive!
And you make it difficult for
your friend to improve his life.
Hey, I'm trying
to prevent my friend
from becoming
one of those guys
people snicker at
behind their back
because they
look ridiculous,
no offense to you
personally!
All you people with hair
think you're so damn superior.
You have no idea
what it's like.
You ever look down into
the bottom of your tub
and see a fistful of hair?!
How'd you like to start
your day with that?!
All right, take it easy!
Take it easy! Hey!
I'm sorry!
Please.
[HUMMING]
Hey, Jerry.
George, you decided
to get a rug.
Good for you, Jack.
Well, I--
I'm just looking, really.
Oh.
Uh, Tommy, I'm gonna
need a little adjustment.
I'll be right with you.
Listen, George,
I got some bad news.
I'm not gonna be able
to give you that parking space.
What?
This judge has to use it
for some scofflaw.
And you know you
can't fight city hall.
You know, Gary...
I had a little chat
with George the other day.
You didn't!
I did.
JERRY:
And he told me that--
GARY:
I lied to him. I'm not 100% recovered yet.
Give me that thing.
[SIGHS]
How's your life?
All right?
Yeah.
Not bad at all.
And now, ladies and gentlemen
of the press,
it is my pleasure to introduce
you to Mr. Jake Jarmel.
[APPLAUSE]
So, Jake, what's your percentage
on this book?
Oh, actually, I have some very
interesting information on that.
You know, uh,
this is a co-venture...
Where did you get those?
and as such--
Those glasses. Where did
you get those glasses?
Where--? Wh--?
Is this supposed to be
some kind of a joke on me?
Because it's not very funny.
Give me those.
I want the glasses!
Give me those!
[BOTH SHOUTING]
I have to go look
for some socks.