I find it fascinating
when you go into
a stationery store,
that they are manufacturing
millions of pens.
Constantly.
We're all buying them.
I must have bought
6000 Bics in my life.
I've used up maybe two of them.
Where is the rest of them?
When you move the refrigerator,
there's always a couple
back there, but that doesn't
account for it.
Where are all the pens?
That's why it's so embarrassing
if you don't have one.
"You got a pen?
Could I borrow a pen?"
We always have to whisper
because it's so humiliating.
"I don't have a pen."
"They're making millions
of them every week."
"I know. Where are they?"
[♪]
May I help you?
Yeah. Hi.
I'm looking for a Rolamech 1000.
It's a mechanical pencil.
Oh, I know the Rolamech 1000.
No, I'm sure you do.
They're pretty expensive.
Well, it's for my boss.
What do you do?
Whatever.
Well, we don't have any
in stock right now,
but I would be happy
to order it for you.
Just give me
your phone number.
And when it comes in,
I'll give you a call.
Your name is...?
Elaine.
And your last name?
It's just Elaine.
Like Cher.
[LAUGHS]
[FAKE LAUGHS]
And your number?
Uh, it's KL5-2390.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
Okay. Thanks a lot.
You'll be hearing from me.
Okay. So long.
Why did you give him
my number?
Don't worry
about it.
I think
he got ideas.
I wonder if any woman
ever said that about Einstein.
Just call me when
the pencil comes in, okay?
Why does Mr. Pitt prefer
a pencil to a pen anyway?
Hey, look who's here.
ALL:
Hey!
Oh, hi,
Jerry.
Hi, Julie.
Elaine, Julie.
Hi.
Oh, hi.
Elaine's my
middle name.
Oh. Mine's Ike.
[GEORGE LAUGHS]
Hey, you wanna get
some lunch?
Just had a big bowl
of Kix.
Oh, well, that's
very mature.
What about you?
Oh, please come,
Elaine.
No, no. But maybe you could
bring me back something.
All right.
What do you want?
Um, hmm...I don't know.
A big salad.
What big salad?
I'm going to
the coffee shop.
Oh, they have
big salads.
I've never seen
a big salad.
They have
big salads.
Is that what
I ask for?
The big salad?
It's okay.
You can just forg--
No, hey,
I'll get it.
What's in the
big salad?
Big lettuce,
big carrots,
tomatoes like
volleyballs.
So, you're gonna
be upstairs? Mm-hm.
All right, we'll see you
in a little while.
ELAINE:
Maybe I should just get married.
Dating really
is starting to get embarrassing.
Isn't it?
I know.
You know, whenever I'm
on a date,
I always feel like
people can tell.
People on dates shouldn't even
be allowed out in public.
Boy, that's right.
It's embarrassing
for them.
It's painful for us to watch.
Right.
I'm going out
with someone later.
I'm not even taking her
out of the house.
Good for you.
I don't need a bunch
of people staring at us.
You're telling me.
[THUMPING]
What is that?
Gendason.
What a jerk!
I'm never playing golf
with him again.
Who? Gendason?
Steve Gendason.
Why does that name sound
so familiar?
He used to be
a baseball player.
Oh. How'd you end up
playing golf with him?
Well, I met him on the course
a couple years ago.
Yeah. Played with him a lot.
But today was it.
We're on the 15th hole.
Yeah, he's beating me
by a couple of strokes.
Then, he's about to hit
his second shot, when...
he picks up
the ball
and cleans it.
So what?
Pfft. Sorry.
But the rules clearly state
that you cannot clean the ball
unless it's on the green.
The rules are very
clear about that.
Certainly are.
So I penalized him
a stroke.
Wow. So, what happened?
He lost it!
We almost came to blows.
We're like face to face,
like a manager and an umpire.
You know, we're like:
"What are you
talking about?!"
"Think I'm gonna
put up with you?!"
All right. All right!
You're in my face.
I still don't see
what the big deal is.
Hey, a rule is a rule.
And let's face it,
without rules, there's chaos.
I like Anna Quindlen's
column and Safire.
Don't you like Safire?
Uh. Safire.
[CHUCKLES]
Although at times,
he can be rather pedantic.
He can be pedantic.
And Bob Herbert's great.
He used to work for
the Daily News.
Yes. Yes.
You know what's
interesting?
The quarterback
for the Atlanta Falcons
is Bobby Hebert.
No R.
Which I find fascinating.
You know,
it's Herbert,
H-E-R...B-E-R-T.
Hebert. H-E...B-E-R-T.
Hebert.
It's a fun name
to pronounce.
Try and say it.
Hebert.
Go ahead.
Take a shot.
Oh--
All right, no.
Thank you.
I got it.
No, no. I'd like
to pay for mine.
Oh, now Julie, Julie.
Don't insult me.
What difference does it make
who pays for lunch?
It's totally meaningless.
Okay. Thanks, George.
Here's your big salad
to go.
Oh, thank you.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
No, she's not here.
Okay, fine.
Whatever.
Yes, I'll tell her.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Stationery store guy.
Called to say
he ordered your pencil.
I told you. He has ideas.
He doesn't even care
if a man answers.
Or you.
Wh--
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
ALL:
Hey.
Sorry we're late.
Oh, it's
no problem.
Here's your
big salad.
Thank you,
Julie.
You're very
welcome.
So, well, I guess
I better get going.
I'm meeting Mother
at the Guggenheim.
You sure you don't
want to go?
No, you Guggenheim. I'm not
much of a Guggenheimer.
Are you sure, George?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You go.
Okay. I'll see
you later. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Take care then.
Did you see
what just happened here?
Well, that
all depends.
Did you happen to notice
that Julie handed
the big salad to Elaine?
Yeah. So?
Well, she didn't buy
the big salad.
I bought the big salad.
Is that a fact?
Yes, it is.
She just took credit
for my salad.
That's not right.
No, it isn't.
I bought it.
Yes, you did.
Shouldn't she have
said something?
She could have.
Oh, I know.
Imagine. Her taking credit
for your big salad?
You know, you buy
a big salad for somebody,
it would be nice
if they knew it.
Obviously.
Turn on the TV.
What?
Put it on.
Put it on!
NEWSCASTER:
Neither the district attorney's office
nor the police department
have answered
any questions as yet.
To repeat, in case
you're just joining us,
former baseball star,
Steve Gendason,
has been taken to police
headquarters for questioning
in the murder of Bobby Pinkus,
the owner of Royal Dry Cleaners
at 2759 Amsterdam Avenue.
According to Pinkus' wife,
Gendason had been involved
in a dispute with
the cleaner over a stain
on a pair of
gray Sansabelt slacks.
We also have a report
that earlier in the day,
a groundskeeper at
Van Courtlandt Golf Course
reportedly saw
an irate Gendason
leaving the clubhouse
in a huff.
Whether there is a possible
connection between the two
is something we'll just
have to wait and find out.
Jerry.
Well, it had nothing
to do with you.
Yeah, but maybe
he was so mad
from the penalty
stroke
that he murdered
the dry cleaner.
[SILENT GASP]
Well, generally
speaking,
you don't need any
extra incentive
to murder
a dry cleaner.
I wouldn't worry
about it.
I like Julie.
She's very
personable.
Yeah, she's lovely.
That's great,
George.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah.
[MAKES POPPING SOUNDS]
So did you enjoy your lunch?
Yeah. The big salad.
It was very good.
Actually, it was
too big.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Why?
Oh, no reason.
Because, you know,
she handed you the bag.
I could have handed
you the bag.
But she happened
to pick it up
at the restaurant,
even though...
Even though what?
No, it's just...
You thanked her,
even though...
What's
the difference?
What? What are you trying
to say, George?
It's just that
I was the one
that actually paid
for the big salad.
She just happened
to hand it to you.
But it's
no big deal.
You want the money for
the big salad, George?
No. No.
Then what is
your problem?
There is no problem.
Just a small
miscommunication
whereby you
thanked her
instead of the person
actually responsible
for the purchasing
of the big salad.
JERRY:
Kramer golfed with him.
And Kramer thinks
a penalty stroke
may have
driven him to it.
Well, they haven't
even arrested him yet.
Come on. Let's go out.
Uh, no.
I don't think so.
Why not?
We don't need a bunch
of people staring at us.
Who's staring?
Oh, they're staring.
They know we're on a date.
They're making fun.
Come on. It's embarrassing.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
No, she's not here.
Yes, I will tell her.
No, I don't know what time
she might be coming back.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Look, I got to go.
Bye.
That's--
It's a long story.
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
I was wondering if you knew
where Kramer was?
No, I don't. Why?
You know, Gendason.
This is something,
isn't it?
I suppose.
What did Kramer say?
I don't know.
Nothing.
C'mon, Jerry.
You know something.
Tell me! Tell me!
Ooh, Chunkys.
Margaret?
Hello.
You two know each other?
You might say that.
We used to go out.
Well...toodle-loo.
[SNICKERS]
Nice seeing you again,
Margaret.
Bye, Jerry.
Have fun.
[LAUGHS]
You went out...with Newman?
Just a few times.
Why?
I liked him.
You liked Newman?
Look, I'm a little
uncomfortable
talking about this, okay?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm just a little curious.
I mean, why did you
stop seeing him?
He ended it.
He ended it?
Yes! Yes.
It was a couple of years ago.
Why?
Does it matter?
No.
No, of course not.
Jerry...they found
a tee.
What tee?
A golf tee
in the dry cleaner.
Newman.
She went out
with Newman.
It must be a mistake.
No, it isn't.
And the most distressing
part about it is,
not that she went out
with him,
but that he stopped
seeing her.
Do you understand?
He, Newman.
Newman stopped seeing her.
Newman never stops
seeing anybody.
Newman will see whoever
is willing to see him.
So the question then is
not so much
why did she see him--
as disturbing as that is--
but why did he, Newman,
stop seeing her?
Perhaps there's more
to Newman than meets the eye.
No. There's less.
It's possible.
No. It isn't.
I've looked into his eyes.
He's pure evil.
Maybe he's an enigma.
A mystery wrapped in a riddle.
Yeah, he's a mystery
wrapped in a Twinkie.
Can I get you
some more coffee?
No. But thank you.
Oh, by the way,
your stationery store guy called.
He's got your pencil.
Oh. You are kidding me.
No, he left
the store early,
made a special trip to
the distributor and got it.
I bought one yesterday
on 14th Street.
What did you do that for?
He already ordered it.
I wanted to please
Mr. Pitt.
Well, you better
go down there and tell this guy.
He's very excited.
Oh, boy.
Oh, hi, Julie.
Hi.
Hi, Julie.
Hi. How are you,
Elaine?
I'm meeting
George here.
Oh...well then,
I better get going.
Otherwise George will
make me buy him lunch
to make up for that big salad
he bought me yesterday.
How do you know that?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
NEWMAN:
Who is it?
It's Jerry.
Well, it's kind of
a bad time now.
Could you come back later?
Come on, Newman,
open the door!
Hello, Jerry.
What a rare treat.
What brings you down
to the east wing?
Okay, pudgy, let's stop
playing games.
Now, what happened
with Margaret?
No need to
get excited.
Can't we discuss this
like gentlemen?
No, we can't.
My skin is crawling
just being inside
your little rat's nest.
Now, what happened?
All right, you wanna
know what happened?
I'll tell you
what happened.
She wasn't my type.
Not your type?
Not really.
Well, how come?
Oh, she just didn't
do it for me.
But what is wrong with her?
[LAUGHS]
Well...
if you're happy with her...
that's all that matters.
You don't think
she's attractive?
No.
I need a really pretty face.
But, hey...that's me.
Okay, Newman,
thanks a lot.
Care for some lemonade?
No, thank you.
Drop by any time...Jerry.
[LAUGHS]
Jerry. All right.
Now, listen to this.
"If a player cleans his ball
"during play of a hole,
"except on the putting green,
he shall incur a penalty
of one stroke."
That's the rule, Jerry.
But, it's just
a friendly game.
Why do you always have to be
such a stickler?
Because that's the way
I was raised.
You know, when I
was growing up,
I had to be in bed
every night by 9:00.
And if I wasn't...
Well, I don't have to
tell you what happened.
What are you so worried
about this for?
You know, he talked
about Pinkus on the course?
He did?
Oh, yeah.
He said he brought a pair
of pants into Pinkus',
and they came back
stained
with some kind of
dry-cleaning fluid.
And Pinkus denied
responsibility.
You see, he was very
upset with Pinkus.
So it had nothing
to do with you.
Yeah, but maybe
I pushed him over the edge.
No, I don't think so.
Poor Pinkus.
Poor little Pinkus.
Hey, let me ask
you a question.
You met Margaret.
You think Margaret's
good-looking?
Oh. She's a natural beauty.
No makeup.
Ooh, I like that.
Yeah.
And the curls?
You like the curls?
Oh, I love curls.
Yeah, me too.
All right, I'll see
you later.
Where you going?
Gendason's.
You're going
to see Gendason?
It's weighing
on my conscience.
You know...I think I could
have played with dolls,
if there were dolls
in the house.
That seems like
fun to me.
It doesn't seem like
a gender thing.
I think I would like
to play with dolls.
What's so terrible?
So, George, I was talking
to Elaine before--
Uh, uh. We're
just friends. [LAUGHS]
Yes, well, anyway,
she said something
that was kind of intriguing.
Oh. Share.
Well...when I came
over to the table,
she mentioned
something about
how she had better
hurry up and leave,
or you would make
her buy lunch,
to make up for the one
that you bought yesterday.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
I'm not following.
Well, my question is,
how could Elaine be
under the impression that
you bought the big salad,
when I was the one
that handed it to her?
Well, she probably
just assumed.
Hmm.
Did she?
[LAUGHS
UNCOMFORTABLY]
Wait--
Wait a second.
Are you suggesting that
I went out of my way
to tell Elaine that,
even though you handed her the big salad,
that it came from me.
That's what I'm suggesting.
Well, it was a big salad.
And what I would like
to know is,
how does a person who has
virtually nothing to do
with the big salad,
claim responsibility
for that salad,
and accept that thank-you
under false pretenses, huh?
Huh? Huh?
George, all I did
was hand someone a bag.
It's just that my boss
is very demanding,
and he needed the pencil
right away.
Well, why did you tell me
to order it
if you knew you were going to
get one someplace else?
No, no. No.
I didn't know.
I'm--
I'm sorry.
I went all the way down
to the warehouse.
It took me three hours.
I had a big fight
with the foreman.
Really? A fight
with the foreman?
Yes.
Well, again, I'm just...
[GROANS]
...awfully sorry.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, then how about
going out with me?
Okay.
I mean, they found a tee,
and he played golf that day.
I mean, nobody walks into
a dry cleaners with a tee.
Circumstantial evidence
is overwhelming.
You had how many dates
with him? Three?
Around three.
I don't know.
And...?
I told you.
He stopped calling me.
I moved on.
I'm not hung up on him.
What are you
looking at?
What?
I'm not looking.
Nothing.
Why are you
looking at my face?
Where am I gonna look?
Kiss me.
I can't.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[WHISPERS]
Newman!
JERRY:
Newman ruined it for me.
All I could think of
when I was looking at her face...
was Newman found this
unacceptable.
Well, I'm going out with
the stationery store guy.
You're going out with
the stationery store guy?
I felt so guilty about
the pencil, I couldn't say no.
[GROAN OF DISGUST]
Well, well, well.
I'm not treating you
to lunch anymore!
You had to tell Julie
that I made special point
of telling you that I bought you
the big salad, didn't you?
Uh...
You know, if it was
a regular salad,
I wouldn't have
said anything.
But you had to have
the big salad!
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
What?
You're kidding.
I'm turning it on.
Oh, my God.
Get out of here.
Hey, listen to this.
They issued a warrant for
Gendason's arrest. He escaped.
And the police have
just spotted him on the New Jersey Turnpike.
NEWSCASTER:
As you can see, it is a white Ford Bronco.
The police have cleared
the highway traffic
in front of them,
but they are keeping
their distance.
They don't want
this situation to escalate.
And we have gotten
an identification
on the driver of the vehicle.
His name is...Kramer...
and he's reportedly one of
Gendason's golfing buddies.
DISPATCHER:
9-1-1. What are you reporting?
Yeah, this is Kramer.
I got Gendason in the car.
Now, he wants
to see his fish.
I'm taking him
So tell the police
to back off.
Okay, sir.
And what's your name?
My name is Kramer.
You know who I am,
damn it.
I told you not to take
the turnpike.
Yeah, well, I thought
we would blend in.
If you took the Palisades,
this never would have happened.
Then we would have had
all that bridge traffic.
GENDASON:
Ah, just drive.
[♪]
To me, murder doesn't
even really seem like
that great a revenge.
Wouldn't years of subtle
psychological mind games
be a lot more satisfying?
You know, just constantly
calling them
and hanging up when
they pick up the phone?
Sending pizzas and taxis
to their house all night long.
You know, after a while,
they would go,
"I wish this guy would just
kill me already.
I can't take it anymore."
And how come
whenever the police catch
some really bad criminal,
they always put him
in the handcuffs,
and they hit him with the baton,
and they put
the chokehold on him.
But then they don't
want him to hurt his head
when they put him in the back
of the patrol car.
"Watch your head there.
Watch your head.
"Don't hit that
metal edge there.
That really hurts."