The worse part about
a car breaking down
is when you're
out on the road,
you're a guy,
'cause now you have to get out
and pretend like you
know what you're doing.
You gotta go,
"All right, honey,
I'm gonna go check it out."
Walk around the front,
open up the hood.
That's good
'cause it obscures her view.
That's the main reason
you wanna do that.
You're lookin' in there.
You know, you're hoping you're
going to see something in there
so simple, so obvious,
so incredibly easy to fix,
even you can handle it,
like a giant on/off switch
turned off.
So you're going out
with David Puddy?
Yeah.
What, is that
a problem?
Well, I think
he could have asked me.
He's supposed to be
a friend of mine.
I guess he figured
you just wouldn't care.
It has been
a few years.
Elaine, you always care
who an ex-girlfriend dates.
You don't want it to be
someone you know,
and you don't want it to be
someone better than you.
Now, even though the latter
is obviously impossible...
Oh, God.
...the former still applies.
I don't know
what it is.
I just can't see you
with a mechanic.
Oh, yeah,
right, right.
Well, all those mechanics do
is work all day
with their hands and their
big muscular arms on machines,
and then they come home
dripping with animal sexuality
like Stanley Kowalski.
What a huge turnoff
that is.
All right.
Hey, look at that.
They got lobster
on the menu.
Who would order
a lobster here?
I mean, do they bring
a lobster in every day,
hoping today's the day?
So what if they
have a lobster.
Suddenly you're
a shellfish connoisseur?
You know, I think
we really need
to be in front
of a television set.
You take TV out of
this relationship,
it is just torture.
So...
I'm getting
an eye job.
An eye job?
Ma, you don't
need an eye job.
Georgie,
I'm a divorcée.
No, you're not a divorcée.
You're just separated.
You're a separatée.
Well, I'm out there,
George.
No, you're not
out there.
I am too.
You're not
out there.
You can't be
because I am out there.
And if I see
you out there,
there's not enough
voltage in this world
to electroshock me
back into coherence.
Well, anyway,
the operation is on Tuesday,
and I need you
to drive me home
because I'll be
all drugged up.
Tuesday?
I can't do it Tuesday.
Steinbrenner
needs me--
This is the only time
the doctor had.
Kramer, hey, hey!
Hey, buddy.
Come on over here.
I gotta go somewhere.
No, you're gonna sit down,
you son of a gun, you.
All right.
I'm sitting down.
How are ya?
So, Kramer,
I'm getting
an eye job.
Oh. Yeah.
Good for you.
Hey, you have to
look your best.
You're out there now.
She's not out there.
So who's your doctor?
Uh, Bakersaul.
[WHISTLES]
He's good.
He's very good.
He worked on this kid
from Guatemala with no nose,
turned him into
Ricardo Montalban.
Kramer, what are
you doing Tuesday?
Tuesday? Uh...
Why doesn't he pick you up
after the operation?
He's got the car with
the bench seats that you like.
Oh, I don't care.
I can't drive anybody
anywhere until I go down
to that motor vehicle bureau,
get my new plates.
Well, giddyup.
[WHIP CRACKING SOUND]
KRAMER:
Yeah, I'm here to pick up my new plates.
My name is Kramer.
Cosmo Kramer.
Kramer.
All right.
Sign right here,
please.
Okay.
Alrighty.
Thanks.
Assman?
No, no, these don't
belong to me.
I'm not the Assman.
I think there's
been a mistake.
What's your name
again?
Cosmo Kramer.
You are the Assman.
No, I'm not the Assman.
Well, as far as the state of
New York is concerned, you are.
[EXHALES]
How do you feel?
Fine.
Something
the matter?
No.
No, what is it?
No, nothing.
Hey.
I was with David Puddy
last night.
Yeah, so?
He did the move.
What move?
You know.
The move.
Wait a second.
My move?
David Puddy
used my move?
Yes, yes.
Are you sure?
Jerry,
there is no confusing that move
with any other move.
I can't believe it.
He stole my move.
What else did you
tell him?
The two of you must have had
quite a little chat.
Oh, it wasn't
like that.
I didn't even mention you.
You know, we were
in the garage.
You know how
garages are.
They're conducive
to sex talk.
It's a high-testosterone area.
Because of all the pistons
and the lube jobs?
Well, I'm going down
to that garage
to tell him
to stop doing it.
W-- Wait a second.
What?
Isn't that
a little...
rash?
No.
He stole my move.
Yeah, but...
I like the move.
Yeah, but it's
like another comedian
stealing my material.
He doesn't even do it
exactly the same.
He uses a pinch at the end
instead of the swirl.
Oh, yeah,
the pinch.
I've done the pinch.
That's not new.
Besides, I don't know how you
can trust any of his moves now.
His whole repertoire
could be lifted.
You know, it's strange because
he's such an honest mechanic.
I know. He's probably the only
honest mechanic in New York.
So he stole my move,
and he's using it on Elaine.
You told David Puddy a move,
and you didn't tell me.
I need a move. You know
I have no moves, Jerry.
Give me a bite.
Can I just get it
open first?
I can't believe
you're hoardin' sex moves.
I'm out there rubbing
two sticks together,
you're walkin' around
with a Zippo.
All right, all right.
Here.
That's good.
That's very good.
You feel better?
Yeah, much better.
So what's the move
because I need something.
This woman I'm dating,
it's like she's doing her nails
during lovemaking.
Nancy Klopper?
Yeah.
I've never
seen anyone so bored.
I'm working like a dog here.
Give me a moan, somethin'.
I'd settle for a belch
for God's sake.
All right, come on,
let's have it.
All right, George,
I'm gonna tell you.
But I just wanna
make sure--
Yeah, yeah. It's in the vault.
I'm puttin' it in the vault.
It's not even
a question of that.
The point is when something
like this is passed along,
one must be certain
that's going to be used
in a conscientious way.
This is not
some parlor trick to be used--
Are you gonna
tell me or not?
All right.
On your bed,
you got a headboard?
You'll need a headboard.
I got a headboard.
Is it padded?
No.
Good.
How tall is she?
Five foot four.
Why?
You can't have more than
a one foot differential
in your heights.
Otherwise, you could
really hurt your neck.
I can't tell you
how much I appreciate this.
George, if you can master this,
you'll never be alone again.
Now the end is
kind of an option.
I use the swirl.
I like the swirl.
I'm comfortable
with the swirl.
I feel the swirl
is a great capper.
He uses the pinch,
which I find
a little presumptuous.
Is it a clockwise swirl?
I prefer it clockwise,
but it's not
written in stone.
Ah!
There you go, buddy.
What is it?
It's Fusilli Jerry!
It's made from fusilli pasta.
See the microphone?
When did you do this?
In my spare time.
You know, I'm working
on one of you, George.
I'm using ravioli.
See the hard part
is to find a pasta that
captures the individual.
Huh.
Why fusilli?
Because you're silly.
You get it?
Oh.
Yeah.
Well, thank you
very much.
So did you get
your new plates?
Oh. Yeah,
I got my new plates.
But they mixed 'em up.
Somebody got mine,
and I got their vanity plates.
What do they say?
"Assman."
Assman?
Yeah, Assman,
Jerry.
I'm Cosmo Kramer,
the Assman.
Who would order a license plate
that says Assman?
Maybe they're
Wilt Chamberlain's.
It doesn't have to be someone
who gets a lot of woman.
It could be just some guy
with a big ass.
Or it could be
a proctologist.
Yeah.
Proctologist.
Oh, come on.
No doctor would put
that on his car.
Have you ever met
a proctologist?
Well, they usually have
a very good sense of humor.
You meet a proctologist
at a party,
don't walk away.
Plant yourself there
because you will hear
the funniest stories
you've ever heard.
See no one wants
to admit to them
that they stuck
something up there.
Never.
It's always an accident.
Every proctologist's story
ends in the same way.
"It was
a million-to-one shot, doc.
Million to one."
[PHONE RINGS]
Oh, there's my phone.
So where you gonna
stick this?
I'll tell you where
I'd like to stick it.
Hey, David.
Oh, hi, Jerry.
Hey, what's
the story?
I hear you're
doing my move.
What move?
What move.
My move.
The one I told you about.
You used it on Elaine.
Your move?
What, are you kidding?
I was doing that
before I knew you.
All you told me about
was the end.
The ending's
the whole thing.
Without the ending
it's nothing.
You had nothing.
Oh, that ending
was so obvious.
I would have figured
that out anyway.
I didn't need you to
tell me that stupid twist.
Swirl.
I don't even do it.
I know.
You do the pinch.
Yeah,
that's right.
You can't come up
with your own stuff
so you steal
other people's?
You're nothing but a hack.
Are you through?
'Cause I gotta
get back to work.
Well, I'll tell you
what I'll do, you know,
if you want to do it
out of town, okay.
But not in the city.
All right, how about the next
time your car breaks down
you take that
out of town?
Fine.
Good!
[RADIO PLAYING JAZZ]
[SIGHS]
[RATTLING]
[GEORGE GRUNTING]
NANCY:
Ow! George!
What are you doing?
I'm, uh...
you know, uh...
pleasuring you.
Well, stop it.
You don't like
the move?
No, I don't.
You're kidding?
No, I'm not.
It feels like aliens
poking at my body.
Sorry.
I-I'll just go back
to my usual routine.
ELAINE:
Oh, God!
Oh, God, David!
Oh, yes!
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What?!
I can't do the move.
What?
Ah, he's ruined it for me.
Well, oh.
Oh, come on, please.
No, he called me
a hack.
I'm just not into
doin' it anymore.
Oh, so--
So that's it?
I'll come up
with some new stuff.
"Call me. 36-24-46.
I think I have what
you're looking for."
I must caution you
about one thing.
You can't cry
for at least 10 days.
You can ruin
the operation.
Oh, okay.
Now is someone coming
to pick you up?
Yes.
My son's friend should
be here any minute.
Can I help you?
Yeah, Dr. Cosmo Kramer.
Proctology.
Oh, okay.
Sure, doc.
Yeah, thanks.
Have a good day.
I just can't get over
how fantastic you look.
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah, this takes
20 years off.
And it was all
done by laser.
I don't even
need bandages.
MAN:
Yo, Assman.
Look at the Assman.
Did he say "Assman"?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
MAN 2:
Hey, the Assman's in town.
You got that straight!
Boy, I never dreamed
it could make such a difference.
JERRY:
Well, you must've done something wrong.
You probably screwed up
the order.
Did you close with the swirl?
You're supposed to close
with the swirl?
Oh, my God.
Yes, you close
with the swirl.
There's a progression there.
I told you to write it down.
Yeah, yeah.
Should've written it down.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah.
Elaine.
You know what?
Do me a favor.
Don't even do
the move anymore.
You're gonna give it
a bad name.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Yeah, this
is Jerry Seinfeld.
What?
$2,800?
That's the estimate on my car?
No, don't even do anything.
I'm gonna think about it.
Okay. Bye.
What's to think about?
If Puddy says that's
what it is, it's what it is.
He's not gonna cheat you.
Except it's not Puddy.
What happened to Puddy?
We had a little fight
about the move.
I took it to
this other place.
I think they might be
trying to screw me.
Well, of course they're
trying to screw you.
What do you think?
That's what they do.
They can make up anything.
Nobody knows.
"By the way, you need
a new Johnson rod in here."
"Oh, a Johnson rod. Yeah, well,
you better put one of those on."
Hey, Laney.
Yeah, yeah, hello.
Was it something I said?
Yes, as a matter of fact.
David Puddy won't
do the move anymore.
Really?
Oh, he's come up
with some other move.
You should see this thing.
What is it?
Oh, it's a lot of just
fancy, shmancy stuff.
You know what it's like?
It's like
a big budget movie
with a story
that goes nowhere.
Huh.
I mean
this move is no good, Jerry.
It's just takin' up
a lot of my time.
And I...will not stand by
and allow him to perform
this move on me
while a perfectly
good move
is just sittin' in the barn
doin' nothin'.
Let me ask you a question.
This new move?
Is there a knuckle
involved in any way?
Yes.
Yes, as a matter of fact,
there is.
I think that's mine.
I'm not surprised.
Listen. I need you
to do me a favor.
When's the next time
you're gonna see him?
Why?
You gotta get an estimate
on my car from him.
I think this garage
is trying to screw me.
An estimate? How am I
supposed to do that?
Well, look.
Here's the work order
with everything that broke.
Just kind of bring it up
at the right time and find out.
What?
What is this?
Oh, that's, uh...
Fusilli Jerry.
Fusilli Jerry?
Yeah, Kramer made it.
All right, listen.
I'll see you guys later.
All right.
Hey, Assman.
Hey!
Hey.
Well, this is Sally.
Hello.
Hi.
Shall we go?
Okay.
All right.
ESTELLE:
You can't face the fact that I'm improving myself.
You're not the only one
improving yourself.
I worked out with
a dumbbell yesterday.
I feel vigorous.
Just take your mail
and go home.
I have things to do.
I got things to do too.
Don't upset me!
I can't cry!
Getting an eye job
like some Manhattanite, huh?
Well, it's
already working.
Kramer made
a pass at me.
a pass at you?
Kramer made
[CHUCKLES]
You're crazy.
I'm not crazy.
He stopped short
and made a grab.
He stopped short?
That's my move.
I'm gonna kill him.
Hey, let me ask you
a question.
Sure.
What do you charge
for blown shocks?
What?
Two-, 300?
I don't know, maybe 500.
Ahhh.
[BOTH MOANING]
What about a bad gasket?
Bad gasket?
Yeah, like a terrible gasket?
[EXHALES]
What is all this?
Nothing, nothing.
I'm just...taking an interest
in what you do.
What kinda car is it?
Oh.
Any kind of...
Of, uh, Swedish car.
All together that could
run about $1,600.
Oh.
Is that with
the parts and labor?
Uh-huh.
Mmm.
ELAINE:
Mmm, no.
Dave, no, please,
not the knuckle.
[BOTH PANTING]
Well...
That was...
great.
I mean...
wow.
That just came to me.
I mean, I've-- I've--
I've-- Never in my life
have-- Have I...
What--? What was that?
You mean in the end?
Mm.
A counter-clockwise swirl.
What's that?
What?
On your hand. Let me see
what's on your hand.
Nothing.
It's a mole.
Gimme that. Let me see
what's on your hand.
Just some dirt.
I wanna see!
Number one?
Take her leg--
Oh, my God.
Crib notes?
You've got crib notes?
It's a very complicated move.
I couldn't remember it all.
Oh, my God, you're sick.
You know,
it's not the SATs!
Assman.
I'll give him Assman!
JERRY:
Sixteen hundred dollars,
that's all?
Oh, they are
ripping me off.
What are you
going to do?
Well, that's it.
I'm going back
to Puddy.
No move is worth this.
You don't care if he
does the move anymore?
Are you kidding?
He can do every move
I've ever done.
Do you know what
a good mechanic is worth?
You can't compare
that to sex.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi, Mr. Costanza,
what's--?
Where's your friend,
Kramer?
I don't know, why?
Because I'm lookin'
for him, that's why.
He stopped short.
What do you mean?
In the car with my wife,
he stopped short.
You think I don't
know what's that about?
That's my own move.
I used it on Estelle
40 years ago.
I told everybody about it.
Everybody knows,
mmm, I stop short.
Really?
Stopping short?
That's a good move.
You're not kiddin'
it's a good move!
Hey. Hey, Frank.
JERRY: Hey.
Don't Frank me.
I know what you did.
How dare you stop short
with my wife?
Come on, Frank.
Relax.
I don't even know what
you're talkin' about.
Think
I don't know?
Assman!
To think I almost
split the profits
on the Mansiere
with you.
Bro.
Mansiere!
Bro!
[SCREAMS]
Oh, my God.
If I wasn't there,
I wouldn't have believed it.
Me either.
They say this guy's
the best.
He had to use
corkscrew pasta.
Jerry, Jerry, come here.
Take a look at this.
The name on the boat.
Look at it.
JERRY:
"Assman"!
Yeah. He's the Assman.
Jerry, he's the Assman!
Which one is the son?
I am.
Ah. I'm Dr. Cooperman.
I just want you to know
that this won't take long,
and he's going
to be fine.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, excuse me. Uh...
You didn't by any chance
just recently get
the wrong license plates?
Yes! I'm still waiting
for the motor vehicle bureau
to straighten it out.
So...you're the Assman.
FRANK:
Million to one shot, doc.
Million to one.
Where have you been?
You were supposed
to fix the stove.
I've been waiting for hours.
I fell on some fusilli.
Fusilli?
You know, the corkscrew pasta?
It was a fusilli Jerry.
It got stuck in me.
I had to go to
the proctologist.
The proctologist?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, I was so worried.
Ma, don't cry.
Oh, I can't help it.
Ma, your eyes!
Oh!