I can't figure out
why they make
these bizarre toilet seats
that they have.
You know?
Like the clear Lucite ones,
with all the coins in it?
It's a lovely tribute to our
past president, by the way.
It's not bad enough Lincoln
got shot in the head.
We gotta pull down our pants
and sit on it too.
It's just incomprehensible that
you would buy a thing like this.
You install it
on your toilet seat.
This says what about you?
Well, I can't afford to just
throw money down the toilet,
but look how close I am.
I cannot believe Lindsay's
still seeing you
after that Breakfast
at Tiffany's thing.
I think she finds
my stupidity charming.
As we all do.
Anyway, she's having
some kind of a family lunch.
I'll swing by after.
You gonna
meet the mother?
Yeah, I'll zip in,
"how do you do?"
Zip out, she'll love me.
You're good
with the mothers.
You know, I'm better
with the mothers
than I am
with the daughters.
You should
date the mothers.
If I could talk
to the mothers
and have sex
with the daughters,
then I'd really
have something going.
Oh, you got
something going.
Hey.
Hey, you got
a hammer?
What do you need
a hammer for?
Well, I got this new poster.
3-D art. Computers do it.
Oh, yeah,
I wanna see that.
Bring it over.
No, no, I don't have it now.
I gotta pick it up
at Mr. Pitt's.
Elaine was framing
a bunch of stuff for him,
so she did me a favor.
Wanna take a ride?
No, I don't think so.
George, you wanna
go for a ride?
Nah.
Oh, c'mon!
Hey, could you wait
until the man finishes?
All right, I've had it
with you two.
Hey, guess what?
Remember that woman
you saw me with the other day?
She was
an Olympic gymnast.
A gymnast?
Yeah.
She's Romanian.
She won a silver
at the '84 Olympics.
A gymnast, Jerry.
Think of the flexibility.
That sex
will melt your face.
Yeah, well,
I think I'm bailin'.
Bailing?
You know, Kramer,
there's always a price to pay
for just a sexual dalliance.
Jerry, you should pay
that price.
She's Romanian.
What am I gonna
talk to her about?
Ceausescu?
Ch-- W-what?
Gymnast?
I can't believe it.
You didn't tell me
she was a gymnast.
What is this?
What? I'm putting
my shirt back on.
Back on? What was
it doing off?
I take it off when I
go to the, uh-- You know, to the office.
What for?
Frees me up,
no encumbrances.
Unbuttoned or
all the way off?
All the way, baby.
Of course.
Ow!
Again?
Kramer, if you keep
getting these attacks,
you should see the doctor
and have it checked out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You always
take the shirt off?
Always.
Boy, I tell ya.
Knowing you
is like going
into the jungle.
I never know what I'm gonna
find next, and I'm real scared.
PITT:
Elaine,
I need you to proofread
this report for my meeting
with the Poland Creek
bottled water people.
What meeting?
I told you.
I sit on the board
of trustees for Morgan Springs,
and we're trying
to acquire Poland Creek.
Oh.
Are you using a fountain pen?
Yes.
They smear!
Under no circumstances is ink
to be used in this office.
All right, I'll use
a pencil, Mr. Pitt.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Elaine.
Come in. Come in.
Yeah.
Hi, right there.
[RIPS PAPER]
That's not it.
Kramer, it's that--
There she blows.
Kramer... Kramer,
can you do this at home?
I've got work to do, okay?
These are
nice corners.
Elaine, did I hear--?
PITT:
This is very odd.
Yeah, it's 3-D art. Computers
generate 'em. Big computers.
Yes, I've heard about these.
How do they work?
Well, you blur your eyes
like you're staring straight
through the picture
and keep your eyes
unfocused.
Like that.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah!
I don't see it.
It's a spaceship surrounded
by planets, asteroids.
I still don't see it.
Okay. Kramer,
that's enough.
Mr. Pitt has got
work to do.
You ever dream in 3-D?
It's like the boogie man
is coming right at you.
A spaceship, where?
Right in here.
Keep your eyes
unfocused.
Wah! Oh, mama!
Kramer, what's wrong?
Mama!
Are you okay?
I think I gotta go
to the doctor.
Oh, mama!
How long does it
usually take?
[LAUGHING]
George, it is so nice
to finally meet you.
And I'm sorry we kept
Lindsay so long.
Mother.
No, not at all.
No, I have always felt
that the most important thing
in the world, is spending
time with family.
Oh? Are you and
your family close?
Very close, yes.
Almost painfully close.
Mother, I'm gonna walk
Nana and Aunt Phyllis
to the elevator.
George, do you mind waiting
just one more minute?
Mind? Would why
would I mind?
I would love to wait.
Nana, nice to see you.
Nee-nee, nee-nee, Nana!
Aunt Phyllis, a pleasure,
what a pleasure.
Hey, let's do this
again real soon.
I had fun, huh?
Can I offer you
anything to eat?
Oh, no,
I'm fine.
Let me help you
with these dishes.
George, you don't
have to.
No, I know I don't have to.
I want to.
George...you are
such a gentlemen.
I'd argue if I could,
Mrs. Enright.
Here we go.
All right.
Uh... Ugh...
[GARBLED]
Mrs. Enright!
Look it, there's
a spaceship.
That is so cool.
Where is it?
Right here.
I'm looking there!
No, no. Unfocus.
I am unfocused!
[PHONE RINGING]
Hm. Man.
Hello?
Oh, yeah, okay.
Fine.
He'll be right down.
Car is here to pick you up
and take you to the meeting.
Meeting?
The Poland Creek merger?
Why don't you go for me.
How can I go?
All they're gonna do
is read the report.
Mr. Pitt, I do not think that
is just such a good idea--
Oh, damn this thing!
So, Ceausescu, he must
have been some dictator.
Oh, yes, he was not
shy about dictating.
He must have been dictating
first thing in the morning.
"I want a cup of coffee
and a muffin."
And you could not refuse.
You would have
to be crazy.
He was a very
bad dictator.
Yes.
Very bad.
Very, very bad.
JERRY:
So let me get this straight.
You find yourself
in the kitchen.
You see an Êclair
in the receptacle,
and you think
to yourself,
"What the hell.
I'll just eat some trash."
No, no, no, no, no.
It was not trash.
Was the in the trash?
Yes.
Then it was trash.
It wasn't down in.
It was sort of...on top.
But it was in the cylinder.
Above the rim.
Adjacent to refuse
is refuse.
It was on a magazine,
and it still had the doily on.
Was it eaten?
One little bite.
Well...that's garbage.
But I know who took the bite.
It was her aunt.
You, my friend, have
crossed the line that divides man and bum.
You are now a bum.
Hey.
What's with you?
I got a stone.
What stone?
A kidney stone.
What is that anyway?
It's a-- It's a stony
mineral concretion
formed abnormally
in the kidney.
And this jagged chard
of calcium pushes its way
through the ureter
into the bladder.
[WHINING]
It's forced out through the urine.
Oh, that's gotta hurt.
MAN:
Our shareholders
have given basic approval
for the merger,
including the stock swap.
Ah. A stock swap.
Let's swap some stock.
If you'll just give this
to Mr. Pitt and tell him
that we expect to be in full
scale production by this spring.
All right.
Hey, you guys, what's the name
of the new company gonna be?
Moland Spring.
Moland?
Yes, we combined
Morgan and Poland.
Yeah, I know,
but...Moland?
I wouldn't drink
anything called Moland.
But it was
Mr. Pitt's idea.
Oh? Well, what's in a name.
I mean, water is water, right?
We've got to do
something about that name.
GEORGE:
No, Lindsay, it was not
in the garbage.
It was above the garbage,
hovering,
like an angel.
Of course, I know
your aunt bit it.
I kissed her goodbye.
Listen, can I tell you
something else?
In my family, we ate out
of the garbage all the time.
It was no big thing.
That's right.
O-okay.
Bye-bye.
I'm back in. She gave
me a second chance.
Good for you.
Yes! Good for me.
You know what you
should do now?
Get her some flowers,
smooth it out.
Yes.
Flowers.
I will get her flowers.
I will go to the florist.
Behold, the games
of the '84 Olympiad.
Katya's silver medal
performance.
Kramer, you're
still on this?
I've seen gymnasts.
I know what they do.
It's not gonna make
any difference.
Jerry, what is
your problem?
Kramer, you know, guys
like you with no conscience
don't know what it's like
for guys like me.
I'm in
the unfortunate position
of having to consider
people's feelings.
All right, Jerry, are you
familiar with the Kamasutra?
No.
Tantric yoga?
Jerry, you stand
on the threshold to the magical world
of sensual delights
that most men dare not dream of.
Boy, you can really
talk some trash.
I guess that's better
than eating it.
All right, why don't we just
watch the tape, huh?
Pass your stone yet?
Not yet, but the suspense
is killing me.
Hey, that's her.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah
that's her.
Look at the height,
Jerry, the extension.
Now, watch the tuck,
handstand, half turn,
giant into a straddle,
back into a handstand,
nice kip,
reverse hecht.
Oh, nice
leg extension.
Good form.
Now comes
the big dismount.
Look at the rotation.
Full in, double back,
and she sticks the landing.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Perhaps you'd like
to keep the tape.
I'll take that
as a yes.
[WHISTLING]
JERRY:
Well, here we are.
Yes. We are here.
How did you stay
on that beam like that?
I mean, it's only
this wide.
I can balance myself
in any position.
It is amazing, after
years of training,
how one can
contort one's body.
Of course, it is only
useful in gymnastics.
Oh, boy.
JERRY:
I couldn't believe it.
I thought I was entering
a magical world
of sensual delights.
It was just so ordinary.
There was nothing
gymnastic about it.
What'd you think
she was gonna to do?
Well, you know.
I mean... I don't know.
No, what?
Well, obviously,
I prefer not to mention--
Did you think she would
to take chalk--?
You see, now, I really
don't wanna get into this.
Oh, come on,
one thing.
One thing!
What?
Well, frankly,
I thought, you know,
I was gonna kinda
be like the apparatus.
You mean like
the uneven parallel bars?
See, again,
I really don't feel like--
The balance beam?
Could we stop?
[GASPS] Not the pommel horse.
All right.
Let's just drop it.
So let me ask you this.
How long would you say
I have to put in now because of,
you know, last night.
I don't know,
at least three weeks.
Oh, great.
Jerry, that is such
small potatoes.
I think that I may have
single-handedly
put the kibosh
on the big water merger.
Between Poland and Morgan.
Yeah. Started
a big name controversy.
[KRAMER YELPS IN PAIN]
Kramer! The stone!
What happened?
Did you pass the stone?
KRAMER:
No, I tried to do a reverse hecht off my couch,
and I didn't make it.
[GEORGE SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
You call this coffee?
Hey!
What the hell was that?
I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry--
Clean that up!
Oh, sure.
Of course.
Could you hold these
for just a second?
Here you go.
Don't worry about a thing.
It's gonna be fine.
Here we go.
Look at this shine.
Look at this sparkle.
Mrs. Enright!
[HORN HONKS]
Lindsay, I had accidentally
spilled coffee
on the gentleman's
windshield.
Why would I do that?
I have a job.
Well, did she see
a squeegee?
Well, you're not gonna make
a dime without a squeegee.
That's right.
Just tell your mother it was
all a big misunderstanding.
You won't regret it.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
Strike two.
You think
I'm going down?
You're behind
in the count.
Hey, what are you
doing later?
I'm going out with Katya,
thanks to you.
Well, you know,
maybe you should try again.
You know what happens
the first time?
People are a little shy,
a little reticent.
If I do it again that extends my
payment book another two weeks.
Where are you going?
We're going to the circus.
One of her old Olympic
teammates is an acrobat.
I don't feel like going.
Jerry, it's
your obligation, c'mon.
Well, you know, if I gotta go
and spend time with this girl,
you're coming
with me Doctor Cyclops.
I don't wanna go
to the circus, Jerry.
Yeah, well,
you're going.
But I'm afraid of clowns.
PITT:
I didn't send you over there to complain about the name.
I couldn't help it.
Moland Spring?
I like the name Moland.
I picked it out.
After all those months
of negotiating.
Well, I'm so sorry. I--
Well, I'm going riding.
I haven't been on Jenny
for three days.
All because of this
blasted painting.
[PHONE RINGS]
Elaine.
Oh, sorry.
Hello.
Wait a minute.
[CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TOY HORN HONKS]
So, Jerry, you're
enjoying the circus?
Greatest show on earth.
My father used to
take me to the circus.
When the elephants came by,
he would scream curses at them,
blaming them for all
the ills of society.
Well, they certainly
take up a lot of space.
Ah, Misha.
Katya.
Misha, this
is Jerry.
Ah, yes,
the comedian.
[SPEAKING IN ROMANIAN]
ELAINE:
Oh, yes. Yes, I'll tell him.
Yes, thank you.
Hold on. Hold on.
Mr. Pitt.
I think I'm
on to something.
Mr. Pitt, the board
of directors is on the phone.
They've called
an emergency meeting.
They want you there
to discuss the merger.
You said keep your eyes out of
focus, which is misleading.
You want deep focus.
Yes. Hi. Okay, fine.
Hold on a second.
Let me just...
Yeah, I've got it--
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He'll be there.
Mr. Pitt.
You have got to stop
staring at that poster.
I see something that
could be a spaceship.
Is it round?
Is it pointed?
No. You don't see it.
You are never gonna see it!
Mr. Pitt, you have to meet
with the shareholders.
You have to leave now.
Do you hear me?
Mm. Yes.
My goodness.
What's happened to me?
When's the meeting?
In about 20 minutes.
Oh! Do I have time
to change?
Umm...no.
Well, excuse me, I better
get straight over there.
Uh, Mr. Pitt.
Yes?
Umm...
There's a, just--
Is that ink?
No.
GEORGE:
Well,
here we are.
Do you wanna come in?
My mother is having
a little party.
Maybe I could just
use the bathroom.
Sure.
Let's go.
ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]:
Ladies and gentlemen, may I direct your attention
to the center ring,
where the incomparable Misha
will balance 10 stories
above the circus floor
on a wire no wider
than a human thumb.
It is time.
Well, break a leg.
Show biz.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the incomparable Misha!
Those capes
are really coming back.
Oh. Sorry I
took so long.
They've got one of those
3-D art posters in there.
It's mesmerizing.
Ow!
Owww!
Yah!
[DRUM ROLL]
[KRAMER SCREAMS]
What is that sound?
It is horrible.
[ROARING]
[TRUMPETING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[CROWD GASPS]
Whoo!
Anybody see that
poster in there?
That was weird,
wild stuff, huh?
Whoo.
I have been accused
of wrongdoing,
but these false accusations
will not deter us.
We will annex Poland
by the spring at any cost!
And our stock will rise high.
The doctor said Misha
is going to be all right.
I must go and be
with Misha now.
I don't want you
to come with me.
Why not?
It has been three days
since our night together.
Misha said that was all
the time I needed to put in.
Really?
In my country, they speak
of a man so virile, so potent,
that to spend a night with such
a man is to enter a world
of sensual delights
most women dare not dream of.
This man is known
as the comedian.
You may tell jokes,
Mr. Jerry Seinfeld,
but you are no comedian.
[WHISTLING]