The love seat is an interesting
little item there.
I guess some guy thought, "If we
can't get them to sit closer,
why not just shorten
the furniture?"
My other favorite
furniture brand is the La-Z-Boy.
This is very flattering
to the prospective customer,
isn't it?
Why don't we just call it
"the half-conscious dead beat
with no job, home all day,
eating Cheetos
and watching TV" recliner.
And it goes back so far,
that thing.
I mean, go to bed already.
It's over. You're wiped.
JERRY:
So she got you to join a book club?
I got a feeling
I'm gonna be
much smarter than you
pretty soon.
Well, I think
that statement alone
reflects your burgeoning
intelligence.
Hey, what about
this one?
No, I don't like
that one.
So, what's your first book?
Breakfast at Tiffany's.
90 pages.
It's kind of old, isn't it?
They wanted to read
a Truman Capote book.
Oh, sure.
Truman Capote.
Yeah, he's a great writer.
Oh, yeah.
Did you ever
read anything by him?
No, you?
Nah.
Oh, what about
this one?
Look at this.
This is it.
This is what
I'm looking for.
Oh, yeah.
ELAINE:
Hey, what's going on?
New couch,
baby.
New couch?
Why?
I love this couch.
You know what
the best part about it is?
It doesn't fold out,
so no one can sleep over.
Hello.
Oh, let me
get the door for you.
Ooh, be careful,
be careful.
Wait till
you see it.
It's perfect.
The guy told me
it's one of a kind.
They stopped
making it.
What are you doing
with your old couch?
Nothing, the moving guys
are taking it.
Why, you want it?
Yeah, I'll take it.
Oh, I'm sure they can
deliver it to your apartment.
Yes, they can.
Hey, couch
is coming?
It's here.
All right,
yeah.
You know, I'm excited
about this, Jerry.
In a way I feel like
I'm getting a new couch.
Yeah, so do I.
Ooh, you remember
Poppie?
Oh, you mean
from Poppie's Restaurant?
Yeah, yeah. Anyway, uh, we're
going into business together.
You remember that idea
I had a few years ago
about the pizza place
where you make your own pizza?
Yeah.
What was that again?
It's a pizza place
where you make
your own pie.
We give you the dough,
the sauce, the cheese.
You pound it, slap it.
You flip it up into the air,
put your toppings on,
and you slide it into oven.
Sounds good, huh?
[SOUTHERN ACCENT]
Ooh, I can't wait to get me a fella
and make my own pie.
What made you resurrect
that old idea?
Well, I happened to be
eating at Poppie's
when I told him
the old idea,
and his eyes...
just lit up.
You know, he wants
to back it.
I heard Poppie's
was good.
Let's go.
I'm not going there.
Didn't he get busted
by the board of health?
Well, that was
in the past, Jerry.
As it happens,
New York magazine
just judged
his kitchen
to be one of the cleanest
in the city.
They got a duck there--
You think you died
and went to heaven.
Ooh, I love duck.
Come on, come on.
Well, you gotta order it
two days in advance.
You know,
I'm gonna call him.
I'm gonna order
the duck for you.
Oh, Kramer--
Right there,
guys.
That's perfect.
Huh?
What do you think,
Lainie?
Well,
I don't know.
I'll have to
sit on it.
Oh no, I don't want
anyone sitting on it.
Sign here.
Excuse me.
Um, I was wondering
if it would be possible
if you could deliver
the old couch
to my apartment.
It's not very far.
Sure.
Okay.
You, uh-- You got room
in the truck for me?
Uh, heh, heh.
Yeah, I think we can
squeeze you in.
Oh, goody.
Okay.
Well, uh...
I'll see you chumps later.
Did you offer those guys
a drink?
Uh, no.
Should I have?
What kind
of a person are you?
I don't know.
GEORGE:
Okay. Breakfast at Tiffany's.
So, he puts
the couch down,
and just as he's
about to leave,
he says,
"Do you date moving men?"
Uh-huh.
You wanna know
what I said?
Oh, I can't wait.
"I do now."
Clever.
Is that something?
Yes.
You're something.
So, anyway, when they were
in my house before--
Yeah?
--I didn't offer them
anything to drink.
Well, they're real men, Jerry.
They get sweaty.
So anyone sweaty
comes into your house
has to be offered
a drink?
Yes.
Well, would you
apologize for me.
Mm-hm.
Hello.
Jerry, so good
to see you again.
Hello...Poppie.
This is Elaine.
Nice to meet you,
Poppie.
Let me show you
to your table, huh?
Okay.
Your duck is a-cookin'
as we speak.
It is so succulent,
so succulent.
Well, Kramer told us all about
your business venture together.
Your friend and I are gonna
make a lot of money, huh?
Ha, ha.
Of course, I already have
a lot of money.
Poppie does very well.
Very well.
Well, your mother must be
very proud of you.
My mother was taken
from my house
by the communists
in the middle of the night
when I was 10 years old.
She was sent
to a slave labor camp,
where she labored
for 12 years.
Finally,
they released her,
and she was
on a boat to America
to reunite with us.
But she was served
some bad fish,
and she died
on the high seas.
So, what's good
tonight?
Boy, I'm really
looking forward
to this duck.
I've never had food
ordered in advance before.
Meh, I could have stayed home
and ordered a pizza
from Pokeno's.
Pokeno's?
Oh, no, you should never
order pizza from Pokeno's.
Why not?
Because the owner
contributes a lot of money
to those fanatical
anti-abortion groups.
So you won't eat the pizza?
Uh-uh, no way.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, what if, uh,
Poppie felt the same way?
Well, I...
I guess I wouldn't
eat here then.
Really?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, perhaps
we should inquire.
Poppie!
Oh, Poppie.
Could I have
a word?
Yes, Jerry.
I just checked
your duck.
It is more succulent
than even I had hoped.
Oh.
Poppie, I was just curious.
Where do you stand
on the abortion issue?
When my mother was abducted
by the communists,
she was with a child.
Oh, boy.
But the communists,
they put an end to that.
So on this issue,
there is no debate.
And no intelligent person
can think differently.
Well, Poppie,
I think differently.
And what gives you
the right to do that?
The Supreme Court
gives me the right to do that.
Let's go, Jerry, come on.
I heard that.
Let's go, Henry.
We just got here.
I'm with you,
Poppie.
Let's go.
And I am not
coming back.
You're not welcome!
Well, I'm certainly glad
I brought it up.
JERRY:
Well, you should have seen it.
It us quite a scene
over there.
I'm sorry
I missed it.
Oh, you really
missed something.
And I have to say,
it was pretty much
all my fault.
[LAUGHS]
So, how's the book coming?
I said, how's the book coming?
Oh, pretty good.
So, what's it about?
Well, it's about
Holly Golightly.
Holly Golightly?
She's quite a character.
Yeah. You haven't read a page,
have you?
No.
Yeah.
Big surprise.
I couldn't.
You know,
if it's not about sports,
I find it very hard
to concentrate.
You're not very bright,
are you?
No, I'm not.
I would like to be,
but I'm not.
Well, what
am I gonna do?
The book club meets
in a few days.
Why don't you rent the movie.
Why don't I rent the movie.
You see,
this is when I like you.
All right,
now I'm relieved.
So...
How was the dinner
last night?
Oh, well...
Did you enjoy the duck?
Oh, Elaine,
I was just asking
how dinner went
last night.
Oh, well...
All right,
what did you do to Poppie?
Nothing.
Well, he's in the hospital,
and the cook said says
you put him there.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
I'm gonna go
and visit him later.
It would be nice
if you got him something.
[KNOCKS TABLE]
We should
get him something.
Yeah,
you're right.
Do you know
that I have been using
the same bottle
of shampoo for a year,
and I shampoo every day.
So, what do you think
of my conversation?
Not much.
I-I would have
invited you up,
but I, uh-- I don't
have any furniture.
You don't have
any furniture?
No, I hate furniture.
I can't look at it.
Oh, I can
understand that.
I'm a pretty good
date, huh?
Yeah.
No heavy lifting.
KRAMER:
Anyway, Jerry and Elaine felt very badly
about what happened to you,
and they wanted you
to have this.
What's this?
A bottle of wine
and five-alarm chili.
They're trying
to kill Poppie?
Why?
Well, don't they know I have
a gastrointestinal disorder.
If I would have any of this,
I would die.
Then Poppie
is no good to anyone.
This is a sick,
sick joke on Poppie.
How could you be friends
with those two?
Well, we're not
very close.
They owe me
for those ducks.
Yeah.
They're flown in
from Newfoundland.
Oh, they got
good ducks there, huh?
Oh, very good ducks.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'm in love!
Whoa.
This is it, Jerry.
This is it!
He is such
an incredible person.
He's real. He's honest.
He's unpretentious.
Oh, I'm really lucky.
Did you tell him I was sorry
I didn't offer him the drink?
No, I forgot.
The best part is, he doesn't
play games, you know?
There are no games.
No games?
What is the point of dating
without games?
How do you know if you're
winning or losing?
Well, all I know is,
he doesn't like games,
and he doesn't
play games.
You know, he has too much
character and integrity.
Uh-huh.
And what is his stand
on abortion?
What?
What is his stand...
on abortion?
Well, I'm sure he's pro-choice.
How do you know?
Because he...
Well...
He's just
so good-looking.
Well, you should
probably ask.
Because if he's gonna
be coming over
with those Pokeno's pizzas,
it could be trouble.
GEORGE:
I'd like to rent Breakfast At Tiffany's.
Uh, this is out.
Someone has it.
Out?
Oh, no.
I've been
to four other places.
You're the only ones
that have had it.
I could put it
on reserve for you
if you'd like.
Maybe we could call them
and ask them to return it.
Oh, sorry.
We can't do that.
Well, maybe they're
done with it.
I could go pick it up.
I don't think so.
It doesn't work that way.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
MAN [ON INTERCOM]:
Yes?
Um, excuse me,
are you Joel Temple?
Yes.
Uh... Yes.
Uh, you don't know me.
Uh, my name
is George Costanza.
Did you happen to rent
Breakfast At Tiffany's?
Hey.
Hey, what's happening?
Yeah, well, you know,
Poppie's over my place.
You know, tonight's
the big night.
I'm gonna make the first
test pizza at the restaurant.
Oh, hey, you got a regular
Manhattan Project
going over there.
Yeah.
Anyway,
he's about to leave.
He wants
the duck money.
Oh, okay. Hi, Poppie.
Hello.
I'm sorry
about the gift.
I didn't know
about your condition.
That's fine.
If you just give me
my duck money,
I'll be on my way.
Okay, I'll get it.
Why don't you
sit down, Poppie.
You're still
recuperating.
Ah.
Oh, you tired,
Poppie?
No.
Hey, Poppie.
You really think people wanna
make they're own pizza?
Kramer, did I ever tell you
about my mother?
My mother--
Here you go.
Anyway, I'm, uh,
sorry again about the--
The...
The what?
Okay, Poppie.
The...
So, so long,
huh?
I'll see you
tonight.
All right.
Kra-- Kramer,
w-what is this?
What is what?
This puddle on my sofa.
What puddle?
Th-that puddle!
I don't know.
Is it?
Could it?
Could-- Could
he have...?
It is!
Poppie peed
on my sofa!
You sure?
Well,
what is it then?
My new sofa!
Poppie peed
on my new sofa!
I'm sure
it'll come out.
I don't care
if it comes out,
I can't
sit on that anymore.
You're making
too much of it.
Yeah, you're right.
Just a natural
human function.
Happens to be on my sofa...
instead of the toilet,
where it would normally be.
Right.
GEORGE:
Well, anyway the book club meets tomorrow, Mr. Temple.
Well, I was gonna
watch it with my daughter.
She likes Audrey Hepburn
very much.
Yeah, she was
a delicate flower.
Why didn't you just
read the book?
Well, as I say,
the, uh, pinkeye
made my vision
quite blurry.
Remy.
Uh, this is George.
Would you mind
if he watched
Breakfast at Tiffany's
with us?
CARL:
Hi.
I missed you.
Oh, I missed you.
I don't remember
the last time
I felt this way.
Me either.
I think about you
all the time.
You do?
Do you think about me?
Oh, yeah,
all the time.
All the time.
Although...recently
I've been thinking
about this friend
of mine.
What friend?
Oh, just this woman.
She got impregnated
by her troglodytic
half-brother
and decided
to have an abortion.
You know, someday
we're gonna get
enough people
in the Supreme Court
to change that law.
So anything to,
uh, nosh?
What did you want?
Popcorn.
Popcorn?
Where do you think
you are?
Well, a lot of people
keep popcorn in the house.
Well, we don't.
You might wanna try it.
Makes the movie more enjoyable,
that's all.
Here's some
nuts.
Oh, nuts!
Excellent.
You know
what I love?
How there's two nuts
named after people.
Hazel and filbert.
Can we watch
the movie now, Daddy?
Hey, let's turn off
the lights,
get some real
movie atmosphere.
The lights
are fine.
KRAMER:
See, everybody can do this.
Yeah.
No, no,
use your wrist.
It's all
in the wrist.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa!
Not too high!
Aha, yeah.
Very good.
That's very good.
All right.
Sauce on here.
[MUMBLES IN ITALIAN]
Some cheese.
Not too much.
And...cucumbers.
Wait a second.
What is that?
It's cucumbers.
No, no, no.
You can't put
cucumbers on pizza.
Well, why not?
I like cucumbers.
That's not a pizza.
It'll taste terrible.
Yeah, but that's the idea.
You make your own pie.
Yes, but we cannot
give the people
the right to choose
any topping they want.
Now, on this issue,
there can be no debate.
What gives you the right
to tell me
how I would make my pie?
Because it's a pizza!
It's not a pizza till it
comes out of the oven.
It's a pizza the moment
you put your fists
in the dough.
No, it isn't.
Yes, it is.
["MOON RIVER" PLAYS
ON TELEVISION]
I'm home.
Hey, honey.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, baby.
Hello.
Breakfast
at Tiffany's?
Yeah.
Well, I just came
back from Angela's.
It's not looking
very good for Duncan.
Oh, that's
too bad.
Yeah, the doctor thinks
it's just a matter of time.
GEORGE:
Ahem.
Joe...
Could you?
Poor guy.
I hate to see him
suffer like this.
Yeah.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I hate to be
one of those people,
but we're right in the middle
of this thing.
I can't hear.
Who are you?
This is
George Costanza.
It's just very hard to follow
with all the talking.
I'll pause it,
okay?
Any more
grape juice?
Who is this guy?
He's in some
book club.
And what's
he doing here?
Cheating on his test.
[HUMMING "MOON RIVER"]
So, uh, are we
watching the movie,
or are we
still talking?
Okay, come on,
let's go.
What?
Come on,
you took my seat.
It's not your seat.
I was-- I was
sitting there, come on.
You didn't save it.
I had the arm.
Joe?
What's the difference?
Well, I was
very comfortable.
I've got
my nuts here.
It's my couch.
All right, come on,
come on, scootch over.
Wait.
Daddy,
make him move!
Oh!
Look!
Look what you did!
You got grape juice
all over our couch.
You ruined our couch!
Joe.
Oh, my God.
You see?
So, are you gonna get
a new couch?
Well, I guess
I have no choice.
What-- Do you want
your old couch back?
I was hoping you'd offer.
Yeah?
CARL:
It's the movers.
Okay.
Who's that?
Your boyfriend,
he's taking it out.
No, he's not
my boyfriend.
Why?
Take a guess.
Oh, really.
Uh-huh.
Ha, ha, ha.
Hi.
Hey, Carl,
I also need you
to go to Elaine's
and bring
my old couch back.
Today?
Could you?
Sure.
What are you doing
with this couch?
George
is taking it.
Did you tell him
it was peed on?
He said
he doesn't care.
He'll just
turn the cushion over.
CARL:
I'm sorry you feel that way, Elaine.
Yeah, me too.
It's just too bad.
Yeah, it is.
Well, I better
get this couch
back to Jerry's.
Can I offer you
anything to drink?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, all I've got
is grape juice.
Throw it.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
The couch!
She didn't want
the constraints
of any relationship.
That's why she got rid
of the cat.
The most important thing
in Holly's life
was her independence.
Well,
not really.
After all, she did
get together
with George Peppard.
I mean, Fred.
George,
Fred's gay.