If you have a close friend
and they get involved with
someone in a relationship,
it affects your friendship,
doesn't it?
Because it's like
you were a comedy team,
and now there's
this third person.
You know, it kind of
throws off the timing.
Whose on first?
I don't know.
Dear, who do you think
is on first?
In fact, whenever
a friend of mine
starts with a new
girlfriend,
he should just say,
"I look like the person
you used to know,
"but I've been modified to
survive in this relationship.
"In other words, if we're having
an argument and she's there,
"I may say I totally disagree
with you, but what that means is
"I'd like to help you out,
but I'd rather continue
to see her naked."
Okay, cowboys,
what'll you have?
I'll have the turkey club
without the bacon.
And I'll have the bacon club
without the turkey.
George, don't make me
get tough with you.
Why? You think you
can beat me up?
You wouldn't want me to mess up
that beautiful face of yours.
[SNORTS]
Stop it. Stop it.
You don't want bacon.
I'll surprise you.
Wow. Is she
not terrific?
She does have a way.
You think she thinks
I have a beautiful face,
or is she
just saying that?
Well, they do
work on tips.
"George, don't make me
get tough with you."
Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Who says that?
She is really cool.
What do you think?
Do you think she likes me?
Ah, I should have got
the egg-white omelet.
Why should she like me?
Who am I?
There's a million
people to like.
The omelet.
Damn.
Maybe she could like me.
Is it that far-fetched?
Maybe she sees something.
Is it possible?
No.
Not possible.
Hey.
Hey. Hey, Laney.
Laney.
How was the trip?
What trip?
You were gone?
I went to England.
With Mr. Pitt,
for five days?
Huh. Pfft.
How was it?
Actually,
it was great.
I met an Englishman,
and we really hit it off.
Yeah, well,
that relationship's
obviously got
a lot of potential.
Yeah, well, Jerome,
I happen to be flying him in
on my frequent-flier miles.
Flying him in?
How long is he
staying for?
It's an open-ended
ticket.
He can return
any time he wants.
All this in five days.
Oh, no.
It's Kenny Bania.
GEORGE:
Who's he?
He's this awful comedian.
Hey, Jerry.
Hey, Kenny.
Elaine, George.
Hi.
How's it going?
Great.
I've been working out.
Went from a size 40 to a 42.
No kidding.
Yeah.
I'm huge.
Well, I'll leave
you guys alone.
Oh.
Okay, thanks.
Oh!
Jerry, you know what
just hit me?
I was thinking.
What size suit are you?
I'm a 40, why?
I just got a brand-new
Armani suit.
Doesn't fit me anymore.
You want it?
Well, I don't know if I--
Aw, come on. Why should it
just sit in the closet?
An Armani suit?
Take the suit.
Well...
Okay.
I guess.
You gonna be home later?
Yeah.
I'll drop it off.
[KNOCKS]
Hey, hey.
New suit.
Yeah, yeah.
Lucky me.
Here.
I personally made you
a cold chicken sandwich.
It's not even
on the menu.
Oh, this is fabulous.
GEORGE:
She is nice.
I like her.
I like her, Jerry.
She's got substance.
She oozes substance.
Well, go in there
and talk to her.
She's not gonna put
'em on the glass.
You mean to walk back in?
That's the toughest move
in the business.
You're sending me out
into no man's land,
and if I get shot down,
I have to crawl
all the way back.
Well, I can't do it.
I can't do it, I tell you.
Pull yourself together.
You're going in there,
soldier.
That's an order.
Get in there.
Hey.
Hi.
Listen, I need you
to do me a favor.
What?
I need you to help me
move my refrigerator.
Why?
Because I'm getting rid of it.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
KENNY:
It's K.B.
I have the suit.
All right.
Come on up.
So.
Why are you getting rid
of your refrigerator?
Well, after that kidney stone,
I only want fresh food.
It's gotta be fresh.
I'm not eating any
more stored food.
Plus, you know,
I want the space.
What for?
I could put a dresser
in there.
I could get dressed
while I'm making breakfast.
Hey.
Here you go.
Yeah.
You didn't think I was really
gonna give you a suit, did you?
You giving
him this suit?
That's right.
And it's Armani.
Armani.
Hey, Armani,
Jerry.
Yes, yes, I heard.
Come on.
Try it on.
No, it's okay.
Come on. I wanna see
how it fits.
All right.
There you go.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, boy. Look at that.
That looks great.
I can't believe
you're giving him this.
I don't even want
anything for it.
He's very generous,
isn't he?
Yes.
Yes, he is.
I'll tell you what.
You can take me out
to dinner sometime.
Dinner?
Yeah, you buy me a meal.
Can't get a better
deal than that.
No, you'll never get
a better deal than that.
All right.
I'll leave you alone.
Yeah.
All right.
Look at that.
Armani, huh? Yeah.
Yeah, that's a deal.
That's a terrible deal.
I don't wanna go out
to dinner with him.
I'd rather make
my own suit.
I did it.
It's all done.
Hey!
I did it, huh?
We're going out as soon
as she gets off of work.
And it'll still
be daytime.
I'm much better in the daytime
than at night. Less pressure.
I love the day date.
No wine, no shower.
There you go.
ELAINE:
So the trip was good?
Yes.
Apart from that dreadful
airline food.
It wreaked absolute havoc
with my stomach.
You know, I have to say,
I've never admitted
this to anyone, but, um...
I kind of like airline food.
It's probably
because of...
[MUMBLES]
What?
Yeah, what?
[SIGHS]
What?
Where I come from,
we don't say "what."
It's proper
to say "pardon."
Oh, that should be...
[MUMBLES]
Pardon?
Nothing.
WAITRESS:
So then about a year ago I started selling
these funky little
hair clips.
It's going
pretty good.
I make them
in my apartment.
I'm just doing this
waitress thing for a while
because I wanted to go
to Europe this summer,
and I could use
a few extra--
Careful.
Oh, it's just
horse manure.
Horse manure's
not that bad.
I don't even mind
the word "manure."
You know, it's "newer,"
which is good,
and a "ma"
in front of it.
Ma-nure.
When you consider
the other choices,
manure is actually
pretty refreshing.
[LAUGHS]
That's a nice watch,
George.
Yeah.
You know, my boyfriend
has the same one.
Huh, really?
Yeah, he loves
watches.
He's a real
watch freak.
Well, how about that.
Oh, look out.
You stepped
right in it.
Yes.
I sure did.
So you just pretended
it didn't bother you?
What is that,
boyfriend?
I don't
understand that.
What does she think
I asked her out for?
It's the way they just
slip it in there too.
Yeah.
Yeah. Like it's all just
part of the conversation.
"Oh, my boyfriend
really likes watches.
He's a real watch freak."
Well, that's fabulous.
Well, let me
ask you this.
What exactly did you say
when you asked her out?
I said, "Would you like to go
for a walk or something?"
Oh, a walk.
Well...
Or something!
I said, "Or something."
"Or something."
Yeah, that's a date.
There you go.
Of course, you know, there is
always the possibility
that she called an audible.
What do you mean?
If she got up to
the line of scrimmage,
didn't like the looks
of the defense,
and changed the play.
I think things
were going okay.
We were having
a nice conversation.
Uh-huh.
I mentioned how
I liked horse manure.
You did.
Yeah.
You said you
liked horse manure?
Yeah.
You know, about how when
you break it down,
it's really
a very positive thing.
You know, you have a "newer"
with a "ma" in front of it.
Ma-nure.
It's not bad.
And it was around
this point
that she mentioned
the boyfriend.
Yeah.
Oh, you think because of what
I said about the manure?
I was just saying how it
takes a negative thing
and puts a positive
spin on it.
I'm just saying
there's a chance
she may not
have been enamored
with your thoughts
and feelings on manure.
So you don't think she
really has a boyfriend?
My honest opinion?
I think she made it up.
Then she's just a liar,
isn't she?
Hey.
Ah, you want something to eat,
don't you?
Oh, no, no, no.
You got me all wrong, buddy.
I am loving this
no refrigerator.
You know what
I discovered?
I really like depriving
myself of things.
It's fun.
Very monastic.
Well, what do you eat?
It's all fresh.
Fresh fish, fresh foul,
fresh fruit.
I buy it.
Mmmmm!
I eat it.
I'm glad it's
working out.
Oh, yeah.
It's working out.
And I got a date with that
waitress who works at Reggie's.
Boy, if I could meet a hostess,
we could open up our own place.
Ha, ha.
Yeah. Well, I'll tell you,
she's a full-figured gal.
Is she?
Oh, you better believe it,
buddy.
Hey, George, we could
double sometime.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we could.
You know, Kramer,
the next time you talk to her,
find out if she knows
Kelly from Monk's.
I wanna know if she
really has a boyfriend.
[PHONE RINGS]
All right.
Hello.
Hi, Jerry.
It's Kenny.
Oh, hi.
I was thinking,
if you're not busy,
maybe I can get
my meal today?
Yeah, you wanna
get that meal, don't ya?
How about Mendy's.
Ooh. Ever been there?
No, I haven't.
You're gonna love it.
I'll meet you around 7.
All right.
Yeah, I really needed
that suit.
KENNY:
I start off with curls.
That's good for the bicep.
I do 10 reps, two sets.
That's fantastic.
You work out
with weights?
No, I don't.
You should.
Why?
You worn the suit yet?
No, not yet.
Have you decided?
Oh, get
the swordfish.
Best swordfish
in the city.
The best, Jerry.
I'll have the salmon.
And you?
Uh, you know what I think?
I'm just gonna have soup.
Yeah, I'll save the meal
for another time.
Another time?
What other time?
I had a hot dog earlier.
I'm not that hungry.
No, no, Bania, no.
This is the dinner.
The soup counts.
Soup's not a meal.
You're supposed
to buy me a meal.
I'm not stopping
you from eating.
Go ahead and eat.
Get anything you want.
I don't want
anything but soup.
Then that's the meal.
But I had the hot dog.
I didn't tell you
to have a hot dog.
Who told you
to have a hot dog?
Hey, I give you
a brand-new Armani suit,
and you won't even
buy me a meal.
All right.
Fine.
Get the soup!
JERRY:
So he just gets soup.
He wants
to save the meal.
So now I gotta do
it all over again.
What kind of soup
did he get?
I don't know.
Consommé or something.
Consommé.
Hm.
What?
Well, that's really
not a meal, Jerry.
I mean, if he had gotten
chicken gumbo or matzo ball,
even mushroom barley,
then I would agree with you.
Those are very hearty soups.
Elaine, you're missing
the whole point.
What?
The meal is the act
of sitting down with him.
It doesn't matter
what you get.
As long as he's sitting in
that restaurant, it's a meal.
Was it a cup or a bowl?
You see, again--
I'm just curious.
A bowl, okay?
Did he crumble
any crackers in it?
As a matter of fact,
he did.
Oh, well,
crackers in bowl.
That-- That could be a meal.
It's like I'm talking
to my aunt Sylvia here.
Oh, hi, Simon.
This is Jerry.
Hello.
Elaine, do you have
any cash on you?
Um, yeah,
in my purse.
No, there was
only $6.00.
Well, I have
some money.
What do you need?
Twenty should
cover me.
Thanks, mate.
Where you goin'?
Just visiting.
Oh, okay.
See you later.
I won't be back for dinner.
[BRITTISH ACCENT]
Pardon?
So is she working?
Is she here?
Yeah, yeah,
she's here.
Have you said
anything to her?
No, but I'm very
uncomfortable.
Are you gonna
say anything?
I don't know.
Hello.
Well, what's it
going to be?
What's it gonna be?
Yes. What'll you have?
Are you eating?
It's in that vein.
I'll, uh-- I'll just
have a bowl of chili.
I'll have an egg-white omelet.
What's it gonna be?
Hear that?
Yeah, that was bad.
Did you feel that tension?
We used to have banter.
There's no more banter.
Oh, no.
It's Kenny.
Slide out so
he can't sit here.
Hey.
You worn the suit yet?
Actually I did.
I put it on last night
and slept in it.
You did?
No, I'm joking.
Oh. Ha, ha!
Can I squeeze in?
Sure you can.
Can I take your order?
What kind of soup
do you have?
Why don't you
get a sandwich.
Okay.
I'll have tomato soup
and, uh, tuna on toast.
Okay.
This is it,
you know.
This is the meal.
So stock up, buddy boy.
What are you
talking about?
This isn't a meal.
Yes, it is.
Soup and sandwich.
That is a meal.
You're suppose
to buy me dinner
in a nice restaurant
like Mendy's.
I tried to do that.
This is lunch
in a coffee shop.
Doesn't matter.
This is it.
This completes
the transaction.
Oh, soup and a sandwich
for a brand-new Armani suit.
Is that any kind
of a gesture?
I'm really not
comfortable--
Hey, I just spoke to Hildy
about your friend.
Yeah?
She doesn't have
a boyfriend.
She made it up.
Hi.
Where's Simon?
Oh, he'll be right up.
He's just getting some beer.
And I'm not
expecting any change.
When's he leaving?
About two days.
Although he's hinting at
how he'd like to stay.
Fortunately, he has no money
and no prospects.
Hey, mate.
Fancy a beer?
No thanks.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
No, I'm sorry, Bania.
I'm not going over this again.
Well, who told you
to order soup?
No.
There's no dinner.
There's not going
to be any dinner.
You've had a sandwich
and two bowls of soup,
and that's it.
Goodbye.
[SIGHS]
Hey, what size suit
are you?
Forty.
Perfect.
Brand-new Armani suit.
You want it?
Absolutely.
Great.
It's yours.
I can't stand
the sight of it.
Elaine,
here's the car keys.
Thanks.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah.
KENNY: Listen, Jerry.
I been doing some thinking.
I want my suit back.
I don't have your suit.
I gave it away.
Well, it's my suit.
Well, it's gone.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye, Bania.
Hey.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, uh, well,
how's everything?
Okay.
Good.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Really.
You want food, don't you?
It's not for me.
It's for Hildy, the waitress
I was telling you about.
She's hungry.
She wants food.
If I go back in there
without any food,
there's gonna be trouble.
All right.
Go ahead.
Did you find anything?
Uh, yeah.
There's a few things
in here.
Peanut butter,
cheese, yeah.
Cheese is good.
What kind?
Uh, Swiss.
All right.
It'll have to do. Come on.
JERRY:
What are you doing out here? Aren't we gonna eat?
I can't go in there.
I'm too uncomfortable.
What are you saying?
We're not going
in there anymore?
Hey, what are you
doing out here?
We can't eat
here anymore
because he took a waitress
out for a walk.
What's the difference?
Let's go to Reggie's.
Reggie's?
I can't eat
anything there.
It's the same menu.
There's no big salad.
They'll make you
a big salad.
What do you think?
They're the only ones
that make a big salad?
All right.
Let's go to Reggie's.
So what's going on
with Simon?
Did he leave?
Ugh, wait until
you hear this.
So Simon picks this woman up
right in front of me.
Look at this.
They make a point of saying,
"No egg-white omelets."
Look at that.
So what?
Have a yolk.
It won't kill ya.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Hildy.
Can I get
an egg-white omelet?
Did you read the menu?
All right.
Just give me a Western.
How 'bout a big salad?
A big salad?
You see?
Just tell her what you want.
They'll make it for you.
It's a salad, only bigger,
with lots of stuff in it.
I can bring you
two small salads.
Could you put it
in a big bowl?
We don't have big bowls.
All right.
Just give me
a cup of decaf.
We have Sanka.
GEORGE:
I mean, it's not fair.
I been going there
for seven years.
She's been there
three weeks.
Not fair.
If anyone should be forced
to leave that place,
it should be her.
She's on your turf.
I wish she could
get fired.
Is there any way
that could happen?
I mean, I know how
to get myself fired.
You're the best.
Well.
But how do I get
someone else fired?
Well, as I see it, you've got
to apply the same principles
that get you fired,
but redirected outwardly.
Hey.
She's hungry,
Jerry.
Well, there's nothing left.
There's no food.
No food?
Well, you gotta
have something.
I can't go back in there
with no food.
She expecting something, Jerry.
You don't know what she's like
when that blood sugar drops.
HILDY:
Move!
You see, she's already
in a bad mood.
She just got fired.
Why did she get fired?
Oh, because I called over
there a couple of times,
and the manager
didn't like it.
[SNAPS]
So Simon is definitely
going back now.
He's meeting me here
to return my keys.
Boy, he's a real bounder,
isn't he?
Yes, he's one of
those bounders.
Egg-white omelet, big salad.
Ah, thank you.
I Just wanted you guys to know
that Friday is my last day.
Bloomingdale's ordered
a bunch of my clips.
Thank God, I don't have
to do this anymore.
Oh.
Hey, Jerry.
Where's my suit?
I don't have it.
You want half
my omelet?
I told you she's busy.
She can't come
to the phone now.
You better tell your boyfriend
to stop calling here.
He's not my boyfriend.
It's that bald guy
with the glasses
who's always here with them.
He's trying to get me
in trouble.
Hey!
Yeah.
I got a message for you.
You tell your friend George
that the next time
I see him around here,
I'm gonna turn him into
my own personal hand puppet.
SIMON:
Well, hello.
Here you are as promised.
You see,
I'm a man of my word.
When are you leaving?
Elaine, are you trying
to get rid of me? Ha-ha-ha.
I was supposed
to leave tomorrow,
but all of a sudden I've been
set up with a job interview
that might enable me
to extend my visit indefinitely.
And it is all due
to this suit.
How do I look?
I'm a shoo-in,
aren't I?
Thanks again, hon.
Hey, Kenny.
You still wanna get
that suit back? Yeah.
There it goes.
KENNY:
Hey!
Come here, you!
SIMON:
You unhand me!
KENNY:
Take it off!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING,
METAL BANGING]
[SIGHS]
[RATTLING]
[THUDS & ROLLS]