The Christmas tree
certainly seems to inspire
a love-hate relationship.
All that time is spent
selecting it and decorating it,
and then a week after,
it's just thrown somewhere.
You see it by the side
of the road.
Looks like a mob hit.
Car slows down, the door opens,
and this tree just rolls out.
Bo-bum-poom-boom.
People snap outta
that Christmas spirit
like it was a drunken stupor.
They just wake up one morning
and go, "Oh, my God! There's
a tree inside the house.
Just throw it anywhere!"
Ready to go, Lois?
Boy, you sure like to say
my name, don't you? Yeah.
Excuse me, Lois.
Stand back, Lois.
Jimmy's in trouble, Lois.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Oh, Mr. Meyer,
this is my friend, Jerry--
Jerry Seinfeld.
Duncan Meyer.
You two
know each other?
Yeah.
We, uh, went to high school
together, didn't we, Jerry?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gee, I hope
you're not leaving now.
We still have
a lot of work left to do.
Would you be able to come
all the way downtown again
in rush hour
and pick me up?
Why, I'd have to be Superman
to do that, Lois.
ELAINE:
No.
No, no, no.
This is all wrong.
Where's the chicken cashew?
You no order
chicken cashew.
No, I-- I didn't order
any of this.
I'm not payin' for this.
Fine, Benes.
We're putting you
on our list.
What list?
The do-not-deliver list.
Merry Christmas to you!
[SCOFFS]
Well, I guess we'll just go out.
Yeah.
What are you doin'
with the Daily Worker?
Weird, Ned must have
left it here.
Your boyfriend reads
the Daily Worker?
What is he a communist?
He reads everything.
You know,
Ned's very well-read.
Maybe he's just very well...Red.
A communist?
Don't you think he probably
would have told me?
Well, does he wear bland,
drab, olive-colored clothing?
Yes.
Yes, he does dress
a little drab.
Ha-ha. He's a communist.
Ah.
Hey, look at this.
"Exciting, uninhibited woman
seeks forward-thinking comrade.
Appearance not important."
"Appearance not important"?
This is unbelievable.
Finally, this is
an ideology I can embrace.
Hey-o.
GEORGE: Hey-o.
ELAINE:
Hey.
Where's Lois?
She couldn't make it.
I can't believe
you're really going out
with a woman named Lois.
I know. Finally!
But, George,
guess who her boss is.
Duncan Meyer.
Duncan Meyer?
Who's he?
Elaine, only one other person
in the world knows
what I'm about to tell you,
and that's George.
When we were
in the ninth grade,
they had us all line up
at one end of the schoolyard
for this big race to see who was
gonna represent the school
in this track meet.
Mm-hmm.
I was the last one on the end.
George was next to me.
And Mr. Bevilaqua--
What's that?
Mr. Bevilaqua,
the gym teacher.
Oh, of course, right.
He was down
at the other end.
So he yells out,
"Ready?
"On your mark.
Get set."
And I was so keyed up,
I just took off!
By the time he said "go,"
I was 10 yards
ahead of everybody.
Nooo.
Yes.
I looked up,
I couldn't believe it.
By the time the race was over
and I had won, I was shocked.
Nobody had noticed
the head start.
Really?
Yes.
And I had won by so much,
a myth began to grow
about my speed.
Only Duncan suspected
something was amiss.
He's hated me ever since.
And now, he's back.
Well, what happened
when you raced him again?
I never did.
In four years
of high school,
I would never race
anyone again,
not even to
the end of a block
or to catch a bus.
And so the legend grew.
Everyone wanted me to race.
They begged me.
The track coach called
my parents, pleading,
telling them
that it was a sin
for me to waste
my God-given talent.
But I answered
him in the same way
I answered everyone.
I choose not to run.
So now Duncan is back?
He's back.
[BANGS BOTTLE ON TABLE]
As I knew he would be
some day.
[BANGS CUP ON TABLE]
[EXHALES]
Man, that's some tart cider.
Hi.
Sorry I missed
the Chinese food.
Oh, so am I.
[SIGHS]
How's, uh, Duncan?
He's okay.
He say anything?
About what?
Oh, nothin'
in particular.
Why did you cheat
in that race?
I did not cheat.
He said that you got
a head start.
Oh, he's just jealous
'cause he came in second.
Really?
Yeah.
So you were the fastest kid
in school?
Faster than
a speeding bullet, Lois.
ELAINE:
So how was work?
Another day?
Another...dollar?
I guess.
Yeah, well,
nothin' wrong with that.
Gotta make those big bucks.
Money, money, money,
money, money, money.
[GIGGLES]
Are you a communist?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Yes, as a matter
of fact, I am.
[GASPS]
Ohhh! Whoa!
A commie.
Wow. Gee, man.
It must be a bummer
for you guys, what,
with the fall of the Soviet
empire and everything.
Well, yeah. Well,
we still got China, Cuba.
Yeah, but...
[SCOFFS]
...come on.
I know,
it's not the same.
Well, you had a good run.
I mean, what was it?
Seventy-five,
80 years wreaking havoc,
making everybody nervous?
Yeah, we had a good run.
Well, so enjoy yourself.
[LAUGHS]
GEORGE:
So you lied to her?
I couldn't tell her
the truth.
I don't know what's gonna
happen between us.
What if we have
a bad breakup?
She'll go straight
to Duncan,
and I want him
to go to his grave
never being certain
that I got that head start.
Well...
I'm dating a communist.
Wow.
A communist.
That's somethin'.
Yeah, that's
pretty cool, isn't it?
Hey, did I tell ya?
I called one of those girls
from the personal ads
in the Daily Worker?
Oh.
The Daily Worker has personals?
Yeah. And they say that
appearance is not important.
Yours or hers?
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Merry Christmas,
everyone!
Merry Christmas!
Wow, look at you.
So you got the job!
Yeah, you're lookin'
at the new Santa
at Coleman's Department Store.
Oh! Congratulations!
GEORGE: Way to go, there!
Yeah, yeah.
Isn't it great?
Hey, Mickey!
[LAUGHING] Look at Mickey.
How are ya?
Yeah.
Get your beard on.
We're late.
Ooh. Tshhh!
On, Prancer!
On, Dasher!
On, Donna!
It's not Donna.
It's Donner.
It's Donna.
Yeah, right.
On, Prancer.
On, Dancer.
On, Ethel.
On, Harriet.
[PHONE RINGS, DOOR CLOSES]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Lois.
He wants to get together?
What for?
Uh, I don't know about that.
I'll have to think about it.
I'll let you know.
Okay. Bye.
What's up?
Duncan wants to get together
with me and her for lunch
tomorrow.
He's gonna try to get me
to admit I got a head start.
I don't think
she believes me.
And he wants to meet you?
I'll tell you what?
I'll show up.
He doesn't know we're friends.
I'll pretend I haven't seen you
since high school.
I'll back up the story.
That's not bad.
Not bad?
It's gorgeous.
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Well, come on,
little princess,
tell Santa what you want.
Don't be shy.
She doesn't
speak English. Oh.
Santa speaks the language
of all children.
Uh, norche-worche-dorche-doo?
Okamaka-miki-mooki?
Abratcha-datcha-natcha-dooti?
Hey, Mickey,
when do we get a break?
My lap is killin' me.
There is no break.
This is like a sweat shop.
[WHISPERING]
Kramer.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Aah!
ADA:
There's a Natalie on line 2.
Natalie?
From the Daily Worker?
Thank you.
Hello.
Yes, Natalie.
Uh, well, yes,
this is a business office,
but, uh, I'm not
a businessman per se.
I'm-- I'm here working
for the people.
Yes, I'm, uh--
I'm causing dissent,
stirring the pot,
getting people to question
the whole rotten system.
Elaine.
Arlene.
Hi.
Hello.
Doin' a little Christmas
shopping?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah?
Oh! This is Ned.
He's a communist.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Big communist.
Big, big communist.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, it's awfully nice
to see you.
Yeah, we'll see you later.
Okey-dokey.
Nice to meet you.
Bye-bye.
Hey, listen,
as long as we're here,
what do you say we do
a little shirt shopping?
Out of the question.
Oh.
Kramer!
Oh, hi, Elaine.
ELAINE: Hi.
Hi, Mickey.
How are ya?
This is--
This is Ned.
Oh, hey.
How are you doin' there, buddy?
Hey, you guys
stay here, okay?
I'll be right back.
Right back.
Eight hours of jingle-belling
and ho-ho-hoing.
Boy, I am hoed out.
Anyone who works here
is a sap.
Hey, watch it, pal!
Whoa, whoa, easy.
Come on, come on.
Huh!
What's the matter
with you?
You know the Santa's
at Bloomfields
are makin' double
what you are?
Double?
[SCOFFS]
I bet the glue
from that beard itches.
Oh, you've got that straight.
So when you get a rash
all over your face in January,
you think Coleman's will be
there with a medical plan?
Look, you take that commie crap
out to the street.
Kramer, I've got
some literature in my car
that will change
your whole way of thinking.
Talk to me, baby.
Don't listen to him, Kramer.
You got a good job here!
DUNCAN:
There's just no way
you could have beaten me
by that much.
I'd already beaten you
in junior high school
three times.
I didn't hit puberty
till the ninth grade.
That's what gave me my speed.
Besides, if I got
a head start,
why didn't Mr. Bevilaqua
stop the race?
That's what I've always
wondered about.
Well, uh--
Oh, my God!
No! Oh, my God!
Jerry!
I'm sorry, uh...
George!
George Costanza!
Oh, George Costanza.
Kennedy High.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
This is unbelievable.
Hi, George.
Wh--? Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me.
It starts with a...
Duncan!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh, wow. This is something.
I haven't seen you guys in what?
Twenty years?
Yeah. This is Lois.
Hi, there.
Hello.
[CHUCKLES]
So, what have you been doin'
with yourself?
Well, uh--
I'm a comedian.
Uh-huh.
Well, I, uh--
I really wouldn't know
about that.
I don't watch much TV.
I like to read.
Ah.
You do a lot of that "Did you
ever notice" kinda stuff?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, it strikes me
a lot of guys
are doin' that kind of humor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you really went
bald there, didn't you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You used to really
have a thick...
full head of hair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Poof.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well, I guess
I started losin' it
when I was about 28,
right around the time
I made my first million.
Oh.
Yeah.
You know, it's true
what they say.
The first million
[KNOCKING ON WOOD]
is the hardest one.
Yeah, yeah.
What do you do?
I'm an architect.
Have you designed
any buildings in New York?
Have you seen the new addition
to the Guggenheim?
You did that?
Yep, yep.
Y'know, it didn't take
very long either.
Well, you've really built
yourself up into something.
Well, well, I, uh--
I had a dream, Jerry.
Yeah.
You know,
one can't help but wonder
what brings you
into a crummy little
coffee shop like this.
Well, I like to stay in touch
with the people.
Ah-ha. You know, you got
a hole in your sneaker there.
What is that? Canvas?
Yeah, you know, my driver
is waiting outside.
I really...should get running.
Good to see you guys again.
Good to see you.
George, George, George,
hang on a second.
I haven't seen you
in so long.
Uh-huh.
I thought we might
reminisce a little more.
Duncan and I were just talking
about the day of the big race.
Oh, the big race!
Yes, yes.
You were there?
Oh, sure, sure.
I certainly was.
Yeah, I remember that day.
Well, I'll never forget it
because that--
That was the day
that I lost my virginity
to Miss Stafford,
the voluptuous homeroom teacher.
Miss Stafford?
Yes, yes.
You know, I was in detention,
and she came up behind me
while I was erasing
the blackboard.
George.
But I digress. Heh.
Let me see now.
As I remember,
you were standing
at one end of the line,
I was right next to you,
and, uh, I remember that
we were even for, like,
the first five yards,
and then baboom!
You were gone.
Did I get a head start?
Head sta--
Oh, no.
Absolutely not. No.
You satisfied?
So you see?
No. I'm still not
convinced,
and I never will be.
Why don't the two of you
just race again?
That's a good idea.
No, no, no, no.
Another race,
out of the question.
I know. You've been
saying that for 20 years
because you know
you can't beat me.
You couldn't beat me then,
and you can't beat me now.
Race him, Jerry.
Race him!
All right.
I'll do it!
The race is on.
You're gonna race him?
Yeah, and he's calling
all these people
from high school
to come and watch.
I knew this day would come.
I can't do it.
I can't go through with it.
I'm calling it off.
I can't let the legend die.
It's like a kid finding out
there's no Santa Clause.
"Each according to his ability
to each according to his means."
What does that mean?
Well, if you got means
and ability,
that's a pretty good
combination.
So what if I wanna
open up a delicatessen?
There are no delicatessens
under communism.
Whoa. Why not?
Well, because the meats are
divided into a class system.
You got pastrami
and corned beef in one class,
and salami and bologna
in another.
That's not right.
So you can't get
corned beef?
Well, you know,
if you're in
the politburo, maybe.
Yeah, this is George Costanza.
Any messages for me?
Why does Mr. Steinbrenner
wanna see me in his office?
Communist?
I'm not a communist.
All right.
All right, all right!
I'll be there.
My secretary, Ada,
told Mr. Steinbrenner
that I'm a communist!
Now, he wants to see me.
So? You'll just explain to him
that you're not a communist.
You just called the woman
for a date.
[RINGS]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Duncan.
No, 4:00 tomorrow--
That is not going to work.
Why? I'll tell you why.
Because I choose not
to run!
NED:
I'm sorry, Elaine.
This shirt's too fancy.
Just because
you're a communist,
does that mean you can't
wear anything nice?
You look like Trotsky.
Good.
Fine. You wanna be
a communist?
Be a communist.
Can't you at least look like
a successful communist?
All right.
I'll try it on.
All right, I'm gonna
order Chinese food.
You're ordering
from Hop Sing's, right?
[GROANS]
Does it have to be Hop Sing's?
I kinda had a fight with him.
Elaine, when my father
was blacklisted,
he couldn't work for years.
He and his friends used to sit
in Hop Sing's every day,
figuring out how to survive.
Your father was blacklisted?
Yes, he was.
And you know why?
Because he was betrayed
by people he trusted.
They named names.
Okay. Okay.
Um, yeah, hi.
I'd like a delivery please
to 16 West 75th Street,
apartment 2G.
I know that address!
You're Benes, right?!
You're on our list.
No more deliveries!
Uh-- No, no.
D-- Uh--
She doesn't
live here anymore.
This is someone else.
Oh, yeah?
What's the name?
Why do you need a name?
You already have the address.
We need a name.
Give us a name!
Okay. Okay.
Ned Isaacoff.
I want a racing car, Santa.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
A racing-car set!
[QUIETLY]
Listen, you don't want that.
Those are assembled in Taiwan
by kids like you.
And these Coleman pigs,
they sell it
for triple the cost.
But I want
a racing-car set.
No, don't you see, kid?
You're being bamboozled.
These capitalist fat cats
are inflating the profit margin
and reducing
your total number of toys.
Hey, this guy's a commie!
Hey, kid, quiet!
Heh. Where did a nice
little boy like you
learn such a bad word
like that, huh?
Commie! Commie!
Traitor to our country!
Santa is not
a commie.
He just forgot
how his good friend
stuck his neck out
for him
to get him a good job
like this,
didn't he, Santa?
Is there a problem here?
Whoa! Ho-ho-ho-ho!
This guy's a commie,
and he's spreading propaganda!
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's enough, pinko.
You're through!
The both of you!
I got two kids
in college!
Oh, you can't fire me.
I'm Santa!
Not anymore.
Get your skinny ass
outta here!
Hi, how are ya?
Fine.
What's the matter?
I just spoke to Duncan.
He said, if you don't race,
he's going to fire me.
What?
He can't do that.
Yes, he can.
He controls the means
of production.
What are you gonna do, Jerry?
Don't worry, Lois.
I'll think of something.
Ah-ha! I knew it was you.
You tried to trick Hop Sing!
You're on our list,
Elaine Benes!
And now...
you're on our list,
Ned Isaacoff.
You got me blacklisted
at Hop Sing's?
She named name.
You, uh, wanted to see,
Mr. Steinbrenner?
Yes, George, I did.
Come in. Come in.
George, the word
around the office
is that you're a communist.
What? A communist?
I am a Yankee, sir,
first and foremost.
You know, it struck me today
that a communist pipeline
into the best reservoir
of Cuban baseball talent
could be the greatest thing
ever to happen
to this organization.
Sir?
You could be invaluable
to this franchise.
There's a southpaw down there
nobody's been able
to get a look at.
Something Rodriguez.
I don't really know his name.
You get yourself down
to Havana right away.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
Do my best.
Good.
Merry Christmas, George.
And bring me back some of
those cigars in the cedar boxes.
The ones with the fancy rings.
I love fancy rings.
They kinda distract you,
while you're smoking.
The red and yellow are nice.
Looks good against
the brown with a cigar.
The maduro,
I like the maduro wrapper.
The darker, the better.
That's what I say.
The claro's good too.
That's more of a pale brown.
A milky coffee.
I find the ring size confusing.
They have it in centimeters,
which I don't understand.
Whoa, that was great!
Nice job, Santa!
Yeah!
I knew that commie stuff
was gonna get us in trouble.
Yeah, well, I didn't realize
it was such a sensitive issue.
Communism? You didn't realize
communism was a sensitive issue?
What do you think's been
goin' on in the world
for the past 50 years?
Wake up and smell the coffee!
I guess I screwed up!
Oh, you sure did!
Bigtime!
[CHEERING, CLAPPING]
How do you feel?
I need a miracle.
Now, you're gonna see
what kind of a liar
you're mixed up with.
Well, if he beats you,
I want a big raise.
If he beats me,
I'll not only
give you a raise,
I'll send you to Hawaii
for two weeks.
George, listen, I parked
in front of that restaurant.
As soon as this race is over,
we gotta go to the airport.
Okay, I'll be there.
All right.
You ready, boys?
Yeah, Mr. Bevilaqua.
All right. This is the way
it's gonna work.
You take your marks.
I say, "Ready.
On your mark. Get set."
And then fire. You got it?
BOTH:
Yes, Mr. Bevilaqua.
Come on, Jerry.
Ready?
On your mark!
[BOOM]
[THEME FROM SUPERMAN PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE & CHEERING FADE IN]
So will you come
to Hawaii with me, Jerry?
Maybe I will, Lois.
Maybe I will.
[♪]
You wanted to see me,
el presidente?
Sí, sí. Muévete. Come here.
I understand you're
very interested
in one of our players, huh?
Oh-- Sí, sí.
Ordinarily, I would not
grant such a request,
but I have heard you are, uh--
How you say?
--communista simpatico, huh?
Muy simpatico. Muy, muy, muy.
Well, good!
Then you can have your pick.
Oh, oh!
They will play for your Yankee!
Oh, well.
[LAUGHS]
Gracias, el comandante,
gracias.
Muy, muy. Heh, heh.
And I would be honored
if you would be my guest
for dinner tonight
at the presidential palace.
There will be girls there.
Ohhh.
And I hear some pretty
good food.
Of course, the problem
with parties is,
you invariably have to eat
standing up,
which I don't care for.
But on the other hand,
I don't like to balance
a plate on my lap either.
Once, when I was at a party,
I put my plate
on someone's piano.
I assure you,
if I had not been a dictator,
I would not have been able
to get away with that one!