The whole concept of
the wanted poster has gotta be
the most wildly optimistic
crime-fighting idea.
I mean, so, how does it work?
Okay. I'm on the line
at the post office.
I see the guy.
I see the list of offenses.
I check the guy
standing in line behind me.
If it's not him...
that's pretty much all I can do.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Okay.
It's not that I don't
wanna help.
You know, the annoying thing is,
you think,
why didn't they
hold onto this guy
when they're taking his picture?
No, we don't do it that way.
We take their picture,
and we let 'em go.
So we get the front
and side shot.
The front is his face.
The side is him leaving.
Look at you.
Why don't you use a fork?
You're no good
with the sticks.
I know. I need a lesson.
You stink.
You know you stink.
What is this?
Ooh! My ballet tickets.
Oh, your ballet tickets.
Hey, have you ever been
to the ballet?
No, but I've seen
people on tiptoes.
You know, I'm going as a beard.
A beard?
Yeah.
This friend of a friend
knows this banker guy.
He's, I don't know, 30-ish,
unbelievably gorgeous.
Of course, he's gay.
Yeah.
So,
anyway, his boss has
this box at the Met.
And he invited him
to go see Swan Lake
with him and his wife,
but he's afraid that his boss
can't handle his orientation,
so I'm going along as his date.
Why are you doing this?
Swan Lake, at the Met.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
GEORGE:
Get it on with your bad self.
[SNIFFS]
Ooh.
Chinese food.
I knew I smelled somethin'.
Hey!
Is George still wearing
that toupee? Yeah.
Doesn't he know how ridiculous
he looks in that thing?
I think he looks fantastic.
[LAUGHING]
Oh, come on.
No. I never realized
what an attractive man he is.
Oh, he's a real looker,
that one.
Hey!
People. People, people,
people, people.
Not bad, huh?
[LAUGHS]
Yeah.
[GASPS]
All right.
Excuse me.
You look ridiculous
in that thing.
Is that so?
Or could it be that you're
just a little bit worried
that you may have
missed the boat.
[LAUGHS]
Well, I think
they might have sutured...
that thing...
to your brain.
[BOTH LAUGH]
All right.
Go ahead. Deride.
Deride if you must.
But let me tell you something.
With my personality
and this head of hair,
you know what I am now?
I am in the game.
I no longer defer
to the coiffed. I'm a player.
KRAMER:
You know, I just thought of something.
I know this gorgeous woman.
She called me up this morning.
She's moving into the city,
and she asked me if I know
of anyone she could meet.
Now, you can go out with her.
Well, what about me?
No, I think
he's got you beat, buddy.
So, she's gorgeous, huh?
Yeah, well,
last time I saw her she was,
five years ago.
Well, you got a picture?
No. No.
Well, I have to see her.
Hey, I know what we can do.
I got a friend.
He works
over at the police station.
He's a composite artist.
Really?
Maybe I can get him to draw
a picture of her for you.
I would love that.
You think he'd do it?
Yeah, yeah.
I think he will.
It sounds like
an excellent idea.
Hey, Jerry.
You done with all this?
'Cause I'm gonna give it
to a homeless person.
You know, I'm very excited
about this.
I always wanted to see how
these sketch artists do it.
Here you go, brother.
Some food for you.
Thank you.
You're a good man.
Bless you.
You gonna be here
in an hour?
Where am I going?
All right.
Enjoy.
Wait up!
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
And make the eyes, um--
What's that nut?
Almonds?
Almonds.
Yeah, That's it.
Can I see?
No, no. Not yet.
And make the lips fuller.
Poutier.
Poutier?
I like that.
Can't go wrong
with pouty.
I'm excited
about the pouty.
All right. I think
that about does it.
All right, George.
Come on. Take a look.
Oh, my God,
you were right.
She is gorgeous!
Hey, Lou, who's that
woman over there?
Huh?
LOU:
Oh, that's Sergeant Tierny.
Nice officer.
You wanna meet her?
Well, this worked out okay.
Hey, you gonna see
that police woman?
Yeah, I think I will.
I like the idea of
having the law on my side.
Hey, man.
Did you enjoy the food?
Oh, yes, I did.
Where did the Chinese learn
to cook like that?
Listen.
I'll take
that Tupperware now.
I don't think so.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's mine.
You gave it to me.
No, no, look.
I didn't say
you could keep it.
See, I don't give
away Tupperware.
You shoulda said something.
Well, I didn't think I had to.
Look, with a piece
of Tupperware, you just assume.
Yeah!
I really gotta
thank you for this.
The bank I work for
is so conservative.
Oh, well, by now,
you'd think
people would be
a little more open-minded.
Oi.
Would you excuse me?
I have to run to the bathroom.
Okay.
Great.
Sssso...
you and Robert, hmm?
Yup. Mm-hmm.
Really?
Yes, indeedy.
I'm surprised.
Really?
Why?
No reason.
Well, believe me.
This didn't happen overnight.
Robert is not exactly
a one-woman man,
if you know what I mean.
No, siree, Bob.
Sure, I mean, in a lot of ways,
he's a typical guy.
He likes his sports.
But he counters that side
with the side you see
here tonight
at the ballet
or the pleasure he gets
watching Miss Liza Minnelli
belt out a few choice numbers.
It's those two halves
of his personality
that just come together
to make him the very special guy
that he is.
Excuse me.
Oh. Hi, honey.
ELAINE:
It was just such a great night.
Oh!
And did they suspect anything?
Mmm.
No, I was a fantastic beard.
I held hands,
I called him "honey."
And we discover
yet another talent:
posing as a girlfriend
for homosexuals.
Oh, it was just
such a great night.
You said that already.
Oh, I did?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Don't tell me.
You like him?
He's incredible!
Yeah, but--
Yeah. I-- I know.
So?
What?
Not conversion?
You're thinking conversion?
Well, it did occur to me.
You think you can get him
to just change teams?
He's not gonna suddenly
switch sides.
Forget about it.
Why? Is it irrevocable?
Because when you join that team,
it's not a whim.
He likes his team.
He's set with that team.
But we've got a good team.
Yeah, we do.
We do have a good team.
Well, why can't he play for us?
They're only comfortable
with their equipment.
But we just got along so great.
Of course, you did.
Everyone gets along great
when there's
no possibility of sex.
No, no, no.
I sensed something.
I did sense something.
I perceived
a possibility, Jerry.
You realize your venturing
into uncharted waters.
I realize that.
Are you that desperate?
Yes, I am.
JERRY:
Are you gonna bring your gun?
Yeah, I think
you should leave it at home.
Well, I don't really
know you that well.
What if we get into a fight
or something?
You know, you lose your temper.
Who knows
what you're capable of.
All right,
then it's settled.
First date, no weapons.
All right.
I'll see you then.
Okay, bye.
Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
What are you lookin' for?
Tupperware.
Sorry, I don't have
any Tupperware.
See, I knew
this was gonna happen.
I just made
a delicious casserole,
but now it won't keep
'cause I have no Tupperware!
What about a plastic bag?
You must be kidding.
What is the difference?
The patented burp, Jerry.
It locks in freshness.
Hey-oh.
Hey. Hey.
So, I, uh...
I spoke to your little
friend Denise last night.
Oh, yeah.
You talked, huh?
Yeah. For two hours.
She's nuts about you.
Yeah, well, we go
way back, you know.
Why didn't anything ever happen
between you two?
Who's to say it didn't?
Chk!
So did you describe yourself
to her over the phone?
Yes, I did.
What did you say?
What do you think I said?
I don't know.
I told her the truth.
As you see it.
Yes, as I see it.
Did you tell her about
your little hat there?
What hat?
You know, your little
hair hat there.
No.
Don't you think she could tell?
No, no, no.
She can't tell.
It's a perfect match.
Beautiful job.
Are you kiddin'?
I could spot that bird's nest
two blocks away.
You only think that
because you know me.
Have you noticed
people staring at your head?
I notice people
staring at my head
because they like what they see.
I think you should
either take it off
or tell her about it.
He's not gonna
take it off.
If he was gonna
go over bald,
I wouldn't have
introduced them.
All right, look.
I guarantee she won't know.
Yeah. That's it.
I'm gonna go down
to the precinct.
I'm gonna have lunch
with Lou.
Oh, I'll split
a cab with you.
Hey, I'm really sorry
about the other day, man.
Really sorry.
Hey! That's my coffee.
JERRY:
Hi, sarge.
Hi. I'm sorry
I'm late.
Some of our lineup decoys
didn't show, so...
Hey, any of you guys
want to be in the lineup?
Make a quick 50 bucks?
Sure. I will.
Perfect. Okay.
Just go right over there
with Officer Lampart.
Oh, all right.
MAN:
All of you, turn to the left.
The left.
Now, turn to the right.
[HUMMING]
GEORGE:
Oh, my God. There she is.
That's the face.
Just like the picture.
George?
Yeah.
Hi.
It's great to meet you.
Likewise.
Have you been waiting long?
No, no, no. I just got
here two minutes ago.
Good, good.
Well, why don't you take off
your hat, stay awhile?
[CHUCKLES]
What's that?
Polygraph.
What you civilians call
a lie detector test.
Oh, all right.
Let me ask you.
Now, when someone is lying,
is it true that their pants
are actually on fire?
If I could tell you the famous
faces that have been up here.
Get out.
A certain cast member
of Melrose Place.
Really?
Have you ever seen the show?
No.
You can admit it, Jerry.
It's okay.
I'd admit it.
I don't watch it.
Hey, Lou.
Maybe we should put him
on the poly.
The poly?
Yeah.
I think you've seen it.
ELAINE [LAUGHING]:
Melrose Place?
Yes. Melrose Place.
[LAUGHS]
I just didn't know
you watch that.
Well...I do.
I mean, every time
I've mentioned it,
you never say anything
or join in the conversation.
Well, maybe I was
a little embarrassed.
You mean this whole time, Jerry,
we could have been discussing
Sydney and Michael and Jane?
And Billy and Jake and Allison.
Yes, we could have
discussed it.
Why? Why were you
so embarrassed?
The point is, I'm gonna be
taking this lie detector test.
And that needle's gonna be
goin' wild.
[LAUGHS]
This is so stupid.
Why didn't you just confess?
It's too stupid to confess.
Look what I'm confessing to.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Maybe I could beat the machine.
Ohhh...
Who do you think you are?
Costanza?
Hey, you know what?
I have access to one of
the most deceitful, duplicitous,
deceptive minds of our time.
Who better to advise me?
Oh, God, this is terrible.
Did you shake it up?
No.
You gotta shake it up.
No. I'm sick of shaking.
You gotta shake everything.
Yeah, that's a real nuisance.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Oh, this is killin' me.
Yeah.
GEORGE:
So, I'm going out tonight
with Robert
and the boss and his wife.
So, tonight
you gonna make the move?
Yeah, I think I might.
Hey, there he is.
So, what happened?
Could she detect it?
It's an interesting question.
How so?
I'll tell you how so.
She's bald!
What do you mean, bald?
What do you think I mean, bald?
Bald!
"Bald" bald.
She's bald?
She's bald, Jerry.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, come on.
"Oh, come on"?
No, come on.
She took off her hat,
and there she was.
Hello!
It was like I was looking
at myself in the mirror.
Well, maybe she got
a haircut or something.
You know, let me tell
you something.
No one walks into
a beauty parlor and says,
"Give me the Larry Fine."
Women go bald?
Yeah, I've heard of that.
I mean, they usually wear a wig.
Hey, buddy.
JERRY: Hey.
Ha-ho...
You fixed me up
with a bald woman!
[SPUTTERS]
Bald?
Yeah, that's right.
Do you see the irony here?
You're rejecting somebody
because they're bald.
So?
You're bald!
No, I'm not.
I...
was bald.
Elaine.
KRAMER:
Hey, hey, hey, come on.
Ah! Ah! Aah!
Give it--
Don't--
No, no, no!
No, Elaine!
I don't like this thing!
And here's what
I'm doing with it!
No!
What about when you started
that fight with me.
Well, I figured
that's what couples do.
You almost convinced me
we were a couple.
Oh, well, it was easy.
Really.
Well, good night.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Oh, wait a second.
Um...
Would you like
to come...
upstairs?
Upstairs?
Yeah.
Elaine...
Well, I was-- I was
hoping, you know, you...
You might be
interested in...
changing teams.
"Changing teams"?
Have you ever
thought about it?
But I'm a starting shortstop.
Robert...
we need a shortstop.
Real bad.
I tell you, when she threw
that toupee out the window,
it was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Good.
I feel like
my old self again.
Totally inadequate,
completely insecure,
paranoid, neurotic.
It's a pleasure.
It's good to have you back.
And you know what else
I've decided to do?
I'm gonna keep seeing
the bald woman.
She's as good as anybody else.
Scalp was clean.
She had a nice skull.
Just wasn't a lot of hair on it.
You know, you've had, like,
a religious awakening.
You're like a bald-again.
[LAUGHS]
I need
a little more coffee.
So, George, how do I beat
this lie detector?
I'm sorry, Jerry.
I can't help you.
Come on. You got the gift.
You're the only one
that could help me.
Jerry, I can't.
It's like saying to Pavarotti,
"Teach me to sing like you."
All right. Well,
I gotta go take this test.
I can't believe
I'm doin' this.
Jerry...
just remember:
It's not a lie...
if you believe it.
Hey!
Hey.
I did it!
What?
I turned him. He defected.
Get out.
How?
How did you do that?
'Cause I'm a woman.
♪ Ba-ba-ba-boom, chicky
Boom, chicky ♪
♪ Boom-boom-boom ♪
Elaine, do you know
what you've done?
You've given hope to every woman
who's ever said
"too bad he's gay."
Well, it's a lesson
for the kids out there.
Anything is possible.
Indeed.
Jeromy, I have hit the jackpot.
The perfect man.
Nothing but sex and shopping.
What's your name?
Jerry Seinfeld.
What is your address?
129 West 81st street.
Did Kimberly steal Jo's baby?
I don't know.
Did Billy sleep with
Allison's best friend?
I don't know.
Did Jane's fiancé kidnap Sydney
and take her to Las Vegas?
And if so, did she enjoy it?
I don't know.
Did Jane sleep
with Michael again?
Yes!
Yes, that stupid idiot!
He left her for Kimberly!
He slept with her sister!
He tricked her into givin'
him half her business!
And then she goes ahead
and sleeps with him again!
I mean, she's crazy! How could
she do something like that?!
I mean, that Jane!
Oh, she just makes me so mad!
He went back?
What do you mean,
he went back?
He went back.
I don't understand, you were
having a great time.
The sex, the shopping.
Well, here's the thing:
Being a woman...
I only really have
access to the...
equipment...
What, 30, 45 minutes a week?
And that's on a good week.
How can I be expected
to have the same expertise
as people who own
this equipment...
and have access to it
24 hours a day...
their entire lives?
You can't.
That's why they lose
very few players.
Yeah, I guess I never
really stood a chance.
Well, there's always
a place for you...
on our team.
Yeah. Thanks.
Is Melrose Place on?
Yeah, comin' on
in a few minutes.
Okay.
Hey. Don't worry
it hasn't started.
Hey, you know, George,
I am really proud of you.
I really do admire
what you've done.
Do you?
That makes me so happy.
Elaine's proud of me, Jerry.
What is the matter?
I got rejected by a bald woman.
What?
A bald woman rejected me.
Huh?
You like that one?
A woman with no prospects
and no hair
told me that I wasn't her type.
Apparently,
baldy likes a slimmer guy!
Well, I'll tell you
what I think.
I think she saw you with that
piece off and was devastated.
You blew it, boy!
You really blew it!
And you had to ruin it for him,
didn't you?
I didn't ruin anything.
He looked like an idiot.
No.
He did. And it made him
act like a jerk.
All right. Shut up,
shut up.
Melrose Place is coming on.
[THEME FROM MELROSE PLACE
PLAYING]
Oh, that Michael.
I hate him.
He's just so smug.
How you doin', Stu?
Eddie, my man.
You again?
Boy, you're a slippery one.
You better straighten up
and fly right, buddy boy.
What do you got?
I got an eye witness to
that jewelry store break-in.
Come here.
Do you recognize anybody
in this line-up?
That's the guy, officer!
The guy there in the middle,
the tall guy with the high hair.
I'd recognize him anywhere.
Hey, you.
You with the high hair.
Step forward.
Me?