[PLAYING COOL, CHEERFUL JAZZ]
ELAINE:
I can't believe I'm going out with this guy.
Wow, he's so cool.
Maybe he'll write
a song about me.
That would be amazing.
"Oh, Elaine,
you are so beautiful.
"So, so beautiful.
"Not to mention
your personality,
"which is so, so interesting.
"If you want,
you can quit your job
and never work again."
[APPLAUSE]
[♪]
ELAINE:
Jerry, you have got to come see him.
He is so terrific.
Maybe he'll write
a song about you.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, right.
Like that really matters.
So I take it he's sponge-worthy.
Oh, yeah.
Well, he's a musician.
I guess they're supposed
to be very, you know,
uninhibited and free.
Well, actually, he's--
He's not that way at all.
Oh, no?
Yeah, in fact, he--
[GROANS]
Oh-ho...
Come on.
I don't wanna!
Elaine,
you're among friends.
Well, actually, he, um...
doesn't really like to do...
[INHALES]
...everything.
Yeah.
It's surprising.
Yes, it is.
It is surprising.
Does that bother you?
No. No,
it doesn't bother me.
I mean,
it would be nice.
I'm not gonna lie to you
and say...
[LAUGHS]
it wouldn't be nice.
Sure.
Why not? You're there.
Exactly.
But you said he was just
coming out of a very serious
relationship.
Maybe he's, you know,
still kind of--
He's...
It's not gonna happen.
Hey, Jerry. Listen.
I need you to come downstairs.
Help me get my stuff
out of the car.
What stuff?
I just came from the Price Club.
I'm loaded up, baby.
All right, fine.
[♪]
What, are you outta your mind?
Look at this.
What did you buy here?
You will never be able
to finish all this stuff.
Of course, I will.
These are all staples.
A 4-pound can
of black olives.
That's a staple?
Lindsay Olives, Jerry.
A 48-pack of Eggo waffles.
A gallon of barbecue sauce.
Ten pounds
of cocktail meatballs.
Yeah, 17.50.
You can't beat that.
Look at this can of tuna.
Yeah, StarKist, Jerry.
Most tuna don't make their cut.
This isn't for a person.
This is for Biosphere 3.
Hey, Clyde.
Hey, Kramer.
What's happening, dude?
Hey, this is Jerry.
How you doing?
Hi.
Clyde plays backup
with John Germaine.
John Germaine?
That is amazing. I was just
talking about him
upstairs with Elaine.
CLYDE:
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. My friend Elaine
and him are going out.
They're pretty hot and heavy.
Is that right?
Hey, listen, how about
giving me a hand,
bring some of this stuff
upstairs?
Sorry, Kramer.
I got to watch the hands.
My hands are my life.
[♪]
ESTELLE:
Georgie,
can you zip me up?
Yeah.
Yeah, one second.
Well, come on.
All right. All right.
Let's not get into panic mode!
Let's not make a big deal
outta this thing,
or we're never gonna
get through this night.
Well, I'm meeting your in-laws.
I think I should look nice.
My in-laws. Oh, my God.
So, what do you think?
Your old man can look pretty
good when he wants to, huh?
I don't like that tie.
What's the matter
with this tie?
I've hardly worn it.
It's too thin.
They're wearing wide now.
How do you know
what kind of ties they wear?
Go to any office building
on 7th Avenue
and tell me
if there's anyone there
wearing a thin tie like that.
Go ahead.
Oh, get the hell outta here.
7th Avenue?
George, do you think
he should wear a tie like that?
I think he should wear
whatever tie he wants.
We gotta stop off and pick up
a marble rye from Schnitzer's.
It's out of our way.
Why can't we pick up
something at Lords?
It's right over here.
No, we have got to go
to Schnitzer's.
I'll show these people
something about taste.
Ooh.
This is gonna be fun.
[♪]
You'll never guess
who I bumped into.
This guy Clyde.
He's in your friend
John Germaine's band there.
So, what did he have to say?
Nothing. I told him you two
were pretty hot and heavy.
Hot and heavy?
You said, "hot and heavy"?
Yeah.
What did you do that for?
What?
What if he tells John?
Then John's gonna think
that I think
that we're hot and heavy.
I don't want him thinking
that I'm hot and heavy
if he's not hot and heavy.
Oh.
I'm trying to get
a little squirrel
to come over to me here.
I don't wanna make
any big, sudden movements.
I'll frighten him away.
Well, Clyde might not tell him.
How do you know that?
I should have helped Kramer
with those packages.
Let me give you a hand.
Hey, Kramer, how are you?
Could you do me a favor?
I'm taking the family
to Disney World next week.
I wonder,
can you pick up my mail?
Yeah, sure, sure.
In fact, you know what?
How'd you like to take
my hansom-cab for the week?
Drive the horse?
It'll just be sitting there.
You can really clean up.
500 bucks a day.
I'll split it with you.
Oh. Giddyup.
[♪]
This is delicious, Mrs. Ross.
MR. ROSS:
Why are you complimenting her for it?
She didn't make it. Rowena did.
What is this thing anyway?
It's Cornish game hen.
What is that,
like a little chicken?
No, it's, uh--
It's not a little chicken.
[CHUCKLES]
Little chicken. No, it's a--
It's a game bird.
Game bird?
What do you mean,
like, you-- You hunt it?
Yes.
How hard can it be
to kill this thing?
I couldn't help but notice
but you have
quite a library in there.
If I had a dime...
for every book
he's actually read...
[LAUGHS]
I'd be broke.
More wine, anyone?
Yeah, I'll take more.
Thank you.
How do you like
the merlot?
Merlot?
I never heard of it.
Did they just invent it?
Oh, brother.
She's, uh--
She's heard of merlot.
Let me understand.
You got the hen,
the chicken and the rooster.
The rooster
goes with the chicken.
So who's having sex
with the hen?
We can--- We can
talk about it another time.
But you see my point here?
You only hear of a hen,
a rooster and a chicken.
Somethin's missing!
Something's missing, all right.
They're all chickens.
The rooster has sex
with all of them.
That's perverse.
So has anybody seen Firestorm?
Firestorm, that's a hell
of a picture.
Remember when they had
the helicopter land
on top of that car?
Hey, come on!
I haven't seen it yet.
It doesn't have anything
to do with plot!
Still, still!
I like to go in fresh!
Oh, Mother of God.
[♪]
Ho. And of course, uh,
this is Central Park.
Uh, this was designed in, uh,
1850 by Joe Pepitone.
Built, uh, during the Civil War
so the Northern armies could
practice fighting on-- On grass.
Oh, yeah.
On, Rusty!
[♪]
Now, I-I'd like to play
something that--
Well, actually,
it's my latest.
So it's nice and fresh.
It's called "Hot and Heavy."
[PLAYING SULTRY JAZZ]
[♪]
GEORGE:
Thank God that's over.
The mother seems to hit
the sauce pretty hard.
I didn't like that.
And who doesn't serve cake
after a meal?
What kind of people
are they?
Would it kill them to put out
a pound cake? Something!
So they didn't give you
a piece of cake. Big deal.
It is a big deal.
You're supposed to serve cake
after a meal.
I'm sorry, it's impolite.
It's not impolite.
It's stupid, that's what it is.
You gotta be stupid
to do something like that.
Your father is absolutely right.
We're sitting there like idiots,
drinking coffee
without a piece of cake.
What is this?
The marble rye?
Oh, dear, I forgot to put out
that-- That bread they brought.
We forgot to bring it in.
No, I bought it in.
They never put it out.
Where is it?
I dunno.
Where'd you put it?
Right over there.
Well, it's gone.
You stole the bread?
What do you mean stole?
It's my bread.
They didn't eat it.
Why should I leave it there?
Because we brought it for them.
Apparently, it wasn't good
enough for them to serve.
Is it possible
they took it back?
Who would bring a bread
and take it back?
Those people, that's who.
I think they're sick.
People take buses
to get that rye.
Maybe they forgot
to put it out!
No, they didn't forget to put
it out! It's deliberate!
Deliberate, I tell ya!
[♪]
JERRY:
They stole back the rye?
Yeah.
Why?
Why? Why?
'Cause he's off his rocker,
that's why.
So do the Rosses know?
I don't know.
They're all very suspicious.
Why wouldn't they be?
Rye bread
doesn't just disappear.
Now because of that stupid rye,
I gotta keep them all separated
for the rest of my life.
Bad situation.
I tell you what I'd like to do,
I'd like to replace that rye.
What do you mean, replace?
You know, you go out,
you get another rye.
Of course, it would have to be
the same one from Schnitzer's.
You put it
in the kitchen somewhere,
and you say, "Ah! There it is."
So there you go.
What's so hard about that?
How am I supposed to get it in?
I can't just walk in with it.
I have to get the Rosses out.
All right, all right.
Don't panic.
Let's just think about it.
Get the Rosses out
of the apartment.
That can't be so hard.
Wait a minute.
Wait a second. Wait a second!
You know Kramer's been driving
that hansom-cab?
So?
So Kramer can take them around for a while.
And it's their anniversary
Friday night.
I can send them
for a hansom-cab ride.
Y-y-you think they'd like that?
Are you kidding? People love it.
There's something about the
clip-clop. They're nuts for it.
They go off, by the time they
come back, the bread is there.
What about Susan?
She's working late that night.
W-we're supposed
to have dinner at 8:00,
so I'll set up the rye for 7:00.
Beautiful.
You think Kramer will do it?
Of course, I'll do it.
I'd be happy to.
All I gotta do is be there at 7?
Yeah, just take them out
and ride them around
for about half an hour.
That's easy.
What the hell
are you doing there?
It's Beef-a-Reeno.
And I got 50 cans.
You want some?
No. No, thanks.
Jerry, I think I bought too much
at that Price Club.
I don't have any room
for it all.
Hold on, hold on. Wait a minute.
How am I gonna get the rye bread
into the apartment?
Just put it under your shirt.
Have you ever seen
a Schnitzer's rye? I-it's huge.
I tell you what,
I'll bring it over.
I'll stop by Schnitzer's,
I'll come by five after 7,
right after they leave.
Oh, well, this is all
lockin' in now.
It is all lockin' in!
Hey. Is that your horse outside?
That's Rusty.
What, he's outside?
Uh-huh.
Ah, come on,
I wanna see him. Yeah!
KRAMER:
He's a great horsey.
Laney, wanna see the horsey?
You really did me in
this time, didn't you?
First guy I like
in a really long time.
I mean, we're getting along,
everything is just...
Mwah! Great.
I mean, all right,
so he doesn't do everything,
and then you have to come along
with your hot and your heavy.
So you think Clyde told him?
He wrote a song about it!
Well, maybe it's a good thing.
No, it's not a good thing.
It's a bad thing!
Do you know what this is like
to have no control
over a relationship
and you-- And you feel sick
to your stomach all the time?
Do you know what that's like?
No, no.
But I've read articles.
And I must say,
it doesn't sound very pleasant.
You know, one of these days,
something terrible
is gonna happen to you.
It has to.
No, I'm gonna be just fine.
But as far as your situation,
you're seeing him tonight
so talk to him about it.
I can't.
He's got a big showcase
for record producers
at his late show tonight.
I don't wanna upset him.
Oh, what the hell?
I'll upset him.
[♪]
MR. ROSS:
Eh, George, I gotta tell ya,
this is a very nice gesture.
We really appreciate it.
Oh, well, you know,
it's your anniversary.
It's-- It's the least I can do.
I-I just want you guys
to go out and have a good time.
So you think we should, uh,
we should get downstairs?
Ah, we got about 20 minutes.
You, uh,
seem a little nervous,
George. Anything wrong?
No, no, no, no.
Nothing. I'm fine.
Everything's fine. Fine.
Just get a little nervous
on the weekends, that's all.
Can I, uh--? Can I
get a glass of water?
We've got water.
I don't think we have any bread,
but we've got water.
[♪]
Yeah. Here you go, big fella.
That's Beef-a-Reeno.
♪ I'm so keen-o
On Beef-a-Reeno ♪
♪ What a delicious cuisine-o
Fit for a king and queen-o ♪
Yeah, eat up.
I got 34 more cans.
[♪]
Nice night for a hansom-cab
ride, eh, George?
MRS. ROSS:
You know, George,
we haven't done anything
romantic like this in years.
GEORGE:
Oh, my God. It's 7:01.
What have I done? My whole plan
is depending on Kramer?
Have I learned nothing?
How could I have made
such a stupid mistake?
He'll never show up.
[HOOVES CLOPPING]
Ah-ha!
There he is.
Right on time, as usual.
[♪]
Fifty-three.
Uh, 53.
I'd like a marble rye.
No plastic. In a bag.
Ah, you're lucky,
it's our last one.
Wait a second,
that's your last marble rye?
That's right.
There's none left?
That's what I said.
Number 54.
Uh, excuse me.
I know this is
gonna sound crazy,
but I--
I have to have that rye.
It's a-- It's a long story,
but a person's whole future
may depend on it.
Well, I'm sorry, but you
should've got here earlier.
Yes, well, be that as it may,
if you could just find it
within yourself to give it up--
You're not getting this rye.
All right. All right.
I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I will give you double
what you paid for it.
You're in my way.
[♪]
Ah, Mr. Ross, Mrs. Ross,
my name is Cosmo,
and I'll be your driver
for this evening.
We have, uh, blankets
for your comfort.
I also have hot chocolate
if the mood should strike you.
My favorite.
Well, if we're all set to go,
why don't you two hop aboard
and let me show you
a little taste of old New York
the way it once was?
Oh, happy anniversary.
On, Rusty!
[♪]
All right, look.
I'll tell you what,
I'll give you $50.
Now, be reasonable.
You cannot turn down $50
for a $6 rye.
No? Watch me.
Give me that rye.
Stop it.
I want that rye, lady.
Help! Someone help!
Shut up, you old bag.
Stop him, he's got
my marble rye!
[♪]
I'm sorry to just show up
unexpectedly like this.
I know you've got your big
showcase coming up later,
and I know how important it is.
I know how hard
you've worked for this night,
but I-I just had
to tell you
that I never told Jerry
"hot and heavy."
I didn't think
we were hot and heavy.
I mean-- I mean
who's hot and who's heavy?
Whoa. Hold on, Elaine. I--
I'm kinda disappointed.
Disappointed?
Yeah, I mean...
I was excited when Clyde
told me that.
You were?
Absolutely.
Oh! Whew!
I am so relieved.
Listen, uh...
I've still got
a couple of hours to kill
before the next show.
My place is only
a few blocks from here.
[CHUCKLES]
Really?
Yeah.
And you know what,
I've been thinking
about what we do,
and I'm thinking
of adding a new number
to my, you know,
my...repertoire.
Oh.
[♪]
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
[HUMMING]
[RUSTY GRUMBLES]
What is that?
I-I-I think it's the horse.
Oh, my God.
Hey, how's everything?
Y-you need anything?
This is
really intolerable.
Excuse me. What do you
feed this animal?
Oh, you know, oats and hay.
Yeah, they like that stuff.
I can--
I can't take this.
Get me outta this thing!
Turn this thing around.
We've had it.
We can't breathe back here.
And hurry it up.
Rusty!
[♪]
[WHISTLES]
Whoa, Rusty. Whoa.
Wh-what happened?
What are you doing back so soon?
Ask Rusty.
I'm terribly sorry,
Mr. Ross. One never knows
how the gastro-intestinal
workings of the equine
are going to function.
Thanks for nothing.
Come on, George,
let's go upstairs.
What the hell happened?
The horse is gassy.
Must've been the Beef-a-Reeno.
Beef-a-Reeno? You fed
the horse Beef-a-Reeno?
Well, I overbought.
George!
[♪]
What's going on?
Where is he?
Uh, he'll be here soon.
I'll give him 10 more minutes.
I'm not gonna stay here
all night.
[♪]
How much did you give him?
Just a can.
But he really
liked it, though.
GEORGE:
Jerry, up here.
JERRY:
Yeah, hey, what do you want me to do with this?
GEORGE:
I can't come out, they're standing right by the door.
Throw it up here.
Really?
Yeah, yeah,
it's the only way. Come on.
What are you kidding me?
Can you get this horse
outta here?
I can't get any oxygen.
I don't wanna
go back on there.
Come on.
Ugh!
Yah!
Hey, hey! Wait a second.
I got an idea.
[♪]
No, no. Don't be silly, John.
You were very good.
You just don't have
to try so hard.
Good luck, honey.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Come on. Come on.
JERRY:
Just wait a second.
I never baited a hook
with a rye before.
Your hook is too small.
Th-this is for,
like, a muffin.
All right, take it away.
Come on.
Yah! Yah.
[GRUNTS]
Schnitzer's.
[♪]
Ladies and gentlemen,
John Germaine.
[APPLAUSE]
[BAND PLAYING SMOOTH JAZZ]
[PLAYS SOUR NOTE]
[PLAYING HARSH, OFF-KEY MELODY]
[CONTINUES PLAYING
OFF-KEY MELODY]