People can be so vain,
don't you know?
I have a friend
who wears eyeglasses,
no prescription in the glasses,
because he thinks he looks
more intelligent.
Now, why?
Why do we think
that glasses makes us look
more intelligent?
Is it from the endless hours
of reading and studying
and researching that
this person supposedly
blew out their eyeballs?
And that's why they need
the glasses?
It's just a corrective device.
If you see someone with
a hearing aid, you don't think,
"Oh, they must have been
listening real good...
yeah, to a lot
of important stuff."
No, they are deaf.
They can't hear.
[♪]
Hey, boys and girls.
Hey.
I need you both to sponsor me
in the AIDS Walk.
Isn't that tomorrow?
Yeah, yeah.
So...get-- Get.
Well,
I admire you for joining
the fight against AIDS.
KRAMER: Yeah, well,
if I didn't do somethin',
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself.
It's hard enough
livin' next door.
But I tell ya,
there's some people, they just wear a ribbon,
and think they're somethin'.
Mm.
Not me. I talk the talk,
and I walk the walk, baby.
Yeah, I'm gonna be
right back.
New jeans?
Yeah.
Hah.
Still a 31 waist?
Yep, since college.
Hm.
Hey, Lena Small's
on this list.
Lena Small?
Yeah, she's a girl
I was gonna call for a date.
She was unlisted,
and now here's her number.
Oh, you are not gonna cop
a girl's phone number
off an AIDS charity list?
Elaine, you should admire me.
I'm aspiring to date
a giving person.
But you're a taking person.
That's why I should date
a giving person.
If I date a taking person,
everyone's taking,
taking, taking.
No one's giving.
It's bedlam.
She's gonna ask
how you got her number.
Oh, I'll tell her
I met some guy who knew her,
and he gave it to me.
Oh, what's he look like?
I really didn't pay
much attention.
I had just come
from buying a speedboat.
You're buying a speedboat?
See we're already off
the subject
of how I got the number.
[LAUGHS]
All I gotta do is get past
the first phone call,
and I'm home free.
I don't know about that.
So if Billy had got your number
off the AIDS Walk list,
you wouldn't have gone out
with him?
Well...
Yeah.
So you really like this guy?
Very much.
Yeah.
How's the sexual chemistry?
Haven't been in the lab yet.
But I am birth control
shopping today.
Are you still
on the pill?
Oh, Kramer--
No, I'll tell ya,
I think birth control
should be discussed
in an open forum.
The Sponge.
KRAMER:
Okay?
The Today Sponge.
Yeah, but wasn't that
taken off the market?
Off the market?
The Sponge?
No, no.
No way.
Everybody loves the Sponge.
Well, I read it
in Wall Street Week.
Louis, uh, Rukeyser.
[CHUCKLES]
JERRY:
Hello, Lena?
Hi, it's Jerry Seinfeld.
How did I get your number?
I met a guy that knows you.
He gave it to me.
I don't remember his name.
I think it began with a W.
Maybe a Q.
I wasn't paying
that much attention.
I'd just come from shopping
for a speedboat.
[♪]
You know, I really liked those
new jeans Jerry was wearing.
He's really thin.
Not as thin as you think.
Why? He's a 31.
I saw the tag on the back.
The tag, huh?
Mm-hm.
Let me tell you somethin'
about that tag.
It's no 31, and, uh,
let's just leave it at that.
Why, what are you
talking about?
He scratches off a 32,
and he puts in 31.
What?
Oh, how could he be so vain?
Well, this is
the Jerry Seinfeld
that only I know.
I can't believe
I just told you that.
[CHUCKLING]
Why not?
Well, Jerry doesn't want
anyone to know.
Well, it's all right.
I'm your fiancée.
Everybody assumes
you'll tell me everything.
Where did you get
that one from?
Well, we're a couple.
It's understood.
I never heard of that.
Well, you've never been
a couple.
I've coupled. I've coupled.
Keeping secrets.
This is just like
your secret bank code.
This is totally different.
That was my secret.
This is Jerry's secret.
There's-- There's
attorney-client privileges here.
Well, if I play it
by your rule,
I-I-I-- No one will ever
confide in me again.
I'll be cut out of the loop.
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
What's the matter?
Had a fight with Susan.
What about?
Oh--
Clothing, something,
I don't know.
So, uh, what are
you doin' tonight?
I got a date
with that girl, Lena.
Lena? How'd you meet her?
I actually, uh, met her
a few weeks ago, uh, but...
So Jerry got
Lena's unlisted number
from Kramer's AIDS Walk list.
Monica? Jerry got
Lena's unlisted number
off of an AIDS Walk list.
He got her number off
an AIDS Walk list?
You met her
a few weeks ago, but...?
I didn't call her till today.
So, uh, wanna double?
What?
Well, you know,
I just had a fight.
I need a group dynamic.
I don't know.
Hey.
Well,
Kramer was right.
My friend Kim told me
the Sponge is off the market.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do a hard target
search of every drugstore,
general store, health store,
grocery store
in a 25-block radius.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Just for these Sponges?
Hey, man, women are really loyal
to their birth-control methods.
What does Susan use?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I, uh...
figure it's somethin'.
[PANTING]
Wh-what are you
all out of breath from?
The elevator just broke.
[SIGHS]
I had to walk up five flights.
And you got
the AIDS Walk tomorrow.
Y-you're never gonna make it.
You're in horrible shape.
Hey, I'm in tiptop shape.
Tiptop?
Better than you.
I got a 31 waist, mister.
Yeah, well,
I'm walkin' for charity.
What are you doin'?
What am I doin'?
I'm...datin' a woman
who happens to be sponsoring
one of these walkers.
[♪]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
PHARMACIST:
Can I help you?
Yeah, do you have
any Today Sponges?
I know they're off the market,
but I was ju--
Actually, we have a case left.
A case?
A case of Sponges?
I-I--
I mean, a case.
Hah.
Uh...
H-how--?
How many come in a case?
Sixty.
Sixty?
Um...
Well, I'll take three.
Three.
Yeah.
Well, make it 10.
Ten?
Twenty Sponges should be plenty.
Did you say 20?
Yeah, 25 Sponges is just fine.
Twenty-five?
Yeah.
You're set with 25?
Yeah, yeah.
Just give me the case.
I'll be on my way.
[♪]
Hey, I have found
the best-smelling detergent.
Lena, smell my shirt.
Mm, very nice.
It's All TempaCheer.
I use Planet.
It's biodegradable,
and it doesn't
pollute the oceans.
Yeah, the oceans are
really gettin' very sudsy.
[CHUCKLES]
Can you wrap up all the
leftovers on the table, please?
I always take
the leftovers.
I work in a soup kitchen
every morning at 6 a.m.
Mm.
They serve soup at 6 a.m.?
Yeah.
That's all they have.
Do the bums ever complain?
"Soup again?"
I'd get tired of it.
How could you not?
Guess who volunteered
last week?
Mick Jagger.
LENA:
No.
Maya Angelou.
Oh, the poet.
So let me ask ya something.
These people eat soup
three times a day?
I don't know.
Did you get to talk to her?
Talk to who?
Is it a lot of cream soups?
Maya Angelou, the poet.
No, I didn't
get the chance.
SUSAN & GEORGE:
Oh.
Wow, you know,
I'm sure you can reach her.
She's a poet, you know?
What does a poet need
an unlisted number for?
I'm goin'
to the ladies' room.
I'll go with you.
What are you lookin' at me
like that for?
Why'd you have to mention
"unlisted number"?
What are you talkin' about?
All right,
I gotta tell you something,
but you cannot tell Susan.
[♪]
SUSAN:
Jerry got
her phone number
off of an AIDS Walk list?
Oh, that's awful.
I know. But don't
say anything to anyone.
He told me not to tell you.
But you told me, anyway?
Well, you know, I was thinkin'
about what you said before,
and you're right.
I've never really been a couple,
so if that's the rule, I'm--
I'm gonna go by the rule.
Thank you, honey.
So you want to go home and...
make up officially?
[CHUCKLES]
Can we stop by
a drugstore first?
What for?
Oh, I'm out
of birth-control stuff.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Uh, where am I
gonna park here?
Oh, no, don't park.
I'll just sit in the car.
You can run in.
Me run in?
Wha--?
Why don't you run?
You don't know what I use
for birth control, do you?
Of course, I do.
You do? What?
You know,
you use the, uh--
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
The what?
You know, the--
[COUGHS, MUMBLES]
Just get me some Sponges,
please.
Wait a minute.
W-wait-- Wait a minute.
They, uh,
They don't have 'em anymore.
What?
I just found out
they just took 'em off
the market.
Off the market?
The Sponge?
Yeah, so you gotta use
somethin' else. I can't!
I-I love the Sponge!
I need the Sponge!
Okay.
I think I know
where we can get one.
[♪]
[KRAMER & MEN SHOUTING,
LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
Kramer,
what the hell
is going on in here?
It's a poker game.
And I'm kickin'
some serious butt.
Are you out of your mind?
You know you got
the AIDS Walk tomorrow?
MAN:
Hey, Kramer, are you in?
Oh, you gotta be kiddin'.
You see those two ladies
I got showin'?
Do they look scared?
What were you sayin'?
You're never going to make it.
[GIGGLES]
KRAMER:
Let's go. Let's go.
Get 'em up.
Come on.
[♪]
You, uh...
You wanna go
in the bedroom?
Oh...
[GIGGLES]
Okay.
Hold on just a second.
[WHISPERS]
Okay.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Elaine, it's me, George.
Hey, sorry to bother you
so late.
Yeah.
Hey, how ya doin'?
Um, did you get
any of those Sponges?
Yeah.
I cleaned out
the whole West Side.
[LAUGHS]
Why?
Well, Susan.
Oh, Susan uses
the Sponge.
Susan loves the Sponge,
ha-ha.
Yeah, I-I'm sorry George.
I can't help ya out.
What?
I-I can't do it.
No way.
There's no how.
Wait, Elaine--
Elaine.
Let me just explain
something to ya.
You see, this is-- This is not
just the weekend routine.
Uh-huh.
I'm on the verge
of makeup sex here.
You know about makeup sex?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
George, I know all about
makeup sex,
Yeah.
and I'm really sorry.
Ah, b-but, Elaine.
Elaine, can I just explain
something to you very privately?
Susan and I have been together
many, many times now, and,
just between you
and me, there--
There's really
no big surprises here,
so makeup sex is
all that I have left.
I'm sure you'll have
another fight, George.
Ow! Ow!
Hold that thought.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪]
SUSAN:
Oh, so listen to this.
But don't tell anyone.
Um, Jerry Seinfeld...
He got a woman's number
off an AIDS Walk list.
He got her number
off an AIDS Walk list?
He what?
[♪]
How'd you find out?
A friend of a friend
of a friend knows Susan.
[WHISPERS]
George.
Pardon?
What?
Ah, nothing.
Listen, I'm sorry. I just--
It's okay.
There's nothing to be
sorry about. I don't mind.
You don't mind that I got your
number off the AIDS Walk list?
No, not at all.
No problem.
[CHATTERING OUTSIDE]
See you later, okay?
Ah, you're lucky you're
walkin' out of here
with a pair of pants on.
[LAUGHS]
What do ya mean--?
You went all night?
Mm.
Jerry, yeah!
Breakfast on me.
Kramer, are you
out of your mind?
You got the AIDS Walk
in three hours.
Oh.
You're never gonna to make.
AIDS Walk.
That's a cakewalk.
Hey.
Hey!
So, George?
Yeah.
Guess what.
Lena found out
how I got her number.
Really?
How'd she do that?
A friend of a friend
of Susan's.
My Susan?
Why'd you tell her?!
I had to, Jerry.
It's a couple rule.
We have to tell
each other everything.
You know what this means,
don't ya? What?
You're cut off.
You're out of the loop!
You're cut--?
You're cuttin' me off?
No, no, no, Jerry,
don't cut me off.
You leave me no choice.
You're the media now,
far as I'm concerned.
Oh, Jerry, come on.
Please, it won't happen again.
If you were in the Mafia,
would you tell her
every time you killed someone?
Hey, a hit is
a totally different story.
I don't know, George.
So Lena was upset, huh?
You know what?
That was the amazing thing.
What?
It didn't bother her?
No, she said it was fine.
Oh.
Something very strange
about this girl.
What?
She's too good.
Too good.
I mean, she's giving and caring
and generally concerned
about the welfare of others.
I can't be with
someone like that.
I see what you mean.
I-I mean, I admire
the hell out of her.
You can't have sex
with someone you admire.
Where is the depravity?
No depravity.
I mean, I look at her.
I-I can't imagine
she even has sex.
On the other hand...
What?
Thanks again
for last night.
Hey, I didn't even use one.
Yeah.
You said it was imminent.
Yeah, it was.
But then, ugh,
I just couldn't decide
if he was really Sponge-worthy.
Sponge-worthy?
Yeah. Jerry,
I have to conserve
these Sponges.
But you like him.
Isn't that what it's for?
Yes, yes.
Before they went off the market.
But I mean,
now I've gotta re-evaluate
my whole screening process.
I can't afford to waste
any of 'em.
You know you're nuts
with these Sponges.
George is gettin' frustrated.
[♪]
Uh, uh, Cosmo Kramer.
Uh...okay.
You're checked in.
Yeah, thank you.
Here's your AIDS ribbon.
Uh, no, thanks.
You don't wanna wear the ribbon?
Ah, no, no.
But you have to wear
an AIDS ribbon.
I have to?
Yes.
Yeah, see,
that's why I don't want to.
But everyone wears the ribbon.
You must wear the ribbon.
You know what you are?
You are a ribbon bully.
ORGANIZER:
Hey!
Hey, you! Come back here.
Come back here and put this on!
[♪]
GEORGE:
Elaine and her Sponges.
She's got like a war chest
full of 'em.
Well, I don't see why
you can't just use condoms.
Oh, no, no.
No, condoms are for single men.
The day that we got engaged,
I said goodbye
to the condom forever.
Oh, just once
for the makeup sex.
Makeup sex?
You have to have that
right after the fight.
We're way past that.
Come on, just once?
No, no,
I hate the condom.
Why?
I can never get the package
open in time.
Well, you just tear it open.
It's not that easy.
It's like Beat the Clock.
There's a lot of pressure there.
[♪]
Hey, where's your ribbon?
Oh, I don't wear
the ribbon.
You don't wear
the ribbon?
Aren't you
against AIDS?
Yeah, I'm against AIDS.
I mean, I'm walking, aren't I?
I just don't wear the ribbon.
Who do you think
you are?
Put the ribbon on.
Hey, Cedric, Bob.
This guy won't
wear a ribbon.
Who?
Who doesn't want
to wear the ribbon?
[♪]
So you think
you're Sponge-worthy?
Yes, I think
I'm Sponge-worthy.
I think
I'm very Sponge-worthy.
Run down your case for me again.
[SIGHS]
Well, we've gone out
several times.
We obviously have
a good rapport. Mm-hm.
Um, I own a very profitable
electronics distributing firm.
I eat well.
I exercise.
Blood tests, immaculate.
Mm-hm.
And if I can speak frankly,
I'm actually quite good at it.
You gonna do something about
your sideburns there?
Yeah. I told you,
I-I'm-- I'm gonna--
I'm gonna trim my sideburns,
yeah.
And the bathroom
in your apartment?
Cleaned it this morning.
Uh-huh.
The sink, the tub, everything?
Everything, yeah.
Uh-huh.
It's spotless.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Hey, look at this.
I just got a citation
in the mail
for my work with shut-ins.
Oh, the shut-ins.
That's nice.
You know, they're
a very eccentric group...
because they're--
They're shut in.
Of course,
they're not locked in,
they're free to go
at any time.
Oh, by the way,
I checked at the soup kitchen.
They do have cream soups.
Hey, that's dynamite.
You know, Lena,
I wanted to talk to you
about something.
You know, because
you're such a good person.
Oh.
That I--
Hang on to that thought.
I'm rinsing a sweater.
I left the water running.
Oh.
Hey, Jerry, can you get me a
towel out of my bedroom closet?
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God.
Look what's goin' on here.
She is depraved.
Hup.
There you are.
Thanks.
So you were saying?
What? Nothing.
No, you said
I was a good person.
Oh.
You seem like you wanna
tell me something.
Tell you something.
I-- I do.
What is it, Jerry?
You can tell me anything.
Oh, um,
you see these jeans
I'm wearing?
Yeah?
I change the 32 waist
on the label
to a 31 on all my jeans.
So, ya know...
That's it.
[♪]
SUSAN:
Come on, George, just rip it open.
I'm trying, damn it.
Look, tear it.
Tear it from the side.
I tried to tear it
from the side.
I can't get
a good grip here.
You got to do it
like a bag of chips.
No, here,
give it to me.
Would you wait a second?
Wait a second!
Just give it to me.
Give it to me.
You see?
[WHISPERS]
There. Got it.
Come on.
Come on!
It's too late.
[♪]
So!
What's it going to be?
Are you going to wear
the ribbon?
No.
Never.
But I'm wearing the ribbon.
He's wearing the ribbon.
We're all wearing the ribbon.
So why aren't you
going to wear the ribbon?
This is America! I don't have
to wear anything I don't wanna!
What are we gonna do with him?
I guess we just going
to have to teach him
to wear the ribbon!
[WHIMPERING]
[YELLS]
[♪]
It completely
turned her off.
Well, I can see that.
Why--? What do you
have to do that for?
Who cares about your pants size?
I don't wanna be a 32.
I'd kill to be a 32.
She said
I wasn't Sponge-worthy.
Wouldn't waste
a Sponge on me.
I wish I had one.
That condom killed me.
Why do they have to make
the wrappers
on those things so hard to open?
It's probably so the woman
has one last chance
to change her mind.
You never run out, do you?
Where's Kramer?
Everything's finished here.
Oh, I told him
he'd never make it.
He was up all night.
Oh, my God.
Kramer?
[PANTING]
JERRY:
Look at ya.
I told ya.
Up all night playin' poker.
Come on.
Hey, where's your
AIDS ribbon?
[♪]
Well.
Good morning.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
How'd ya sleep?
Oh!
Great.
You?
Fine, fine.
Everything, uh, okay?
Yep.
No regrets?
Nope.
What are you doing?
Uh--
What do you mean?
Oh, I-I don't think so.
Why not?
I-- I thought you said
everything was fine.
Oh, I wish I could help you,
but I can't afford two of 'em.
[♪]