The whole concept of being
separated, to me, is strange.
It's like your engaged
to be divorced.
We're gonna try and make
not being together work.
First we were separated,
then we met,
and then we were together,
and now we're gonna try
being separated again.
We think actually some sort of
giant rubber band
might be the solution.
Of course,
when you were a kid in school,
you'd get separated
for having too good a time.
If you two kids don't stop
laughing and having fun,
I'm gonna have to separate you.
Then the kid finds out
his parents are breaking up,
and he thinks
it's because they got caught
fooling around,
which is probably true.
[♪]
Hairdo?
Yeah.
You look like Brenda Starr.
Is that good?
Better than Dondi.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, my God,
look at that.
It's David
and Beth Lukner.
You know, I heard a rumor
they're marriage
was a little rocky.
Really?
Mm-hm.
You know, I have a little thing
for Beth Lukner.
Well...
I have to admit,
I've always thought David
was kind of Sponge-worthy.
Yeah, I've been waiting out
their marriage for three years.
Yeah, me too.
Well, I've been waiting out
two or three marriages,
but this is the one
I really had my eye on.
This car out there
is taking up,
like, three parking spaces.
Oh, ha-ha, that's mine.
You have a car?
My friend lent it to me
for the week.
She's out of town.
I've never seen you drive.
Me neither.
Jerry?
Elaine, hi.
Hi, David.
Hi, Beth.
Oh, uh, George,
this is my husband, David.
Oh, hi, David.
Hello.
So, George, you're
the one who works for the Yankees, right?
Yeah, why?
What do you do?
Well, I sell insurance,
but Beth used to be
Don Mattingly's doctor.
Really?
Mm-hm.
Ha! A physician married
to a salesman.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, I gotta tell you, Beth.
You could have done
a lot better than him.
[ELAINE LAUGHS]
[♪]
Hey, Jerry.
Hey.
Hey, Mickey,
what's going on?
Very nervous. Auditioning
for the Actors' Studio tonight.
Really?
It's in Method, Jerry.
It's intense.
Kramer's gonna be
my scene partner.
Kramer?
He doesn't have to say anything.
He just has to sit there.
I'm playing a detective.
And I'm playing a businessman
accused of murder.
Oh, boy.
Well, I gotta meet Elaine
and run some errands, so...
Oh, look at this, Mickey.
These pants are falling apart,
huh?
When I met you, Kramer, you used
to wear jeans all the time.
Yeah, well,
I was a different man then.
With a different body.
Hey, I got the body of a taut,
preteen Swedish boy.
I don't know.
Now, what are you thinking?
You think that I'm not able
to wear jeans anymore?
Is that what you're saying?
Because if that's what you're
saying, Jerry,
I'll go and I'll--
I'll buy some jeans.
I swear to God, I will.
Don't think I won't, Jerry.
All right. That's it.
[♪]
God, it is so great
to drive again.
I miss it so much.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Hey--
How about a left turn signal,
you moron!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Whoa!
[HORN HONKING]
I'm so nauseous.
She's the worst driver.
You know what?
On my road test, I hit a dog.
Ha.
I think it was
a golden retriever.
No, no, no, it was a--
It was a yellow Lab.
Oh,
I better check my messages.
[DIALS PHONE]
[TIRES SCREECH]
MAN: Hey!
I'm so carsick,
I'm gonna vomit.
Oh, my God, Jerry!
My friend, Kim, called.
David and Beth
got separated last night.
[WEAKLY]
Yeah?
They're getting divorced!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[♪]
So now what is our move?
What do we do?
I don't know,
but we don't have much time.
The city is probably teeming
with people
waitin' out that marriage.
Right.
It's like when a tenant dies
in a rent-controlled building.
You gotta take immediate action.
Yeah,
but David and Beth
are gonna need
their grieving time.
Their grieving time's
a luxury I can't afford.
I'm calling Beth tonight,
and if you want a shot at David,
I suggest you do likewise.
Yeah. Yeah.
But we gotta make it seem like
we're not calling for dates.
Then why are we calling?
Good question.
Why are we calling?
Calling...calling...
Why are we call--?
Ah!
I got it. I've got it.
We're calling just to say:
"I'm there for you."
I'm there for you.
Then after a period of being
"there for you,"
we slowly remove the two words,
"for you,"
and we're just "there."
JERRY & ELAINE:
Hey.
Remember Beth and David
from yesterday?
They got separated.
Really?
Well...
you don't think it had anything
to do with what I said, do you?
What'd you say?
You know, that--
That thing about her
being too good for him.
I mean,
I was just being folksy.
You-- They could tell
I was being folksy.
Yeah,
I thought you were being folksy.
Totally folksy.
Hey, uh...
What'd you get
there?
Yeah, I bought dungarees.
Oh.
Kramer, they're painted on.
Well, they're the slim fit.
Slim fit?
Yeah, they're streamlined.
You're walking like
Frankenstein.
They just gotta be worked in
a little bit, that's all.
See you.
[♪]
Well, David,
oh, it happens.
Sure, Beth, these things happen.
So have you told
many people yet?
Because it's really
nobody's business.
Anyway, I just called
to tell you that...
I'm there for you.
There is, um...
anywhere you want me to be.
Sure.
Dinner would be fine.
And I can just be there...
for you.
Jerry, you gotta help me.
What's wrong?
I can't get my pants off,
and Mickey's audition
is in 20 minutes.
I'm supposed to be
a businessman.
I gotta be in costume.
All right. Undo 'em.
I'll help you get them off.
I already did it.
It won't come off.
Okay, you just gotta
wiggle your hips a little bit.
Pull down.
All right. All right.
Let go.
Let me-- Let me try getting them
from the bottom.
Just gimme your--
Wait, Jerry.
Wait a minute--
Pull.
Man, these are tight.
Squinch your hips in.
I am squinching my hips.
Keep squinchin' them.
Come on--
All right,
it's not gonna work.
Let me just think
for a second here.
You better get me.
Get me up, get me up.
Oh, hold it, hold it.
Hold it. Look.
You need the Jaws of Life
to get out of those things.
Look, I don't have time to wait.
I'm gonna be late.
Maybe you can soak in a tub.
You better get the door.
BETH:
It was nice to get your call.
Well, I just want you to know
I'm there for you.
Of course,
now I'm here for you,
but when I'm not here for you,
I'm there for you.
Well, wherever you are,
I appreciate it.
So how did all this happen?
Well, actually, it had a lot
to do with George's comment.
Is that right?
I thought,
maybe I could do better.
Maybe, maybe.
Well,
it wasn't just that.
I realized after three years
of marriage
that David's little quirks were
getting on my nerves a little.
Yeah, three years is a long time
to be married.
Like, in the middle
of our fight last night,
he did this thing
that he always does,
where he asks questions
to himself aloud
and then answers them.
Am I happy Beth left me?
Of course not.
Can I hope to pick up the pieces
and move on? Absolutely.
You're gonna
pick up the pieces.
Just had our third anniversary
on April 8th.
Tenth.
Right.
You know,
as far as I'm concerned,
this whole thing
is George's fault.
Well, David,
the thing about George
is that he's an idiot.
[♪]
All right. Auditioning next
is Mickey Abbott,
uh, doing a scene from
the Terrence Klufer play,
Flesh Wounds in Ithaca.
I'm sorry, my scene partner
isn't here yet, so I guess, uh--
Oh.
Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
What's with the jeans?
You're a businessman.
It's a long story.
Well, just get up there.
So, Bradley...
I guess this is the last place
you expected to find yourself.
[SIGHS]
Well, we're gonna be here
a while, so take a seat.
You know, if it hadn't been
for that secretary of yours...
I said, sit down.
Are you deaf, Bradley?
I said, sit down!
I have a problem.
Bradley...
It's very important
that you sit down.
Now, for the last time...
Try again...
to sit down.
Sit down, you big, stupid ape!
[♪]
Did I have a great time with
David Lukner last night?
I sure did.
Do I think
there's a future here?
I don't see why not.
I'll tell you,
that "there for you" crap
was a stroke of genius.
Oh, please.
Never mind.
Oh, come on.
You're a genius.
All right.
Hey.
Mm! Georgie!
Hey, hey!
Yay! Georgie boy!
All right! Way to go!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What--? What's going on?
What's going on?
You're the man of the hour.
That's what's going on.
That is right.
What do you mean?
Well, thanks to you
and your little comment there
to David and Beth,
Jerry and I are in prime,
pouncing position
to scoop these two up
before they know what hit 'em.
S-so it was my--
My comment that broke them up?
According to them.
Yeah, ha-ha.
I-- I feel terrible.
I can't be responsible
for breaking up a marriage.
Oh, no.
Wh-where you goin'?
Well, I gotta go
talk to Beth.
Talk to Beth?
I gotta undo what I did.
You're not undoing anything.
Oh, yes, I am.
Oh, no, you're not.
All right.
Get out of my way.
All right. Don't make me
get physical here!
You be careful, George.
Oh, ho-ho!
All right-- All right!
[GRUNTING]
[♪]
George.
Hi, Beth.
[♪]
And, anyway, uh,
Jerry told me that, uh,
it might have been
my comment in the coffee shop
that broke you up.
Oh, well, you know,
it's funny, George.
Sometimes you don't know
how you're really feeling
about something
until a person like you
comes along
and articulates it so perfectly.
[SNORTS]
Ho-ho, articulate.
Me? I-I've never articulated
anything.
I'm completely incoherent.
[PHONE RINGS]
I don't know about that.
Hold on.
Hello.
Hi!
Yeah, last night I did too.
Really? That's so funny.
He's here right now.
Could you put him on?
I'd love to say hello.
Sure.
George, it's Jerry.
He-- He wants to talk to me?
Yeah, he says
he wants to say hello.
Sweet guy.
Hello?
What the hell are you doing
over there?
Mind your own business.
Now, stay out of my affairs!
Oh, Jerry, Jerry,
that is so sweet of you,
but actually,
I already ate.
Ate? What? What the hell
are you talking about?
Now, you listen to me.
Get out of that apartment.
If you screw this up for me,
I swear--
Chocolate chip mint?
[CHUCKLES]
No.
Actually, Jerry,
I prefer chocolate chip.
What is it about the chocolate
and the mint
that makes it go so well
together?
What are you talking about--?
Oh, of course, you can use it.
Sure.
Okay. Bye-bye.
What are you talk--?
Don't hang up on me, George--
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
Are you still wearing
those things?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think they're, uh,
startin' to loosen up a bit.
Oh, hi, Mrs. Zanfino.
Oh, Kramer,
would you do me a favor?
My babysitter hasn't shown up.
Could you come watch Joey
for an hour?
Yeah, sure, Mrs. Zanfino.
Yeah.
Oh, he's sleeping already.
You don't have to do anything.
See you later, buddy.
See you later.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hi, Jerry. It's Beth.
Oh, hi, Beth.
Hi.
I've-- I've been doing
a lot of thinking today,
and I don't know.
Maybe I made a huge mistake.
[MUTTERING]
George!
I'm just feeling very confused.
Um, I'll-- I'll call you back,
okay?
Okay.
Trouble.
What?
George.
Is it?
Yeah.
Damn.
What do we do?
You get your ass
over to Beth's tout de suite.
And turn on
that so-called charm
you're always telling me about.
Yeah, I can try and do that.
You don't try.
You do it.
I got the loser
in this relationship,
and I'm breathing new life
into him.
In three more days he won't
be able to remember her name.
You got the winner.
You got the easy part.
All right, let's go. I'll drive
you over there. Come on.
No, you go on ahead.
I'll take the bus.
What? I'm parked outside.
Let's go.
I'll take the subway.
It doesn't matter.
I'll take you.
Uh, I can hitchhike.
What's your problem?
It's not necessary.
What's your problem? Come on.
[♪]
The, uh-- The shoelaces
that you bought me.
They-- They worked out well.
Well, you know,
if you need some more,
I can get 'em for you.
It should be a while,
though.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
That was close.
Confide in her.
Open up to her.
You know, women like that.
I don't feel so good.
JERRY:
Anyway, Beth...
You know, I was thinking
on my way over
how when I was 9,
I wanted these handball
sneakers.
They were all black.
But they only came
in adult sizes.
So...
you know, I never...
got the sneakers.
Oh, really.
My father left us
when I was 9,
so I guess that's why I have
such a fear of abandonment.
Wow, that's so touching.
Yes, it is.
Hey, it's George.
Oh, maybe we should
go someplace else.
No, let's go in.
Oh, uh...hi-- Hi, David.
Hi, George.
Elaine.
Hi.
Listen, uh, David,
I-- I-- I want to apologize
about that comment--
George, please, please,
I'm fine.
Oh, yeah, this is my fiancée.
Susan,
this is David.
David.
Oh, fiancée.
Boy, you could have done
a lot better than him.
Come on, Elaine.
Let's go.
[♪]
[SCREAMS]
It's Frankenstein.
It's Frankenstein!
Joey.
Joey!
Mickey, you were so incredible
in that scene yesterday.
The rage.
Right. The rage.
Tons of rage.
I don't believe this.
[PHONE RINGING]
[SIGHS]
Hello?
Mickey.
Oh, hi, Kramer.
What do you want?
I'm busy.
Look,
you gotta do me a favor.
What? Now? I can't.
Hey, you owe me.
I got you in Actors' Studio.
They thought what we did
was the scene.
A-a-all right. All right.
I'll-- I'll be right over.
Oh, uh, you ready?
[SIGHING]
Oh.
You know what, George?
Uh, why don't--
Why don't you go ahead.
I think I'd like to be alone
for a while.
Oh, sure.
Sure, you want to be alone.
Sure. I understand that.
You want a little time to think,
uh... Thing-- Ponder things.
You know. Ruminate.
You go ahead.
A lot of stuff on your mind.
You think things out.
Think.
Mull. Just mull.
Do a lot of mulling.
Ha-ha!
Now,
I gotta go find this kid.
So all you gotta do
is lay here,
pretend you're asleep
in case she gets back.
Here,
get the covers over you.
Why don't you just cut the pants
and get them off, already?
Hey,
I'm breaking them in.
Just hurry.
What am I gonna do in here?
Just keep the lights out
and your eyes closed.
I'll be back.
Oh!
GEORGE:
Jerry! Jerry!
J-- Jerry! Jerry! The most
unbelievable thing has happened.
It is too unbelievable!
I'm sitting in the coffee shop.
I'm talking to Susan.
We're talking about shoelaces.
[IMITATES GUNSHOT]
So in walks--
In walks David, right?
He walks right up
to the table, right?
I introduce him to Susan,
and he says--
[CHUCKLING]
Now get this.
He says, "Boy, you could do
a lot better than this guy."
Huh? Right? The exact same thing
that I said to him.
Just to get back at me.
And then-- And then she says she
wants to be alone for a while.
Alone, Jerry.
I think that she thinks
that she could do better.
Do--? Do you appreciate this?
Do you see the irony of this?
You see what's going on
here?
What's the matter?
I'm nauseous.
Is that what's hurting
your appreciation?
A little.
It's a pretty good story,
don't you think?
It's not bad.
Yeah.
Hey, Joey, there you are.
[SCREAMS]
Hey-- Hey, Joey!
It's a monster!
I'm the babysitter.
[♪]
Good night, honey.
Good night.
[MRS. ZANFINO SCREAMS]
It's gotta have something to do
with Kramer.
[♪]
Elaine.
Hm?
Here's to you being there.
And here.
[LAUGHS]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
Hm.
Beth?
David.
Ow.
I'll tell you, it's not bad.
[♪]
George?
Yeah?
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Yeah, sure. Sure.
I've been doing
a lot of thinking
about the wedding and all,
and, um...
[SIGHS]
I've decided
to go with the chicken.
[♪]
Hi.
So chasing little kids,
huh?
You're in a lot of trouble,
mister.
No, look. I was babysitting--
Yeah, yeah. All right.
Sit down.
What are you, deaf?
I said sit down.
Hey, for the last time,
sit down.
Oh, yeah.
[♪]