I've never been anyplace
where there was no coffee.
People are constantly trying
to give you coffee.
"Would you like coffee?"
"Can I get you some coffee?"
Coffee is one of the only things
you can have
that people continue
to try and give it to you.
Waitresses are always
coming over,
"Can I fill it up?"
"Can I warm it up?"
"Can I top it off?"
You can lift up a manhole cover,
"We just made a fresh pot.
Would you like some?"
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS & APPLAUDS]
This liquid
has taken over humanity.
There are coffee machines
we have to call "mister."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Coffee anyone?"
"Hey, that's Mr. Coffee to you."
[♪]
And then I hear
this rabbi on television.
Imagine.
I'm really sorry, George.
I-I-- I wasn't jealous of you.
It was just the whole...
marriage thing.
You know,
I was just a little surprised.
Why would anyone
eat canned fruit?
I mean,
can anybody answer that?
What about
all the "loser" stuff?
I don't know where
the rabbi got that.
You know,
I never said that.
I said,
"I've never seen you looser."
JERRY:
I could see the can
if you're in the army.
But fresh fruit,
it's available.
It's there.
It's two aisles over.
Well, scintillating as always.
Where you going?
I'm going shopping with Susan.
What kind of shopping?
Clothes shopping.
Where you going?
Ross'.
That's a nice store.
It's her uncle's.
Ah. Discount?
One would hope.
[♪]
KRAMER:
So, you know,
my friend and I were
going to the movies,
and we stopped off
and bought this café latte.
What is that? Italian coffee?
That's right.
Half milk, half coffee?
Yeah.
Mm-hm. You take a sip?
Yes, I did.
When you took the sip,
did you notice it was hot?
Were you able to sip
in your normal fashion?
No, I wasn't able to sip it
in my normal fashion.
Mm-hm. All right, all right.
You take big sips?
Well,
I think I take a normal sip.
Okay. You take normal sips.
Nothing wrong with that.
Then what happened?
Well, you know, uh...
They don't allow outside drinks
in the movie theater,
so I had to put it in my shirt
and sneak it in.
Yeah, see they like to sell
their own coffee. Yeah.
Now, is that gonna be a problem?
Yeah, it's gonna be a problem.
It'll be a problem for them.
This is a clear violation
of your rights as a consumer.
It's an infringement
on your constitutional rights.
It's outrageous,
egregious, preposterous.
It's definitely preposterous.
So...then what happened?
Well...
I was trying to get to my seat
and I had to
step over someone,
and I kinda got pushed,
and it spilt on me.
Was there a top on it?
Yeah.
Did you put the top on,
or did they put the top on?
No. They put the top on.
And they made the top.
You didn't make the top,
did you?
Suzy...
want you to go down
to Java World.
Get me a café latte with a top.
We gonna run some tests
on that top.
Whoa.
Have you been to the doctor?
Uh, no. No, I haven't.
Suzy, call Dr. Bison.
Set up an appointment
for Mr. Kramer here.
Tell him it's for me.
So, uh, what do you think,
Mr. Chiles?
Jackie.
Jackie. I mean, we got a chance?
Do we have a chance?
You get me one coffee drinker
on that jury,
you gonna walk out of there
a rich man.
[SMACKS LIPS]
[♪]
GEORGE:
I don't like it. It's red.
It's too flashy.
You could use a little flash.
All right, don't change me.
Susan, don't change me.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, there's a lot of women
that would love to be
in your position right now.
Name one.
So...did you
find anything?
Oh, he is impossible
to shop for, Uncle Ned.
I'm going on vacation
to Costa Rica.
Maybe I'll see you in a
couple of weeks.
Okay.
Excuse me, Mr. Ross.
See, now,
this I don't get.
What?
The security guard.
What about him?
Why does he
have to stand?
Because he's
a security guard.
I mean, look at him.
He's gotta be on his feet
like that all day?
I mean, that's brutal.
I think I'll say something
to your uncle.
George, you just met him.
Don't say anything to him.
Aren't you concerned
about the security guard?
Not really.
GREORGE:
She's not concerned about the security guard.
What kind of a person is this?
I'm marrying a person
who doesn't care
that this man has to stand
there eight hours a day
when he could easily
be sitting.
All right, George.
What do you think?
[♪]
What'd you do
last night?
Nothin'.
I know, nothing,
but what did you actually do?
Literally nothing.
I sat in a chair, and I stared.
Wow, that really is nothing.
I told you.
Hey.
Why are you
all dressed up for?
Oh, I, uh, just came
from a meeting with my lawyer.
Oh, yeah?
How's that lookin'?
I'll tell ya how it's looking.
My lawyer Jackie says
if there's one coffee drinker
on that jury,
I'm gonna be a rich man.
Oh, that's despicable.
How does he know how
all coffee drinkers will vote?
I'm a coffee drinker.
If I was on that jury,
I wouldn't give you a nickel,
Kramer.
Well, you wouldn't
be on that jury.
He would have
weeded you out.
Frankly, I'm surprised
you're so litigious.
Oh, I can be
quite litigious.
I mean,
who ever heard of this anyway?
Suing a company
because their coffee is too hot?
Coffee is supposed to be hot.
Yeah, but Jackie says
the top was faulty.
[SCOFFS]
Jackie says the top was faulty.
[KNOCKING]
Hey, Maestro!
Ah, Kramer!
Hey, I'm in here.
How's it going?
Hi, Bob.
[COUGHS]
Oh.
I'm sorry.
"Maestro."
Ooh, boy, this is
a surprise, huh? Look at you.
I just wanted to drop off
this Chinese balm
for your burns.
It's supposed
to be great stuff.
It's all herbal.
Oh, Maestro, you--
What are you doing?
You don't have to do this.
Do you believe this Maestro?
It's nothing.
You haven't been around
for a while. Oh, yeah.
I've been at my house
in Tuscany.
Oh, Tuscany.
You hear that, Jerry?
That's in Italy.
I hear it's beautiful there.
Well, if you're thinking
of getting a place there,
don't bother.
There's really nothing
available.
Hm?
Oh.
Hello.
Well, hello.
And who might you be?
I might be Elaine.
This is Bob Cobb.
Maestro.
ELAINE:
Ooh.
Maestro.
It is my very great pleasure.
Oh.
[FRENCH ACCENT]
Enchanté.
[LAUGHS]
BOTH:
Well, I have to get going.
Jinx. Buy me a Coke.
Ooh.
I love it when that happens.
I know. I know.
That is so, um...
Coincidental.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, uh, bye, you guys.
Ciao.
Oh, hey, and, uh,
thanks for the balm.
Yeah.
You know you hurt
the Maestro's feelings.
Oh, why, because I didn't
call him "Maestro"?
That's right.
You know, I feel a little funny
callin' somebody "Maestro."
Why?
Because it's a stupid thing
to be called.
Jerry, he's a conductor.
Oh, "conductor."
He conducts
the Policemen's Benevolent
Association Orchestra.
Well, he's still
a conductor.
Well, he sure worked pretty fast
with Elaine.
Oh, you should see him do
"Flight of the Bumblebee."
He just...
T-t-t-t-t-toom!
[♪]
New shirt?
Yeah, you like it?
Not particularly.
Why, the color?
Yeah.
Too flashy?
Yeah, it's burning my retina.
Susan picked that out for you,
right?
No.
All right,
what's it gonna be here?
Let me ask you something.
When you go into a store,
does it bother you
that they make the security
guard just stand there all day?
No.
Hey, didn't bother Susan either.
That's why I'm different.
I can sense
the slightest human suffering.
Are you sensing
anything right now?
Let me just say this.
It is inhumane to make a man
stand on his feet in one spot
for eight hours a day.
Why shouldn't he have a chair?
Well, what about
criminal activity?
He's gotta be alert.
What, he can't
jump out of the chair?
How long does that take?
Here, look at this.
Here, watch.
Criminals! Boom! I'm up.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Maybe they offered him a chair,
and he turned it down.
Would you get outta here?
Who's gonna turn down
a chair?
I would be very interested to
know how he felt about all this.
Maybe I'll have a talk with him.
I know you will.
Hey, hey, hey.
Listen to this.
Jackie just called.
Who?
His lawyer.
Java World wants to settle.
What?
Yeah. I'm gonna be rich!
Why are they settling?
'Cause they're afraid
of bad publicity.
All this because you spilled
coffee on yourself?
Yeah! That's right!
I'm gonna need a coffee here!
Very hot! Boiling!
MAESTRO:
And then, about...
four years ago,
I was on holiday in Tuscany,
Uh-huh.
and I fell in love
with this house. Oh.
Are you ready to order?
Mm.
Oh, gosh.
What are you gettin', Bob?
Good question.
We'll need
a few minutes.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
You know, I'm sorry, but...
I didn't mention it earlier,
but, actually,
I prefer to be
called "Maestro."
Excuse me?
Well, you know,
I am a conductor.
Yeah. So?
Oh, I suppose it's okay
for Leonard Bernstein
to be called "Maestro"
because he conducted
the New York Philharmonic.
So he gets to be called
"Maestro," and I don't.
Well, I mean, don't you think
that he was probably called
"Maestro"
while he was conducting?
Not in social situations.
I mean, his friends probably
just called him "Lenny."
I happen to know for a fact
that he was called "Maestro"
in social situations.
I once saw him in a bar,
and somebody came up
to him and said,
"Hello, Maestro.
How about a beer?"
Okay? So that's a fact.
"Maestro," huh?
Okay.
[LAUGHS]
Maestro.
[♪]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BANGING]
[RATTLING]
Jerry!
[CRASHING]
Jerry! Jerry, my burn,
it's gone. Look.
What do you mean?
Well, I put that Chinese balm
on it the maestro gave me,
and look, it healed it.
So?
So...
my lawsuit,
I'm finished.
I thought
they wanted to settle.
Well, what happens
if they wanna see it?
Then you're
in a lot of trouble.
Yeah!
[♪]
[CHUCKLES]
Tired?
No.
How come, uh...
no chair?
What?
I couldn't help
but notice
that you don't
have a chair.
I don't need a chair.
I didn't mean
to imply you did.
You're obviously a very
well-proportioned individual.
What I was just
wondering is, uh...
have they ever offered
you a chair?
No.
Would you like
a chair?
I suppose if they gave me one,
I'd sit down.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
You would, wouldn't you?
Obviously I'd rather
sit than stand
if that's what you're asking.
That's exactly my point.
Well, who wouldn't?
Because I tell you,
frankly,
I'd like to walk
in here one day
and find you
sitting down.
That would give me
a lot of pleasure.
Ha!
Call me crazy.
[♪]
You put the balm on?
Who told you
to put the balm on?
I didn't tell you
to put the balm on.
Why'd you put the balm on?
You haven't even
seen the doctor.
If you gonna put a balm on,
let a doctor put a balm on.
I guess I screwed up,
huh, Jackie?
You damn right
you screwed up.
Where the hell did you get
that damn balm anyway?
The Maestro.
The who?
What you talkin' about,
"Maestro"?
My friend, he's a conductor.
Oh, oh, oh.
So a maestro tells you
to put a balm on,
and you do it?
Well, my stomach was burning.
I tell you what this is.
This is a public humiliation.
I didn't know the balm
was gonna work.
Do you know what a balm is?
You ever seen a balm?
Didn't you read
the instructions?
I was--
No one can tell what a balm's gonna do.
They're unpredictable.
All right,
I'm sorry, Jackie.
Pull over here, driver.
This is it.
Yeah. Get over.
[♪]
You have a good time?
Yeah,
he's very interesting.
Did you know
that Mozart died
while he was writing
the "Requiem"?
Yeah. Everyone knows that.
It was in Amadeus.
Really?
So, what about
the "Maestro" stuff.
Did he make you
call him "Maestro"?
Yeah, I called him "Maestro."
You didn't mind?
Well, I did at first,
but, actually,
I kinda got used to it.
Okay, from now on, I want you
to call me "Jerry the Great."
I am not calling you
"Jerry the Great."
Why not?
You call him "Maestro."
He is a maestro.
Well, I'm great.
So you say.
What about his house
in Tuscany?
Did he mention that?
Yeah.
I'm invited.
Hm.
You know, when I told him
it was beautiful there,
out of the clear blue sky,
he says
there's nothing to rent,
as if he doesn't want
anyone else there.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe he's embarrassed
by Americans.
Yeah, well, maybe there aren't
any houses to rent there.
In all of Tuscany?
I wonder.
[♪]
I say we offer him $50,000.
That's it, take it or leave it.
How do we know
how severe the burns are?
Why don't we have him
examined by a doctor?
Listen, the faster we dispose
of this, the better.
This thing gets into the paper,
it'll kill us.
All right.
We'll start with 50,000
and free coffee
at all of our stores.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yes?
WOMAN:
Mr. Chiles and Mr. Kramer are here.
Send them in.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Gentlemen.
Gentlemen, come in.
Now, we don't want to take up
much of your time.
Let's make this short and sweet.
Okay.
We're prepared to offer you
all the free coffee you want
at any of our stores
throughout North America
and Europe,
plus--
I'll take it!
[♪]
JACKIE:
"I'll take it"?
"I'll take it."
Who told you to take it?
Did I tell you to take it?
No.
The Maestro didn't tell you
to take it. He wasn't there.
I thought we were lucky
to get anything.
Free coffee?
Yeah.
I don't want free coffee.
It's not hard to get coffee.
I can get my own damn coffee.
I wanted to know
what came after that "plus."
Well, I didn't hear any "plus."
Twenty years practicing law,
I never experienced
anything like this.
Look, Java World.
Hey, listen,
I'm gonna get out here.
Gonna get myself
a free café latte.
[♪]
[BEETHOVEN'S "SYMPHONY No. 7"
BLARING OVER SPEAKERS]
Hey!
Hi, Maestro.
[CHUCKLES]
Beethoven's "Seventh."
Yeah.
We were just talking about you.
You know the other day
how you mentioned there were
no houses available in Tuscany.
You didn't find one, did you?
No.
Not really looking.
Nor should you.
But are you telling me
there's not one house to rent
in all of Tuscany?
The houses are passed down
from generation to generation.
It's very hard.
I can't get a sublet,
a guest room,
a cot, nothing?
It's booked solid.
It's booked, Jerry.
How'd you get yours?
Got lucky.
Come on, Elaine,
let's take a ride.
I was about to pop in
some Verdi.
[SINGING ARIA IN ITALIAN]
MAESTRO:
Ciao.
Maybe I'll check out France!
Hey.
Hey, George,
you believe this guy?
Who?
Bob Cobb.
Bob Cobb?
You know, the Maestro.
Oh, I missed
the Maestro?
Yeah, get this.
He tells me there are no houses
anywhere in Tuscany to rent.
Hm.
You renting a house
in Tuscany?
No.
So, what do you care?
[♪]
Yeah, well, I just wish
I could figure out
if this guy's trying
to keep me out of Tuscany.
Of course he is.
There's got to be houses
for rent in Tuscany.
Do you know how big
Tuscany is?
I have no idea.
It-- It's huge.
It's probably
like North Dakota.
Oh. No way it's that big.
It's a big region.
You know how big
North Dakota is, stupid?
I don't know why
I bother even talking to you.
Hey, no one's got
a gun to your head.
All right.
So I spoke
to the security guard.
Yeah? And?
Well, it was tough
to get a good read,
but I think,
if I brought him a chair,
he'd sit.
You're gonna get him a chair?
Yep. It's really just
a question of what kind.
I'm thinking
about a barstool.
Hm. Yeah.
That'd give him some height.
Be able to check things out.
With a back or without?
Oh, I think
I'd go for the back.
Swivel?
I suppose he could swivel.
Hey, maybe a director's chair.
What do you think of those?
I think that's kind of
a pompous look.
You know, my parents
used to have a kitchen chair
that would've been perfect.
You mean, one of
those vinyl things? Yes.
Vinyl, yeah. Maybe.
How can I figure out
if there's any places
to rent in Tuscany?
Wait a minute.
Poppie's from Tuscany.
I'm gonna go call him.
Yeah. Good luck.
Hey.
I'll meet you outside.
[♪]
[BOLD, FESTIVE OPERA BLARING]
[BOTH SINGING IN ITALIAN]
Poppie told me
to talk to his cousin.
He lives down
in little Italy.
What do you think
about a rocking chair?
You can't put a limit on my
café lattes. Says so right here.
And I don't want dirty looks
when I come in here.
If I want a café latte,
you give me a café latte.
If I have any problems,
I'll get my lawyer,
Jackie Chiles,
and you'll be in big trouble.
Hey, hey, hey,
slow down.
What's the matter?
They're making faces 'cause
I've had some café lattes,
but I'm entitled to them.
I can have as many as I want.
That was the settlement.
That's it?
That's it.
Want one, George?
I can get one.
No problem.
Jerry, you want one?
They're delicious. My pleasure.
You've got to stop it.
You're-- You're all hopped up
on the caffeine.
I feel like I'm talking fast,
but it's hard to tell.
You're racing.
I got things to do.
I'll see you later. Bye.
[♪]
[BOTH MOANING]
Oh, Bob.
Bob.
Maestro.
[♪]
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Nope. Just, uh, giving a chair
to the security guard.
Did Mr. Ross
tell you to do this?
What's your name?
Evan Fain.
I'm engaged
to Mr. Ross' niece.
I'm probably gonna be taking
over this whole place someday,
so if I were you,
I'd stay on my good side.
I'm terribly sorry.
I didn't know.
Innocent mistake.
Well...
There you go.
What do you think?
Mr. Ross said this was okay?
I'm his nephew, all right?
Don't worry about it.
Go ahead.
Check it out.
Well.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
[LAUGHS]
[♪]
Uh, excuse me.
I'm looking for a Mr. Ciccio.
Sí, sí.
I'm Ciccio.
Poppie sent me
to see you, Mr. Ciccio.
Sí, sí, Poppie.
Um, did he--? Did he mention
to you why I called?
Sí.
The house in Toscana.
Yeah, right, right.
So is there anything
there to rent?
Sí.
Two million lire.
You give me the check.
No, I didn't actually
wanna rent it.
The keys.
Here are the keys.
You give me the check.
Two million lire.
Seventeen hundred American.
Molto generoso.
Ah, sí. Sí.
No, see, um...
I didn't say that
I wanted to rent it.
I was just wondering
if there were...
houses there to rent.
Sí.
This one.
Capisce?
[♪]
It's been
a rough couple of weeks.
You know,
I really needed to get away.
I told you.
It's paradise.
You were right, Maestro.
[HORN HONKS]
[MAN SHOUTING IN ITALIAN]
KRAMER:
Come on, Jerry, this guy's crazy. Get out.
I'm getting out.
You didn't have to push me.
KRAMER:
Didn't push you.
How much did
you pay that guy?
Seventy-five thousand lire.
Seventy-five thousand lire?
Are you out of your mind?
Kramer, you don't understand
the conversion rate.
Oh, yeah.
The conversion rate.
You know, I don't even know
why I brought you.
Nobody put a gun
to your head.
[WOMAN SINGING OPERA]
Not bad.
Yeah.