Have you noticed that every
little place you go into lately
has that tip jar on the counter?
What is the service
that this tip is for, anyway?
I mean, isn't the man
basically just turning around?
Isn't that really all it is?
I think we're tipping people now
just for the absence
of outright hostility.
"Thanks very much, and here's
"a little something extra
"for not taking my head
"and smashing my face
through the glass countertop.
Really good service here."
[♪]
GEORGE:
Well, currently the, uh,
doors on the bathroom stalls
here at the stadium
don't offer much
by way of privacy.
But I was thinking,
if we extend the doors
all the way down to the floor--
Are you out of your mind?
You'd suffocate in there.
You're lucky
you have doors at all.
When I was in the Army--
Hey, Costanza,
what is that you're eating
over there? Looks tasty.
I-it's a calzone, sir.
Calzone, huh?
Yeah? Let's see it.
Pass that on down.
Let's get a look.
Big Stein wants
a little taste. Come on.
Pass it down there.
That's a good boy.
Okay, let's ta--
Hey, what's in this thing?
Uh, cheese,
pepperoni,
uh, eggplant.
Eggplant, huh?
Mm, that's a hell of a thing.
All right. Back to business.
Here you go.
Very good. Very good.
Excellent.
Excellent little calzone
you got there, Costanza.
Okay. I'm a little jealous.
All right. Here we go.
[SPEAKING QUICKLY]
Like I told you last week,
the renovation of the press box
is taking too long.
Oh, you know,
that eggplant was very good.
Very good. Everybody out.
I got eggplant on my mind.
Costanza...go get me
a couple calzones right now.
Pronto. Move it out.
Big Stein wants
an eggplant calzone.
He must have one.
Everybody out.
Hurry up, hurry up.
JERRY:
So who are you having dinner with?
Oh, one of these
fabric wholesalers.
This guy, Todd Gack.
I won a bet from him.
Yeah, what bet?
He bet me that Dustin Hoffman
was in Star Wars.
Dustin Hoffman
in Star Wars?
Yeah.
Short Jewish guy
against Darth Vader?
I don't think so.
Yeah, that's
what I said.
So the bet was
the loser
has to buy dinner?
Yeah.
Huh.
What?
No, nothing.
[DOOR OPENS]
Sss.
What's with you?
Feel this.
Wow, that's hot.
It is, piping hot.
It's fresh
out of the dryer.
Here, Elaine...
you gotta feel my pants.
I'll see you later.
Oh. All right.
You don't know
what you're missing.
I'm loving this.
I am never putting on
another piece of clothing
unless it's straight
out of the dryer.
So every time
you get dressed now,
you'll use
the basement dryer?
Oh, yeah.
It's a warm
and wonderful feeling,
Jerry.
So, uh, what are
you doing later?
I got a date
with Nicki.
Oh, yeah. She's a beauty.
Oh, yeah.
She's also quite bold.
Mm. Bold and beautiful.
STEINBRENNER:
Ah. This calzone is fantastic.
And, look, the pita pocket
prevents it from dripping.
The pita pocket.
[RINGS]
Yeah, what is it,
Watson?
A lost and found,
huh?
No, I don't think
we need that.
If people can't
hold onto things, tough luck.
You got a little junk
on your lip, by the way.
You know, a lost and found
could be a good idea.
Hold it, Watson.
You like
a lost and found, George?
Definitely.
Hm.
All right.
A lost and found.
But there's gotta be
a time limit.
We're not running
a pawn shop here.
Hey, Elaine.
Jerry. Hi.
This is Nicki.
Hi.
Hello. This is
Todd Gack.
Oh, of course.
Who did you bet
was in Star Wars?
Sammy Davis, Jr.?
[LAUGHING]
So, what movie
are you guys gonna see?
Means to an End.
Oh, we were gonna see that,
too, but it's sold out.
So we're gonna see
Blame It on the Rain.
Why don't you
see what you can do.
Okay.
What's she gonna do?
They don't
have anymore tickets.
[QUIETLY]
We'll see.
Hey, Jerry,
you like cigars?
Yeah, why?
I'm going up
to Montreal tomorrow.
They sell Cubans there
dirt-cheap.
Hey, that's a nice idea
for George's wedding.
So should I get you a box?
Sure, if they're cheap,
why not?
All right, I'll buy them
and get them to Elaine.
Okay. Two tickets.
Means to an End.
Told ya.
How'd you do that?
I just talked
to the manager.
All right, enjoy...
Blame It on the Rain?
Nice meeting you.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So they're putting in a lost and found because of me.
I mean, there's a time limit,
but still.
They're really building
a utopian society up there.
And you attribute all this
to the calzone?
Yeah.
I'm like a drug dealer.
I got the guy hooked.
I'm having lunch at his desk
every day this week,
just him and me.
He doesn't make a move
without me.
It's very exciting.
Boy, with you two guys
at the helm,
the last piece
of the puzzle's in place.
Yeah.
So let me ask you a question
about the, uh-- The tip cup.
'Cause I had a little thing
with the calzone guy there
this week.
I go to drop a buck
in the tip jar,
and just as I'm about
to drop it in,
he looks the other way.
So then, as I'm leaving,
he gives me a look like:
"Thanks for nothin'."
You got no credit.
Exactly.
It's like I'm throwing
a buck away.
I mean, if they don't notice it,
what's the point?
So you don't make a habit
of giving to the blind?
Not bills.
So George,
remember I was telling you
how Nicki always
gets whatever she wants?
We're at the movies last night.
It's sold out.
Nicki goes and talks
to the manager. Right in.
Beautiful women. You know,
they get away with murder.
You never see one of 'em
lift anything over three pounds.
They do what they want,
whenever they want.
Nobody can stop 'em.
She's like a beautiful Godzilla.
And I'm thousands
of fleeing Japanese.
[♪]
Hey.
What the hell
is all this?
It's my change.
I need quarters for the dryer.
Why can't you do this
on your table?
Because I don't have a table.
Hey.
Hey, so how was, uh,
Blame It on the Rain?
Hey, thanks for getting us
tickets too.
Oh!
Elaine, let me ask you
a question.
Was the movie
part of the bet?
No, we were both
in the mood for one.
You know, Elaine...
it's not my way to intrude
on the personal lives
of close friends--
Oh, is that so?
Absolutely.
--but I feel I must inform you
that what happened last night
was more than a simple bet.
What? What are you talkin'
about? Come on.
Dustin Hoffman in Star Wars?
He made a bet
he knew he was gonna lose
just to take you to dinner.
Oh, that doesn't make any sense.
I mean, if he wanted
to ask me out,
why didn't he just ask me?
If he doesn't ask you out,
he doesn't get rejected.
He's found a dating loophole.
I don't buy it.
So, what happened
after the movie?
Nothing. He walked me home.
To the door?
Yeah.
That's a date.
No, it's not.
But I never walk you home.
That's just because
you're a jackass.
Ha!
I found a quarter. Okay.
Anybody want their clothes
heated up?
No, no, no, thanks.
So how'd you leave it
with him?
I'm supposed to meet him
to pick up your cigars.
That's another loophole.
That's two dates
without asking you out.
You're crazy.
Crazy like a man.
[♪]
VENDOR:
Number 49.
You know, uh, my last name
is Costanza.
That's Italian.
So you and I are kind of like
countrymen. Paisanos.
Six fifty your change.
Ah, yes.
And I always take care
of my paisanos,
so here's
a little something--
Antonio!
[YELLING IN ITALIAN]
Hey, hey, you steal my money?
No, you don't understand.
I wasn't taking it out.
I know what you tried to do.
Now, get out of here.
Don't come back again, ever.
Or I break your head open
like a--!
Oh, my God.
GEORGE:
I got the calzones, Mr. Steinbrenner.
Oh, beautiful.
I'm starving, George.
So I thought tomorrow maybe
we'd try a little corned beef.
Corned beef?
Meh, I don't think so.
It's a little fatty,
don't you think?
How 'bout Chinese?
Chinese?
No. Too many containers.
Big mess. Big mess, very sloppy.
We're gonna stick with
the calzones from Paisano's.
That's the ticket.
I just thought it'd be nice,
a little variety.
Mm, mm, mm,
no, no, no.
Let me tell you something:
when I find something I like, I stick with it.
From 1973 to 1982, I ate
the exact same lunch every day.
Turkey chili in a bowl
made out of bread.
Bread bowl. You'd eat the chili.
Then you'd eat the bowl.
Nothing more satisfying
than looking down after lunch
and seeing just a table.
[♪]
So thanks for dinner.
Well, I had to give you
these cigars, right?
And since we were
both hungry.
Hey, Todd...
let me ask you a question.
Um...
Was this whole bet thing
just a way of asking me out?
What?
I mean, Dustin Hoffman
in Star Wars?
[LAUGHING]
Come on.
Elaine,
that was a legitimate bet.
I lost,
so I bought you dinner.
Oh. All right.
Well, good night.
Yeah.
Hey, if you're not
doing anything Saturday night,
you wanna meet somewhere?
See, now, what is that?
Is that a date?
Why? Why can't two people
just go and do something
without it being a date?
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
It's-- It's not a date.
No way.
So I'll see you Saturday?
All right.
Pick you up at 8.
[♪]
[THUMPING, POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
You know what the posted
speed limit is on this road?
Gotta be 55.
That's right, it is.
You know how fast
you were going?
[CHUCKLING]
A lot faster than that.
Step out of the car, sir.
Okey-doke.
Can I have your license
and registration, please?
Absolutely. Nicki?
Yeah?
Would you mind bringing
the officer
the registration?
Not at all.
I got you on the radar
at 93 miles per hour.
Huh.
You must have got me when
I slowed down to take that curve
because for a while there,
I was doing well over 100.
Officer.
Hi.
Do you really
have to give us a ticket?
All right, Nick.
Let's hit it.
[♪]
Hey, buddy.
I'm waiting for my shirt.
You got your shirt in my oven?
Well, I didn't have enough
quarters for the dryer,
but this is better, anyway.
And it's more convenient.
Oh, for both of us.
And I have
a lot more control.
I got a shirt going
for 10 minutes at 325.
What's wrong
with your oven?
I'm baking a pie.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
GEORGE: Yeah.
Come on up.
What, you got cigars?
Yeah, I got some Cubans
for George's wedding.
It was more than I wanted
to spend, but what the hell.
Oh, baby, yeah.
Jeez!
What are these?
"Producto de Peru."
Jerry, if you think
those are Cubans,
you got another think coming.
Peru?
I paid 300 bucks for these.
I could have got a house
in Peru for 300 bucks.
You got rooked, buddy.
I gotta pay
this Todd Gack guy 300 bucks
just so he has some excuse
to see Elaine again
without asking her out?
That's a nice name:
Todd Gack.
What is that, Dutch?
[OVEN DINGS]
Oh, baby, here we go.
Wow, wow, wow.
Oh, mama.
Be right back.
Hey, George, hey.
Yeah.
Well, this is really bad now.
I really am
in a bad situation now.
So, what's Steinbrenner gonna do
if he doesn't get his calzone?
What's he gonna do?
That's exactly the point.
Nobody knows what this guy
is capable of.
He fires people
like it's a bodily function.
Why don't you get somebody else
from the office
to go to Paisano's?
Because before you know it,
he's having lunch with him.
You know how
interoffice politics work.
No, I never had a job.
I decided to go
with the brown ones.
What the hell is this?
Kramer's cooking up
some corduroy.
There's gotta be some way
to get back into Paisano's.
Oh, Paisano's.
That's that place
by the stadium, isn't it?
Yeah, you've heard of it?
Newman raves about it.
It's on his mail route.
He stops by there every day.
I'll see
you guys later.
What kind of pie you cooking?
Huckleberry.
[♪]
Well, you certainly are
in a bind.
Yeah, and I thought since
you go by there every day,
maybe we could
help each other out.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Let me be perfectly blunt.
I don't care for you, Costanza.
You hang out on the west side
of the building
with Seinfeld all day,
just laughing it up,
wasting your lives.
You gonna help me or not?
All right.
All right. I'll help you.
I will help you.
But I will expect
something in return.
What?
Well, for starters,
I want a calzone of my own.
All right.
And a slice of pepperoni pizza.
And a large soda.
And three times a week,
I shall require a cannoli.
A bit steep, don't you think?
You know, I hear
that Mr. Steinbrenner
can be a bit erratic.
I'd hate to see him
when he's hungry.
All right! All right!
Do we have a deal?
Just make sure
you get them to me by 1:00.
He's very regimented
about his meals.
I know exactly how he feels.
Well, nice doing business
with you.
Do come again.
[LAUGHS MENACINGLY]
Ow!
[♪]
Oh, this is nice.
Hi.
Gack, party of four.
Party of four?
Who are we meeting?
Mom, Dad.
This is Elaine.
Hello.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪]
ELAINE:
It was, uh, nice meeting you.
[CHUCKLES]
Bye, Ma.
She's wonderful.
What the hell was that?
What?
Why did you
introduce me to your parents?
They're nice people.
I thought you'd like them.
Come on, Todd.
Admit it. This is a date.
Why is this a date?
Saturday night
with your parents?
I mean, unless I'm your sister,
this is a date.
Elaine, I don't understand why
you can't meet someone's parents
without classifying it
as a date.
Well, if it's not a date,
then what is it?
It's a lovely evening together.
I don't believe this.
I'm gonna get a cab.
You wanna join me?
Nah, it's okay.
I'll just walk home.
All right.
Well, good night.
Now, what is that?
[♪]
[NEWMAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ I'm singing in the-- ♪
Hello.
What's this?
Well, I was dropping off
the calzone money for the week. Um...
Shouldn't you
be at work by now?
Work?
It's raining.
So...?
I called in sick.
I don't work in the rain.
You don't work
in the rain?
You're a mailman.
"Neither rain nor sleet nor--"
It's the first one!
I was never
that big on creeds.
You're supposed to deliver
my calzones. We had a deal.
I believe the deal was that
I get your calzones on my route.
Well, today I won't be going
on my route, will I?
Perhaps tomorrow.
But I'm paying you!
Yes, thank you.
Newman!
[♪]
Peru?
I thought you wanted
cigars from Cuba.
I did.
Well, if these aren't what
you wanted, why pay him?
Well, what could I do?
Unless...
you paid him a visit.
Okay.
Kramer?
Hey, you.
Hey.
I need you to do me a favor.
Get me lunch at Paisano's.
Wait, what happened
to Newman?
He called in sick.
Oh, right.
Yeah, it's rainin'.
Listen, can you do it?
Well, what time you want it?
One o'clock. You--
You need some money?
No, no, I got eight tons
of change.
I gotta unload it.
All right.
[RATTLING]
Hey, hold that bus!
Hey!
[♪]
Hey, buddy.
It's really
wet out there, huh?
What can I get you?
Yeah, I hear you make
a mean "calazon."
Calzone.
Yeah, calzone, yeah.
The best.
All right.
Well, uh, lay 'em on me.
I'll have three of them.
Three calzone.
Yeah, yeah.
Boy, that's a...
That's a big oven, huh?
Hey, listen, uh...
I wonder if you could
do me a favor, huh?
[♪]
Hey, Todd.
Hi, Elaine.
Hi.
You know Nicki, right?
Hi, yeah, sure.
Wait, Elaine'll settle this.
Elaine, what does the M
stand for in Richard M. Nixon?
Milhous.
I told you so.
He said it was Moe.
[LAUGHS]
You owe me a dinner.
[♪]
All right.
Your order's ready.
Three calzones...
and one hot shirt
and jacket.
Ow! Jeez.
This is all burned up.
Look at this.
What the hell do I know
about cooking a shirt, huh?
Seven fifty for calzones.
Burned up. I don't know.
What the hell is this?
Pennies?
Yeah.
You're paying in change?
That's all I got.
No, you've got to have bills,
paper money.
You can't pay with this.
That's all I got.
Then you got no calzones.
Wait a minute! Wait!
[YELLING IN ITALIAN]
[BABBLING]
[♪]
What happened to you?
Where are the calzones?
He wouldn't give them to me
because I wanted
to pay in change.
What the hell
happened to your shirt?
He overcooked it.
It's all ruined.
Your clothes smell
just like Paisano's.
There's another Italian place
right over on Jerome.
Maybe I can fool him.
You want me to say it again?
I'll say it again.
I haven't had a pimple
since I was 18,
and I don't care
if you believe me or not.
And how's this? You're fired.
Okay, you're not. I'm just
a little hungry. I'm sorry.
It's Costanza.
Where's my calzone?
It's 1:15. He's late.
[SNIFFING]
Wait a second.
I gotta call you back.
That smell. I know that smell.
He's in the building.
Costanza is in the building.
And he's not in this office.
He's got the calzone! Costanza!
I catch you,
I'm killing you, Costanza!
[♪]
[COUGHING]
Stupid cigars.
You know, if I didn't send Nicki
over to Todd with these things,
they never would have
gotten together.
These are terrible.
It's like trying
to smoke a chicken bone.
What kind of a name
is Todd Gack, anyway?
I think it's Dutch.
I gotta get goin'.
Where are you goin'?
I, uh, promised Nicki
I'd walk her dog for her.
But she dumped you.
I know, I know.
But somehow she explained it
to me, I couldn't say no.
Smells like a rubber fire.
What's that?
I said "rubber fire."
Ah-ha.
Did you end up paying Todd
for these things?
Actually, it's being
taken care of right now.
[♪]
Hey, you Gack?
Yeah.
Yeah, here's your money.
[♪]
What did he do with it?
It's gotta be here somewhere.
I'm not crazy. I can smell it.
[SNIFFS]
These clothes.
Hey, Costanza, how come these
clothes smell like calzones?
My friend put them
in the pizza oven.
Put them in a pizza oven?
What for?
To heat them up.
That is not a bad idea.
What about this?
We'll put all the uniforms
in big pizza ovens
before the game.
That's fantastic.
Keep those muscles
loosey-goosey.
This could be big.
Clean up this mess, will ya?
Big Stein's onto something.
I smell a pennant!