I always feel bad for the
silver-medal winner
in the Olympics.
I mean, how do you live
with that the rest of your life?
People are gonna keep asking,
"How much did you lose by?"
"I don't even know.
It was like: now to now.
"Like, now to now. Now.
It was like, now, now!
"Now, now.
"It was like...
"And that was it, I lost.
"I trained, I worked out,
I exercised.
"I did everything.
I was doing pushups, sit-ups.
"I never did anything
but exercise
"and work out for 20 years.
"I flew halfway
around the world:
"Da-da-da.
"And that was that.
"It was a photo finish.
"Silver, gold.
If I had a pimple,
I would have won."
JERRY:
I can't believe you write for this J. Peterman catalog.
Get this one:
"I packed my rod and reel.
"Thirty hours later,
lost in the fjord,
"a welcoming smile.
"Thank God she spotted
the epaulets
on my Norwegian
ice-fishing vest."
This catalog
is all about
how to score
in a foreign country.
Yeah. What do you do all day?
Not that much.
Uh-huh.
I thought that
new promotion
was supposed to be
a lot more work.
Yeah, when the season starts.
Right now I sit around
pretending that I'm busy.
How do you
pull that off?
I always look annoyed.
Yeah, when you look
annoyed all the time,
people think
that you're busy.
Think about it.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[SIGHS]
Yeah, you do.
Yeah.
He looks busy.
He looks very busy.
I know what I'm doing.
In fact, Mr. Wilhelm
gave me
one of those
little stress dolls.
All right.
Back to work.
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHING]
So did you come up
with a little stupid story
for the Himalayan
walking shoe yet?
No, I'm completely blocked.
In fact, I'm gonna
work on it tonight.
Oh--
Oh, no.
Oh, I can't.
I got that marathon runner
coming in tonight.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
What marathon runner?
You know,
this guy, Jean-Paul?
Jean-Paul. I met him when
I was working at Pendant,
editing a book on running.
Oh, wait. Jean-Paul,
Jean-Paul.
Yes.
Isn't he the guy--?
He overslept at the Olympics
four years ago,
missed the marathon.
Yeah, that's him.
He's from, uh,
Trinidad and Tobago, right?
Yeah, yeah. He's
Trinidadian and Tobagan.
[GIGGLING]
How do you oversleep
at the Olympics?
Oh, I know. I know.
I mean, it's like
the biggest event of your life.
You think you'd have, like,
six alarm clocks.
Paying off little kids
in the village
to come banging
on your door.
Yeah. Well, he was
pretty devastated.
I mean, this is his first
race in three years. Hm.
That's a big responsibility
on your hands.
What responsibility?
I don't have any responsibility.
What, you gotta
wake him up.
Oh. He'll get up.
Hi, Judy.
Hi, Elaine, how are you?
I'm fine. Heh.
I've seen her
in your building. Yeah.
I didn't know
she was married.
[WHISPERS]
She's not.
And the guy just took off.
Don't say anything
to anybody.
Who am I gonna tell?
I know. It's just something
you have to say.
[FLY BUZZING]
George...we just got
the final budget numbers.
We went over budget
on some of the items,
but I don't think
there's gonna be a problem.
I'll let you get back
to work, George.
[FLY BUZZING]
JERRY:
He overslept and missed the whole race.
Isn't that
amazing?
I'll tell you what happened.
I bet he got
the a.m.-p.m. mixed up.
Hm. My money's
on the snooze.
I bet he hit the snooze
for an extra five,
and it never came back on.
[DOOR OPENS]
Imagine, your whole life
riding on an alarm clock.
Alarm clocks. I never use them.
Don't trust them.
What do you do?
Oh, I have a, uh,
mental alarm.
I set my head
for quarter to 7 and...
[MAKES POPPING NOISE]
...I get up.
Always works?
Oh, it never
fails.
See, it's based on
your body clock.
See, your body has
an internal mechanism.
It knows what time it is.
Mm-hm. What's
with the bucket?
Lomez, he sold me
his hot tub.
[CLICKS]
Hot tub?
Yeah, it's in
my living room.
I just gotta
fill it.
You put a hot tub
in your living room?
Oh, it's a beauty.
It's got these high-volume
accusage jets,
oscillating and pulsating,
soothing your every
aching muscle.
That water's gonna get
over 120 degrees.
[CLICKS]
Is that tolerable?
Oh, it's tolerable.
Isn't that
the same temperature
of the coffee
that scalded you?
Oh, I think it's
a little cooler than that.
He, uh, doesn't have
any running water?
I don't ask those kind
of questions anymore.
Jerry. Jerry,
this is Jean-Paul.
Ah, hi, Jean-Paul.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry about the Olympics.
Me too.
Listen, listen.
I'm gonna go call work,
see if I can get
my deadline extended.
I-I can't come up with anything
for this thing.
Oh. Catalog-writer's block?
Yeah, that's funny.
So, what happened?
The snooze alarm,
wasn't it?
No, man, it wasn't
the snooze.
Most people think
it was the snooze.
But no. No snooze.
A.m.-p.m?
Man, it wasn't
the a.m.-p.m.
It was the volume.
Oh, the volume.
Yes,
the volume.
There was a separate knob
for the radio alarm.
Oh, separate knob.
Yes, separate
knob.
Why separate knob?
Why separate knob?!
Some people like to
have the radio alarm
a little louder than the radio.
Oh, please, man. Please!
Don't worry. It's not
gonna happen again.
Not if I have
anything to say about it.
Elaine, what's
the alarm clock
situation
at your house?
Jerry--
It's a simple question.
I've got an alarm, okay?
That old one?
Didn't I once
miss a flight to Cleveland
because of that alarm clock?
Flight to Cleveland?
It works.
Elaine.
"Singing duo,
Captain and..."?
[GROANS]
[SNAPS]
Tenille!
Come on.
Ahhh!
[POUNDING PEN
ON NEWSPAPER]
George. Uh...
I think you may be
taking work
a little too seriously.
Well, I've got a lot to do!
George, I'll tell you
what I'd like you to do.
I-I'd like you to
drop everything.
I have this fun little
assignment I think you'll enjoy.
There are some, uh, reps in
from the Houston Astros
for talks on that
Interleague Play.
And I want you
to show them a good time.
[GROANS]
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
You're 40 minutes late.
What happened?
I got held up.
Do you mind if
I heat this muffin up?
No.
What? What is
the problem?
Well, you said you were gonna
be here a certain time...
and you weren't.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. And this
all means, uh, what?
Well, it means that a man
has come from very far away
to compete
in a very difficult race.
He's put his faith in you. And
frankly, I'm a little concerned.
Oh, are you?
Yes, I am.
Uh-huh. Hey.
I'm not running
in the marathon. He is.
Yeah, I know that.
I got enough
to think about
just trying to come up
with some load of crap
for that Himalayan
walking shoe.
I mean, I've given him
a place to stay,
I'll set an alarm,
but I'm not gonna turn my life
completely upside down
for this guy.
I'm not talking about
upside down.
I'm talking about
waking him up.
Hey, Jean-Paul.
Hey, Jean-Paul,
how was your soak?
Was it a good soak?
Oh, man, very good soak.
The soak of the year.
What's burning?
Oh! My muffin.
Oh, shoot.
What happened?
Oh, I don't know.
I set this thing
for 20 seconds.
Oh, this was set
for two minutes, see?
Don't say anything.
Don't say
anything!
You mis-set the timer?
Jean-Paul, it's not
my microwave, okay? Okay?
All right, listen,
let's just go.
Come on, Jean-Paul,
let's go.
Let's go.
Okay.
All right. We'll see you
at the race, okay?
Yeah, I hope so.
Oh, that's cute.
Kramer, I'm telling you,
Elaine doesn't know
what the hell she's doing.
I gotta take over
this whole operation.
Jerry, look how
tense you are.
You need to take a soak.
I'm not taking a soak
in that human bacteria frappe
you got going there.
Oh, no, I'm telling you,
it's great.
I opened up all the windows.
The air is cold,
the tub is boiling hot.
It's like Sweden, man.
Swee-den.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Oh...
yeah.
Ahh!
Till this bastard
over here says:
"Let's call the sons
of bitches,
go visit them
in New York."
[ALL LAUGHING]
Well, we're certainly so glad
that you could make it.
I like your organization,
George. Heh-heh.
We've been talking to
a real friendly
son of a bitch
in the front office.
Wilhelm, I think
his name is.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Mr. Wilhelm, yeah.
He told us that
George Costanza's
gonna be taking us
bastards
out on
the town.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I said,
"That son of a bitch
doesn't know what he's got
in store for him."
[ALL LAUGHING]
Finish your drink?
Oh, yeah, al-almost.
Almost.
Well, let's get
that bastard
to bring us another round.
Come on, now.
You a big drinker,
George?
Well, maybe not as much
as this bastard.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I can hold my own.
[KRAMER SHIVERING]
[SHIVERING LOUDLY]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
Jean-Paul, I asked you
down here this morning
because I am
concerned.
Concerned that tomorrow
is perhaps the biggest race
of your entire career.
And the person with whom
you have chosen to stay...
is, uh...
What are you saying?
I'm saying, get the hell
out of there!
Let me put you in a hotel.
You'll be comfortable.
You'll be near
the starting line.
And most importantly,
you'll have a wake-up call,
Jean-Paul.
A wake-up call.
Wake-up call.
These people never fail.
They sit in a room
with a big clock all night long,
just waiting to make that call.
No, I will stay
with Elaine.
it would be rude.
Hey, you bastards.
Hey, so how was
the meeting?
You know, I really like
those sons of bitches.
Sons of bitches?
Yeah.
That's how they talk,
you know.
Everyone's a either bastard
or a son of a bitch.
Yeah, it's like, uh,
"Boy, that son of a bitch
Boggs can really hit, huh?"
Really?
GEORGE: Yeah.
That's how they talk
in the Major League.
Oh.
Oh, boy.
Hey-hey.
How many sweaters
you got on?
Oh. Four.
Yeah, could I have
a cup of tea?
Boiling hot.
What's going on?
[SIGHS]
I fell asleep
in the hot tub,
and the heat pump broke.
Water went down
to 58 degrees.
I can't get my core
temperature back up.
Your core temperature?
Here, feel my hand.
Yeah, feel.
This son of a bitch
is ice cold.
[PHONE RINGING]
GEORGE:
Hello.
Is that you, George?!
[LAUGHING]
Yeah, it's me.
Is this Clayton?
Well, listen,
you son of a bitch,
you know where we are?
Thirty thousand feet above
your head, you bastard. Woo!
What are they doing letting
you bastards on an airplane?
Don't they know that's
against FAA regulation?
Hush up now.
I can't hear him.
Listen, I want you guys to
send along those agreements
the minute you land.
Our boys can't wait to
kick your butts.
When's that bastard
coming to Houston?
Hey, Zeke wants to know
when you Yankee bastards
are coming to Houston?
You tell that son of a bitch,
no Yankee is ever
coming to Houston.
Not as long as you bastards
are running things.
Now, now, speak up, George.
I can't hear you.
[SHOUTING]
You tell that son of a bitch
no Yankee is ever
coming to Houston!
Not as long as you bastards
are running things.
George!
Get ahold of yourself.
Mr. Wilhelm.
What's the matter with you?
Well, I--
ELAINE:
It was a cold winter's night in Timbuktu.
Oh!
This stinks.
[GROANS]
Come on. Come on.
God!
Hello.
I'm a friend of Elaine's.
Oh, hi.
Oh.
Look at that
cute little
bastard.
You are mommy's
little bastard,
aren't you?
[LAUGHS]
What the hell are you doing
harassing my tenants?
Oh, come on,
you son of a bitch.
I'm just trying
to be friendly.
All right, that's it.
Let's go.
What? Man, I got
a race tomorrow.
Whoa. It's like
a furnace in here.
What the hell is going on?
Yeah, I turned up the heat.
Turn up the heat
in your own apartment.
I'm freezing.
I just need to get
my hot tub running.
I'm waiting
for my new heat pump.
Well, what's in this giant box
out in the hall?
Huh? Oh,
that must be it.
Yeah? It's huge.
Yeah, yeah. I got
the biggest one they had.
Yeah, it's industrial strength.
Sixteen thousand Btu's.
[RINGS]
Hello.
Yeah. I can be there
in 10 minutes.
You can count on me.
What?
I got the call.
Jean-Paul?
Jean-Paul.
JERRY:
Very lucky to find this hotel, Jean-Paul.
Man, I just want to
get some sleep.
All right. Let's
check out the clock.
Notch good.
6:50.
Volume check.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
What kind of music
you wanna wake up to?
Top 40? Classical?
Man, whatever.
How about adult contemporary?
Fine, adult contemporary.
Just pick one!
All right.
We're going with adult contempo.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[TURNS OFF]
And now the fail-safe.
The wake-up guy.
Yes, yes, the wake-up guy.
MAN:
Front desk.
Yes, this is room 419.
I would like a wake-up call
for 6:50 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
That's room 419,
6:50 a.m.
Four, one, niner.
Yes, I got it,
sir.
You only had to say it once.
I know, but it's a very
important wake-up call,
and I don't wanna take
any chances.
Every wake-up call
I make is important.
You're no more important
than any of our guests.
Well, I just don't wanna
get into a whole thing
with you here, but--
Are you through?
Yeah, I am.
But, I just--
[DIAL TONE]
Hm.
What is it?
I think I offended
the wake-up guy.
No, no.
No, no, I did. I think
he's got it in for me.
Man, he doesn't
have it in for you.
What if he doesn't call now
out of spite?
It is his job.
I'm not comfortable.
For God's sake.
Jean-Paul?
Hey, Jean-Paul?
Oh, man.
Oh, machine.
JERRY:
I'm not here. Leave a message.
Jerry. Jerry,
Jean-Paul's missing.
He's alone in the city.
Call me back.
Judy, hi. Listen--
You know, you have got
some nerve, Elaine.
I told you about that baby
in confidence.
Oh, I didn't tell
anyone.
[SCOFFS]
Well, your friend certainly
seemed to know all about it.
Jerry.
I feel much better here
at my home base, Jean-Paul.
It's a controlled
environment.
It's a marathon, you know,
26 miles.
I need to get some sleep.
Hey, believe me,
if I had been with you
there in Barcelona...
you'd be polishing
that medal right now.
I left a comfortable
hotel bedroom for this.
That wake-up guy was trouble.
All right. I'll be right back.
[MOTOR CHURNING]
Man, that thing is noisy.
Yeah, yeah. We're cranking
along pretty good!
We're almost
up to 80 degrees!
Yeah. Listen.
Do me a favor.
Set your mental alarm
for 6:30 and give me a call.
Yeah. Okay.
Wait--
[MAKES POPPING NOISE]
Done.
[JERRY'S VOICE]
He's put his faith in you. He's put his faith in you.
[JEAN-PAUL'S VOICE]
I trust Elaine. She is my friend.
I trust Elaine.
She is my friend.
[JERRY'S VOICE]
Frankly, I'm a little concerned.
[ELAINE'S VOICE]
Ugh. I'm exhausted.
I've been on this street
1000 times.
It's never looked so strange.
The faces...so cold.
[BABY CRYING IN DISTANCE]
In the distance,
a child is crying.
Fatherless.
A bastard child, perhaps.
My back aches.
My heart aches.
But my feet...
My feet are resilient.
Thank god I took off my heels
and put on my...
Himalayan walking shoes!
[MOUTHS]
Yes!
[JEAN-PAUL SNORING]
[MOTOR CHURNING]
[ELECTRICITY HISSING]
[GASPS]
4:02?
[FRANTICALLY]
8:47! Jean-Paul, wake up! Wake up!
Jean-Paul.
The electricity went out.
Wake up, wake up.
We've gotta go!
It's 8:47!
8:47?
Come on. Just put
your clothes on.
You'll get dressed
in the car.
Idiot, I trusted you!
Kramer, what happened
in the building?
The electricity went out.
Yeah, the heat pump
blew all the fuses.
What happened
to your mental alarm?
Well, I guess I hit
the snooze.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Make way. I've got--
I've got a runner here.
Get out of the way.
Make way, make way.
Make way.
He's a contender.
Hey. Hold it.
I'm late, man.
I'm in the race.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Jerry.
A wonderful driver.
Fantastic route, man.
All right, go.
It's a race! Come on!
You wanted to see me,
Mr. Steinbrenner?
Yes, George.
Come in, come in.
George, word has it you've been
cracking under the pressure.
Can't cope, can't stand
the heat. Spit the bit.
Oh, Mr. Steinbrenner,
I can explain--
We all get a little
cuckoo sometimes.
I used to be
like you.
Berating personnel,
calling managers during a game.
Threatening to move
the team to New Jersey
just to upset people.
And then I found
a way to relax.
I've got two words
to say to you, George:
hot tub.
I'm telling you, I never told
anyone about that baby.
I never even went
near your building.
Then how did
she find out, Jerry?
Maybe you should check
with the rabbi.
You want some hot tea?
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh. There's some runners.
Here they come.
[CROWD CHEERING]
There's Jean-Paul.
He's out front.
He's
leading!
Go, Jean-Paul!
Yeah!
Come on!
Woo!
[KRAMER AND ELAINE
WHOOPING]
One mile to go,
Jean-Paul.
Go Jean-Paul!
[HEART PUMPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CHEERING]
[JEAN-PAUL
SCREAMING]
How are you
enjoying it, George?
Melts that tension away,
doesn't it?
You gotta get that jet
on the good spot.
Oh, oh, ooh, ooh.
Yes, that feels good.
Yes, that's real good.
Oh, yeah, that's where
I keep all my tension.
Right under
that chicken bone.
Sometimes I'll get my wife
to just stick her thumb
right in there
like a screwdriver.
You know, the Phillips head,
not the flat one.
Oh, God. Those flat ones
frustrate me.
You got it in,
but it slips out.
You put it in again,
it slips out again.
You a single man,
George?
Well, I--
I just recently--
If you wanna get something
wild going on in your life,
you get a girl and bring her
in one of these things.
It's like four shots
of Wild Turkey.
She'll think you're
Hopalong Cassidy.
Terrible about that
Mickey Mantle, wasn't it?
You know,
we used to talk.
I don't think he liked me
very much, you know.