[♪]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Hey. Big news.
Hey.
The dog problem has been solved.
Really? What happened?
Well, there's this rabbi
in my building--
You've met him.
He's a very nice man.
Isn't he the one
with the show on cable?
Yeah. That's the one.
Right.
Okay, so I spoke to him
about the dog.
He went down,
talked to the owner,
and she agreed to keep the dog
inside from now on.
That's great.
I know!
[CAR SMASHING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
That looks pretty good.
He's in.
You know,
we haven't even discussed
George's engagement yet.
What's to discuss?
Come on.
George is getting married.
Is he happy?
[♪]
I will never understand
the bathrooms in this country.
Why is it
the doors on the stalls
do not come all the way
down to the floor?
Well, maybe so you can see
if there's someone in there.
Isn't that why we have
locks on the doors?
Well, as a backup system.
In case the lock is broken,
you can see if it's taken.
A backup system?
We're designing bathroom doors
with our legs exposed
in anticipation
of the locks not working?
[SNORTING LAUGH]
That's not a system.
That's a complete
breakdown of the system.
Can we change the subject,
please? Why?
What's wrong with the subject?
This is a bad subject?
No, fine. If you wanna
keep talking about it,
we'll talk about it.
It's not that I wanna
keep talking about it.
I just think that the subject
should resolve itself
based on its own momentum.
Well, I didn't think
that it had any momentum.
How am I gonna do this?
I'm engaged to this woman?
She doesn't even like me.
Change the subject?
Toilets were the subject.
We don't even share
the same interests.
[♪]
Yeah, he seems pretty happy.
Well, that's all
that counts, I guess.
What's the matter?
What? Nothin'.
Well, you don't seem too
enthused about the whole thing.
Well, what do you want me to do?
I thought you'd have
some reaction to it.
Well, I don't.
I think maybe
you're a little jealous.
Oh, what? You think
I wanna marry George?
No, but maybe you wish
it was you who was
getting married, not him.
Oh, please!
That is the last thing
that I want.
Oh, yeah, right.
Yeah. Right.
Laney...
Jer-ry!
You don't wanna get married?
That's right.
I don't wanna get married.
Oh, come on!
Oh, you come on!
It's such--
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Hey, Elaine, listen.
I was talking to a friend
about this dog business.
Do you realize
this is going to be
on our permanent records?
Are you aware of this?
Oh, dear.
It can never be erased.
It'll follow us
wherever we go
for the rest of our lives.
I'll never be able
to get a job!
I mean,
doesn't that concern you?
Everything I've worked for,
down the drain
because of one stupid mistake.
I mean, aren't we entitled
to make one mistake
in our lives, Jerry?
We gotta change the system.
Yes!
Well, I could care less.
I hope it is on our record.
I'm just sorry
they didn't lock me up.
[♪]
Oh, hello, Rabbi Kursham.
Elaine.
Always a pleasure to see you.
Thanks again for taking care
of that dog for us.
Elaine, oftentimes in life,
there are problems,
and just as often,
there are solutions.
Yeah, yeah, I suppose.
Elaine, you don't
seem yourself today.
You seem,
if I may say, troubled.
No, Rabbi,
I'm not myself.
Come upstairs.
We'll have a talk.
[♪]
Hey.
I want your honest opinion
about something.
Have I ever been
less than forthright?
No, you haven't.
Well, maybe you have.
What do I know?
Yeah, I probably have.
Of course I have.
What am I talking about?
Whatever. Okay.
Tell me what you think
about this idea:
extend the doors
on the toilet stalls
at Yankee Stadium
all the way to the floor.
Extend the doors
on the toilet stalls
at Yankee Stadium
to the floor.
Door comes down,
hides your feet.
Yes. I like it.
I like it a lot.
It's good, right?
[SNOOTY ACCENT]
I think it's fantastic. It's a fantastic idea.
You do?
Yes, I do.
Well,
I told it to Susan before,
and she didn't like it.
Hm.
Yeah. Not only that,
This is what she said to me:
"Can we change the subject?"
See? Now, that I don't care for.
Right.
I mean, we're on a subject.
Why does it have to be changed?
It should resolve
of its own volition.
That's exactly what I said!
Except I used the word
"momentum."
"Momentum," same thing.
Same thing.
My God!
I'm gettin' married in December.
Do you know that?
Yeah, I know.
I don't see how
I'm gonna make December.
I mean,
I need a little more time.
Look at me.
I'm a nervous wreck.
My-- My stomach aches.
My neck is killing me.
I can't turn.
Look, look.
You're turning.
Nah. It's not a good turn!
December! December!
Don't you think we should
have a little more time
just to get to know
each other a little?
You need more time,
you should have more time.
What, you think
I could postpone it?
Sure, you can.
Why not?
You're allowed to postpone?
I don't see why not.
So I could do that?
Sure, go ahead.
All right.
I'll tell you what.
How about this?
I got the date.
March 21st,
the first day of spring.
Spring, of course.
Huh?
You know, spring:
rejuvenation, rebirth.
Everything's blooming,
all that crap.
Beautiful.
She's not gonna like it.
No, she's not.
You know, I think
I'm a little bit scared of her.
She's 5'3", like 100 pounds.
I'm frightened to death of her.
Well, she's a woman.
They don't
like to be disappointed.
Especially her.
She does not like
disappointment.
Well, I have to do it.
I can't make December.
There's no way.
Right? You can see that.
I mean, look at me.
You can see. Look, look.
Can I make December?
I can't make it.
Right? Look. Look!
Yeah,
you'd better shoot for March.
March 21st. Hey, hey.
So y-you're gonna
back me on this, right?
Oh, all the way.
You are a good friend.
You know what?
Even if you killed somebody,
I wouldn't turn you in.
Oh, is that so?
Kramer, if I killed somebody,
w-would you turn me in?
[SIGHS]
Definitely.
You're kidding?
No, no.
I would turn you in.
You would turn me in?
I wouldn't even think about it.
I can't believe it.
You're supposed to be a friend.
What kind of person are you,
going around killing people?
Well, I'm sure
I had a good reason.
Well,
if you'll kill this person,
who's to say I wouldn't be next?
But you know me.
I thought I did.
[♪]
I really appreciate
your taking time
to talk with me, Rabbi.
You know,
I'm not of your faith.
In fact, I'm not
a very religious person,
but, um...
I do feel as if I'm in need
of some guidance here.
Would you care for a snack
of some kind?
I have the SnackWells,
which are very popular.
Although I think sometimes
with the so-called
fat-free cookies,
people may overindulge,
forgetting that
they may be high in calories.
No. No, thank you.
I'm not very hungry.
Anyway, um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
This friend of mine,
George, got engaged.
How wonderful.
Yeah, yeah.
Well...
for some reason,
um...
Well, I find myself
just overcome
with feelings of jealousy
and resentment.
Doesn't it give you any joy
to see your friend
enter into this holiest
of unions?
No, no.
No, it doesn't.
No joy. No joy whatsoever.
Just the whole thing
makes me...
sick.
You know, Elaine,
very often
we cannot see the forest
for the trees.
Yeah, I don't know
what that means.
Well, for example,
say there's a forest--
See, the thing is, Rabbi,
it--
It should've been me,
you know?
I'm smart. I'm--
I'm attractive. You know,
my temple has many
single functions.
Oh, no. That's okay.
My nephew Alex
is someone
who's also looking.
Perhaps I could, uh...
No, I-- I don't think so.
He owns a flower store.
Very successful.
[♪]
So you're nothing
but a stoolie. Admit it.
Hey, don't do the crime
if you can't do the time.
Another cafe latte?
Yeah.
You better believe it.
Since when are you so trendy?
Hey, baby.
I set the trends.
Who do you think started
this whole cafe latte thing?
I don't recall you
drinking cafe latte.
I've been drinking cafe latte
since the fifth grade,
and I haven't looked back.
Look at this,
Plan 9 from Outer Space
is playing tomorrow night.
One show only.
I've always wanted
to see it.
I was supposed
to see it five years ago.
I was in a Chinese restaurant
with George and Elaine.
We got screwed up
getting a table and missed it.
Well, let's do it, huh?
All right.
Look at this, Jerry.
Dropping paper on the ground.
See, that's littering.
Maybe you ought to call the cops
and turn me in.
Maybe I will.
[♪]
Hi.
Hi. How was your day?
Good. Good day. How was--?
How was your day?
Oh, it was okay.
So, what's going on?
Oh, nothing much.
You know,
went over to Jerry's,
talked to Jerry. Oh.
Oh, the Lauers
wanna get together
with us on Friday night.
The Lauers? Really?
Do you not want to go?
No. No, I want to go.
So, what did Jerry have to say?
Oh, nothing much.
No, we...
Talkin'.
Oh!
[LAUGHING]
I had an unbelievable
idea today.
Oh, yeah, the toilets.
You told me.
Yeah. No, it's not the toilets.
It's not the toilets.
It's something else.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
Okay. How about this?
All right.
Okay.
We get married...
March 21st,
the first day of spring.
What do you mean? You want
to postpone the wedding?
No, no, no. This has got nothing
to do with postponing.
I think the first day of spring
is the perfect day
to get married.
You know, spring:
rejuvenation, rebirth.
Everything's blooming.
All the--
If you don't want
to marry me, George,
just say so.
Just say so!
No, no. Still marry.
Still marry.
[CRYING]
No, you don't love me.
No, no. Still love.
Still love.
My friends told me
that you were too neurotic
and that
I was making a mistake.
No, no. No mistake.
No mistake.
No, listen, we're gonna
get married over Christmas.
It doesn't make
any difference to me.
It's fine, really.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah.
Sure, sure, Christmas.
Snow, Santa.
All that...stuff.
[♪]
JERRY:
Let me take a guess.
She cried,
and you caved.
How did you know that?
I live and breathe,
my friend.
I live and breathe.
I felt terrible.
I thought she was gonna collapse
and kill herself.
Yes.
It's very difficult.
Few men have the constitution
for it.
That's why breakups
take two or three tries.
You gotta build up
your immunity.
You see those
tears streaming down,
you don't know what to do.
It's like she was on fire,
I was just
trying to put her out.
Well, at least
you probably had some, uh,
pretty good
make-up sex afterward.
I didn't have any sex.
You didn't have make-up sex?
How could you not
have make-up sex?
That's the best feature
of the heavy relationship.
Heh. I missed out
on the make-up sex.
In your situation,
the only sex
you're gonna have
better than make-up sex
is if you're sent to prison
and you have a conjugal visit.
Yeah. Conjugal-visit sex.
That is happening.
[WOMAN SOBBING]
Look, I can tell
you're very upset,
but I'm sorry,
I'm not going.
[LOUD SOBBING]
[WHISPERS]
Wow. Did you hear that?
I can't believe this.
Look at this guy.
He's eating a sandwich.
Are you gonna eat those fries?
This is amazing.
[SOBBING]
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm going back in!
Feel better.
Poor bastard.
[♪]
Good evening, Rabbi.
Good evening. And how does
this evening find you?
Well, Rabbi, well.
I trust you're here
to see your friend Elaine?
Yeah. That's right.
I hope she's feeling better.
What do you mean?
She didn't tell you?
No.
Well, it seems the engagement
of her friend George
has left her feeling
bitter and hostile.
Is that so?
Oh, yes.
In fact,
she told me that she wishes
she was the one
who was getting married.
Really?
She came off
as pretty desperate.
I didn't know any of this.
Apparently,
she doesn't think much
of this George fellow, either.
I recall the word "loser"
peppered throughout
her conversation.
Hm.
Well, this all
comes as news to me.
[♪]
Hi.
Hi. How was your day?
Good. Good day.
How was your day?
Oh, it was okay.
So, what's going on?
Oh, nothing much.
You know,
went over to Jerry.
You know, talked to Jerry.
Um...
Could I--? Could I
talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
All right.
You see, this is the thing.
[CRYING]
I just feel like I can't do this in December.
I just feel like I need
a little more time
because I just feel like
I'm not ready yet.
I'm frightened,
and I'm scared.
And I just feel like we need
a little more time
to get to know each other.
I'm too nervous.
I'm nervous.
But I-- I can do it in March.
I promise. I promise,
no more postponements.
I just need three more months.
Please. That's all.
Just three months.
[SOBBING]
Oh, George. George.
Oh, of course.
Of course
it can wait until March
if that's what you want.
Yeah?
Oh, don't worry.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
[♪]
ELAINE:
I have that magazine article for you.
You know,
I had a little, uh, talk
with the rabbi outside.
Oh, you did?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Understand, uh,
you had a little talk
with him too.
Yeah.
We talked earlier.
Yes.
I know. I know.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Ahh.
He didn't mention...?
Yes, he did.
He told you about
the conversation we had?
Oh, we had quite
a little chat.
He told you about--?
Yes.
About how you were
very jealous of George.
How you wish you were
getting married instead of him.
He told you that?
How could he?
And it didn't take much
prodding, either, I have to say.
Can he do that?
He did it.
But he's a rabbi.
How can a rabbi
have such a big mouth?
That's what's so fascinating.
[♪]
Hey, you'd better finish
your cafe latte.
They'll never let you
in with it. Why not?
Because they don't allow
outside drinks
into the movie.
Well, that's stupid.
That's the rule.
Yeah, well, we'll just see
if we can't get around that.
[♪]
Oh, Elaine.
Come in, come in.
So nice to see you again.
Yeah.
Can I offer you
some kasha varnishkes?
No, no.
Listen, Rabbi,
I'd like to ask you
a question.
Why? Why did you tell
my friend Jerry
what I talked to you about?
Was that a problem for you?
Of course it was a problem
for me!
You-- You didn't--
You didn't tell anyone else
about this, did you?
Well, let's see.
I seem to recall a conversation
with Mrs. Winston in 1-F.
Mrs. Winston?
Yes. We were waiting
for our mail to arrive,
and I happened to mention to her
how you felt it was
never going to "happen" for you.
What about Don Ramsey?
You didn't mention
anything to him, did you?
Don Ramsey?
You know,
that tall,
really good-looking guy.
He lives on the fifth floor.
Oh, him.
Well, this morning,
I happened to find myself
in the elevator with him.
Oh, my God.
You didn't.
[♪]
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Pardon me. Excuse us.
Ooh!
[SCREAMS]
Coffee--
Arhh!
Hey! Hey, what's going on?
What just happened here?
Nothing. Nothing.
What do you got?
One of those
cafe lattes in your shirt?
I don't have anything.
What? Ask him.
All right. Come on,
coffee boy, bring it out.
What? What are--?
Come on, stand up.
Here we go.
Ahh!
[♪]
ELAINE:
The whole thing is a mess.
He told everyone
in the building.
I ran into that cute guy
on the fifth floor,
I mean, he could barely
bring himself to nod.
Elaine,
if I could say a word here
about the Jewish people.
That man in no way
represents our ability
to take in a nice piece
of juicy gossip
and keep it to ourselves.
You didn't say anything
to George, did you?
No.
About how you wished it was
you who was getting married
instead of him?
Feelings of resentment,
hostility.
Yeah, yeah.
So what?
Hey, all.
Georgie!
Congratulations!
Oh, my God!
I haven't seen you
since it happened.
I couldn't be happier for you.
Well, thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
You really,
really deserve it.
Deserve. I don't know
about "deserve."
Are you kidding?
I have seen the changes in you
the past couple of years.
Man, you have grown.
You've matured.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah,
I guess I'm getting older.
Oh. Well, I just think
it's wonderful.
Honestly.
I've gotta run.
But please, please,
give my best to Susan. Yeah.
My most just...
heartfelt congratulations.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, listen,
if you ever get a date,
maybe the four of us
could go out together sometime.
Yes.
Yes, yes. Sure.
Wasn't there some guy in your
building you said you liked?
He lived up
on the fifth floor or something?
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah.
Boy, she is something,
isn't she?
Yeah, she's something else.
Hey, so, what happened?
Did you hold your ground?
Or...?
Nope. I wept like a baby.
What?
Well, I started to tell her,
and then all of a sudden
for some reason,
I just burst into tears.
You cried?
I bawled uncontrollably.
I-I just poured my guts out.
And I'll tell you,
Jerry, it was incredible.
I never realized
how powerful these tears are.
I could've postponed it
another five years
if I wanted to.
Hey.
Sorry about that movie thing.
I was joking around.
Sorry? Are you kidding?
You did me the biggest
favor of my life.
I spoke to a lawyer.
We're suing for millions.
Suing? What for?
The coffee was too hot.
It's supposed to be hot.
Not that hot.
[♪]
The prophet Isaiah
tells us that without friends
our lives are empty
and meaningless.
Don't--
Wait a minute. No. Whoa.
That's the rabbi
from Elaine's building.
I just met this guy
the other day.
A young lady I know--
Let's call her Elaine.
--happened to find herself
overwhelmed with feelings
of resentment and hostility
for her friend.
Let's call him George.
She felt that George
was somewhat of a loser
and that she was the one
who deserved
to be married first.
She also happened
to mention to me
that her friend
had wondered
if going to a prostitute
while you're engaged
is considered cheating.
His feeling was,
they're never going
to see each other again,
so, what's the difference?
But that is a subject
for another sermon.
And now I'd like to close
with a psalm.