Gum is one of
the weirdest human inventions.
It's not a liquid. It's not
a solid. It's not a food.
What is it?
It isn't really anything.
You know, I mean, it's like
a stationary bike for your jaw.
Remember when you were in
school,
and teachers would get
all riled up
if they caught you with gum?
When you're a kid, you think,
"What is the big deal?"
But as an adult,
I can understand it
because when you're chewing gum
you don't look like you're
too thrilled with anything
anybody has to say.
"Oh, World War II, that was
an important historical event?
"Yeah, I'm sure.
"They landed a man
on the moon in 1969?
"Yeah, right.
Yeah, I buy that, teach."
Do you think she's happy?
Who?
The cashier.
Ruthie Cohen?
You know her name?
Sure.
I don't think I've ever
spoken to her.
Maybe that's why
she's happy.
Good morning, gentlemen.
What is this?
Well, it's the latest offering
from the Alex Theater.
That stinky
old movie house?
Yeah, you should smell it now.
We fixed up the place.
What? Spartacus?
Well, it's
a rare archival print.
Twelve extra minutes,
full wide-screen CinemaScope.
And if you come
to the 1:00 show,
you can hear Jeffrey Haarwood.
Jeffrey who?
Haarwood.
He was the assistant
wardrobe man on Spartacus.
He has some fascinating
insights into the production.
Why would I spend $7 to see
a movie that I can watch on TV?
Well, why go to
a fine restaurant
when you can just stick
somethin' in the microwave?
Why go to the park
and fly a kite
when you can just
pop a pill?
Listen, you guys haven't seen
Lloyd Braun, have you?
I'm meeting him here.
Lloyd? What do you
have to meet him for?
Well, he's using his connections
in the mayor's office
to get the theater
landmark status.
I thought he screwed up
the Dinkins campaign.
Well, he did. After that,
he had a nervous breakdown.
Had to spend a few months
in an institution.
Really?
Yeah, but he's doing
a lot better now.
I've taken him under my wing.
Oh, then I'm not worried.
But he still needs
all of our support.
You know, when he gets here,
treat him like he's
one of the gang, huh?
Breakdown, huh?
Hey, Kramer.
Oh, hey, Lloyd.
Hey, buddy.
How you doing?
Hi, Jerry. Lloyd.
George.
Hello, Lloyd.
How you doin'?
Well, he's doin' fine,
George.
Gum?
That's an interesting package.
Yeah, it's from China.
Go ahead, try a piece.
Tell me that's not
the most delicious
gum you've ever tasted.
Yes, yes, we shall all
try a piece
and tell you
how delicious it is.
George?
I don't chew gum.
Mmm.
It's different.
Where'd you get it?
A friend of mine in Chinatown
gave it to me.
If you want, I can ask him
where he got it.
Nah, don't bother.
It's no problem.
I don't want it.
Jerry, Lloyd says
it's no problem.
He's capable
of locating the gum.
All right.
Boy, this is--
This is delicious. Mmm.
[♪]
GEORGE:
You know what?
I think this Ruthie Cohen
gave me the wrong change.
Didn't I pay with a 20?
I'm sure I paid with a 20.
Hey.
I think I finally figured out
what the flavor is in this gum.
It's a little lo mein-y.
What kind is that?
It's Chinese gum
Lloyd Braun gave me.
Lloyd Braun.
How's he doin'?
After Dinkins
lost the election,
he had a complete
nervous breakdown.
They had to lock him up.
That's around the same time
I broke up with Lloyd.
You-- You don't think that I had
anything to do
with his breakdown, do you?
I remember when
we parted company,
I was babbling
incoherently for months.
Yeah, well, I got
news for you.
The whole time that
I was growing up,
all I ever heard
from my mother was:
"Why can't you be more
like that Lloyd Braun?"
In the end Lloyd
became more like you.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Right. Gotta get going.
You coming with us
to Spartacus?
I gotta deliver Christmas
presents to my parents.
Thought they were
out of town?
Why do you think I'm going now?
[♪]
Georgie!
Hey, Mr. Lazzari.
Back in
the old neighborhood, huh?
Yeah, yeah, just delivering
some presents to my folks.
Oh, snazzy car.
LeBaron?
Yeah, '83.
It used to belong to Jon Voight.
The actor, right?
Something like that.
Do you mind if I
look under the hood?
No, no, no, go ahead, Pop.
You always knew your cars.
Yeah.
LAZZARI:
Oh, Deena, Deena. Deena, look who's here.
George Costanza,
is that you?
Hey, Deena, come on,
give us a hug.
Oh, my gosh.
You look as pretty
as you did back in high school.
Boy, those were
some crazy times.
Yeah, yeah.
Speaking of crazy,
did you hear about Lloyd Braun?
The Alex was built in 1922
during the golden age
of movie palaces.
Minor restorations
in 1941, '47, '52, '58, '63
and currently to our
present period of time.
You're really gettin'
into this. Yes, I am.
The icing on that cake would be
getting that landmark status
from the city.
We're hoping Lloyd Braun
can pull a few strings.
Oh, can Lloyd
really do that?
Lloyd Braun can do anything
he puts his mind to.
He's fine, Jerry.
And you should say
hello to him, Elaine.
Lloyd is here? No,
I'd rather-- Right there.
Hi, Elaine.
Lloyd, yes. Hello.
Did Kramer
tell you?
We reserved some special seats
so we can all sit together.
Oh, well, ac--
Uh, actually,
Lloyd,
Jerry and I have to sit
in the front row
because, uh-- Because--
Because he--
He forgot his glasses.
So thanks
for getting us--
You know, we'll see you
afterwards. Come on.
That was odd.
Am I crazy, or does Jerry
not wear glasses?
You're not crazy.
Jerry does wear glasses.
He just forgot 'em,
that's all.
Not crazy.
We're all the way
in the front row?
Why couldn't we sit
in the special seats?
I'm sorry, but
I didn't want Lloyd
thinking I was
leading him on again.
Seeing him made me feel
very uncomfortable.
[ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
No, you don't wanna be
uncomfortable.
Poor Lloyd.
I know.
Completely bonkers.
I'm sorry. I can't be so flip
about this kind of thing.
You know,
after what happened to Pop?
Pop?
What happened to Pop?
I thought you heard.
He had a nervous breakdown
last year.
That's why I'm
taking care of him.
Oh, I tell you. They don't build
them like this anymore.
He-- He doesn't have
the auto shop anymore?
It was too much for him.
Um, I gotta go.
What?
I just remembered,
I gotta be some place.
All right, that's enough, Pop.
Put down the wrench.
Ooh!
[ADVENTUROUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE RASPING]
Pop! Pop!
LLOYD:
It's a great movie, huh?
Sorry you forgot
those glasses.
I don't know
what I was thinkin'.
How did you like that gum?
Ah...
He loved it.
Kramer, you know what?
There isn't a light
in the ladies' room.
Yeah, it's being repaired.
Oh, oh, God.
You all right?
Ugh. I sat too close
to the screen.
I just gotta stretch out
in a hot bath.
It was nice see you again,
Lloyd.
[♪]
Officer, officer,
is there some reason
this man has to always
be using a hose.
I mean, he's flooding
the sidewalk.
It's a waste of water.
Couldn't he just
use a broom?
Lady, you sold me.
Hey,
you with the hose.
KRAMER:
Here, put these glasses on.
Oh, what's this for?
Lloyd's going to be
here any minute.
So what?
Well, he thinks
you wear those.
They're from the lost and found
at the Alex.
This is ridiculous.
I'm not gonna put these on.
Oh, okay.
So he'll just think that
the two of you
didn't sit with him
on purpose.
Oh, yeah, that's very nice.
Very nice.
GEORGE:
Excuse me,
I, uh-- I was in here
this morning, and uh--
I believe I paid you
with a $20 bill,
but you only gave me
change for a 10.
I don't think so.
Oh, I think so.
And I can prove it.
You see, I was doodling
on the bill and, uh--
So if you have a 20
in there with big lips on it...
well, that's mine.
Would you mind
opening up the register?
Not unless you buy something.
Okay.
Fine, I'll buy a pack of gum.
LLOYD:
Hey, George.
Thought you didn't chew gum.
I don't.
Take a look.
I know I gave it to you.
George, would you mind?
I'm kind of in a hurry.
Fine. Fine.
Excuse me.
You think
I'm gonna forget about this?
I haven't forgotten about this.
I don't forget that easily.
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry, look who's here.
Oh, Lloyd.
How you doin'?
Got some more of that gum.
Oh, the gum.
Yeah, let's all
enjoy a chew, huh?
All right.
Ah, boy.
Sit down.
Yeah, now, see, this is what
the holidays are all about.
Three buddies sittin' around,
chewing gum, huh?
KRAMER:
Mm-mm. Yeah.
So, you know, Lloyd, he thinks
he can get more of this.
Well, Lloyd is a very
industrious fellow.
I'm sure he can accomplish
anything he sets his mind to.
Actually, the importer's
right in Chinatown.
I'll introduce you to him.
You can get it whenever.
It's not necessary.
Hey, Jerry, you know, Lloyd
wants to do you a favor.
I know that, Kramer.
Well, if you don't want to--
No, sure, sure,
he wants to.
And it's very kind of you.
Yeah, Jerry, he appreciates it.
Don't you, Jerry?
Yes, I do, Kramer.
So...
Yeah.
How about
that Elaine today, huh?
Oh, baby. What is that
all about, huh?
She was practically undressing
in front of me at the theater.
I didn't see anything.
Yeah, you really missed
a show, buddy. Woo!
Ba-boom, ba-ba-ba-boom-ba.
Yeah.
You're probably wondering
why I wanted to see you again.
Well, you know...
[SCOFFS, SNORTS]
It's understandable.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Because since
my father's breakdown,
I've become very sensitive
to the warning signs.
Warning signs?
Nervousness, irritability,
paranoia.
What?
What are you
talking about?
I-I'm not the one
with the problem.
Lloyd Braun was
in the nuthouse, not me.
Yeah, taking pleasure
in the misfortunes of others.
All my friends do that.
George, I'm only
trying to help.
I'm-- I'm concerned.
[HORSE SNORTS]
George?
Are you
listening to me?
See that woman
on the horse?
She stole $20 from me.
I might have gotten it back,
but Lloyd Braun interfered.
So again it all
comes back to Lloyd.
Hey. Hey, you!
Get back here!
Don't gallop away!
I'm on to you!
[♪]
JERRY:
So you're saying she was on a horse.
I'm telling you, that cashier
is riding horses on my money.
Well, here's what I propose.
Go down to the stables,
snoop around.
See if any high-flying cashier
has been throwing $20 bills
around with big lips.
Hey.
Well, if it isn't
Chesty Larue.
What?
I was chewing gum
with Lloyd Braun
and he was bragging
about the peepshow
you gave him
at the Alex.
Oh, God.
I lost a button.
So my blouse was wide open.
I must have left it
at the theater.
Maybe it's in
the lost and found.
Yeah, I know. I have to
go check it out.
It's a beautiful button,
too, you know.
It's antique ivory.
It was my mother's.
You know, the way you were
wolfing down that popcorn,
maybe you ate it.
KRAMER:
Mr. Haarwood,
well, what
an unexpected surprise
to have you back
at the Alex Theatre.
Well, I-I'm in a bit
of a quandary.
I've misplaced my spectacles.
Well, let's look in
lost and found, shall we?
They're half-glasses.
Brown?
Yes. Yes.
Yeah, uh...
Well, if they're
not in the box,
I'm-- I'm sure
they'll turn up soon.
Listen, could you keep
an eye on the place?
I wanna go out and get
some paraffin wax
and bring out the luster
of this vintage countertop, huh.
Yes, certainly.
Oh.
Oh, my goodness.
What a spanking button.
[ENGINE STARTS, DIES]
[HORN HONKS]
All right. All right.
[HORN HONKS LOUDER]
Hang on. It's warmin' up.
[HORN HONKING]
You mother--
Hey, what is your problem?
Oh, hello. It's you.
Listen, lady, I've got six
minutes left on that meter,
and I'm not budging until
you admit you stole my $20.
Heh-heh-heh!
You're not so tough
when you're not on your horse,
are you, Ruthie?
Your car's on fire.
Merry Christmas.
Fire!
Your hose!
Where's your hose?
Cop made me
disconnect it.
[GRUNTING]
Jeez.
What happened to your car,
buddy?
The Jon Voight car
is no more.
Well, don't you sweat it.
You can use my car
any time you want to.
No kiddin'?
No kiddin'.
Hey, thanks.
I owe you a big one.
Yeah, merry Christmas.
Whatever.
JERRY:
All right. I'm here.
Where's Braun?
What, he's not here?
Look, I'll go to
downtown to Chinatown with him, but that is it.
I'm gonna need
those glasses. Why?
They're Jeffrey Haarwood's.
Here, try this pair.
Wow,
these are really strong.
Hey, gum-buddy.
Nice frames.
You ready to go?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah,
he's all ready to go.
Anybody see Elaine today?
Oh, yeah,
she called a little earlier.
She's coming over
to check out lost and found.
Maybe I'll stick around and see
what she's wearing today...
or not wearing,
if you know what I mean.
Absolutely,
let's just stick around.
I'll tell you what,
they're expecting us.
Let me just
grab a hot dog.
Oh, yeah.
I'd like a hot dog, please.
Are you out of your mind?
Wh-wh-what's the problem here?
This hot dog's been
here since the silent era.
You'd have to be insane
to eat it.
No, no, no, this man
is not insane.
There's nothing wrong
with it or you.
Kramer, maybe--
No, no, I'll show you.
One hot dog, please.
Okay.
[SNIFFS]
Mm, doesn't that smell good?
Yeah, here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Mm. Oh, that's delicious.
This is a perfectly
sane food to eat.
Mm.
Interesting texture.
It's chewy.
I gotta get some air.
[RETCHING]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Weren't you told
to stop using that hose?
How would you happen
to know that?
Well, um, I--
You're that lady that was
talking to the cops, aren't ya?
[STAMMERING]
MAN:
Hey, Joe.
No, wait. You're soaking me.
You're soaking me.
Hey. Hey, everybody.
Whoa, Elaine.
Once again you've managed
to top yourself.
Come on, Jerry,
let's go.
The car's out front.
Lloyd?
What is Lloyd's problem?
Look, honey,
I know you're trying to get
Lloyd to notice you,
but this is too much.
Parading around
in a wet T-shirt.
[SIGHS]
I got sprayed with a hose.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry, but the
Alex is a family theater,
not one of your swing joints.
So you want my father
to pay for this?
Well, you saw him.
He was fiddling with the engine.
God knows what he did there.
And I suppose Lloyd Braun
had something to do with it too?
No, not Lloyd Braun,
but the cashier.
What cashier?
You remember the woman
on the horse?
She wanted my spot.
To park her horse?
No, she wasn't on the horse.
So your car caught fire
because of my father
and the woman on the horse.
That's right.
And him.
The man with the flowers?
Yeah, yeah, the flower guy.
Listen,
I know this all sounds
a little crazy, but--
I can't believe it.
That's Jerry Seinfeld.
Who?
My best friend.
He can explain this.
GEORGE:
Jerry, Jerry.
Over here, Jerry.
GEORGE:
It's me.
Where are you going? It's--
What are you--?
That was your best friend?
Yeah, yeah.
But he doesn't wear glasses.
That man was wearing glasses.
Don't you see? He was doing it
to fool Lloyd Braun.
[♪]
[SIGHS]
I'll run in
and get the gum.
All right.
Got any money?
Here.
I'll be back.
Look, Deena, I know you think
I'm crazy, but I'm not.
This is just a-a series
of bad coincidences.
I don't know, George.
I don't know what to believe.
Believe me.
I am not crazy.
Well...
I guess it's possible.
[GRUNTS]
Here you go.
All this?
Yeah.
A hundred dollars' worth.
I gave you a hundred dollars?
You sure did.
Am I crazy,
or is that a lot of gum?
It's a lot of gum.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Mr. Haarwood, I found your glasses.
Oh, splendid, welcome
to the Institute
for the Preservation of Motion
Picture Costumes and Wardrobes.
Ah, the I.P.M.P.C.W.
We prefer to call it
the Institute.
Is that from Henry VIII?
Yes, yes, it is.
Well, you know,
we're screening that
tonight at the Alex.
You think that I could wear
that to promote the theater?
Well, I'd love
to lend it to you,
but I doubt if it
would fit a man
of your impressive
Raymond Massey-like physique.
The only person who could
really fit into this costume
would have to be
a short, stocky man
of somewhat
generous proportion.
You don't say.
You're really helping
me out with this, buddy.
Kids are gonna
be so thrilled.
Yeah, yeah.
You really cashed in
on that favor pretty quick.
Remember, you are a king.
You must project
a royal bearing.
Oh, I'm going to give you
Wait a minute.
Let me get
a pack of gum.
Can I get
a pack of gum, please?
I beg your pardon,
Your Majesty,
but we don't accept bills
with lipstick on the president.
What?
So I had it all along.
How do you like that?
[SNORTS]
I guess I owe that cashier an apology.
Oh, my God.
No, no, Deena, it's not
what you think.
This isn't mine.
I got it from
the Institute.
The Institute.
Dee--! Deena!
Deena!
[♪]
Ah! Mr. Haarwood.
Well, you certainly know
how to dress for a premiere.
Well, thank you.
Where--? Where is your friend,
King Henry?
Oh, he ran away.
Hey, Kramer.
Let me talk to you.
You know, that button
looks very familiar.
Yes, it's-- It's antique ivory.
I-I think that's my button.
You know, I've been
looking all over for it.
Did--? Did you find it here?
Yes, it was in
the lost and found.
Shall I undo it?
Of course.
Thank you.
HARWOOD:
I'm a little ticklish.
[LAUGHS]
Tickle, tickle.
We really gotta get
that Elaine a boyfriend.
Oh, tell me about it.