I don't know why
people are surprised'
when someone gets hit
in the head with a golf ball.
Have you ever watched
these tournaments on TV?
You got 600 people
crowding around a hole that big,
and no one can believe it
when a Titleist
gets bounced off
of someone's coconut.
You know, you throw
a rock into a crowd,
that's considered terrorism.
But if you have
a nice follow-through...
you know, that's golf.
I'm always impressed, actually,
with the golf cameraman
whose job it is...
to follow the golf ball
when it's in the sky.
You know,
it's a little white ball.
It's doing 100 miles an hour
on a white background.
"I got it. I lost it.
I got it. I lost it."
Why bother?
Aim the camera at the sky,
aim it at the ground,
take a ball out of your pocket,
throw it down.
Who's gonna know
where the hell it came from?
[♪]
JERRY:
How did you lock your keys in your car?
How? 'Cause I'm an idiot.
So why don't you
get a locksmith?
I was going to, but then
I found out the auto club
has this free locksmith service,
so I signed up.
Just waitin' for
the membership to kick in.
How long has your car
been sitting
in the Yankee parking lot?
I don't know.
About three days.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yeah.
Hey.
Hello, boys.
You're not playing golf?
Yes, indeed.
Calendar says winter,
but the gods of spring are out.
And the course is open?
No, no.
I'm sneaking in
with Stan the Caddy.
We've been going through
the caddies' entrance.
Huh. No kidding.
I'll tell you something else.
Stan's advice
has transformed my game.
He's never wrong.
Oh, he thinks
eventually I'll have a shot
at making it big
on the Senior Tour.
Oh, that's my dream, Jerry.
Really?
You're getting that good?
Oh. I'm the real deal.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah, here, Stan. In here.
There he is. Yeah.
Jerry, George,
this is Stan the Caddy.
How you doing?
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Ready to hit the links, Kramer?
You betcha.
Uh, here.
What are those,
cotton pants?
Yeah, yeah.
What? Is it too cold out?
Here's what you do.
You bring
a lightweight jacket.
That way,
the sun comes out,
you play the jacket
off the sweater.
Oh, that makes sense.
That's a good call, Stan.
All right.
We'll see you guys later, huh?
Yeah, we'll see ya.
See ya.
BOTH:
Stan the Caddy.
[♪]
Elaine?
Hi!
ELAINE:
Oh, great.
It's the Braless Wonder.
Who does she think
she's kidding?
Look at her.
She's totally outta control.
I was thinking that woman
looks like Elaine Benes.
Yeah. Ha.
What have you been up to?
Just been hanging out.
I see.
Mm. Oh, listen.
I'm having a birthday party
tomorrow evening.
I'd love it if you came by.
Oh, tomorrow.
Mm-hm.
I don't know if I can.
No?
Yeah, I'm just
really, really busy.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I hope you can
get me a gift anyway.
[LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLES]
[♪]
WILHELM:
George.
Mr. Wilhelm.
I'm sorry to interrupt you,
but Mr. Steinbrenner and I
really want you to know
we appreciate
all the hours
you've been putting in.
Oh, and...confidentially,
Sozonkel, our assistant
to the general manager,
hasn't really
been working out,
and the boss thinks
you're the man for the job.
So keep it under your hat.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[SNAPS]
GEORGE:
Assistant
to the general manger!
Do you know what that means?
He could be asking
my advice on trades.
Trades, Jerry!
I'm a heartbeat away.
That's a hell of an organization
they're running up there.
I can't understand
why they haven't
won a pennant in 15 years.
And it is all
because of that car.
See, Steinbrenner is, like,
the first guy in
at the crack of dawn.
He sees my car, he figures
I'm the first guy in.
Then, the last person
to leave is Wilhelm.
He sees my car, he figures
I'm burning the midnight oil.
Between the two of them,
they think I'm working
an 18-hour day!
Locking your keys
in your car
is the best career move
you ever made.
Hey.
Hey. How you doing?
Better now.
Yeah? What happened?
You know
Sue Ellen Mischke?
Yeah, the woman
I grew up with in Maryland.
She moved here last year.
Sounds familiar.
The heiress to the Oh Henry!
candy-bar fortune?
Oh, yeah.
You mentioned her.
Yes. Yes.
I ran into her today.
This woman has never,
not once ever,
as long as I have known her,
worn a bra.
Oh. It's disgusting.
That is just shameless.
The woman's a pig.
There's no--
Who would look at her?
That's wrong. It's rude.
All right.
There's no point.
Come on!
Come on.
We're only kidding.
Stop.
You don't understand.
See, she hasn't changed at all.
She stole my boyfriend
when I was in high school.
I was at this party,
and I was dating
this really cute guy.
His name was Tom Costley,
by the way.
And she goes walking by
in this little floozy outfit,
and he follows her
right out the door.
She's your Lex Luthor.
Her birthday is coming up, see?
So I decided
to get her a little present.
What are you gonna get her?
A very traditional,
a very supportive...
brassiere.
There's nothing subtle
about that.
No, no. She might
just think it's a gift.
Have I ever bought you
a jock strap as a gift?
[♪]
Ungh. Hey-ho.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed
to be at work?
I'm thinking of getting out of
town with Susan for a few days.
Her parents rebuilt the cabin.
So you're just
takin' off from work?
Yeah, well, they won't know.
I got the car there.
Think this is
such a good idea
with you being on the verge
of this big promotion?
My presence in that office
can only hurt my chances.
[♪]
WOMAN [OVER INTERCOM]:
Sue Ellen Mischke to see you.
Sue Ellen Mischke?
Uh, all right.
Send her in.
Hi, Elaine.
Hel...lo.
I happened to be
in the neighborhood,
so I thought I'd stop in
and thank you
for your lovely gift.
Oh.
You're...welcome.
Is anything wrong?
Well, Sue Ellen.
It's, uh...
It's not a top.
It's a bra.
Oh, I know.
Thanks again.
[♪]
GEORGE:
This is the life, isn't it, huh, kid?
You wanna check out
a swap meet?
Yeah, maybe.
Where'd you get that?
Oh, it was on the windshield
of the car
when we came out
of that rest stop.
[CHUCKLES]
[PHONE RINGS]
Yo.
Hey, hey, it's George.
I need you to do me a favor.
What?
I just remembered.
There's this Chinese restaurant
near Yankee Stadium that puts
fliers on all the cars.
So?
This is what you gotta do.
I need you to go out
to the parking lot,
take the fliers off my car.
Last time you had me
throwing a rye bread
up three floors to you.
Now you want me
to go up to the Bronx,
take fliers off your car.
Where does it end?
All right, fine. I'll drive
the three hours each way,
six hours altogether,
and take 'em off myself!
All right. I'll do it!
Oh.
Hey, what are you up to?
Nothin'.
Wanna go see if there's
fliers on George's car?
Sure.
Guess I could've said just
about anything, couldn't I?
Yeah.
[♪]
[PIGEONS COOING]
Oh, man,
look at this mess.
You know what's gonna happen
if they see this?
[SIGHS]
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, we gotta
get it washed.
Oh, the keys are locked inside.
Wait a second.
What are you gonna do?
I'll just snag the lock
with this.
There we go.
Ah, this is quite a life
I lead here, huh?
[♪]
Well, George has gotta
be happy about this.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Kramer, is that woman
just wearing a bra?
KRAMER:
Oh, mama.
Kramer!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CRASH]
[♪]
ELAINE:
My God, are you okay?
Well, I got a cut on my head,
and I banged my shoulder.
I guess I have to bring his car
back up to the stadium,
if it can make it.
So how did this happen?
He was staring at some woman.
Well, I couldn't help it.
You saw what she was wearing.
What woman?
There was this beautiful woman
walking down the street,
wearing just a bra.
I can't get that image
out of my mind.
Oh...my God.
What?
Was it a tall woman,
in a black blazer?
Yeah.
[GASPS]
That's Sue Ellen Mischke.
Sue Ellen Mischke?
That's the bra
I gave her!
She's wearing it
as a top!
A woman is walking around
in broad daylight
with nothing but a bra on?!
She's a menace to society!
Hey, you know,
my arm really hurts.
Wonder if it's gonna affect
my golf swing.
Oh!
I got your message.
How's the shoulder?
Yeah, it's my left arm.
I can't swing it.
Oh, no.
Not the left arm.
What happens
if I can't play like I was?
What about the tour,
all my dreams?
[GASPS]
I got it!
Let's sue her.
Sue her?
Yeah. She's loaded.
She's the heiress to
the Oh Henry! candy-bar fortune.
No, I can't. I learned my lesson
from that coffee company.
Kramer, listen to me.
Listen. This is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Your dreams
have been shattered.
Somebody's gotta be
held accountable.
Come on. We'll take her
for every penny she's got.
What do you think, Stan?
Let's go for the green.
You know a good lawyer?
[♪]
So you're driving in the car.
You're with your friend,
minding your own business.
Yeah.
Then what happened?
Well, then we saw this woman,
and she was wearing a bra
with no top.
No top?
She didn't have a top on?
Yeah.
So I got distracted,
and I crashed the car.
Well, how would you
describe this woman?
Would you say she was
an attractive woman?
Oh, yeah.
So we got an attractive woman,
wearing a bra, no top,
walking around
in broad daylight.
She's flouting
society's conventions.
She was flouting.
That's totally inappropriate.
It's lewd, lascivious,
salacious, outrageous.
It was outrageous.
And she's the heir to
the Oh Henry! candy-bar fortune.
Could you repeat that?
I said, she's the heir to
the Oh Henry! candy-bar fortune.
Oh Henry!?
That's one of our
top-selling candy bars.
It's got chocolate,
peanuts, nougat.
It's delicious, scrumptious,
outstanding.
Have you been to a doctor?
No.
Suzy.
Call Dr. Bison.
Set up an appointment
for Mr. Kramer.
Tell him it's for me.
So, what do you think, Jackie?
I mean, we got a case?
Like taking candy from a baby.
Tk-tk!
[♪]
I think I got it.
How about this?
We trade Jim Leyritz
and Bernie Williams
for Barry Bonds.
Huh? What do you think?
That way I have Griffey
and Bonds in the same outfield.
Now you got a team!
I don't know, George.
I'm still worried
about this car thing.
Would you stop worrying?
Well, what about the fliers?
Jerry took the fliers
off the car.
I got the whole thing covered.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING,
TIRES SQUEALING]
[♪]
[KNOCKING]
STEINBRENNER:
Come in.
Ah, Wilhelm.
Mr. Steinbrenner, I am very
concerned about George Costanza.
How about a good morning?
Oh. Yes, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning to you, Wilhelm.
Anyway, his car
is in the parking lot,
the front end is bashed in,
and there's blood in the car,
and we can't find him anywhere.
Obviously, he was in some sort
of a terrible car accident,
and trooper that he is,
he tried to make it
into work, sir.
Wilhelm, listen to me.
I want the stadium scoured.
He could be bleeding to death
in the bullpen.
Put everyone on alert.
Check the area hospitals.
Clinics, shelters.
We've gotta find that kid.
Yes, sir.
We must find George.
Find him, Wilhelm!
Yes, sir!
[♪]
Excuse me,
do you happen to know
the gentleman
across the hall?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Oh. Do you know
if he'll be back anytime soon?
No. I don't.
Oh.
Is there something
I can help you with?
No, I really just needed
to speak with him.
Well, you can wait for him
in here, if you like.
Oh.
Well, maybe I will.
If you don't mind.
No, no, not at all.
Thanks.
I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What is with these people?
All day long.
Come in. Come in.
Oh. Mr. Steinbrenner, you know,
we've searched everywhere.
There's no sign of him.
Not even anyone who remotely
fits his description, sir.
Oh, my God.
Do you know
what this means, Wilhelm?
What, sir?
He's dead!
Co-- Costanza's dead!
No, no, sir, well, you see--
Oh, as quickly
as he came here, he's gone.
The poor little guy.
Easy. Easy, Big Stein,
get it together.
Okay, Wilhelm.
Yes, sir.
Find out where
his parents live. Parents.
I'm gonna personally
notify them.
And, uh, line up
some candidates
to fill that "assistant to
the general manager" position.
We can't grieve forever.
Right.
We've gotta get
back to business.
Back to business, Wilhelm!
Yes, sir!
[♪]
Well, buddy,
he's takin' the case.
Jackie Chiles is right on it!
Right on it!
He's all over it.
Oh, really?
Why? What?
What's wrong? Come on.
I don't know. So the woman
was walking around in a bra.
I mean, it's no big deal.
You're still driving.
You should've been
watching the road.
Well, your attitude
has certainly changed.
I don't think my attitude
has changed.
Listen, I'm gonna need you
to testify.
[WHIMPERS]
I don't know if I can.
Jerry, Jerry,
you've gotta testify.
Kramer, I don't think I--
Listen!
This is a million dollars
we're talking about, Jerry.
Now, this is the big league,
the big time.
Now, I need you on my team,
Jerry.
Well, I'm just not sure
how I feel about it, Kramer.
All right, what's gotten
into you? What's happened?
Nothing's happened.
[GROANS]
Dyah-gh.
Oh.
What's this?
Oh. Now, wait a second.
Wait a second.
Oh, I see. Yes.
I--
Little Miss Candy Bar
paid a visit, didn't she?
Kramer,
it is not what you think.
Ahhh! I know what I think.
I think you're gaga
over this dame.
She's twisted you around
her little finger,
and now you're willing
to sell me and Elaine,
and whoever else you have to,
right down the river.
And what about you?
Trying to bilk
an innocent bystander
out of a family fortune,
built on sweat and toil,
manufacturing quality
Oh Henry! candy bars
for honest,
hard-working Americans.
You're just out for sex!
You're just out for money!
Ahhh!Ahhh!
Mrs. Costanza?
Yes.
My name is George Steinbrenner.
I'm afraid I have some
very sad news about your son.
[GASPS]
I can't believe it.
He was so young.
How could this
have happened?
Well, he'd been logging
some pretty heavy hours.
First one in in the morning,
last one to leave at night.
That was kid a human dynamo.
Are you sure
you're talking about George?
You are
Mr. and Mrs. Costanza?
What the hell did you trade
Jay Buhner for?
He had 30 home runs
and over 100 RBIs last year.
He's got a rocket for an arm.
You don't know
what the hell you're doing!
Well, Buhner was
a good prospect.
No question about it.
But my baseball people
loved Ken Phelps' bat.
They kept saying,
"Ken Phelps."
JERRY [ON MACHINE]:
I'm not here. Leave a message.
FRANK:
Jerry, it's Frank Costanza.
Mr. Steinbrenner is here.
George is dead. Call me back.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Hey, it's George.
Where have you been?
What?
I just got the most bizarre
message from your father.
Steinbrenner's at your house.
They think you're dead.
Dead?
Yeah, and we had an accident
with your car.
It's a--
It's a little crumpled.
My car's a little crumpled?
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't know what to do, so
I put it back at the stadium.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
They saw the car, saw the blood.
They couldn't find you.
That's why Steinbrenner
thinks you're dead.
All right,
I gotta head back right away.
I-- I gotta figure
something out here.
You gotta call your parents.
I can't. Steinbrenner
might still be there.
Aren't you going to tell
them you're alive?
Oh! They could use the break.
[♪]
Elaine, do you see this?
Do you see
what I'm holding in my hands?
Yeah. It's a bra.
I saw a woman in our hallway
wearing one of these as a top.
What exquisite beauty.
I ran down the hallway
to talk to her,
but the elevator door closed.
It was not to be.
Perhaps our paths
will cross again some day.
Wh--? What is this
all about?
I want to market this item
as a new direction
in women's fashion.
Oh--
We're gonna sell this
as a top.
Here's the angle:
Zelda Fitzgerald--
Uh...somebody in the '20s,
--wearing this at wild parties,
driving all the men crazy.
Have it on my desk
by the end of the week.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in. Come in.
Mr. Steinbrenner.
[GASPING]
Is it you?
Yeah.
It's me, sir.
[GROANING]
It's been a harrowing few days.
After the car accident,
I crawled into a ditch,
and managed to survive on grubs
and puddle water
until a kindly, old gentleman
picked me up.
Grubs, huh? Got to admit
I never tasted one of those.
Anyway,
as I was lying in the puddle,
I think I may
have found a way
for us to get Bonds and Griffey,
and we wouldn't have
to give up that much.
Oh, don't tell it to me.
Tell it to the new assistant
to the general manager.
I didn't get the job?
Well, once you were dead,
we couldn't sit on our hands.
We had to make a move.
But you still have
your old job.
Of course, we'll have to dock
you for the time you missed.
We're running a ball club here.
I give special treatment to you,
everyone will want it.
Next thing you know, it's chaos.
And I can tell you this:
Chaos does not work
for the New York Yankees.
Not as long
as I'm running the show!
JACKIE:
So it was the meeting on the street
that prompted you to buy
the bra for Miss Mischke.
Would you say
that was correct?
Yes. Um--
Yes. That's correct.
And you have also
brought with you
another bra
exactly like the one
that she so flagrantly
exhibited herself in?
Yes, that's correct.
What was your golf score
the last round you played?
Before your shoulder
was injured?
Three under par.
JACKIE:
Whoo.
Three under par.
Mm.
That's what the professionals
shoot, isn't it?
Well, if they're lucky.
Would you tell this jury
exactly what you saw
at the corner
of 83rd Street and Columbus?
JERRY:
I...
don't remember.
Did you or did you not see
the defendant wearing the bra?
I don't know. Maybe.
Mr. Seinfeld,
I might remind you
that you are under oath.
Now I ask you again.
Did you or did you not
see this woman wearing a bra?
All right!
I saw her. I saw her.
[CROWD MURMURING]
And she was beautiful
in that bra!
I'm crazy about her!
I love her whole free-swinging,
freewheeling attitude!
This court will come to order.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
You may step down.
Well, Kramer,
I think we got this wrapped up.
Yeah. Yeah.
What's your read, Stan?
You're close.
You're on the green.
You just have to
go for the cup.
What do you mean?
Have her try on the bra.
See if it fits.
No, no, no, no.
Do it, Jackie.
Stan's the man.
Stan?
Who the hell is Stan?
He's my caddy.
Your caddy?
This is a big mistake.
Okay-- G-g--
Your Honor,
we request at this time
that Miss Mischke
try on the bra.
[CROWD CHATTERING]
[GAVEL CRACKING]
This court
will come to order.
Go ahead, Miss Mischke,
try it on.
[GRUNTS]
It doesn't fit.
I-- I can't put it on.
You damn fools.
Look at that.
We got nothing now.
Nothing.
I've been practicing law
for 25 years.
You're listening to a caddy!
This is a public humiliation.
You can't let the defendant
have control of
the key piece of evidence.
Plus, she's trying it on
over a leotard.
Of course, a bra's not gonna
fit on over a leotard.
A bra's gotta fit right up
against a person's skin.
Like a glove!
[♪]
Oh. Hey, Elaine.
How about some lunch?
Oh. No, I don't think so.
Great job on the Gatsby
Swing Top. It's a winner.
Yeah. Yeah, thanks.
You sure you don't wanna go?
We have reservations.
Oh, I don't think you'll have
any trouble getting a table.
Ciao.
Buh-bye.
Tsk.
[♪]