When did tick-tack-toe
become the pound sign?
That's what I'd like to know.
Why don't they call it
what it really is?
"Leave your numeric message now,
and then press Archie's head."
And what is that redial button?
Let's face it, you're either
gonna get the person,
the machine,
or they have call waiting.
Who is redialing
and redialing?
This is like the harassment key
for people in a fight, you know?
"Hey, I'm not through--" Click.
[IMITATES PHONE RINGING]
"You can't do that
to me--" Click.
[IMITATES PHONE RINGING]
"And another thing--" Click.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Hey, who would win a fight
between you and me?
What-- What do you mean?
Well, if you and I
ever got into, like,
a really serious fight,
you know,
and the punches started flying,
who do you think would win?
Well, I think
that's pretty obvious.
Yeah, me too.
JERRY: Hey, Elaine.
Hey.
Who--? Who do you think
would win a fight
between me and, uh,
Gorgeous George here?
You mean a real
"fight" fight?
Mano a baldo.
George.
Ah-ha!
Why?
George fights dirty.
Really?
What would you do?
Pull hair, poke eyes,
groin stuff,
whatever I gotta do.
Hm.
So listen,
you're not doing anything
tomorrow, are you?
Because I have an extra ticket
to the historical clothing
exhibit at the Met.
I'm sorry.
George?
Would I want to see
what Mary Todd wore
to Lincoln's funeral?
There's nobody
I can go with.
[DOOR OPENS]
You know what?
I don't have one
female friend left.
Oh, no, of course
you don't.
You're a man's woman.
You hate other women,
and they hate you.
Thank you.
So, Jerry, what time
we going to the movies?
Uh, how about
the 8:30?
Saddle up and ride.
Wanna get something
to eat first?
[MUMBLING]
No, I'm good.
I wonder if, uh, Susan...
No.
I better just go.
All right,
see you.
There's nothing
more pathetic
than a grown man
who's afraid of a woman.
Hey,
why don't you ask Susan?
George's Susan?
Yeah.
Yeah. Why not Susan?
We should be friends
with Susan.
Of course!
Susan! Oh!
Okay.
I'll see you guys. Bye.
That's gonna be trouble.
Why?
Jerry, don't you see?
This world here,
this is George's sanctuary.
If Susan comes into contact
with this world,
his worlds collide.
You know what happens then?
[IMITATES ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
I tell you I'm getting
a new telephone number?
How come?
Phew. Chicks, man.
Too many chicks
know my number.
Hey, Jerry.
How are you,
Mr. Backstroke?
Kramer, this is Ramon from
the new health club I joined.
You know what happened?
No, what?
They fired me.
JERRY:
Really?
Yeah.
Said I put too much
chlorine in the pool.
Oh.
Hey, well, uh,
stay out of the deep end.
Okay,
see you later.
What's in the deep end?
[♪]
GEORGE:
Hello?
ELAINE:
Hey, George.
Hey, Laney. What's going on?
Nothing.
Um, can I talk to Susan?
Yeah, right, hang on.
I'll, uh-- I'll get her for you.
[LAUGHS]
Seriously, what's up?
No, George, really,
can I talk to Susan?
Susan? Why?
Because I want to ask her to
lunch and to the Met tomorrow.
Oh, I don't think
you want to do that.
Why not?
Well, what would be
the point of that?
George, are you gonna
put her on the phone?
Where did this come from
all of a sudden?
George, are you gonna let me
talk to Susan, or not?
I really think I should have
been consulted about this.
Here.
Something.
Hello?
Oh, that sounds great.
I love that sort of stuff.
KRAMER:
You want to sit here?
JERRY:
Yeah.
Uh-uh-uh-uh,
over there.
Why?
The little buffer zone.
Hey, if we were
in my apartment
and were watching a movie
on the couch,
would we sit right
next to each other?
You got a point.
All right.
I can't--
What are you doing?
Well, these seats
have no lumbar.
Oh, hey, there's Ramon.
Pre-- Pretend we're talking.
We are talking.
Pretend it's interesting.
Uh, so, well,
then I had to kill him,
and, uh-- Well, the police
are still looking for me.
That sounds--
Hey! Hi, Jerry.
Oh, hey, Ramon.
I took
a lot of napkins.
You want some?
Uh, no, thanks.
Hey, uh--
Uh, is this seat taken?
No.
[♪]
JERRY:
And then the worst part is
after the movie,
he leeched onto us.
We wound up having coffee
with him for, like, two hours,
then he walks us home,
all the way back
to the front of the building.
Finally, I said, "Look, Ramon,
I gotta go to bed now."
By the way, have you spoken
to Elaine yet today?
No, why?
She called Susan
last night.
Oh, yeah. I know.
How do you know?
Oh, it was my idea.
Your idea?
Yeah.
W-w-what'd you do that,
for?
She was looking for someone
to go to the show with.
Well, that was really
a stupid thing!
You know what's
gonna happen now?
Worlds collide.
W-- Yeah!
Because this world
is your sanctuary,
and if that world
comes in contact with--
Yes! It blows up!
So if you know that,
what did you tell Elaine for?
I didn't know. Kramer told me
about the worlds.
You couldn't figure out
the worlds theory for yourself?
It's just
common sense.
Anybody knows you gotta keep
your worlds apart!
Yeah, I guess I slipped up.
Hey.
He knows
the worlds theory.
What, is it
blowing up?
Ha!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Cosmo. Go.
No, no, no, no.
Boy, this new telephone number's
driving me crazy.
Wrong numbers
every five minutes.
What is it?
Well, it's 555-3455.
555-3455.
Yeah.
Well, wait a second.
Don't you see?
That's 555-FILK.
What's "filk"?
Filk's nothing, but
555-FILM is Moviefone.
Oh, Moviefone.
Yeah, so people are just dialing
it by mistake and getting you.
So I'm filk?
You're filk.
Oh, Mama.
Well, but what about that number
Susan B. Anthony wore
to the 19th Amendment party,
huh?
Whoo!
Ay, ay, ay.
Quite the décolletage
for a suffragette.
[LAUGHS]
Well, it must have been
one hell of a party.
Whoo!
Oh, I know what
I wanted to tell you.
What?
Eh...ah, forget it.
You can tell me.
I'll put it
in the vault.
The vault?
Mm-hm.
[♪]
Hi, Mr. Seinfeld.
We heard you went
to the movies with Ramon.
Uh, well, I didn't actually
go with Ramon,
I just bumped
into him there.
It's good he has friends
like you to cheer him up.
Tell him to call us.
Tell him Dustin says, "Hello."
All right.
I gotta go.
To see Ramon?
[♪]
JERRY:
What else did you two do?
Oh, I don't know.
You know, girlie stuff.
Yeah, so, uh, flower shows
and shopping for pretty bows,
and then back to her place,
strip down to bra and panties
for a tickle fight?
That's really what you
think girls do, isn't it?
Yes, I do.
Alrighty.
Hey, you know,
George isn't too happy
uh, about your
new friendship.
Yeah? Well, I don't really
give a sh--
Hey, buddy,
what's going on?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Oh.
Here we go.
Yeah, hello.
Yeah. No, no, no.
Hold on. Yeah.
Yeah, Cupid's Rifle.
8:30, Sony Lincoln Square.
Yeah. No, no, no.
No problem. Yeah.
You're looking up movies
for people now?
I got time.
[PHONE RINGS]
Who's this?
Cosmo here.
Yeah, uh-huh.
No, no, no, no.
I'll help.
Yeah, Firestorm's good.
I saw it yesterday.
Yeah, well, my buddy Jerry's
seen it twice.
You want to talk to him?
Here.
No, I don't want
to talk--
Just tell him
about the picture!
What's the matter with you?
Stop it.
Yes,
are you still there?
Look,
I'm sorry about that.
All right, there's an 8:30
and a 10:15 showing.
[DOOR OPENS]
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Uh, that's George.
Yeah?
RAMON:
Hey, it's Ramon.
What?
Hey, it's Ramon, Jerry.
I'm coming up.
Oh. O-Okay.
W-w-what is he doing here?
Who? Who is Ramon?
He's the pool guy.
What pool guy?
Do me a favor. Just stick around
while he's here.
Yeah.
No problem.
Hey, Jerry, how are you,
crazy guy?
So, uh, Ramon, this is, uh,
my friend, Elaine, and, uh--
Yeah,
and I was just leaving.
Goodbye, Jerry.
So, uh, what are you doing
around here, Ramon?
I was in the neighborhood.
Figured I'd visit.
Oh, actually, I-- I kinda had
some things to do.
Oh. Oh, yeah? Well--
Well, where are you going?
Uh, just-- You know,
I don't know...
Stuff I gotta do.
Hey, that's cool.
I'm-- I'm up for some stuff.
All right.
[♪]
So get this.
I get down there,
and right away,
I see the drain is clogged.
It's obvious.
Can you believe that?
All right, Ramon.
I'm gonna get going.
Uh, I think we should
separate here, actually.
What are you trying
to say, Jerry?
Look, Ramon, you're nice,
but I only have
three friends.
I really can't handle
any more.
Oh, I see. It's 'cause
I clean pools, right?
That has nothing
to do with it.
You-- Oh!
[INAUDIBLE]
SUSAN:
Yeah, we got along real well.
'Cause you know, uh,
she has no female friends.
You know that,
don't you?
Something strange about a woman
whose friends are all men.
Yeah, I know.
We talked all
about that.
You talked all about that?
Oh, yeah.
Elaine opened up
her vault.
Did you just say "vault"?
Yeah. Why?
Did I use it wrong?
You got that from Elaine.
Yeah.
So, what?
Well,
it's a little strange.
You gonna start to talk
like Elaine from now on?
I don't know.
Anyway, I thought we'd all
go to a movie on Friday.
We'd all go
to a movie on Friday?
Yeah.
This is not good.
Worlds are colliding!
George is getting upset!
You have no idea
of the magnitude of this thing.
If she is allowed
to infiltrate this world,
then George Costanza, as you
know him, ceases to exist.
You see, right now,
I have relationship George,
but there is also
independent George.
That's the George you know,
the George you grew up with.
Movie George,
coffee-shop George,
liar George,
bawdy George.
I-- I love that George.
Me too,
and he's dying, Jerry!
If relationship George
walks through this door,
he will kill
independent George.
A George divided
against itself
cannot stand!
You're killing
independent George!
You know that,
don't you?
George, I don't
even want to get--
You know what word Susan
used last night, huh?
"Vault."
So?
She got that from you.
Well, I didn't tell her
to say it.
What, is she the only girl
in the whole world?
Why can't you find
your own girl?
I like her!
You see?
You see what
I'm talking about?
It's all
just slipping away,
and you're
letting it happen!
So you want to catch a movie
later?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Uh, I don't
have a paper, though.
Hm.
[IMITATING MOVIEFONE OPERATOR]
Hello, and welcome to Moviefone.
Brought to you by
The New York Times and Hot 97.
Coming to theaters this Friday:
Kevin Bacon,
Susan Sarandon...
You've got to get me
over that mountain!
No!
[IMITATES CRASHING NOISES]
[SCREAMS]
There's no higher place than...
Mountain High.
Rated R.
If you know the name
of the movie you'd like to see,
press one.
Kramer?
Is that you?
[VOICE FALTERING]
Elaine?
Uh, what time
does Chow Fun start?
[NORMAL VOICE]
I don't know.
[♪]
Well, well,
look who's here.
What are you
doing here?
You could get in trouble.
No, I don't think so,
Jerry.
You see, they gave me
my job back.
What?
I'm a pool boy...again.
Look, Ramon,
about the other day,
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I get a little crabby
on the subway.
Oh, do you?
What happened
to all the towels?
Oh, wha-- I guess
they must have disappeared.
Hey, Jerry,
look at all the towels
they gave me!
I really
hit the jackpot!
[SNICKERS]
It's been a terrible
situation down there
the past couple of days.
He's really making things
uncomfortable for me.
There's always a big
pile of dirty towels
in front of my locker.
Uh-huh.
Then when I come out of the
pool, my towel's always gone.
Oh,
so frustrating!
Tell me about it.
Oh!
So you want to join
me and Susan for lunch
at the coffee shop?
You're meeting Susan for lunch
Yeah.
I'm meeting George
for lunch at the coffee shop.
Oh. Huh.
Well, this should
be very interesting.
[♪]
Hey!
Elaine, Jerry!
Over here.
There they are,
huh?
Look who I ran into.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Come on, Jerry.
Aren't you gonna join us?
Uh, you know, I'm supposed
to meet, uh...someone.
I-- I-- I'll wait
for him outside.
Yeah, wait here.
Come on, sit down.
What's the matter
with you?
[QUIETLY]
This is gonna be ugly.
What's that, Jerry?
[COUGHS]
I said,
boy, am I ugly.
Huh.
Hey. Hey,
Georgie boy, over here!
One,
two...
three...
four.
Ho-ho!
Hey, George!
Come on, pull up
another chair.
[♪]
I see you there,
Ramon.
Hey! I'm not done.
I know what you're up to,
Ramon.
Because
I'm a member here,
this is my place
to swim.
Hey, you better cut it out,
Ramon. Just stop it.
[GRUNTS]
Ollie, ollie, oxen free!
JERRY:
No!
I think he's gonna need
mouth-to-mouth resuscitation.
Mouth-to-mouth?
Yeah.
Huh.
Well?
Go ahead.
You go.
You knocked him out.
Yeah,
but you pulled him in.
Come on, Newman.
Do it.
Nah.
He might die.
Yeah...
maybe.
ELAINE:
Yeah, Jerry,
we'll meet you at the theater.
Okay, next showing's
at 9:00.
We can't wait any longer.
Elaine,
where could he be?
It's not like George
to just disappear.
Look, let's just leave him
a note, okay?
Oh, I don't know...
Oh, come on.
"George. Elaine and I
went to see Chunnel
with Jerry."
"Love"?
Yeah.
"Love...Susan."
So eventually
these people came,
and somebody
gave him mouth-to-mouth.
He could have died.
Yeah, it was a gamble.
Why didn't you give him
mouth-to-mouth?
How can you possibly
show your face there again?
Oh, I can't.
They revoked my membership.
Newman too. No, we can't go
anywhere near there.
Hi, uh, three
for Chunnel.
Two adults...
one child.
GEORGE:
What the hell is this?
"George, Elaine and I went
to see Chunnel with Jerry."
With Jerry, huh?
With Jerry!
Great. Great!
Probably went
to the 84th Street.
That's where I always go
with Jerry.
[IMITATING MOVIEFONE OPERATOR]
Hello, and welcome to Moviefone.
If you know the name
of the movie you'd like to see,
press one.
Come on. Come on.
Using your
touch-tone keypad,
please enter the first three
letters of the movie title now.
You've selected...
Agent Zero?
If that's correct,
press one.
What?
Uh, you've selected
Brown-Eyed Girl.
If this is correct,
press one.
Why don't you just tell me
the name of the movie
you've selected.
Chunnel.
To find the theater
nearest you,
please enter your
five-digit ZIP code now.
Why don't you just tell me
where you want to see
the movie.
Loew's Paragon,
84th and Broadway.
Chunnel is playing at
the Paragon 84th Street cinema
in the main theater
at 9:30 p.m.
Yeah,
now I got you!
It's also playing
in theater number two at 9:00.
[♪]
MAN:
The English Channel Tunnel, or Chunnel, runs 32--
[WHISPERING]
Jerry. Where are you?
With two openings.
One here. And another here.
I know you like
to sit back here.
That's all we've got.
Thank you. Elaine?
MAN 2: Can I ask something?
Susan?
Shh!
I can't figure out
what's going on here.
I can't follow the plot.
Why did they kill that guy?
I thought he was with them.
No, no, that's not the guy.
That's a different guy.
What is he doing
in the Chunnel?
Would you two please...?
MAN:
Everybody out of the Chunnel!
Everybody out!
The Chunnel's gonna blow!
[EXPLOSION, PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Susan!
Jerry!
Where are you?
I-- I know you're there!
Answer me!
MAN:
Hey, sit down!
Hey, hey! Answer me!
Come on, show yourselves.
MAN 2:
Hey, we're trying to watch a movie here!
Drink your soda!
Come on. I know you're there,
laughing at me.
Laughing and lying
and laughing!
I had to go to Reggie's,
Jerry!
Reggie's!
MAN 2:
I'm gonna throw you off of there!
Where are you?
MAN 3:
Are you sure you got the right theater?
Yeah, yeah. Chunnel!
Susan!
MAN 3:
It's playing in two theaters.
Two theaters?
MAN 3:
Yeah, there's a 9 too!
Oh.
MAN:
Your car is in the Chunnel, somewhere between France--
Sorry.
[♪]
Good, huh?
What did you think,
Susan?
I don't know,
I couldn't hear anything.
The two of you
talked the whole movie.
Oh, well, come on.
Want to go grab a bite to eat?
Ah, no,
I don't think so.
Why not?
Well, you know,
all you guys do is sit around
the coffee shop talking,
sit around Jerry's apartment
talking.
Frankly, I don't know
how you can stand it.
I'll see you.
GEORGE:
I know they're in there, the three of 'em!
Laughing at me, together!
Laughing and lying!
Let's go, pal.
They're killing
independent George!
And-- And they're all
in on it!
Worlds are colliding!
[♪]
MOVIEFONE OPERATOR:
Hello, and welcome to your worst nightmare.
I know you're in there.
Cosmo Kramer,
apartment 5B.
You're in big trouble now.
You've been
stealing my business.
If you'd like
to do this the easy way,
open the door now.
Or please select
the number of seconds
you'd like to wait before
I break this door down.
Please select now.
[♪]