I love it when people
are complimented
on something they're wearing,
and they accept the compliment
as if it was about them.
"Nice tie." "Well, thank you.
Thank you very much."
The compliment
is for the tie.
It's not for you.
But we take it.
And that's kind of
the job of clothes:
to get compliments for us.
Because it's very hard
to get compliments
based on your human qualities.
Right? Let's face it.
No matter how nice
a person you are,
nobody is gonna come and say,
"Hey, nice person."
It's much easier to be a bastard
and just try
and match the colors up.
[♪]
[ELAINE SIGHS]
Look at this.
Boy.
Oh, I miss the days when they
made toys that could kill a kid.
[GASPS]
Oh, cool. Look at that!
Yeah, I'm right there
with you.
[GASPS]
That is a Schwinn Sting-Ray,
and it's the girls' model!
Oh, I always wanted one
of these when I was little.
What do you think,
Jerry?
Jerry.
Yeah?
What do you think?
Oh, yeah, it'd be great
for your paper route.
[LAUGHS]
I love it.
I'm gettin' it.
Can you help me
get it down, Jerr?
Jerry.
Your friend needs some help.
The only way
to really help her
is to just let her be.
[GROANS]
Whoa.
Hey.
[RINGING BELL]
[♪]
SUSAN:
A little baby girl?
Doctor says it could
be any day now.
So...Carrie...
you and Susan are cousins.
So your baby daughter is gonna
be Susan's second cousin, right?
Mm.
So, what does that make me?
Doesn't
make you anything.
Well, so, legally,
I could marry your daughter.
[LAUGHS]
So have you picked out
a name yet?
Well, we've narrowed it
down to a few.
We like "Kimberly."
Oh-ho. Boy.
You don't like "Kimberly"?
Eh. Ahem.
What else you got?
How about "Joan"?
Aw, come on,
I'm eatin' here.
George.
"Pamela"?
All right. I'll tell you what.
You look like nice people.
I'm gonna help you out.
You want a beautiful name?
"Soda."
What?
S-O-D-A. "Soda."
I don't know.
It sounds a little strange.
All names sound strange
the first time you hear 'em.
What, are you telling me that
people loved the name Blanche
the first time they heard it?
Yeah, but, uh, "Soda"?
Yeah, that's right.
It's workin'.
We'll put it
on the list.
I solve problems.
That's just what I do.
[♪]
KRAMER:
♪ Da da da ♪
♪ Da da ♪
Yeah, let's look at that boy.
Mmm, that's good.
You're really going to town
with that turkey there.
Oh, yeah. I got a big appetite.
Oh, Jerry.
You got no mustard.
It's on the door.
What, this yellow stuff?
No, I said "mustard," Jerry.
Dijon.
I'll still do it.
No.
That's bush league. No.
Hey, hey, wait. What, are you
just gonna leave it there?
That's like half a pound
of turkey.
Oh, no, I can't eat that.
You can't eat a sandwich
without Dijon.
Yeah, you're right.
I really should keep
more of your favorites on hand.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm gettin' a vibe here.
What, are you unhappy
with our arrangement?
What arrangement?
Well, I was under the impression
that I could take anything
I wanted from your fridge,
and you could take
whatever from mine.
Let me know when you get
something in there, and I will.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Wh-what's with your neck?
[SCOFFS]
It's still killin' me
from having to get
that bike off the wall.
By myself.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I did get her number.
I think I really
strained it. Ow.
Oh, I doubt you strained it.
Maybe you pulled it.
Yeah, maybe.
Did you twist it?
You could've twisted it.
I don't know.
Did you wrench it?
Did you jam it?
Maybe you squeezed it
and turned it.
You know what? Why don't
you just shut the hell up?
All right.
God, man, this is killing me.
Right now, I would give
that bike to the first person
who could
make this pain go away.
Ah, you're really hurtin', huh?
Oh, Kramer, it's just awful.
Mm-hm.
Well, you're arterioles
have constricted.
All right, lean forward. Relax.
What? What?
Yeah.
Encounter shiatsu.
Wait a minute.
Kramer, you know
what you're doin' here?
Oh, yeah. A wise man once
taught me the healing power
of the body's
natural pressure points.
Uh-huh.
He sells T-shirts
outside the World Trade Center.
He's a genius.
What?
Here we go. All right.
Oh! Oh!
From pain will come pleasure.
[CRACK]
Aah!
Yeah? Voilà, huh?
[PANTING]
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Wow!
That is unbelievable.
[KRAMER CHUCKLES]
The pain
is totally gone.
What's even more amazing
is his formal training
is in pediatrics.
All right.
My work is done here.
Oh, man.
Kramer, thank you.
Yeah, you can send
that bike over any time.
What?
What is he talking about?
I don't know. Oh, 'cause
you said you'd give the bike
to anyone who fixes your neck.
You really think
he wants the bike?
Oh, yeah.
But it took him
like 10 seconds.
Well, that's the most he's
worked in the last four months.
[♪]
[WHISTLING CHEERFULLY]
So I think they really
went for that "Soda."
What are you, crazy?
They hated it.
They were just humoring you.
All right. Very good.
Believe me, that kid's
gonna be called "Soda."
I can tell you I would
never name my child "Soda."
Oh, no, no, no.
No, of course not.
I got a great name for our kids,
a real original.
You wanna hear what it is?
Yeah? You ready?
Yeah?
[WOLF WHISTLES]
What is that,
sign language?
No.
"Seven."
"Seven Costanza."
You're serious?
Yeah, it's a beautiful name
for a boy or a girl.
Especially a girl. Or a boy.
I don't think so.
What, you don't like the name?
It's not a name. It's a number.
I know.
It's Mickey Mantle's number.
So not only is it
an all-around beautiful name,
it is also a living tribute.
It's awful. I hate it.
Well, that's the name.
Oh, no, it is not.
No child of mine is ever
going to be named Seven.
All right,
let's just stay calm here!
Don't get all crazy on me!
[♪]
JERRY:
"Seven"?
Yeah, I guess
I could see it.
Seven. Seven periods of school.
Seven beatings a day.
Roughly seven stitches
a beating,
and eventually,
seven years to life.
Yeah, you're doing
that child quite a service.
Yes, I am.
I defy you to come up
with a better name than "Seven."
All right, let's see.
How about "Mug"?
"Mug Costanza."
That's original.
Or, uh, "Ketchup."
Pretty name for a girl.
All right,
you having a good time?
I got 50 right here
in the cupboard.
How about "Bisquick"?
"Pimento"? "Gherkin"?
"Sauce"?
"Maxwell House"?
All right, already!
This is a very key issue
with me, Jerry.
I've had this name
for a long time.
Oh, I forgot
to call Christie.
Christie, that's the one
you met in the store?
She had this great
black and white dress
with a scoop neck.
She looked like
some kind of superhero.
And you met her
in an antique store.
I don't know how you do it.
I'm not engaged.
I got it!
JERRY: Got what?
I got the answer, Jerry.
Refrigerator problem is solved.
Oh, it's no problem.
You can take whatever you want.
I will.
But now I'm accountable.
All right,
I take what I want. Here.
And I write it down.
One cupcake.
And then I put it
in the bowl.
Voop! There.
See? Very simple.
Sort of a mooching inventory.
No, no. Not mooching.
Because at the end of the week,
you add 'em all up,
and you give me the bill.
All right.
Look, I gotta
run some errands.
When Elaine comes by
with that bike,
you hang on to it for me.
Kramer, I don't know
if you're getting that bike.
Oh, yes, I am.
We had a verbal contract.
If we can't take each other
at our word, all is lost.
[POPS]
Oh, yeah, yeah,
put that on my tab.
[♪]
JERRY:
Well, this is it.
The food is atrocious,
but the busboys
are the best in the city.
May I take your coat, miss?
Yes, thank you.
[♪]
GEORGE:
The same outfit?
The exact same outfit.
How many days was it
between encounters?
Three.
Three days.
Well, maybe you caught her
on a cusp of a new wash cycle.
You know, she did laundry
the day after she met you,
everything got clean,
then she started all over again.
Possibly, but then shouldn't
the outfit only reappear again
at the end of the cycle?
Maybe she moved it up
in the rotation.
Why? It's our first date.
She's already in reruns.
Very curious.
Indeed.
You know, Einstein wore
the exact same outfit every day.
Well, if she splits the atom,
I'll let it slide.
All right. I'm headin' home.
Did Susan change her mind
about the name?
Not yet, but she's weakening.
You know, just because
your life is destroyed,
don't destroy someone else's.
It's Mickey Mantle, Jerry.
My idol.
How about Mickey?
Mickey?
[SCOFFS]
"Mickey."
[♪]
Hey, bud.
Hey, is this
your half a can of soda?
Nope, that's yours.
My half is gone.
What?
Yeah.
I put my half a can
here in the tab.
Why, what's your beef?
You cannot
buy half a can of soda.
Well, why not?
Well, I don't wanna get into
the whole physics
of carbonation with you here,
but you know the sound
a can makes when you open it?
Yeah.
That is the sound
of you buying a whole can.
And the same goes for this.
Okay?
When you pierce the skin
of a piece of fruit,
you've bought
the whole fruit.
Not a third of an apple.
Not a half of a banana.
All right.
You bite it, you bought it.
All right. I'll make
the necessary adjustments.
All right?
Thank you.
Hey.
Oh, so how's the neck?
Nice and loose?
Lookit, Kramer,
you are not gettin' this bike.
I don't even know
why you want it.
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, it's a girls' bike.
It's a verbal contract.
We had a deal.
No, we didn't.
You take these things
too literally.
It's like saying you're hungry
enough to eat horse.
Well, my friend,
Jay Riemenschneider,
eats horse all the time.
He gets it from his butcher.
Oh, God.
This is not the point.
The point is,
you just can't have the bike.
Boy, I am really
surprised at you.
You are the last person
I figured
would do something like this.
I mean, George, yeah,
I can see that. Even Jerry.
But not you, Elaine.
I always put you up here.
They're...over here.
Now you're all-lllll
the way down here.
All right.
Yeah.
Giddi-gi.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Come on.
It's a fantastic name.
It's a real original.
Nobody else is gonna have it.
And I absolutely love it.
Well, I don't know
how original it's gonna be.
Why not?
Well, I was telling Carrie
about our argument,
and when I told them the name,
they just loved it.
So, what are you saying?
They're gonna name
their baby "Seven."
What?
They're stealing the name?
That's my name.
I made it up.
I can't believe
that they're using it.
Well, now it's not
gonna be original.
It's gonna lose
all its cachet.
I don't know how much
cachet it had to begin with.
Oh, it's got cachet, baby!
It's got cachet
up the ying-yang!
[♪]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[CRACKING]
Oh, God.
[GROANS]
Oh...God.
Kramer!
[♪]
Watch your step.
Oh! Ow!
Oh, stupid Kramer.
Excuse me. Elaine?
Huh?
Over here.
I thought that was you.
You're Jerry's friend.
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, Christie?
Yes, how you doing?
I'm fine.
Well, I gotta run.
It was good to see you.
Okay. It was, uh--
It was good to--
Good to...see you.
[BELL RINGING]
WOMAN:
Lookin' good.
MAN: Hey, Cosmo.
Hey!
Nice wheels.
KRAMER:
You got that right.
Hey, you're ridin'
a girls' bike.
ELAINE:
Kramer!
[BELL RINGING]
Kramer.
[BUZZES]
KEN:
Hello.
Uh, hello, Ken.
It's George Costanza.
I think we need to talk.
[♪]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
ELAINE:
Kramer.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Kramer!
Hey.
Yeah-- Ow! God.
Is Kramer back
from his little joyride yet?
Haven't seen him.
How's the neck?
His chiropractic job
was a crock.
I mean, it's even worse
than it was before.
I'm surprised. I would think
Kramer would have a knack
for moving pieces
of a person's spine around.
Hey, you know what?
I think I ran into that girl
from the antique store.
What's her name,
Christie?
You saw her?
What was she wearing?
I don't know. I-I couldn't see.
I couldn't look down
because of my neck.
Well, didn't you get a glimpse?
An impression?
What do you care?
Both times I've seen her,
she's worn the same dress.
[RINGING BELL]
Hey!
Oh.
Whoo!
Did you have a nice ride?
Oh, great ride.
Oh, that's good,
'cause it was your last.
What are you talkin' about?
We had a deal.
You gotta give me back
that bike.
Look at this! Look!
Ow. I couldn't even crawl
out of bed this morning.
Bed? You should be sleeping
on a wooden board for a week.
What? You never told me that.
Well, it's common sense.
Jerry, what is he talkin' about?
He's being ridiculous.
Look, Jerry,
you know the whole story.
You should settle this.
Yeah, Jerry.
Well, I'm flattered
you'd appeal to my wisdom,
but unfortunately,
my friendship to each of you
precludes my getting involved.
What you need
is an impartial mediator.
Yeah, I'd go that.
Would you go for that?
All right, I'm down.
Of course, it would
have to be someone
who hasn't heard
the story before.
Someone who is unencumbered
by any emotional attachment.
Someone whose heart is so dark,
it cannot be swayed by pity,
emotion or human compassion
of any kind.
ELAINE:
So that's the situation.
Hmm...
You present
an interesting dilemma.
Each of you seemingly
has a legitimate claim
to the bicycle.
And yet the bicycle can have
only one rightful owner.
Quite the conundrum.
As a federal employee,
I believe the law
is all we have.
It's all that separates us
from the savages
who don't deserve even
the privilege of the daily mail.
Stuffing parcels into mailboxes
where they don't belong!
Newman!
[SPUTTERS]
But...
you must promise...
that you will abide
by my decision
no matter how unjust
it may seem to either of you.
Do I have your word?
All right, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's begin.
[BELL DINGS]
Ooh!
My cocoa!
KEN:
Why can't we use "Seven"?
It's-- It's my name.
I-I made it up.
You can't just steal it.
Well, it's not
as if Susan's pregnant.
You've already
postponed the wedding.
Who knows if you'll
ever get married?
Hey, hey. Don't worry about me.
I'm not a waffler.
I don't waffle.
Look, we're both
big Mickey Mantle fans.
And we love the name.
It's very unusual.
What happened to "Soda"?!
I thought
we all agreed on "Soda."
Well, we don't care for "Soda."
You don't care for "Soda"?!
No, no.
We don't like "Soda" at all.
How do you not like "Soda"?
It's bubbly. It's refreshing.
[GASPS]
What is it?
I felt something.
Are you okay, honey?
I'm going into labor.
Oh, God. Okay,
let's not panic.
Let's just
get to the hospital.
Okay.
All right?
I got the suitcase
packed right here.
Let's go.
What about "Six"?
"Nine"? "Thirtee--"?
"Thirteen" is no good.
"Fourteen." "Fourteen."
[♪]
Are you okay, Jerry?
You seem quiet.
No, I'm just
a little, uh, worn-out.
I know exactly what you mean.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
JERRY:
What in God's name is going on here?
Is she wearing the same thing
over and over again?
Or does she have a closet
full of these like Superman?
I've got to unlock
this mystery.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
Oh.
I can't go
to the movies like this.
Do you mind if we go back
to my apartment so I can change?
Change?
Yes, I think
that's a super idea.
[♪]
CARRIE:
Are we almost there?
Just keep breathing,
okay?
Okay, okay.
Okay.
You know, the thing is,
I kind of promised
the widow Mantle
that I would
name my baby Seven.
Now's not
the best time, George.
It's just that I know her.
And, boy--
George! She's in labor!
So am I!
[♪]
Well, you both presented
very convincing arguments.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
On the one hand, Elaine,
your promise
was given in haste.
But was it not still a promise?
Hm?
And, Kramer,
you did provide a service
in exchange for compensation.
But does the fee, once paid,
not entitle the buyer
to some assurance
of reliability?
Hm? Huh?
Ahhh.
These were...
not easy questions to answer.
Not for any man.
But I have made a decision.
We will cut the bike
down the middle
and give half to each of you.
What?
This is your solution?
To the ruin the bike?
All right. Fine, fine.
Go ahead.
Cut the stupid thing
in half.
No, no, no.
Give it to her.
I'd rather it belong to another
than see it destroyed.
Newman, give it to her.
I beg you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not so fast, Elaine.
Only the bike's true owner
would rather give it away
than see it come to harm.
Kramer, the bike is yours!
What?
Sweet justice.
Newman, you are wise.
But this isn't fair.
Lookit, my neck
is still hurting me.
And now you have the bike?
Well, tell it
to the judge, honey.
I'm going for a ride.
[BELL RINGING]
[♪]
CHRISTIE:
Here we are.
Ah, so this is
the Fortress of Solitude.
Well, I guess
I'll go change.
Yes, change.
By all means, change.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
JERRY:
August 17th, 1992.
The same dress!
She never changes. Oh, my God.
She's gotta have hundreds
of these dresses.
There must be a secret stash
around here somewhere.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Are you looking
for something?
I thought you were changing.
You know, maybe we should
just call it a night.
No, no, no. Come on.
Put something else on.
It's early. Let's go out.
If it's all the same to you, I
think I'm just gonna go to bed.
You know,
I'm kind of tired myself.
Maybe I'll just sleep here
on the couch.
Then in the morning,
we'll walk out together.
Both dressed, different clothes.
I'll be in the same clothes.
You'll be in different clothes,
because it's your apartment.
We'll go downstairs.
Me in my same clothes,
you in different clothes.
Jerry...
I don't think so.
You wanna throw something on
and walk me to a cab?
Get out.
Tell me what
you're wearing tomorrow.
I'll help you lay it out
on the bed.
[♪]
Okay, breathe, honey. Breathe.
You're really being
very selfish.
It would be nice if you'd think
of someone other than yourself.
I'm having a baby!
You're not getting "Seven."
Now, get outta here!
Please, I have so little!
I'm sorry, sir. Family only.
I'm family!
I'm having sex with the cousin.
Seven! Seven!
[♪]
Hello, Christie.
I was wondering
if we could get together again.
Oh, really?
Well, you can't break up
with me over the phone.
You gotta do this in person.
It doesn't even
have to be one-on-one.
Bring a group of friends.
I just wanna see you.
Wait, don't hang up on me.
Why do you always wear the
same dress all the time? Hello?
Hey, Jerry, if you're gonna
be snackin' on these,
you can't expect me to pay
for the whole box.
All right, Hobo Joe.
I didn't wanna put a damper
on your smorgasbord here,
but it's the end of the week,
so I added up your tab.
Ah?
Yada!
I know, pretty steep.
Well, I don't
have this kind of cash.
Few do.
I'm good for it.
Yeah, well,
until this bill is paid,
the food court is closed.
Closed?
All right.
I'll get that money for you
in five minutes.
And don't eat anymore.
[♪]
Hey, that's my bike.
[RINGING BELL]
Gangway!
This is my bike.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I bought it from Kramer.
He was hard up for cash.
Fifty bucks. Can you believe it?
Of course, I had to make
some minor modifications.
You know, solid tires,
reinforced seat post,
heavy-duty shocks.
But, baby,
this is one sweet ride.
No, you gotta give me back
that bike.
Newman, give it.
Elaine! Elaine!
Okay! Help me!
Help! Help! Help!
[♪]