The pilot comes on
with his little announcements.
"I'm going over this.
I'm going over that.
"I'm taking a left. I'm bringing
it up. I'm taking it down.
I'm going right. I'm going this
way. I'm going that way."
And we're back there,
"Yeah, that's all fine.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
"Just do whatever the hell
you gotta do.
I don't know what the hell
is going on."
Do I bother him?
Do I go knocking
on the cockpit door?
"I'm having the peanuts now.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Just thought you might
like to know what we're doing."
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
JERRY:
Thank you. Good night.
Ah. Whew.
Jerry!
Hey, hey.
Sally Weaver.
Susan Ross' roommate
from college? Hello?
Right. Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, so you saw the show?
Saw it? I loved it.
Ah. And thank you
for the free tickets.
You are so funny.
Oh, thanks.
No, no, I mean it.
You're very funny.
I believe you.
Aw, anyway,
let me show you Memphis.
I am taking you out to dinner.
Oh, I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm going straight
to the airport.
Oh, that's too bad.
Susan thought we'd
really get along.
I guess 'cause
we're both wacko!
[CHUCKLES]
You know what?
Um, you have to give this
to them for me. Okay?
Here, it's a wedding present.
Oh.
Oh, and Jerry, be careful with it, okay?
Be very careful.
Uh-huh.
FRANK:
George, as you may be aware
your mother and I
are not moving
to Del Boca Vista,
Florida.
I am aware.
So I was wondering,
would it be okay
if I turned your room
into a billiard parlor?
A billiard parlor?
Regulation table, the hi-fi,
maybe even a bar.
Give it some
real...authenticity.
Well, that's-- Elaine.
Oh, hi, Frank.
Yeah, sit down. Join us, please.
Actually, I've gotta
get to the, uh...thing.
The thing's canceled.
Sit down.
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
So...
Frank, did George
ever show you that photo?
What photo?
The photo I took in Tuscany
of the little man
in front of the sign
that said "Costanza."
There's a Costanza in Tuscany?
Did he look like me?
Did you talk to him?
I didn't talk to anyone.
I was just walking by
and I saw the sign.
I thought George
might get a kick out of it.
I gotta get that picture.
Could be my cousin, Carlo.
Who is that?
When the Costanzas came here,
one brother stayed behind.
I played with his son every day
until the age of four
when we were separated.
So you weren't born here?
No.
That's why I could never
be president.
It always hurt me.
That's why,
even at an early age,
I had no interest in politics.
I refuse to vote.
They don't want me,
I don't want them!
I don't know why
you're getting all riled up.
There's probably
a million Costanzas--
Don't bring me down.
You have a copy of that photo?
No, I-- I don't, but...
well, the Maestro might.
The Maestro? What Maestro?
He's this guy
that I went to Tuscany with.
He's a great guy,
but I just wouldn't
feel comfortable calling him.
Really? Why?
Because he hasn't called me
since we got back.
I spilled wine
on this 8-by-10 photo
of one of his favorite
Italian opera stars.
Hm. Who?
You know the Three Tenors?
Yeah, Pavarotti, Domingo
and, uh, the other guy.
The other guy.
STEWARDESS:
Can I take that box for you?
Uh, well, you better not.
I'm supposed to be careful
with it.
Then I'll have to put your bag
in the overhead.
Oh, okay.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[STEWARDESS GRUNTS]
There.
JERRY:
Oh, look at this.
What?
I bought a bottle
of barbecue sauce in Memphis.
I think
the stewardess broke it
when she tried to jam it
into the overhead compartment
because of this stupid thing.
Don't press the panic button.
I'm sure that we can
still salvage some sauce.
I don't care
about the sauce.
It came in this funny bottle,
and there was a guy on the label
looked exactly like
Charles Grodin.
I see.
No, you don't see.
Because I'm going
on the show this week,
and this was gonna be
my bit on the show.
Why don't you do your material?
I'm out.
[SIGHS]
Boy, you better get to work.
Thanks for the tip.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, buddies.
Hey. Hey, this is for you.
It's from Susan's roommate,
Sally.
Oh, yeah,
Sally called Susan.
Said you guys
really hit it off.
Nobody hit anything off.
She just gave me the box.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, I'm salvaging the sauce.
What's a matter with you?
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on, come on.
Jerry, why don't you do a bit
on Styrofoam?
Like what?
Well, you know,
"What is all this stuff?
"Why do we need this stuff?
And why do they make 'em
so small?"
Wh--? Where is the punchline?
It's all attitude.
This is certainly a crappy gift.
A doormat?
That's what she had me lug up
from Memphis?
Pretty chintzy, huh?
Considering the money she makes.
She's a big executive
for Federal Express.
Federal Express?
Is she out of her mind?
Why didn't she just ship it?
Look, it's personalized.
"The Costanzas."
No. No, forget it.
I don't want it.
Let's just get rid of it.
Maybe your father
would be interested in that.
I doubt it.
You know what he's doing now?
He's putting a pool table
in my old bedroom.
Oh, yeah?
Well, maybe I'll go
out there
and knock a few balls
around with him.
You know,
show him a thing or two.
So, what's your game?
What do you like to play?
Eight ball.
No, nothing doing.
Let's you and me play a game
of straight pool. Hm?
You like to gamble, Cosmo, huh?
Yeah, now and then.
You know how it is.
Five dollars a game, huh?
I'll break.
Okay.
That's it. That's it.
Seven ball.
GEORGE:
What's, uh...?
What's all this?
Oh, I'm just moving in
some more of my stuff.
[MUTTERS]
More of her stuff.
SUSAN:
Oh, I put up my doll collection.
Oh, my God.
What is that?
What? What is it?
This doll looks like my mother.
George, it's a doll.
I know it's a doll.
But it looks like my mother.
Oh, get outta here.
Seven, low.
ESTELLE:
What's going on in here?
Are you two still playing?
You've been up here
three hours.
We haven't finished
the first game.
First game?
Well, we're still, uh, learning
the subtleties of the table.
He knows the Maestro.
He could have the picture.
Oh, forget about it.
It's not your cousin.
You don't know that!
We gonna go see him, huh?
Soon as the game is over.
Oh, boy.
Eleven, corner pocket.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
What is this thing doing here?
Oh, I used to love to sleep
with my dolls
when I was a little girl.
I'm-- I'm sorry,
I can't do this.
Why?
I feel like I'm in bed
with my mother.
Stop it, hm?
Eh--
JERRY:
Hey, Elaine,
you have got to buy this new
electric toothbrush I just got.
The Oro-Dent.
Oh, yeah?
Every time you use it,
you feel like you came
from the dentist.
That's dynamite.
Wanna come see me
on The Charles Grodin Show
tomorrow?
Who else is on the show?
One of the Three Tenors.
The Three Tenors? Which one?
Uh, it's not Pavarotti,
it's not Domingo--
The other guy?
Yeah, the other guy.
Ah! My God!
I can't believe the other guy
is gonna be on the show.
Why?
Because I ruined this autographed picture of him
that belonged
to the Maestro.
You think I could go?
I could get his autograph?
Why not?
[GASPS]
Wow. The other guy.
Hey, you look awful.
I'm on no sleep, bro.
Problem in the bedroom?
Susan has this doll collection.
One of the dolls looks
exactly like my mother.
She likes to sleep with it.
You were in bed with your mother
last night?
It felt like it.
I tell you,
this doll is pretty spooky.
It's really freaking me out,
man.
And now I gotta go back out
there and pick up this doormat.
Thought you didn't
want the doormat.
I don't.
Susan wants to have it out
when Sally comes tomorrow.
Sally?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
She's coming to New York?
Yeah, Susan said
you'd be excited.
Excited?
I'm gonna kill her.
She knew she was coming here,
and she made me carry that box?
Who is Sally?
Susan's college roommate.
It's because of her
that bottle got broke
that I was gonna give
to Charles Grodin on his show.
Call her up and tell her
to bring you another one.
So? She'll be delighted
to talk to you.
Oh, I will. Don't worry.
I'll have her bring up
a whole case of the stuff.
It'll be really heavy.
Let's see if she likes
sitting on a plane
with a big box
on her lap.
That sounds pretty juvenile.
Hey, a dinosaur!
FRANK:
His name was
Carlo Costanza.
We played together
every day until I was 4.
If I could look at your photos,
maybe I can recognize him.
Unfortunately,
those photographs are at home.
Well, listen.
If you bring 'em by,
maybe we could interest you
in a game of pool.
Yeah. Frank here,
he's got his own billiard room.
Yes, it's, uh--
It's, uh...
What do you call it,
Kramer?
It's a billiard room.
No.
Th--
What?
The name?
The billiard--
Not billiard--
Not the billiards-- It was--
Come on, already. Come on.
We call it the--
The place to be.
The place to be!
Yes, it's the place to be.
Then I shall be there.
Now, gentlemen,
if you will excuse me,
I must prepare for the symphony.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Oh.
My pants.
It's an old conductor's trick
I learned from
Leonard Bernstein.
Really?
You keep a perfect crease
by not sitting in them
before the performance.
That is...
Ho, ho.
That's good thinking.
GEORGE:
You see?
It doesn't look
exactly like her.
Jerry, come on.
If my mother keeps shrinking,
this is exactly what she's
gonna look like in 10 years.
Why don't you just
get rid of it? I...tried.
I almost threw it down
the incinerator,
but I couldn't do it.
The guilt was
too overwhelming.
Susan's so attached
to this thing.
Well, where you going?
Don't take your dolly
and go home.
Hi, Elaine.
[ELAINE SCREAMS]
Did you see that?
I'm just glad it's outta here.
What's that?
Oh, it's a poster
of the Three Tenors.
Oh.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah.
SALLY: It's Sally!
Did you bring
the barbecue sauce?
A whole case.
Excellent.
So did you buy that electric
toothbrush I told you about?
No.
How come?
I told you, it's fantastic.
Eh, I like mine.
I've had yours.
I'm telling you,
this one is 10 times better.
Don't you believe me?
I don't want it.
I don't understand
this attitude.
Why wouldn't you wanna
get something that's better
if I'm telling you
it's better?
And it's not a little better.
It's much better!
It doesn't matter to me.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
Well, here I am.
Oh, hi.
Elaine, this is Sally.
Hi.
How was your flight?
Uncomfortable?
The seat next to me was empty
so there was no problem at all.
Oh.
Wait.
This isn't the sauce
that I asked for.
That's right.
It's a special gourmet sauce.
The pride of Memphis.
No, no, I wanted the one
in the little bottle
with the guy on it
that looks like Charles Grodin.
This is much better.
And frankly, in Memphis,
we think that other sauce
is kind of a joke.
I know it's a joke.
It's supposed to be a joke.
Now, I'm going on The Charles
Grodin Show with nothin'.
Nothin'!
You could just
do your material.
I don't have any material!
He's got nothin'!
[♪]
ESTELLE:
Georgie,
don't eat with your hands!
Why do you eat so fast?
You can't even taste it!
Don't tell me
how to eat.
Still wearing that shirt?
You've had it
for five years already.
Why don't you buy
a new shirt!?!
Because I like this one!
Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
Oh, hi, Deena.
That man should really be
in a sanitarium.
KRAMER:
Oh, this is remarkable.
I'm lounging and yet my pants
remain perfectly creased.
It's him!
It's Carlo Costanza.
KRAMER:
Come on. Are you sure?
I'd know him anywhere.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I've seen that man in Tuscany.
Eccentric fellow.
Reputation of being
kind of a village idiot.
I still say we're related.
Oh, I love this piece.
All right, come on, Frank,
it's your shot.
I can't make anything.
Because you don't know
how to follow through correct.
Follow through?
What do you mean?
Right here, let me show you.
Take hold of your stick.
Yeah, I got it.
All right, get down.
Right.
Bring it back slowly.
It's a little unnatural,
but I think I'm getting
the hang of it.
Oh, my God.
JERRY:
I'm such an idiot.
I was gonna do
this whole bit on that bottle.
Now I got nothing to talk about.
Have you ever considered writing
new material?
Maybe if I didn't have
so many people
in my apartment all the time,
I'd be able
to get some work done.
Me? Are you talking about me?
No, you're never here.
Boy, that doll was
really freaky, wasn't it?
Yeah, really.
Hey, maybe I could talk
about that on the show.
What?
Show the doll. Show a picture
of George's mother.
It's pretty funny.
I'm gonna call him.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hello, Susan, it's Jerry.
Hi, Jerry, it's Sally.
Oh.
Is George there?
No, but he should be home soon.
Listen, this is important.
Tell him to meet me
at the TV studio
with a picture of his mother
and that doll
that looks like her.
Is this for your comedy routine?
Yes.
Don't worry, I'm on the case.
I, uh...think
I'll get some air.
Yeah.
This is no good.
Hey, the baton.
Yeah, I've got a hunch, fat man,
I can't miss.
Thirteen, in the side.
Giddyup.
Six, in the corner.
This table's mine.
You know where it's going.
Hey.
Is George here?
Not yet.
The other guy.
[GASPS]
It's...
...you.
It's really you. Oh.
I'm-- I'm such
a huge fan of yours.
Would you mind signing
this poster for me?
My pleasure.
Oh, thank you so much.
Here you go.
[GIGGLES]
Thank you so much, Mr. Camaro.
Mr. Casea.
Well, whatever.
I'm gonna take this
to the Maestro.
He's playing at
the Queens Convalescent Center.
Yeah, that's a hell of a gig.
Hey, look,
I got something for you.
The Oro-Dent.
Ohhh...
Thank you.
Huh.
What--? Why does a toothbrush
come in such a big box?
Well, it's a delicate mechanism,
it needs a lot of packing.
How am I supposed to carry
this thing?
What are you doing?
Well, I wanna sit down.
So?
It's a trick I just learned
from Kramer.
Keeps the crease in the pants.
Madam, you have been
an extremely gracious hostess.
[GIGGLES]
Oh.
Thank you, Maestro.
Here, take a look at this.
Yeah, what is it?
It's Carlo. I found him.
You've been cooped up
in this room too long.
You never support me!
Let's see what George
says about this.
Where are my pants?
Oh, beautiful.
SALLY:
Hey there, Mr. Hairy Legs.
Where's George?
Don't worry,
I brought your doll.
Ta-da!
No, that's the wrong doll.
Jerry, I saw the doll
you were talking about.
Not funny.
This doll is much funnier.
Look, it has a little bow tie
and a cute little hat.
I think it's a riot!
[SOFTLY]
This is a nightmare.
Well, I'll be watching.
Don't screw up.
Too much sauce.
My pants!
Mr. Seinfeld, you're on.
[KNOCKING]
Elaine. What a surprise.
I-I-I know you're very busy,
but I just wanted to come by
and give you this.
Oh, Oro-Dent,
that electric toothbrush.
I've heard
so much about it.
No, no, no.
Not the toothbrush. This.
Oh.
What a sweet gesture.
An autographed poster
of my favorite tenor with...
those two other guys.
Oh, Elaine,
this is magnifico.
I just felt so bad
about what happened in Tuscany--
MAN:
Maestro, you're on.
Oh.
Elaine...
wait for me after the concert.
We'll celebrate.
Oh, okay.
[ORCHESTRA TUNING UP]
[APPLAUSE]
[MOZART'S "THE MARRIAGE
OF FIGARO" PLAYING]
[ORCHESTRA PLAYING OFF-KEY]
[ORCHESTRA STOPS PLAYING]
SUSAN:
I wanna know why
you took my doll
out of the house.
I just wanted a second opinion.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[SIGHS]
Take a look at this.
Does that look like
my flesh and blood?
Of course, your mother--
ESTELLE:
Oh, stop bothering everybody with that picture.
It's ridiculous.
Ridiculous?
I'll show you ridiculous!
Get--! Come here!
No, Mr. Costanza-- No, no--
[SNAP]
There.
Now what have you got
to say for yourself?
I told you
it looked like her.
[GRACEFUL ITALIAN FOLK SONG
PLAYING]
Carlo.
It's me, Frank.
Huh?
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
I'm your cousin, Frank.
Aren't you Carlo?
Carlo? No.
Me nome è Giuseppe.
What do you know?
[SNIFFLES]
All right.
I guess I was wrong.
Hm.