I think
if the wedding invitations
were left up to the men,
we'd just drive around sticking
fliers in windshields, you know.
Just...
Not even typed up either.
Just magic markers,
Xeroxed, you know.
"Party!"
What's needed
is a divorce announcement.
"Mr. and Mrs. Fred Johnson
"request the honor
of your presence
"at the returning
of their daughter
back to Mr. and Mrs.
Fred Johnson."
Hi.
Hi, can I help you?
Yes, we'd like
some wedding invitations.
Oh! Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
When's the wedding?
June.
Late June.
Oh, well, we have quite a few
to pick from.
They're arranged
in order of price.
The most expensive
are in the front.
Mm-hm.
Uh...
I don't know, what--
What about this one?
Uh, to tell you the truth,
they haven't manufactured
that one for a number of years.
I might have
a couple boxes left
in our warehouse
in New Jersey.
I'd have to check.
Oh, no.
George, that's so ugly.
We don't want that.
What's the difference?
You just read it
and mail it right back.
These ones.
Why don't they make them
anymore?
Well, for one thing,
the glue isn't very adhesive.
It takes a lot of moisture
to make them stick.
So we pick up some Elmer's.
All right.
Do you see what
I do for you?
Hey, Kramer.
KRAMER:
Hey, George.
Lilly.
No, Susan.
No, no, it's Lilly.
I think I know my own name.
It's Susan.
Well, you--
You look like a Lilly.
It's coming, Jerry,
it's coming.
What's coming?
The day.
Ah, the day.
We ordered
the wedding invitations today.
Nothing can stop it now,
nothing.
It's here. It's happening.
Can I do this?
I can't do this.
Look at me.
Look at me,
I can't do this.
I can't do it.
Help me, Jerry, help me.
Why don't you just
break it off with her.
Tell her it's over.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I can't face that scene.
You know what kind of a scene
that would be?
I'd rather be unhappy
for the rest of my life
than go through something
like that. I can't! I can't!
I've tried to psyche myself up
a million times.
I cannot go through that!
All right, take it easy.
Just take it easy.
What about a letter?
A letter?
I write a letter
and then I go to China.
I disappear in a sea of people
for like six months, a year.
You know, just while
things simmer down.
Uh, uh...
"Dear Susan,
I'm sorry." Uh...
"I made a terrible mistake.
I'm really, really sorry."
That's it?
What, too short?
Seems a--
BOTH:
Little short.
You can't go to China.
What about your job?
Right. My job!
Write a letter, move to another
borough. Move to Staten Island.
It's a lot easier to blend into
a sea of people
in Staten Island than China.
Yeah, yeah.
Staten Island.
What about my clothes?
How do I get the clothes?
Ah, you come back
for your clothes.
I'm not going back in there.
So forget about your clothes.
Well, I'm not starting up
a whole new wardrobe now!
Look, freedom and no clothes
is a lot better
than no freedom with clothes.
If she would just
take a plane somewhere.
And what,
hope for a crash?
It happens.
Do you know what
the odds are on a crash?
It's a million to one.
It's something.
It's hope.
Hey. Hey!
Hey.
Georgie, you know
what I just realized?
The wedding is like
a month away.
[LAUGHING]
Ha-ha. Elaine.
What?
Oh, by the way,
what am I gonna get to be
in the wedding party?
What do you mean?
Well, Jerry's gonna be
the best man
and Kramer's gonna be the usher.
So, what am I gonna be?
I don't know, I don't think
you're anything.
Well, I have
to be something.
I'm a close friend.
Well...wh-what about
being a bridesmaid?
Well, those are Susan's friends.
[SCOFFS]
Well, then how about
being an usher?
All right, I'll--
I'll ask Susan about it later.
You don't ask.
You tell.
What about the letter?
Should I think about the letter?
Hey, Elaine, if a guy wanted
to end a relationship with you,
what could he do?
Start smoking.
Smoking.
Does she hate cigarettes?
Yes, she hates cigarettes.
But you don't smoke.
[TSKS]
No-ooh.
You know, I think I'm starting
to get a little depressed
about George's wedding.
Really?
Yeah, well,
once he gets married, that's it.
She'll probably get pregnant.
They'll move to Westchester.
I'll never see him again.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Then it'll be just me,
you and Kramer.
No, not me, pal.
I can't keep this up
much longer.
I'm sick of being single.
I'm getting out.
So it's just gonna be
me and Kramer?
Yeah, just you and Kramer.
See ya.
Huh, me and Kramer.
[♪]
Hey, buddy.
Hey, I thought of
a great invention for driving.
A periscope in a car
so you can see the traffic.
Now, how are you gonna drive
while you're
looking through a periscope?
Besides which,
it's not a submarine.
There's no room
for a periscope in a car.
Oh, you make a higher roof.
They're not making higher roofs.
Well, why can't you
make a higher roof?
Because it's a stupid idea.
No one's gonna go for it.
Don't you understand?
It's stupid, it's stupid!
Stupid. It's stupid.
Hey, hey, hey, look out!
[HORN HONKS]
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, my God.
You saved my life.
Shouldn't there be
some kind of reward for that?
Oh, I...
You should be a lot more careful
crossing the street.
Otherwise you could die,
if that bothers you.
Well, yeah--
See? To me,
this is a waste.
What?
The shirt you got on under your sweater.
It sits in a drawer for
three weeks waiting to come out
and when it finally does,
it only sticks up half an inch
out of your collar.
I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
Jeannie Steinman.
Hey, same initials.
How do you like that?
I like it.
GEORGE:
Listen, I was talking
to Elaine today, and she said
that she would really like
to be an usher at the wedding.
No, out of the question.
I don't want any women ushers
at my wedding.
And while we're on the subject,
Kramer's not an usher either.
Why not?
He doesn't even know my name.
Oh. That was an honest mistake.
No.
He's too weird.
He'd fall or something.
He'd ruin the whole ceremony.
Yeah, you're, uh...
You're probably right.
What are you doing?
Since when do you smoke?
[COUGHING]
I've always smoked.
I've never seen you smoke.
Oh, yeah, well, big smoker.
I gave it up for a while,
but it was too tough.
You know...
[COUGHING]
...I don't got the willpower.
Oh, I don't like this one bit.
Well, I can't stop now.
[GASPING]
I'm addicted. They got a hold on me.
Well, you are gonna
have to quit.
Oh, God.
WOMAN:
Menus?
No, I know what I want.
The usual?
Yeah.
And for you?
A bowl of Cheerios,
not too much milk.
Okay, two bowls of Cheerios.
You too?
Yeah.
Hey, did you hear
the bank on the corner
is offering $100
if you go in there
and they don't greet you
with a hello?
Oh, really?
That's nice.
Come on.
What's with you?
I think I'm in love.
Oh, come on.
No, it's true.
This woman saved my life.
I was crossing the street.
I was almost hit by a car.
And then we talked, and...
The whole thing
just seemed like a dream.
If a guy saved your life,
you'd be in love with him too.
No, no, this woman is different.
She's incredible.
She's just like me.
She talks like me.
She acts like me.
She even orders cereal
in a restaurant.
We even have
the same initials.
Wait a minute, I just
realized what's going on.
What?
Now I know what
I've been looking for
all these years.
Myself.
I've been waiting
for me to come along.
And now I've swept myself
off my feet!
Will you stop it, man?
You're freakin' me out!
Jeez.
Hey.
W-w-wait a second,
you didn't say "hello."
Yes, I did.
No. No, you didn't.
Hundred dollars.
I get $100.
No, no, I said "hello."
No, no, you said "hey."
Well, "hey" is "hello."
Same thing.
No. The ad said that
the bank's gonna pay $100
if you're not greeted
with a "hello."
You're taking that
much too literally.
Now, sir, do you have
any business to transact?
I wanna speak
with the manager.
Well, he's not here right now.
Then I'll be back.
ELAINE:
So I'm not gonna be an usher?
GEORGE:
No.
So I'm nothing?
Jerry is best man,
Kramer is an usher,
and I am nothing?
Well, Kramer's not an usher
anymore.
What are you talking about?
You've been demoted.
Why?
Because you called her
by the wrong name.
But she really looks
like a Lilly.
Jerry.
Hey, Jerry.
Susan says I can't be an usher
at the wedding.
Yeah,
me neither.
Hey, George, I think I wanna
bring a date to the wedding.
Who?
I just met her.
She's incredible.
Oh, this is great!
Now I'm gonna be stuck
at the singles' table
with all the losers?
You can go with Kramer.
No, no, no, no, no.
Weddings are a great place
to meet chicks.
I have to be unfettered.
All right, do you see
what this is turning into?
Do I need this?
I have got to get
out of this thing.
Did you try
the cigarettes?
Yeah, they made me sick.
All right,
all right.
Let's get down here.
You really wanna get out
of this thing?
Yeah.
All right.
I got two words for you:
Pre-nup.
Prenup, what does that mean?
Ask her to sign a prenup.
What does that do?
Because most women
when they're asked
to sign a prenup
are so offended,
they back out of the marriage.
They are?
Elaine?
I wouldn't
sign one.
Prenup.
Of course.
Kramer.
Get outta here.
Ha-ha!
Hi.
Hey, I've been going over
the list.
What about the Drake?
Wanna invite him?
Oh, got to invite
the Drake.
Listen, um...
There's something
that's been on my mind,
and we haven't really
talked about it,
and it's-- It's kind of
important to me.
What is it?
Well, I-I've put a lot
of thought into this,
and I think
that I would like you
to sign
a prenuptial agreement.
A prenup?
Yeah.
[SNORTS]
What's so funny?
[LAUGHING]
You don't have any money.
I make more money than you do.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah, give me the papers,
I'll sign 'em.
A prenup.
[SUSAN LAUGHING]
[SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRASH]
KRAMER; Oh, g--!
Excuse me.
Jerry.
[EXHALES]
Hey, Jeannie.
Hello.
Remember I told you
about the bank? Yeah.
Yeah, well, I went in there,
and they said, "Hey."
"Hey" is the same as "hello."
What do you think?
It's the same thing.
Oh, big surprise.
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
Delivery from
Melody Stationers.
Oh, those are
the invitations.
Just sign here.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Thank you.
See you later.
Oh, these are so cheap.
Hey, don't forget tomorrow.
We're going shopping for rings
so don't make any plans.
And this time
we're not skimping.
KRAMER: Hey.
JERRY: Hey.
Jeannie left?
She's coming to
my act tonight.
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's nice.
I'm sure that's
right up her alley.
What's with you?
Nothing.
Something on your mind?
No.
Looks like there is.
Come on, something's
on your mind. Out with it.
I don't like her!
Huh? You don't like her?
That's right,
I don't like her.
I never liked her
from the get-go.
What's wrong with her?
Everything she thinks,
you think.
Everything you think, she
thinks. No, I can't take it.
I can't take it, Jerry.
It's too much!
It's too much.
Well, if you can't take her,
maybe you can't take me either.
So that's how
it's gonna be?
That's how
it's gonna be.
Oh, God help us!
Ugh, awful.
[♪]
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
MAN:
Can I help you?
Uh, yeah. I, uh--
I was in here the other day,
and I went up to that teller,
and he didn't say "hello."
Well, then you are
entitled to $100.
That's our policy.
Yeah, but he wouldn't
give me the money. Mm-hm.
Jim, can I see you for a second?
Yes, can you give me a minute?
Yeah.
He'll, uh...
be right over.
What is this, oak?
I think it's pine.
Pine is good.
Yeah, pine's okay.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Ahem. Jim, our man here
says, uh...
came in the other day,
you didn't say "hello"?
No. No, that's not true.
I said "hey."
You know,
like a friendly greeting. "Hey."
But that's not "hello."
That's a tough one.
Mm-hm.
You know, let me bring
some other people in on this.
Barbara, Jane, Mike,
can I--? Can I see you, please?
How you doing?
What's happening?
What's up?
Excuse us for just one minute.
Just one minute.
Thanks.
How's it going?
Thanks, everybody.
Sir, have a seat.
Well, we've discussed this.
Here's the feeling.
Hm.
You got a greeting. It starts
with an H. How's 20 bucks sound?
I'll take it.
All right, sir.
Will you marry me?
[THROAT CRACKLES]
[ALL LAUGHING]
I would like to
propose a toast--
Wait a second.
George!
George Costanza,
come in here!
Georgie boy.
George, big news.
I'm gettin' married.
Married? What?
September 21st,
first day of autumn.
Leaves changing,
beautiful colors.
All that crap.
You see?
I kept up my end of the pact.
Oh, good for you.
And look,
champagne.
Hey.
To our future wives.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
[EXHALES]
JERRY:
Well, this has been quite a night.
I could sure use
a cup of coffee.
Hey,
what's the deal with decaf?
How do they get the caffeine
out of there?
And then where does it go?
I don't know.
[GRUNTS]
That's a shame.
I'll just have a cup of coffee.
Bowl of corn flakes.
More cereal?
That's your third bowl today.
You had it
for breakfast and lunch.
Hey. So, what's the deal
with brunch?
I mean, if it's a combination
of breakfast and lunch,
how come there's no "lupper,"
or no "linner"?
Hey!
Frank just called me.
Congratulations.
Thanks. Thanks.
Look, I'm sorry about before.
I mean, I'm sure
I'll learn to like her, Jerry.
Yeah. Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
What's the matter?
[WHIMPERS]
I think I may have made a big mistake.
Oh, come on.
No, all of a sudden it hit me.
I realized what the problem is.
I can't be
with someone like me.
I hate myself!
If anything,
I need to be with someone
the complete opposite of me.
It's too much,
it's too much, Kramer.
I can't take it!
It's too bad
you got engaged.
Yeah, too bad.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello? Oh, hey, George.
What?
Really?
All right, I'll call Elaine.
We'll meet you down there.
What happened?
They took Susan
to the hospital.
So she was just lying there?
Yeah.
I wonder
what happened.
I don't know.
Oh, uh, there's the doctor.
Excuse me,
are you the husband?
Well, not yet. Fiancé.
Yes. Well,
I'm sorry.
She's...gone.
What's that?
She expired.
Are you sure?
Yes, of course.
So...
she's dead?
Yes.
Huh.
Let me ask you...
had she been exposed
to any kind of...
inexpensive...glue?
Why?
We found traces
of a certain toxic adhesive
commonly found
in very low-priced envelopes.
Well, she was sending out
our wedding invitations.
That's probably
what did it.
We were expecting
about 200 people.
Well...
Thank you, doctor.
MAN [OVER P.A.]:
Blue team to ICU, please. Blue team, ICU.
She's, uh...
gone.
Dead?
I'm...
so sorry, George.
Yeah. Me too.
Poor Lilly.
Susan.
How did
it happen?
Apparently the, uh, glue
in the wedding invitations
was, uh...
...toxic.
Ah.
Well,
that's weird.
So I guess...
you're not
getting married.
Yeah.
But...
Yeah?
Well...
now I'm engaged.
Yeah?
Well, I thought
we'd both be getting married.
Hey.
What can I tell you?
All right.
GEORGE:
Come on, let's, uh, get some coffee.
We had a pact!
[♪]
Uh, yes, I'd like to speak
with Marisa Tomei, please.
Marisa, hi. It's, uh--
It's George Costanza.
I-I'm the short, funny,
quirky bald man
you met a little while ago. Heh.
Yeah, I was just calling
because I wanted you to know
that, uh,
I'm not engaged anymore.
Well, uh, she died.
Toxic glue
from the wedding invitations.
Well, we were expecting
about 200 people.
Yeah. Anyway, um...
I've got the funeral tomorrow
but, um...
my weekend
is pretty wide open, and...
you know, I was wondering--
[LINE CLICKS]
Hello?