Old people in Florida,
they drive slow,
and they sit low.
Right?
That is their motto.
The state flag of Florida
should be, like,
a steering wheel with a hat
and two knuckles on it.
And that left-turn signal on
from when they left the house
that morning.
Right?
That's a legal turn
in Florida.
It's known as an eventual left.
And old people
get to a certain age
where, when they back out
of the driveway...
they don't look.
You know what I mean?
They're--
They just feel like:
"Well, I'm old,
and I'm coming back.
I survived.
Let's see if you can."
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, you're back!
Oh, I'm back, baby.
Yeah, how was it,
huh?
One of the best jobs
I ever had.
Good for you.
I killed.
You killed.
Wiped the floor
with them.
And not only that.
The money was unbelievable.
Unbelievable!
Yeah. Highest-paying job
I ever had.
How much?
Nah, nah,
I'd rather not.
Oh, come on.
Ah.
Friends shouldn't talk
about money.
It can affect
the friendship.
[SIGHS]
I tell you how much I make.
And I'm always impressed.
Just show me
the check. Come on.
[SNAPS, CLAPS]
All right. Fine. You wanna see it?
I wanna see it.
Okay.
Here.
Check that out.
W-whoa.
This is unbelievable.
I told you.
My God, you're rich.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't know you made
that kind of money.
Gee.
What?
I just don't think
I can talk to you anymore.
I feel inferior.
I never should have told you.
You know, Jerry, I think
this changes the relationship.
I mean, I feel it.
Do you feel it?
No. I can't feel anything.
Well, what are you gonna do
with all that money?
Actually, I was thinking
of donating
a large portion of it
to charity.
Really?
No.
Well, you should,
Jerry.
No, to tell you
the truth,
I was thinking of buying
my father a new car.
Now, you see,
that's nice.
Yeah. Maybe a Cadillac.
Cadillac.
Ooh-la-la!
Yeah.
That would really
blow his mind.
He's always wanted one
his whole life.
He's never been able
to afford it.
I'm gonna do it.
You're gonna score
big points
with the man upstairs
on this one.
Oh, isn't that
what it's all about?
Oh, y--
Who was
Pippi Longstocking?
Mm...
I don't know.
Did she have anything
to do with Hitler?
Hitler? Maybe.
Hey.
Hey, George.
[SCOFFS]
Have you seen Jerry?
I told him 2:00.
You remember Katy?
Hm?
Oh, hi.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We met, uh, skiing
that time.
You're married
to the eye guy.
Also ear, nose and throat.
Oh.
Nose.
[CHUCKLES]
What's the worst
that could happen to a nose?
What does it get,
stuffed?
[LAUGHING]
He's funny.
Uh, you don't have to
tell me.
Ahh.
Ladies, please, please.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, you know what?
He got engaged.
Oh, you did?
Oh...
What, is that bad?
I actually would have set you up
with a friend of mine.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You'd be perfect for her.
She loves quirky, funny guys.
Bald? Uh--
Loves bald.
[CHUCKLES]
Wow. Who, uh--?
Who is she?
Marisa Tomei.
The actress?
Yeah.
Y-you're friends
with Marisa Tomei?
That's right.
Th-that's incredible.
My Cousin Vinny--
I love her.
She was fantastic.
Yeah, I know.
You were gonna fix
me up with her?
Yeah. She's just been
sitting home.
Marisa Tomei's
sitting home, Elaine.
W-w-why didn't you
tell me that Katy
was friends
with Marisa Tomei?
Oh, I don't know
what I was thinking.
JERRY:
I want this baby fully loaded.
Well, how soon
can you get it there?
Oh, that's
terrific.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
Hey, guess what?
I just bought my father
a Cadillac.
Really?
Wow, you are
quite the good son.
Yeah. I'm a very good boy.
I'm flying down there
and surprising them.
You gonna sleep
on the foldout?
Yeah.
I guess.
Uh, let me
ask you something.
You, uh...
You ever hear of
Marisa Tomei?
The actress?
Yeah.
She's, uh--
She's something,
isn't she?
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know Katy,
Elaine's friend?
Yeah.
She happens to be
very good friends with her.
Marisa Tomei?
Mm-hm.
How does she know
Marisa Tomei?
I-I don't know.
I didn't ask.
You didn't ask how
she knows Marisa Tomei?
Not the point.
All right.
Can I finish?
Go ahead.
Seems like
a reasonable question.
That's all
I'm saying.
I would have
asked her.
All right!
So she said that
she could have
fixed me up with her.
What do you mean,
"could have"?
Well, you know,
if I, uh, wasn't engaged.
Ohh.
Could have fixed me up
with Marisa Tomei.
She said I was just her type.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
Do you know the odds
of me being anyone's type?
I have never been
anyone's type.
But, apparently,
this Marisa Tomei
loves funny, quirky
bald men.
You know, she won
an Academy Award.
[CHUCKLES]
Like I don't know that.
My Cousin Vinny,
I love that.
I, George Costanza,
could be on a date
with an Oscar winner.
An Oscar winner, Jerry!
Do you know
what that's like?
It's like, if 50 years ago,
someone had fixed me up
with Katharine Hepburn.
Same thing!
Now, there's a match,
you and Katharine Hepburn.
I mean, you've seen her, right?
Katharine Hepburn?
Oh, yeah.
Marisa Tomei!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, she's beautiful, right?
She's just my type.
The dark hair,
the full lips.
You like full lips.
Oh, I love
full lips.
Something you can really
put the lipstick on.
Mm-mm-mm.
Too bad you're engaged.
Yeah, too bad. Too bad.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
This is no good.
Hi.
Hi, uh...
Excuse me, I'm, uh--
I'm with Plaza Cable.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I-I'm looking for the guy
who lives over here.
Been waiting about, uh...
[CHUCKLES]
...two hours.
Uh.
You, uh, happen to know
where he is?
No.
Could you tell him
the cable company was here?
Sure.
Thank you.
Nice people.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, listen, let--
Let me ask you a question.
Uh...
what if I got a cup
of coffee with her?
Well, what about Susan?
I can't have a cup of coffee
with a person?
I'm not allowed to have coffee?!
Would you tell Susan
about it?
Not necessarily.
Well, if you can't
tell Susan about it,
then there's
something wrong.
Of course there's
something wrong!
We had a pact!
Hey, cable guy's
looking for you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Ah.
Yeah, I've been getting
HBO and Showtime for free.
See, they found out
about it.
So now they wanna come
and take it out.
Well, said he was waiting
about two hours.
Seemed a little put out.
[MOCKINGLY]
Oh, was he?
Well, I guess the cable man
doesn't like to be
kept waiting.
You don't seem
too bothered by it.
Do you remember what they did
to me 10 years ago?
"Oh, we'll be there
in the morning between 9 and 1.
Or we'll be there
between 2 and 6."
And I sat there,
hour after hour,
without so much
as a phone call.
Finally, they show up.
No apology.
Tracking mud all over
my nice, clean floors.
And now...
[CLAPS]
...they want me
to accommodate them.
Well...
Looks like the shoe is
on the other foot,
doesn't it?
Boy, I've never
seen you like this.
Oh, you don't want to
get on my bad side.
--marks without Positraction,
which was not available
on the '64 Buick Skylark.
Hey.
Hey, what are
you watching?
What is that,
My Cousin Vinny?
Yeah.
I thought you saw
that before.
How come you're watching
that again?
I-I-I don't know.
Did you know Marisa Tomei
won an Oscar for that?
Boy, she's beautiful,
don't you think?
I wish I looked like that.
Well, turn it off.
You're making me jealous.
I'm gonna think you like her
more than you like me.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[PHONE RINGS]
ELAINE:
Hello?
[WHISPERS]
Elaine. It's me, George.
How come you're whispering?
Never mind.
Never mind. I need you
to do me a favor. Um...
Remember what we were talking
about at the coffee shop?
No.
Think a second.
You know, y-your friend
was talking about me
and, you know...
[SCOFFS]
George, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
The actress.
What?
[YELLS]
Marisa Tomei!
SUSAN:
What?!
Ah, nothing. Nothing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. What about her?
Well, um...
I think I'd like to do it.
What?
George, no way.
You're engaged.
A coffee. Th-that doesn't
mean anything.
[INCENSED]
Ugh. No, George.
Elaine.
Forget it!
Elaine!
Elaine! Don't!
Oh! Oh!
The judge!
I-I hate this guy!
I can't
believe you're
buying your father
a car.
And best of all,
it's a Cadillac.
[GASPS]
A Cadillac?
Wow.
I had no idea you had
this kind of money.
Oh, I-- I don't like to
talk about it.
Yeah, I mean, I thought
you were doing okay.
I-I-- I just didn't
think you were in
this kind of,
you know, uh...
position.
Ah, it's just money.
So when are you
getting back from Florida?
Oh, I don't know.
Play it by ear. Why?
I don't know. Just...
Things seem a little more
exciting when you're around.
That's all.
Are you okay?
Sure, sure.
What was that?
Quiet. Quiet.
Hey, uh...
you know the guy
who lives here?
Yeah.
All morning
I've been waiting here.
All morning.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, this is...
The guy says he's
gonna be home.
I show up.
And all I do is wait.
I'm getting pretty sick
and tired of it.
And I'm not gonna put up
with it much longer.
I'm loving this.
Hey, there's a guy
out here that--
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, I know.
Oh.
Thanks very much
for yesterday, by the way.
Jerry...he wants me
to fix him up
with Marisa Tomei.
I am not gonna be
a part of this!
"Fixed up"?
A cup of coffee.
A cup of coffee
is not a fix-up.
You wanna meet her.
You wanna see
if she likes you?
So what?
So what if I do?
You're engaged!
I'm aware!
But this is
Marisa Tomei, Elaine.
An Oscar winner.
How can I live
the rest of my life
knowing I could have been
with Marisa Tomei?
She said I was
just her type.
She loves short, stocky,
balding funnymen.
I notice you threw
"stocky" in there.
Yeah, what the hell!
George,
it's cheating.
It's not cheating
if there's no sex.
Yes, it is.
Jerry.
Hundred.
H-hold on a second.
I'm--
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear
what you said.
Um...
Elaine, come on.
Would you just make the call?
Please, make the call.
Yeah. Yeah, fine.
I'll call.
All right.
Eight fifty.
Oh, right.
[PHONE RINGING]
So, uh...
how are you getting
to the airport?
Do you need a ride, or...?
No, don't be silly.
I've arranged a car.
You sure? You sure?
Because, you know...
[SNIFFS]
Maybe I'll let you
pick me up.
Okay.
Oh, hi.
Um, i-is Katy
there?
W--
Uh, what?
Oh, really?
Well, could you tell her
Elaine called?
Yeah, thanks.
Huh.
She's in
the hospital.
She has an arrhythmia.
What about Marisa Tomei?
Morty, what do you have to
open this box for?
There's already
a box of cookies open.
I wanted a Chip Ahoy.
Oh. I don't want
all these open boxes.
Look, I got a few
good years left.
If I want a Chip Ahoy,
I'm having it.
[DOOR OPENS]
Surprise!
Jerry!
Oh, my God!
Oh.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm a good son.
Just like that?
No call?
Just like that.
Oh, you are
really something.
To what do we owe
this great honor?
You wanna know.
Come on outside.
Outside?
What's going on?
Whenever
Jerry comes,
something exciting
happens.
Ha-ha.
Come on, come on.
[♪]
Well, what do you think?
MORTY:
Look at this.
Look at this,
heh-heh.
You bought a Cadillac?
I bought it for you.
It's
yours.
You what?
You bought me
a Cadillac?
I bought you a Cadillac.
Here you go.
Are you out of
your mind? What?
We can't
take this.
You don't want it?
Are you kidding?
He's not buying us
a Cadillac.
What are you,
nuts?
This is a very
nice gesture, Jerry,
but take it
back.
Can you believe this?
I'm not letting him
buy us a Cadillac.
He hasn't got
that kind of money.
How do you know?
Oh, get out of here,
Mr. Big Shot.
Why can't I buy
my father a car?
Your father
doesn't need a car.
Yes, I do!
Oh, Morty.
We're keeping it.
Over my dead body.
What?
Give me those. Give me--
Well, this worked out
just as I had hoped.
[RINGING]
KRAMER [ON MACHINE]:
Giddyup.
MAN:
Yeah, this is Nick Stevens
from Plaza Cable.
Well, I waited
all morning again.
You said you were gonna
be there from 9 to 1.
I was there.
Where were you?
You think I got nothing
better to do
than stand outside
all morning
waiting for you
to show up?
You're not gonna
get away with this.
Hey, Jerry, look at this.
My seat's got a memory,
in case somebody moves it.
I could be in prison
for five years.
I come out, my seat goes
right back to where I like it.
That's what I was thinking.
Hello, Jerry.
Hi, Jack.
So...
how do you
like this?
Whose car?
It's mine.
Yours?
That's right.
My son bought it for me.
He what?
My son bought me the car.
It's a present.
You bought it?
That's right,
I bought it.
You ever see one so nice?
Some car.
You wanna take a ride?
No. Thank you.
Come on, take a ride.
I don't wanna take a ride.
Why not?
I don't feel like taking a ride.
Do I have to take a ride?
He doesn't wanna
take a ride. Uh-huh.
What do you think,
I've never ridden
in a Cadillac before?
Believe me, I have
ridden in a Cadillac
hundreds of times.
Thousands.
Thousands?
What, you think you're
such a big shot now
because you got a Cadillac?
Ahh!
Did you believe
that guy?
Ahh!
GEORGE:
Anyway,
I was thinking
about what you said
about, the...
Me and Marisa.
You know,
about the, uh--
The two of us
getting together,
and--
And I know that I said
that I was engaged.
But, uh, you know,
it's--
It's really just
something you say,
you know.
It's like going steady,
you know, uh...
Going steady, engaged.
It's-- It's-- It's all
just stuff you say.
[CHUCKLES]
Anyway, I, uh--
I was watching, uh,
My Cousin Vinny
on the, uh--
On the tape the other day.
And I was thinking
that, uh, you know,
the two of us might,
uh, take a meeting,
as they say.
[CHUCKLES]
So, what do you--
What do you think?
Move a pinkie
if it's yes.
Can you move a pinkie?
♪ Ba, ba-ba, ba-ba ♪
[PHONE RINGS]
"Yello."
MAN:
Hi, uh, uh, Mr. Kramer.
Uh, this is McNab
down at the phone company.
We got a report about
some trouble on your line.
Hm. Well, I haven't
had any trouble.
Uh, the thing is,
we happen to have a man
right in your neighborhood.
Oh.
Is that right?
Well, I have
been having
a little trouble
with my call waiting.
We can fix that.
Oh, can you?
Well, that's funny.
Because as it happens,
I don't have call waiting.
Seems to me that
the phone company
would know that.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
I was looking at
the wrong work order.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, could you hold on
for a second?
I've got something
on the stove.
[TURNS ON INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[EXHALES]
[HORN HONKS]
KRAMER:
Hey, McNab!
Chunnel's on HBO
tonight!
Why don't you
stop by!
[STAMMERS]
All right. Next thing
on the agenda:
the restoration of the fence
at the Broward Gate.
At the present time,
we are still accepting bids.
Come on, it's been broken
for six months already.
What the hell
are you doing?
Well, I, as your president,
have to find the best price.
And right now, I, for one,
do not think it's cost-feasible.
I'll bet you don't.
What's that?
Come on, Morty.
The jig is up.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I'm sitting here
the whole meeting
holding my tongue.
I know you
a long time, Morty.
But I cannot
hold it in any longer.
What's going on, Jack?
I'll tell you
what's going on.
Morty Seinfeld has been
stealing funds
from the treasury.
Stealing?
What proof
do you have?
Proof?
You want proof?
He's driving around
in a brand-new Cadillac.
Now, what more proof
do you want?
My son bought me that car.
Your son?
Yeah.
Your son could never
afford that car.
We all saw his act
last year at the playhouse.
He's lucky he can
pay his rent.
Jack's right.
He stinks!
It's his material.
I tell you,
he bought it for me!
I move for a full
investigation.
I second.
Impeachment?
That's right.
Have you ever heard of
anything like that?
Can they do that?
If they get the votes.
I told you we shouldn't
have let him give us the car.
Didn't you tell them
I got the bill of sale?
That proves I paid.
It doesn't
make a difference.
They think we're
in cahoots.
You know, you could put
a fence around these condos,
and call it an insane asylum.
Nobody would know
the difference.
No one's ever been
impeached before.
I couldn't live here.
We'd have to move
to Boca.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Evelyn.
Hello, Jerry.
I just got off the phone
with Sol Brandes.
What did
he say?
He's voting
to impeach.
Not because he thinks
you stole the money,
but mainly because
you never thanked him
for giving you his aisle seat
at Freddy Roman's show.
I did so thank him.
No, he never
heard you.
I told you
he didn't hear you.
Ah, he's deaf anyway.
Now...
my sources tell me...
there's three votes
for impeachment,
three votes
against impeachment,
and one undecided.
Who's that?
Mrs. Choate.
Who's she?
MORTY: Oh, that one?
She's been a member
of the board
longer than anybody.
She's very tough
to deal with.
Maybe we should
have her over for coffee
and explain
our side of it.
That's a good idea.
Okay.
I'll see you at
the Lichtenbergs' tonight.
The Lichtenbergs'?
Yes. They're having
a party.
We weren't invited.
Well...
Probably they think
you're too good for them.
You know...
because of the car.
[DOOR CLOSES]
We're losing
all our friends.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
MAN:
Hello, Mr. Kramer?
This is John Hanaran
from Con Ed.
Oh, it's Hanaran now,
is it?
Yes.
We've had some reports
of power surges
in your building.
It seems some jokers
were up on the roof,
and they must have damaged
some of the wires.
Oh, you don't say.
Yeah. Either way, we need
to get into your apartment
and do a safety check.
Oh. You're good.
You are really good.
What are you talking about?
I guess I should just
go introduce myself, huh?
Hey. What are
you watching?
Only You?
That's another
Marisa Tomei movie.
And you've seen that one too.
What? Do you have
a thing for her?
[SCOFFS]
Yeah.
Yeah, I-- I have a thing
for Marisa Tomei.
[CHUCKLING]
Like she would ever
go out with a--
A short, stocky, bald man.
Like, that's her type.
She's an Oscar winner.
Besides, I--
I don't even know her.
It's not like anyone's
trying to fix us up.
Who-- Who would try
and fix me up with Marisa Tomei?
What are you talking about?
[♪]
Have I told you how much
I love you today?
Not in the last
15 minutes.
Well, I do love you
very much.
And I love you, Marisa.
Well, then.
Come on, get dressed.
We're going to be late
for the premiere.
Hm.
[SIGHS]
Oh. Stupid foldout.
Why do they put the bar
in the middle of the bed?
[GROANING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hi, Jerry.
Elaine?
W-what's going on?
Ahem.
I was thinking.
I mean, I'm not really...
doing that much this weekend,
and I thought,
"Well...
"what the hell.
Maybe I'll come down there
and hang out a little."
You want to hang out here
at...
Phase Two
in the Pines
of Mar Gables?
[GIGGLING]
Well...
it's just two hours by plane.
Gee, I-- I don't know
what to tell you anymore.
[BEEP]
Damn it!
Got another call.
Uh, hang on. Don't--
Don't hang up, Jerry.
[CLICKS OVER]
[ANNOYED]
Yeah?
Elaine, you have got to get me
Marisa Tomei's phone number.
Okay, George,
I'm on the other line.
I promise you
I'll get you her number.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
[CLICKS OVER]
Hi.
So, what do you think?
Uh, I don't think so.
Oh.
I'll be back on Monday.
Well, if you would
need that ride,
just, um...
give me a call, heh.
I-I can meet you
at the gate, Jerr.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
All right, I-I'll see you.
Jerr. Jerry?
Yeah?
Bye.
GEORGE:
Yeah, sure.
No, that's fantastic.
Uh, I'll see you then.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay.
I just got off the phone
with Marisa Tomei.
I just spoke
to Marisa Tomei.
And I-I wasn't even
that nervous.
You know, I can't
remember calling a woman
without being nervous.
Usually, I'm pacing
all over the room.
I write down
things to say.
Okay, well,
that's all the time
we have for today.
But why don't we pick up
with this next week?
Where are
you going?
I got stuff to do.
What? You can't
leave yet.
Why not?
We have to discuss
my alibi.
Alibi?
What does that
have to do with me?
I usually spend Saturday
afternoons with Susan.
She's gonna wanna know
what I'm doing.
I can't use Jerry.
He's in Florida.
So you wanna say
you were with me?
Yes.
Okay, fine.
You were with me.
W-wait a second.
Wait a second.
What were we doing?
Where were we?
Why are we together?
What is the difference?
Because if you ever see her,
and it comes up,
we have to be in sync.
Nuh.
[SIGHS]
Okay. Now...
Why do I have to
see you?
Ah!
Because I'm going to
the dentist...
and I'm afraid...
and I want you
to go with me.
That's no good.
Okay.
Fine.
What?
I don't like
the way
you just rejected
my suggestion.
Hey, let's not get
so defensive here.
This is a give-and-take
process.
I thought that
my suggestion was good.
And I think you could have been
a little more tactful.
Okay, look, we've never
worked together on a lie.
You don't understand
how I work.
I have a certain way
of working.
Jerry and I have worked together
a few times.
He knows how I work.
Not a personal
thing.
We're just trying to
come up
with the best possible lie.
That's what this
is all about.
Okay.
All right?
Okay?
Fine.
Good.
Fine, fine,
fine, fine.
Okay.
[EXHALES]
Okay, how about
this?
What?
You are having boyfriend problems,
and I am meeting you
to discuss the situation.
I don't have a boyfriend.
She doesn't know that.
We say that you do.
Ugh.
It's good.
Believe me.
I thought my idea
was just as good.
The dentist thing?
Yeah, right.
The dentist thing.
The dentist thing
was not good.
Okay. All right.
What is his name?
Who is he?
Art Vandelay.
Art Vandelay?
This is my boyfriend?
That's your boyfriend.
What does he do?
[SNAPS]
He's an importer.
Just imports?
No exports?
He's an importer-exporter.
Okay?
All right.
So...
I'm dating Art Vandelay.
What is the problem
we're discussing?
Yes. Yes.
[LOW VOICE]
Hi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi.
Ah!
How about this?
How about he's thinking
of quitting the exporting,
and just focusing in
on the importing.
And this is causing
a problem.
Because why not do both?
Oh, what?
You don't like
that suggestion either?
It's very complicated.
You know, it seems to me
that it's all you,
and none of my ideas
are getting in.
You know, I mean,
you just know it all.
And I am
Miss Stupid.
Right?
MORTY:
What are you doing?
Are you making
coffee? Yeah.
Well, you better make
a pot of tea too.
Morty, you're
driving me crazy.
Look, I don't want
anything to go wrong.
If this woman
votes to impeach me,
I'll be
a laughingstock.
You wanna drive a Cadillac,
expect to pay the consequences.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
There she is.
Hello. Hello,
Mrs. Choate.
Oh, come in.
Come in.
May I take
your coat?
No, no.
I prefer to wear it.
Nobody's taking my coat.
Oh. How about a cup
of coffee or something?
Coffee? Ah.
Uh, I'll take hot water
with lemon, if you have it.
Uh, please,
have a seat.
That's a lovely scarf
you're wearing.
Uh, where did
you get it?
Oh, they're
a dime a dozen.
Oh, hi,
Jerry.
Mrs. Choate,
this is my son, Jerry.
Give me that rye.
Stop it.
Help! Someone help!
Shut up,
you old bag.
Oh. Thief. Thief!
Stop him!
Stop him.
He's got my rye!
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Jerry lives in
New York.
You just came
from New York?
Yeah,
I was visiting my daughter.
And I'll never go back.
The crime
there
is just terrible.
Do you know I got mugged
for a marble rye
right on the street?
HELEN:
Oh, that's terrible.
They stole a rye?
Why would they
steal a rye?
That's what the city's
turning into.
They'll steal anything.
They're like savages.
Yeah, there are
some sickos out there.
You look very familiar.
H-have we ever met?
You ever go to
Camp Tioga?
Maybe you've seen him
on television.
Jerry's a comedian.
No, I don't watch TV.
Well, it was nice
meeting you.
Jerry, don't go.
Oh, I think I'll go.
So, Morty,
what's this
all about?
What do you want?
SUSAN:
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, I--
I didn't tell you?
I-I gotta go, uh, meet Elaine.
Elaine? What for?
I don't know.
She-- she's having
some problems
with this guy she's seeing.
I didn't know
she was dating anyone.
Yeah, yeah.
She's seeing this guy,
Art Vandelay.
So, what does he do?
He's an importer-exporter.
What kind of problems
are they having?
Well, he, um...
He wants to, uh,
quit the exporting and, um...
focus just on the importing.
And it's a problem, because
she thinks the exporting
is as important
as the importing.
Are you having
an affair with Elaine?
[CHUCKLING]
Right. Come on.
I'm having an affair
with Elaine?
If I was having an affair
with Elaine,
I wouldn't tell you
I'm going to see Elaine.
I-I would make up another person
to tell you I was gonna go see,
and then I would go see Ela--
Elaine.
Uh-huh.
[♪]
I'll get you!
I'll get you, Kramer!
You won't get away
with this!
All right, are you
ready to eat?
Oh, right, let's go.
Jerry, let's go.
It's time to eat.
We're going to dinner.
Dinner?
Well, what time is it?
It's 4:30.
Four thirty?
Who eats dinner at 4:30?
By the time we sit down,
it'll be quarter to 5.
I don't understand why
we have to eat now.
We gotta catch
the early-bird.
It's only between
4:30 and 6.
Yeah, they give you
a tenderloin,
a salad and a baked potato
for $4.95.
You know what that
costs you after 6? Ha-ha.
Can't we eat
at a decent hour?
I'll treat, okay?
You're not
buying us dinner.
I'm not force-feeding
myself a steak at 4:30
to save a couple bucks.
I'll tell you that.
[SIGHS]
All right.
We'll wait.
But it's unheard of.
GEORGE:
So anyway,
if you-- If you
think about it,
"manure" is not really
that bad a word.
I mean, it's "newer,"
which is good.
[LAUGHING]
And a "ma" in front of it,
which is also good.
"Ma-nure."
So it's really
not that bad.
You're so right.
I never thought of it
like that.
"Manure."
"Ma" and the "newer."
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Did you just
make that up?
What, you think I'm doing
material here?
No, no.
I'm not saying that.
It's hard to believe
anyone could be so...
spontaneously funny.
And I'm a little tired.
[LAUGHS]
So tell me...
how is it that
a man like you...
so bald and...
so quirky
and funny...
How is it you're not taken?
Well, Marisa...
see, the--
The thing is...
I'm sort of engaged.
What?
I'm, you know...
"engaged."
JERRY:
Hey, look, there's a spot right in front.
MORTY:
Always, Jerry. Always.
Was that delicious
or what?
Where you gonna get
a better meal than that?
It's better
than Danny's.
Danny's? Come on.
MORTY: Hello, Jack.
Doris.
Hi, Jack. Hi, Doris.
Jerry.
Hello, Morty.
Well...
you missed
the early-bird.
Yeah? So?
Must be nice...
to have that kind
of money.
Bernie.
Look who's eating
at 6:00.
Your suddenly
well-to-do president.
[WHISPERS]
Stop it, Jack.
Uh, you enjoy your last meal
in office.
Tomorrow, when they
kick you out,
you'll have plenty of time
to drive around
in your Cadillac.
They're not kicking me out.
You don't have the votes.
That's what you think.
We'll see.
Yes, we will.
All right,
let's eat already.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[SIGHS]
Hi, Susan.
Hi.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Uh, Elaine, I have to
ask you a question.
Oh, sure.
Are you having
an affair with George?
What?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, no.
Don't be ridiculous.
I mean,
why would anyone
wanna sleep--?
Well, obviously...
You know--
Of-- Of--
[STAMMERS]
Why would you think I was
having an affair with George?
Oh.
Because he said
that he had to
talk with you earlier
about some...
problem that
you were having.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did have to
talk with him.
I-I definitely had to
I was having a problem
with my...boyfriend.
Art Vandelay?
Yeah, Art Vandelay.
I'm sorry.
I-- I feel like
an idiot.
[CHUCKLING]
No, no. [LAUGHS]
That's okay.
Just forget
that we ever talked.
It is so forgotten.
All right.
Okay.
It's no problem.
So was George
helpful at all?
Yeah. Oh, yes.
Yes, he was very helpful.
Um...
You know, because Art and I
were getting into
this whole thing
about his business.
You know, he's an
importer-exporter.
Yeah.
George felt that
I was too adamant
in my stand
that Art should...
focus on the exporting
and forget about
the importing.
Wait a minute.
I thought Art wanted to
give up the exporting.
What did I say?
The importing.
I did?
Oh.
So, what does he,
uh...
import?
Chips.
Ah.
What kind of chips?
Potato.
Ah.
Some corn.
And what does he export?
Diapers.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Oh, no, it's okay.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Okay.
[WHISPERING]
Come on, George, pick up.
Oh, pick up.
Hi.
Hi. So, George,
what does
Art Vandelay import?
Matches.
Really long matches.
[MURMURING]
There she is.
Okay, if I could
have your attention
for a minute
here.
We're calling this emergency
meeting of the board
of Phase Two to consider
a motion of impeachment
of our president,
Morty Seinfeld.
Nervous, Jack?
What for?
Because I have the votes.
[CHUCKLES]
Nice to see you,
Mrs. Choate.
Hello, Morty.
Building A,
are you for or against
the motion to impeach?
What does that mean?
It means if you're
for the motion...
you're against Morty.
So why don't you say that?
Hey. I'm running
the meeting.
If you think so.
Building A.
For impeachment.
Building B.
Against
impeachment.
Building C.
For impeachment.
Building D.
Against impeachment.
I can't believe
you got that old bag.
Help. Someone help!
Shut up,
you old bag.
Oh. Thief. Thief!
It's him.
It's your son.
Now I know
where I saw him.
He stole my marble rye.
My son never stole anything.
He's a good boy.
They should lock him up.
Like father, like son.
I change my vote.
I vote to impeach.
Me too. I change my vote.
All those in favor
say aye.
[ALL BUT MORTY]
Aye!
All opposed?
The ayes
have it.
The motion passes.
Morty Seinfeld,
you are officially
dismissed
as condo
president.
As vice president,
Jack Klompus,
in accordance with
the Phase Two constitution,
is hereby installed
as president.
Hear, hear,
Jack.
WOMAN:
Good for you, honey.
[CHEERING,
APPLAUSE]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
All right, I-- I know
you're in there.
I know you can hear me.
You win, okay?
You win.
I can't do it anymore.
What do you want from me?
An apology?
All right.
I'm sorry.
There, I said it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I see now how we made you feel
when we made you
sit home waiting.
I don't know why we do it.
I guess maybe we just
kind of enjoy
taking advantage of people.
But all that's gonna change.
From now on, no more 9 to 12,
no more 1 to 5.
We'll kind of have appointments.
Eleven o'clock
is gonna mean 11:00.
And if we can't make it,
I'm gonna call you,
tell you why.
For God's sakes,
if a doctor can do it,
why can't we?
Anyway...
that's it.
Ah...
I'm sorry, bub.
Oh.
[SOBS]
[♪]
The bags are in the car.
I guess we'd better go.
[SIGHS]