I was thinking about the wig
historically.
I guess the Revolutionary War
was the last war fought in wigs,
and it seems like
that must have been hard.
You know, they're going
into battle, you think,
"Well, do I have my bullets?
Do I have my bobby pins?"
You know, you gotta make sure
you have everything.
Lot more to worry about.
"What if I get killed?
Is my wig on straight?"
I don't know when the whole wig
thing came into style for a man,
but I know when it went out:
when the mirror was invented.
No guy is looking in a mirror,
powdering a thatch of horsehair
on his head, going,
"All right, let's go rap
to the ladies."
JERRY:
I'm lookin' for a crested blazer.
MAN [BRITISH ACCENT]:
A crested blazer.
I wore one once,
and I really think
it did something for me.
Yes, I think we might
have something.
The Joseph Abboud crested blazer
is the finest.
That's hand ticking
around the crest,
and these are the world-famous
corisso buttons
made from the finest
antelope horn.
Huh, then they'll match
my sneakers.
It looks fabulous on you.
Shall I wrap it up?
You know, I'm not sure.
I'll tell you what.
I'll come back later
with someone,
see what they think.
[SIGHS]
Uh-huh.
Really, I-- I'll be back.
Yeah.
JERRY:
So I didn't like the crest all that much,
but the guy spent
15 minutes with me.
So to get out of the store,
I told him I wanted to see
what someone else thought.
And then he makes a face
like he doesn't believe me.
Oh, so he knew
you were making it up?
Yeah, he caught me.
So here's what I want
you to do.
Come back with me
to the store,
and we'll pretend
to look at the coat.
That's ridiculous.
Why do you wanna go back there
if you don't want the coat?
Because he thinks I was lying.
I wanna show him I wasn't.
But you were.
But if you go back with me,
then I'm not.
All right, fine.
Whatever.
Problems
with the houseguest?
Oh-ho!
What houseguest?
This friend of Susan's
is staying with us
for two weeks.
Now, am I wrong,
or is that excessive?
Well, Bob Sacamano,
he stayed with me once
for a year and a half.
Who is he?
He's a wig master.
Hm? What is a wig master?
He's with the touring company
of Joseph and the Amazing
Technicolor Dreamcoat.
He's the guy
in charge of the wigs.
Boy, imagine liking wigs
to the point it becomes
a career choice.
So how about some tickets,
George?
You know, I'd--
I'd kill for a peek.
Yeah, yeah.
Sure, sure, sure.
I gotta drop my car off
at the new lot.
Oh, yeah.
What lot's that?
Jiffy Park.
It's incredible.
Seventy-five dollars a month.
Seventy-five bucks a month?
Yeah, you get this cool T-shirt
when you sign up.
Oh, I'm down.
JERRY:
Remember me?
I said I'd come back
with someone, and I did.
Surprised?
No, I believed you.
Oh.
This is Elaine.
Oh, hello. I'm Craig.
Oh, hi.
Well...here it is.
Oh.
Joseph Abboud.
And look at this hand ticking
around the crest.
You know your clothes.
Well, I'm in the biz. I, uh--
I work for J. Peterman.
I love J. Peterman.
Oh.
I especially enjoy
the catalog.
Those fanciful narratives
really take me away.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You know what?
I write those.
No.
Yeah.
Elaine, what about the crest?
What do you think
of the crest here?
Well, I love it.
You what?
I think it's great.
I think you should get it.
Well...
Will it be check
or credit card?
Check.
I'll need you to write down
your phone number
on the check for me.
Perhaps you could
do the same.
[GIGGLES]
You weren't supposed to
say that.
But I really did
like it.
That's not the point.
You put me in a position
where I had no choice.
Oh, sorry.
What about that guy asking you
out right in front of me?
What is the big deal?
It was very emasculating.
He doesn't know the nature
of our relationship.
You're there approving
new clothes.
That's a girlfriend job.
How dare he?
He dared.
Hi, George.
How was your day?
Good. Good day.
You?
I am getting
so much work done.
See?
Very nice.
Hey, sweetie,
how was your day?
I already asked him that.
He said, "Good. Good day."
[BOTH LAUGH]
Thank God you're home.
I'm locked out.
I dropped my car
at Jiffy Park,
and I forgot to take
my apartment key off the ring.
So you got my spare?
No, I gave it back to you.
You did?
Well, look,
can you take me over there?
Oh, come on.
Oh, come on, Jerry.
It's all the way over
to 12th Avenue.
I didn't tell you
to park in that lot.
Now someone's gotta drive you
every time you need your car?
Take the bus.
I'm not gonna take the bus.
That's why I got a car.
Forget it.
All right, I'm gonna get
George to pick me up.
He won't take you.
[PHONE RINGS]
Got it, got it.
Hello?
Listen, can you take me over
to Jiffy Park?
Yeah, I'll pick you up
right now.
All right. Okay.
Hey, gotta go.
[RADIO STATIONS CHANGING]
So the wig mas--
The wig master said you could
stop by the theater tonight,
and he'll show you around.
[RADIO STATIONS CHANGING]
Would you pick a station?!
I like 'em all.
[RADIO STATIONS CHANGING]
[STATIC BUZZES]
Oh, great.
Now the volume knob
fell off.
What's this?
Oh, God.
What?
It's a c--
It's a condom!
Ah!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
ELAINE:
How do you like working there
at The, uh, Andover Shop?
I mean, it's pretty swanky.
Upscale clientele.
Mm.
Except for Jerry.
[BOTH LAUGH]
So did you see anything
you liked?
Oh.
'Cause I can get you
a, um, considerable discount.
Really?
Hm.
Well, actually, yeah,
I did see this...
amazing little black dress.
It was, uh, sleeveless.
The Nicole Miller.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll take care of it.
Really?
But I barely know you.
Well, we'll, um,
just have to do something
about that.
Won't we?
Ah, ah, ah.
Hey, Greg.
It's Craig.
Oh, right.
Nice lunch with Elaine?
Yes, lovely.
You know,
I'm just curious,
how did you know
she wasn't my girlfriend?
Well, I could just sense it.
Because, you know,
we used to go out.
Oh, you did?
Oh, yeah, we went
way out and wild.
Mm.
Hey, Jer.
Hi, Elaine.
Would you like to buy a rose
for your wife?
[BOTH LAUGH]
How do you know
she's not my wife?
GEORGE:
I wanna know,
how did that
get into my car?
Hey, look,
you walk in this city,
you gotta expect things are
gonna stick to your foot.
You open your car
and bing! Condom.
That doesn't explain
the lipstick on the dashboard.
Here, take a few shirts.
What?
I'm terribly sorry,
Mr. Kramer,
but we can't get
your car now.
The keys seem
to have been misplaced.
Wait a minute.
I need those keys.
I won't be able
to get into my apartment.
Hey, Mr. Kramer...
you like Cadillacs?
Yeah, I like Cadillacs.
Why, what do you got
on your mind?
Take that pink Cadillac
Eldorado over there.
It's a Mary Kay car.
Mary Kay?
Mary Kay car.
Listen, I'll see you later.
Thanks for driving me by.
Hey, what's happening?
I'm gonna hang around here
a little while.
Something funny going on here.
ELAINE:
You were wrong
about Craig,
he's a very sweet guy.
Well, what about the ponytail?
What about it?
Come on.
Ponytail? Get real.
All I know is he promised me
a discount on that dress.
Of course he did.
The guy's working you.
Oh, Jerry, I've been
around enough
to know when
I'm being worked.
Have you slept with him yet?
I just met him
this morning.
It's been known to happen.
I'm telling you right now,
Elaine,
this guy's gonna dangle
that dress in front of you
like a dirt farmer dangles
a carrot in front of a mule.
Well, this is
all very flattering--
Like a shark fisherman
with a bucket of chum.
Okay.
Like a shrimp farmer--
O-kay.
WIG MASTER:
Well, that's the grand tour, uh, but...
I saved the best for last.
Oh, yeah.
Behold,
the Technicolor Dreamcoat.
Whoo. Chok! Wow!
Spectacular.
Excuse me. Would--?
Would you mind if I
ask you a few questions?
Are you a cop?
Oh, no, no.
No, I'm not a cop.
I, uh-- I work
for the Yankees.
Ugh, they stink.
Nevertheless,
I-- I, uh...
was wondering
if you and your friends
are...doing business
here at the Jiffy Park?
You know,
what do you people call it?
Turning tricks?
Anyway, see, the thing is,
I-I-I found a condom in my car.
Now, I'm not saying
it's yours, I just--
I wanna know if I should
change parking lots.
Get lost, mister.
I'm trying to make
a living here.
I'll pay you
for your time.
I just-- I just need
some information.
How much do you want?
Ten? Fifteen?
You have change for a 20?
Fifteen?
George?
Hi, honey.
Well, I hope that
you're telling me the truth.
Of course
I'm telling the truth.
Because I have to be
able to trust you.
If I can't trust you,
there's no way
that this can work.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, then you really have
something to think about
because, you know, if there's
any doubt in your mind--
And it doesn't even have
to be a big doubt, you know,
even a-- A tiny doubt,
a dot of a doubt--
There's no doubt.
Because if there's
any doubt at all,
I feel that we should
cultivate it.
Cultivate it?
Yes, you know,
deal with it.
We have to deal
with the doubt, Susan.
The doubt!
Must be dealt with.
I have no doubt,
George.
Do you?
No.
You know, I can't wait
to get that dress.
Yeah, it should
arrive imminently.
Arrive?
Yes, from Milan.
But you said
it was in the store.
No, no, no. We sold out.
We've had to order some more.
But I thought
Nicole Miller was ma--
Well--
Ian.
Hey, Craig.
Elaine, this is Ian.
Oh, hi, Ian.
"Een."
Ian.
He's a friend of mine
from England.
So tell me,
how are you doing?
Well, I'm working over
at The Andover Shop, actually.
You should come by.
I'll get you a great discount.
Maybe I will.
Nice meeting you.
Oh, nice to meet you too.
Cheerio.
Bye, Een.
So you getting him
a discount too?
Well, why so surprised?
Oh, no reason.
[LAUGHS]
JERRY:
You know,
that clothing salesman
had a lot of nerve
hitting on Elaine
right in front of me.
He stands to make
a big commission too
on that jacket with the crest
that nobody seems to like.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna take that jacket back.
I'm putting this guy
right out of commission!
All right.
I'm gonna turn in.
Turn in?
Yeah, I had a tough day.
It's only 9:00.
Yeah, well, you know,
I don't argue
with the body, Jerry.
That's an argument
you can't win.
I can't go to sleep at 9:00.
Well, you can
go to your room and read.
Hey, look, you know,
you're the one who's locked out.
I'm letting you stay here.
You're wearing my bathrobe.
You should adapt to me.
But I'm tired.
Well, why don't you go
sleep at Newman's?
Oh, he's got
a girl up there.
This quilt is too thin.
Know I'm gonna get cold.
I don't even fit on this couch.
Don't even know
if I'm gonna sleep.
Well, that's all
I've got.
Well, can I sleep with you?
Huh?
Well, you've got
that big, comfortable bed
and that nice,
warm quilt.
Kramer, there's no way
you're sleeping with me.
Why?
Yeah.
Do I really have to
explain why?
Well, I--
Hey.
What's that?
Squire's walking stick.
I had to write about it
for the catalog.
Oh. Wow.
You want it?
Yeah.
You can have it.
I don't need it anymore.
Oh, mama.
Okay, so I am positive
you are wrong about Craig.
Yeah, why?
Because he told a man
he'd give him a discount too.
A man, Jerry.
So? Who is he?
Some friend of his
from England.
Don't you see?
It's all a big scam.
You're nuts.
Well, how do you know
he's not wondering
the same thing about you?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Well, perhaps he thinks
that you're working him
for the discount.
Shaking that little butt
of yours
into big, big savings.
Then when you get it,
you know, you drop him
like a hot potato.
Oh, please.
No, see, the two of you
need to work on trust.
And then, and only then,
will there be a free exchange
of sex and discounts.
The cornerstones
of a healthy relationship.
And now,
if you would excuse us,
we need to get to bed.
Yeah.
This patio furniture's
on sale.
Excuse me, uh...
I think I made
a big mistake.
I-I'd like my deposit back,
please.
What's the problem?
You got hookers turning
tricks in my car.
How's that for starters?
Eh, that is all hearsay.
All right, very good.
I'd like my car and
my deposit back, please.
Can't do it.
What do you mean?
If you read the agreement
you signed,
the deposit is nonrefundable.
Well, does it say anything
in the contract
about my car being used
as a whorehouse?
Because I don't remember
reading that clause either.
What can I tell you, buddy?
Take it up
with Consumer Affairs.
All right,
just give me my car
and let me get
the hell out of here.
That's going to be
a problem.
Why?
It's all the way
in the back.
We can't get it out
for a couple of days.
What are you talking about?
I want my car.
We ask that you
please bear with us.
Bear with you?
This is a parking lot.
People are supposed to be
able to get their cars!
Ideally.
JERRY:
Uh, excuse me, I'd like to return
this jacket.
Certainly.
May I ask why?
For spite.
Spite?
That's right.
I don't care for the salesman
that sold it to me.
I don't think you can
return an item for spite.
What do you mean?
Well, if there was
some problem with the garment,
if it were unsatisfactory
in some way,
then we could do it for you.
But I'm afraid
spite doesn't fit
any of our conditions
for a refund.
That's ridiculous.
I wanna return it.
What's the difference
what the reason is?
Let me speak
with the manager.
Excuse me.
Bob?
This gentleman...
[WHISPERING]
...spite.
What seems to be
the problem?
Well, I wanna return
this jacket.
And she asked me why
and I said, "For spite,"
and now she won't
take it back.
Um, that's true.
We can't return an item
based purely on spite.
Well, so fine, then.
Then I don't want it.
That's why I'm returning it.
Well, you already said
spite, so...
But I changed my mind.
No. You said spite.
Too late.
Nice hat.
Get a calendar, honey.
It's the '90s.
KRAMER:
Elaine.
Oh, hey.
These are my friends,
Jerry and Elaine.
Hi.
Hi, how are you doing?
I'm Charmaine.
I'm Ethan.
Yeah, she's
the costume designer,
and he's the wig master
for the show.
Oh, you're staying
with my friend George.
Right, George. I get the feeling
he doesn't want me there.
Ah, he doesn't even want
himself there.
[ALL LAUGH]
Why don't you sit down
and join us?
All right.
I can't. I've gotta go
meet a friend.
Well, what are we,
dog meat?
Another champagne
coolie, please.
You have really beautiful hair.
Oh, thanks.
Thanks very much.
Ever thought about selling it?
Would make a brilliant wig.
They make wigs
out of human hair?
And pay plenty for them.
Okay, well, you guys
are gonna have fun here.
All right.
See you later.
Bye.
Oh, I just remembered,
I gotta get the Dreamcoat
from the dry cleaner.
You're gonna let me wear
the other one, right?
Yeah, but you have
to be careful.
It's my only backup.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye.
Oh.
There's
your champagne coolie.
Well, looks like it's just
you and me, cowboy.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hm.
ELAINE:
Well, here we are.
I am beat.
Hm.
Oh, that's nice.
So, um...
So do you have any idea
when the Nicole Millers
are coming in?
Oh, yeah,
the Nicole Millers.
Um, well-- Well,
the funniest thing.
Huh.
I've learned that the new
shipment's coming by boat,
which does tend
to take a bit longer,
you know, what,
with the waves and all.
So, um, you'll just have
to be a little bit patient.
Oh.
So you have no idea
when they'll arrive?
[YAWNING]
No, I'm really not sure.
How can you love
a guy like that?
He's a mess.
I just don't see
them together at all.
Ethan?
Yes?
Hi, it's me, Jesse.
Um....George Hamilton's
personal assistant.
Right, right.
How are you?
Good.
Good to see you.
This is Jerry.
Hello.
Yeah. Um...
Ethan, what brings
you to town?
Joseph and the Amazing
Technicolor Dreamcoat.
You're kidding.
Listen, maybe you and I
should, um, get together.
Have you been on the slide
at Club USA? It's...intense.
JERRY:
Excuse me.
Are you asking him out?
Yeah, I guess
you could say that.
Right in front of me?
How do you know
we're not together?
Two guys sitting, laughing,
drinking champagne coolies.
I don't know.
I just didn't think you were.
Well, we're sitting
here together.
Why wouldn't
you think that?
I don't know.
I just didn't.
Well, it's very emasculating.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hi, this is Bob
from The Andover Shop.
I'm trying to reach
Craig Stewart.
He left this number.
Oh, um, is it important?
Well...
Hey, let me ask you something.
Uh, do you know when
the Nicole Millers are
coming in from Milan?
Nicole Millers?
We aren't expecting
any Nicole Millers. In fact,
we have too many
as it is.
Well, do you have any
in a size four?
Yes, several.
Just tell him he doesn't have
to be in tomorrow until 11.
Oh, yeah, I'll make sure
he gets the message.
JERRY:
They make wigs out of human hair?
ETHAN:
And pay plenty for them.
JERRY:
Hm.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[FUNKY DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Break it down ♪
Jesus.
Oh, sweet Maria.
Hey, let's go.
What are you doin' in my car?
Hey, hey, hey!
Where are you going?!
Hey, you just cost me
some money!
Cool it, lady.
Ow.
Cool it. Cool it, lady.
Cool it.
[SIREN WAILS]
MAN:
Police officers, freeze right there.
[FUNKY DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN [OVER SPEAKERS]:
Okay, big daddy, take the hat off.
All right, turn to your right.
I said turn, pimp!
[WHIMPERS]
I'm not a pimp.
[♪]