The other thing I love
is when you're
in the middle of a dream
and your alarm goes off,
you incorporate the sound
of the alarm into the dream
so you can keep sleeping.
And you'll make any adjustment
in the dream to do it.
I was with Marie Antoinette
in a dream last night,
and she was on the guillotine,
the blade came down,
her head fell in the basket,
it rolled over,
and she started singing
Neil Diamond's "Solitary Man."
And I thought,
"That is not my alarm going off.
This is actually happening."
It's June!
It's June! Hey!
[LAUGHING]
It's June!
It's June, June, June, June!
It's June. Ha-ha!
It's June! June!
Ju-uuu-une!
Hey, it's June!
[HORN HONKING]
[♪]
GEORGE:
June!
Juuuuune, baby!
What?
The catering hall screwed up.
The wedding
is delayed until June!
It's like a stay of execution.
Dead man walkin'.
This is my lucky day.
Well, one out of 20,000.
That's not bad.
Hey, wait a second.
You know, good news for you too.
Susan's best friend, Hallie,
broke up with her boyfriend.
She did?
Yeah.
So? Wheels?
In motion.
The wheels are in motion.
Beautiful.
Hey, if this works out,
forget about it.
Vacations together,
movies together,
dinner together.
It's almost as good
as if I didn't get married.
So set it up. We can have
dinner at the Friars Club.
The Friars Club?
I'm thinking of joining.
Pat Cooper said he would
put me up for membership.
Hey. Listen,
do me a favor, will you?
I got a hot date tonight
with Connie.
Knock on my door, wake me up
in 20 minutes, all right?
Catnap?
No, no, no, no.
This is evolutionary.
I've been reading this book
on Leonardo da Vinci.
See, that means "from Vinci."
Did you know that?
Must be some book.
Yeah.
Well, it turns out
that the master slept
only 20 minutes
every three hours.
That works out
to two and a half extra days
that I'm awake per week,
every week.
Which means
if I live to be 80,
I will have lived the equivalent
of 105 years.
Not to mention how much
you'll accomplish.
I got a lot of things
in the hopper.
I didn't know you had one.
Oh, I got a hopper.
A big hopper.
[♪]
PETERMAN:
All right, people.
I'd like to begin with a hearty
"hail and well met, good fellow"
to Bob Grossberg, joining us
from Business Affairs.
[APPLAUSE]
Thanks. Hi, everybody.
Bob, we have a little baptism
by fire for you, so to speak.
Poor bastard.
I want you to handle
all the fact-checking
and the copyediting
for the new catalog.
Could you repeat that?
Why don't you handle
all the copyediting?
I'm-- I'm sorry. What?
Copyediting.
Uh, never mind.
Elaine, you do it.
[♪]
Hi, I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
Pat Cooper made
a reservation.
Yes, Mr. Seinfeld, but, um,
all gentlemen are required
to wear jackets
in the dining room.
Oh. I'm sorry.
How embarrassing
this must be for you.
You just bought
your own dinner.
No problem.
Please, follow me.
Excuse me.
Ha-ho! Funny.
Isn't he funny? Funny guy.
[LAUGHS]
Friars.
Hey, not bad.
I kind of like
this little thing here.
SUSAN:
It's nice.
This way, please.
Here we go.
[♪]
Come on.
I'm telling you,
I can coach for the NFL.
It's not that hard.
That might be the stupidest
thing you've ever said.
Oh, get outta here.
Come on.
No, the stupidest thing
you ever said
was when Steve Kroft
from 60 Minutes
is the same guy
from Seals & Croft.
You watch the old videos.
I'm telling you, look at them.
Oh, come on.
[♪]
This is nice.
Hey, morning.
Morning?
Yeah, what time is it?
Ten-thirty.
Ah. See? I got the whole night
ahead of me.
Boy, that's a nice jacket.
Oh, I don't believe this.
I forgot to give it back.
It belongs to the Friars Club.
Yeah, I like that crest.
All right.
Breakfast?
Oh, yeah.
Most important meal
of the day.
So this da Vinci sleep
is working out?
Oh, I'm percolating, Jerry.
I'm telling you,
I have never felt so fertile.
I'm mossy, Jerry.
My brain is mossy.
Listen to this idea:
A restaurant that serves
only peanut butter and jelly.
What do you call it?
PB and J's.
What do you think?
I think you need
more sleep.
Dah.
So how'd your date work out
with the mysterious Connie?
I am telling you,
this woman is strange.
She never wants to leave
the apartment.
It's almost like she doesn't
wanna be seen with me.
Ah, you're being ridiculous.
Yeah.
No milk?
Oh, I'll be back.
[♪]
Where--?
Jerry?
Hey, Jerry.
Come on, buddy.
Kramer.
Are you awake?
Why? What time is it?
It's 4.
Four in the morning?
Yeah.
What's wrong with you?
I'm bored.
All this free time on my hands,
I don't know what to do.
You wanna do something?
No. Would you just get out?
Well, you wanna rent a movie?
No.
Well, what am I gonna do?
[♪]
JERRY:
Ready for lunch?
I'm stuck here
editing
the stupid catalog
because of stupid Bob Grossberg.
Listen, there's something really
suspicious about this guy.
Every time Mr. Peterman
tries to assign him any work,
he says he can't hear.
And it all gets dumped on me.
You think he's faking?
I don't know,
but I'd like to try
that earpiece on,
see if it's real.
Hey, Elaine.
Oh, you have a friend.
Just wanted to say hi.
Bob, you know what?
Um, I'm kind of swamped here.
You think you could give me
a hand with some of the catalog?
I-I'm sorry. What?
I'm kind of swamped.
Thank you.
I'm having lunch with Mr. P.
I better get goin'.
Did you see that?
Did you see that, Jerry?
That was him?
Yes.
Somehow I thought
he'd be taller.
All right. Listen.
We'll have to do this again
some other time, okay?
I got a lot of work
to do.
See you later.
All right.
Hey, Bob.
Bob?
Hey, Bobby, over here.
Oh, Bob?
Bob?
Hey.
Elaine.
Hi.
I was just in the bathroom.
Okay, Jerry, please, please.
I'm really busy here.
No, no. I was just
in the bathroom with Bob.
So what?
No, I kind of tried
to test his hearing.
Get out! What did you do?
I snuck up behind him
at the urinal
and tried to see
if he could hear me.
And?
Well...he flinched...sort of.
What do you mean, sort of?
What did he do?
Well, he kind of moved his head,
you know?
But it might have been
on the zip-up, I don't know.
So you don't know anything?
Actually, no.
All right. Good job.
Right.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
Last night, huh?
Was that something,
or was that something?
That was something.
She's great, isn't she?
Fantastic. Fantastic woman.
I told you.
I'm nuts about her.
You think she could be an it?
Could she be an it?
She could be an it.
We might have an it!
"It" written all over her.
She's got everything, right?
She's intelligent, smart,
got a great sense of humor.
I don't know.
I didn't really talk to her.
Well, she's smart.
You take my word for it.
Whatever.
We could be like the Gatsbys.
Didn't they always have, like,
a bunch of people around,
and they were all best friends?
That doesn't sound right.
No.
So tonight she's got tickets
for that show
she's been working on,
The Flying Sandos Brothers.
Flying Sandos, beautiful.
Great, 7:30, all right?
Walk me down to the Friars.
Sure.
So, Jerry, there's an empty
apartment in my building.
If you and Hallie want,
we could try to hold it maybe.
It's not here.
What?
The jacket.
It's not here.
It's gotta be here
somewhere.
Oh, boy.
Thanks for that 4 a.m.
wake-up call last night.
Where the hell
is that jacket?
Oh, the one with the crest?
Yeah.
Oh, well,
that's at the cleaner's.
The cleaner's?
How did it get there?
Well, I borrowed it
last night,
and it got
a little dirty.
Great.
Somehow I dozed off and
woke up in a pile of garbage.
Somehow?
You've had an hour and 20
minutes sleep in three days.
Well, so look,
the cleaner's said
you could pick it up
tonight at 6.
All right, I just hope
I can get it to the Friars Club
before the show.
Won't be a problem,
don't worry about it.
Hey.
Hey!
Watch out, boy.
[♪]
Can you give us a hand
with some of these boxes, Bob?
Bob?
I want you so bad, Bob.
You turn me on so much.
You're so damn sexy. Ooh.
I'm starting to unbutton.
Anything getting through?
Bob?
[♪]
HALLIE:
They perform all over. Europe mostly.
GEORGE:
Ah-ha, European tours.
Sorry. Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Jerry.
You're wearing the jacket?
Yeah, it wasn't
ready on time.
I have to return it
after the show.
Sure, sure, sure.
How about these seats?
Are these fantastic, huh?
I feel like Lincoln.
Well, let's hope this evening
turns out a little better.
[WILD FOLK MUSIC PLAYING]
[♪]
So, um...
Are you sure you don't
wanna go to the movies?
No, Cosmo.
I like just being here with you.
Well, it's...
It's a bold adventure, huh?
Ooh.
Well, this is, uh,
risky business, huh?
I'm all atwitter.
[WILD FOLK MUSIC STILL PLAYING]
[CHEERING & APPLAUSE]
ALL:
Ho!
[MUSIC STOPS PLAYING]
[WILD FOLK MUSIC
RESUMES PLAYING]
How would you kind people
like to lend me a hand
with our next trick?
I don't think so.
Please, take off your jacket.
My jacket?
Yes, the jacket.
What do you say,
ladies and gentlemen?
[CHEERING & APPLAUSE]
You can't argue with that.
Come on.
Do it.
Come on, Jerry. Do it!
Give him the jacket.
Go ahead.
All right.
And now...
[DRUM ROLL PLAYING]
We say
the magic word:
Agra-ba.
And we make it disappear.
[♪]
[MOANS]
Oh, Cosmo.
[GIGGLES]
Cosmo.
Oh, Cosmo.
Honey, can you move a little?
This hurts.
Cosmo?
Oh, my God. Cosmo, wake up.
Oh, my God.
He's dead!
He's dead.
Yeah, Tommy, this is Connie.
You gotta help me.
Some guy dropped dead
on top of me.
I can't call the cops
'cause Joey might find out.
I can't. I'm stuck.
You gotta help me.
[♪]
GEORGE:
This is very exciting.
The inner sanctum here.
[CHUCKLES]
Hi, I was
in the audience earlier.
You threw my jacket down.
I just wanted to pick it up.
Jacket? What jacket?
I had a jacket
with a crest on it.
You came into the audience,
you threw it away.
"Agra-ba."
Are you sure it was me?
Well, it was you
or one of your brothers.
Well, two of them
have left already.
[SPEAKS FOREIGN DIALECT]
[BOTH SPEAKING FOREIGN DIALECT]
BOTH:
Nyea.
No.
It doesn't even belong to me.
It belongs to the Friars Club.
[LAUGHS]
Sorry.
Jerry, I'm sure it'll turn up.
I'm sure it won't.
Don't worry.
I'll get the jacket back.
All right, there you go.
She's gonna get the jacket back.
So let's go
get some coffee, huh?
I'm a little tired.
I think I'll go home.
Oh, that's too bad.
What? Really?
Yeah, we'll do it another time.
George, we'll go.
[♪]
[BOTH SIGH]
Hey, oh...
Broke a shoelace today.
Oh, I can get you
shoelaces tomorrow.
Okay.
So, what color?
Brown.
Maybe a black.
More coffee?
No, check...please.
[♪]
That nut is always
up to something.
[♪]
[SHIP HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
Hey!
Sha--!
Mama!
[HORN BLARING]
No!
Help!
[♪]
PETERMAN:
Elaine...
I think I've been
working you
a little too hard
lately.
Oh.
So I have
two tickets for you
to The Flying Sandos Brothers
magic show.
Ah.
It is a real hoot.
Well, thank you, Mr. Peterman.
The tickets are for tonight,
so you and Bob can...
knock off a little early
so you both can get ready.
Mr. Peterman, you--
There's no need
to deny it, Elaine.
I heard every word you said.
And I know you wouldn't
be just having fun
with his handicap.
Ooh, that kind of cruelty
would be grounds for dismissal.
Of course, Mr. Peterman.
JERRY:
Tell him I'll come down and talk to him. Okay. Bye.
Well, that was
the Friars Club.
You think they're gonna
let a jacket stealer join?
I don't think so.
They're gonna charge me
$800 for the jacket,
and I gotta deal
with Pat Cooper.
What kind of show
is that Sandos Brothers?
They take your jacket,
and then they just throw it?
Wh--? I never heard of that.
It was a little unusual.
So Susan and I
were thinking
dinner at our house
Saturday night.
Just the four of us.
No, I don't think so.
Why not?
I don't know.
I'm a little turned off.
Come on, what are
you talkin' about?
I'm...
I'm kind of soured.
You're soured?
Yeah, I'm soured.
Don't be soured.
I'm sorry. I'm soured.
Are you kidding me?
We were all getting along.
Where is all this coming from?
Frankly, I didn't think she was
too concerned about my jacket.
What are you talking about?
She's very concerned.
She said she was
gonna get it back.
Yeah, we'll see.
Because if she gets it back,
then you'll have
no reason to be sour.
You'll de-sour, right?
I'll try and de-sour.
Oh, that's not good enough.
You don't try and de-sour.
You have to sweeten too.
I'll try.
I'll try and de-sour
and sweeten.
I wanna get it back
to when we were the Gatsbys.
I still don't know
what that means.
Yeah.
[GROANS]
God.
Oh, my God,
what happened to you?
She tried to kill me, Jerry!
Who?
Connie!
What did she do?
I don't know.
But I woke up
in the Hudson River in a sack!
I think she drugged me.
But she's a murderer,
and I'm calling the cops.
Why would she try
and kill you?
Well, isn't it obvious?
She doesn't want anybody else
to have me!
Yah!
[♪]
JERRY:
Hey, there's Uncle Miltie.
Yeah, it is.
And there's
David Steinberg.
The comedian
or the manager?
The manager.
Hey, there's Pat.
Hey, Pat.
Hey, what the hell
went wrong?
What's the matter with you?
What are you, a kleptomaniac?
I forgot to take it off.
You forgot to take it off?
Oh, you go
into a department store,
you put a suit on,
and you walk right out.
What are you,
some sort of an idiot?
I'm sorry.
Where's the jacket?
Well, one of the Gypsies
took it.
Oh, the Gypsies took it.
Of course,
New York has a lot of Gypsies.
Ooh, on every block,
there's a Gypsy.
Well, it's true.
I saw it.
Excuse me.
Are you an entertainer?
Are you in show business?
No, I--
Then what
am I talking to you for?
Jerry, bring the jacket
back tomorrow.
All right.
GEORGE:
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Look at that guy.
There, isn't that
the guy from the show?
He's wearing the jacket.
JERRY:
Oh, my God.
You're right.
Come on.
Wait a second.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Are you members?
Well, I'm a prospective member.
Until then,
that's the way out.
But that guy has my jacket.
Come on. Let's go.
Excuse me. The guy is wearing
a jacket that my--
Come on.
Let's go.
If I could talk
to the guy--
BOB:
These seats are fantastic.
It was really nice
of Mr. Peterman
to give us these tickets.
Yeah. Yeah, it was nice.
Yeah...
we got our own little
private box here, don't we?
Get off of me.
Stop it.
Get off of me!
[HUFFING]
Get ahold of yourself!
Bob, get ahold of yourself!
[♪]
I don't know how that guy gave
us the slip at the Friars Club.
Told you, he probably
went out the back.
Oh.
Hey, it's you.
That's my Friars Club jacket.
No, it is not.
This is my jacket.
No, no, that's my jacket.
Give it back.
Come on.
I need this jacket.
[ALL CLAMORING]
I wanna join.
I need it
to become a member.
Help! Help!
[YELLING IN FOREIGN DIALECT]
What is he yelling about?
They're stealing jackets here.
I can't believe it.
JERRY:
Hey, George, you know what?
What?
I think this crest
is different.
It's got
a moose on it.
Moose?
Yeah.
I don't think
this is the jacket.
No, it's not.
This is the jacket.
Oh, she got the jacket back.
It's the-- Yeah.
That's great.
Thank you.
It got a little dirty,
so they wanted to clean it
before they gave it
back to you.
That's nice of them.
That is really nice.
This is nice.
Yeah.
Say, you know--
Let's call Susan.
We'll go have coffee.
I'll see you at the wedding.
[♪]
Great. Now she's sour.
Maybe she'll sweeten.
She won't sweeten.
And I'm bitter!
There they are!
Here. Here, we'll leave it
there for you.
[ALARM RINGING]
[ALARM CONTINUES RINGING,
HEARING DEVICE BEEPING]
[♪]
That's her, officer.
Kramer. Oh, my God.
I thought you were--
What, sleeping with the fishes?
I guess I woke up.
You're under arrest
for the attempted murder
of Cosmo Kramer.
I didn't do anything.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Get your coat.
Gotta take you in.
Can I call my lawyer?
Okay. Go ahead.
[♪]
[RINGING]
You gotta meet me
at the police station.
They're arresting me
for attempted murder.
Attempted murder? Of who?
This guy, Kramer.
Whoa.
Cosmo Kramer?
Yeah, that's right.
I don't want nothing
to do with it.
[♪]