Hey, have you seen
these commercials
for indigestion
drugs?
Pepcid AC.
Tagamet HB?
Ugh. Whole country's
sick to their stomachs.
You know you're supposed
to take these things
before you get sick?
What is this, a bit?
No.
Because I'm not
in the mood.
We're just talking.
Is this not the greatest
marketing ploy ever?
If you feel good,
you're supposed to take one.
Yeah, I know that tone.
This is a bit.
They've opened up
a whole new market.
Medication for the well.
All right. Are you done
with your little amusement?
Then you admit
it was amusing?
It was okay.
But move the "medication
for the well" to the front
and hit the word
"good" harder.
Great. Thanks.
So your firm designed
all the furniture
in here?
Well, we manufacture it.
The original designs
are by Karl Fardman.
Oh. Fardman.
Do you know Fardman?
Mm. Love Fardman.
Most people go
their whole lives
without sitting
in a Fardman.
Well-- If you call that living.
[LAUGHS]
[THE EAGLES'
"DESPERADO" PLAYING]
♪ Desperado ♪
Wouldn't it be great if
Fardman designed shoes?
Brett? Don't you think
that would be great?
Brett?
After the song, babe.
Huh?
This song.
♪ Oh, you're a hard one ♪
So when do I meet
this jerk?
He's not a jerk, Jer.
He only works with
Karl Fardman.
Who?
I don't know.
Some designer.
Anyway, Brett is
so generous. And sensitive.
Last night, he was moved
just listening to a song.
What song?
"Desperado."
"Desperado"?
Uh-huh.
And you're still
dating him?
I'll tell you who sounds
a little desperado.
See that salesman
twirling that umbrella?
Uh-huh.
I invented that.
That had to be
invented?
When I started out as
a comedian, I sold umbrellas.
It was my idea to twirl it
to attract customers. [SCOFFS]
Oh, really?
Well, why don't
we ask him about it?
Elaine.
Excuse me.
Hey, how you doing?
Um, my, uh,
friend here
says that
he invented
that little twirl
you're doing.
Elaine, please.
It was a long time ago.
The man doesn't want
a history lesson.
Teddy Padilac
came up with this twirl.
Oh.
I know Teddy Padilac.
I worked with him
on 48th and Sixth.
Yeah. That's where
he come up with it.
In his dreams.
All right. Can we go?
By the way, you're
doing it too fast.
You'll disorient
the customers.
It's the twirling
that dazzles the eye.
I find it disorienting.
Who buys an umbrella anyway?
You can get 'em for free
in the coffee shop
in the metal cans.
Those belong to people.
Hey. Well...
this was downstairs
for you.
Ka-ching.
Oh, no.
Not more checks.
They're coming in faster
than I can sign 'em.
What checks?
Oh, you didn't hear?
Jerry's a big star in Japan.
I don't know
why.
There's a one-second
clip of me
in the opening credits of
some Japanese comedy show.
Yeah, The Super Terrific
Happy Hour.
They run it
all the time.
Now I'm starting to get
these royalty checks.
Look at all of those.
You're rich.
No. Each one is
for, like, 12 cents.
It's barely worth the pain
in my hand to sign them.
[EXHALES]
Yeah.
Jerry, you need
any new furniture?
Why?
Elaine's new boyfriend,
you know,
he's giving me this oversized
chest of drawers.
It's a Fardman.
He's giving you furniture?
Who is this guy?
Ah. Who are any
of her losers?
You're on that list.
Huh.
All right. I gotta go home
and open up at the house
for the carpet cleaners.
You know they're doing
my whole place for $25?
Oh, no, no, no.
Not the Sunshine
Carpet Cleaners?
Yeah. You heard of 'em?
They're a crazy
religious cult.
The carpet cleaning
is just a means
for them to get
into your apartment.
So? For a $25 cleaning,
I can listen to
some pointless blather.
I do it. I'm not even
getting the cleaning.
I signed over 100 checks
this morning.
Hello.
Twelve dollars.
Excuse me.
Would you please take
a picture, please.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Heh. What d--
I'm gonna ask
this guy something.
Hey, nice twirl
you got there.
You know who
invented that, don't you?
Hey, are you folks
from Japan?
Yes.
You recognize that mug?
That's the funny face
that greets you
at the beginning of
The Super Terrific Happy Hour.
Oh, Super Terrific!
Oh.
Yeah.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
Yeah, huh?
Yeah, that's him.
What is
he doing?
Well, I don't know,
but something
super-terrific, I'm sure.
That's funny.
Oh, yeah, very funny.
And it wouldn't be impolite
to laugh at his antics.
[LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Yeah. That's it.
Everybody laughs
at Jerry here in America.
[ALL LAUGHING]
We're pretty much
finished.
There's just
one more thing.
Here it comes.
[CLEARS THROAT]
You forgot to sign
your check.
Sorry.
You sure, uh...
there isn't
anything else?
No.
So that's it?
Unless you need a receipt.
I wish that was all
I needed.
Life can be so confusing.
I-I'm-- I'm searching
for answers anywhere.
Good luck
with that. But I--
Hey.
What's with the claw?
Super-terrific
carpal tunnel syndrome.
There's no sign
of Kramer.
Oh. Brett.
This is Jerry.
Hi.
That's very funny.
Elaine told me you're
some kind of comedian.
I'm one kind.
Have you seen
the chest of drawers
that Brett
gave to Kramer?
The Fleckman.
Fardman.
Right.
You gotta see 'em.
They're beautiful.
Oh, I'm sure they are.
I'd be happy
to get you some,
if that's what
you're driving at.
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
Don't worry. It's
no charge to you.
Looks like what you
really need is a decent desk
for writing
your skits.
I don't write skits.
Oh, of course you don't.
You don't have a proper
workstation.
I'll fax over
my catalog.
Mm. Brett, um...
[SCOFFS]
...Jerry doesn't
have a...
fax machine.
Oops.
Well, I'm sure things
will pick up for you soon.
[MOUTHS]
Thanks.
Elaine, maybe
we should get going.
Oh. Jerry,
you wanna join us?
Where you going?
The coffee shop?
[CHUCKLES]
I think we can do a little
better than that. [LAUGHS]
You look like
you could use a solid meal
at a real
restaurant.
You look like
you could use a--
Jerry.
KRAMER:
Three hundred dollars.
Hey, Mr. Oh.
How much would these
run you in Tokyo?
Uh...those are
30,000 yen.
Thirty thousand?
Well, these are
practically free.
Giddyup.
You're
a cowboy now.
BRETT:
I feel terrible about your friend, Jerry.
He's upset that I gave Kramer
that chest of drawers, isn't he?
Why? Why do you think
he's upset?
Well, how could
he not be?
Living in that cramped,
little apartment.
That outdated furniture.
So terribly
un-Karl-Fardman-like.
We're not gonna talk
about Karl Fardman
all night, are we?
I hope not.
[THE EAGLES' "DESPERADO"
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
Brett? Is everything
all right? What--?
Shh!
What is it?
Is there someone outside?
Elaine, the song.
Oh. Oh.
♪ Desperado ♪
Oh, phew.
For a minute there, I thought
it was that urban legend
about the guy with the hook
who's hanging on the--
Elaine, could you just
not talk for one minute?
♪ You've been out
Ridin' fences ♪
Sorry.
♪ For so long now ♪
JERRY:
No spiel?
Not a peep.
They just cleaned
the carpets and left.
Call themselves a cult.
So you're angry that
this bizarre carpet cabal
made no attempt
to abduct you?
They could have at least tried.
You know, maybe
they thought you looked
too smart to be
brainwashed.
Please.
Too dumb?
Well. Mackie's
back in town.
Nice duds.
Konnichiwa.
Yeah, it's a gift
from my Japanese friends.
They're known as
gift-givers.
And tonight, we're going dancing
at the Rainbow Room.
Sounds like you're throwing
their money around.
Well, Jerry,
they're Japanese.
I mean, that TV you watch,
that sushi you eat...
I mean, even that
kimono you wear...
Where do you think
all that money goes, huh?
That's right.
How'd you hook up
with these guys?
Well, they recognized Jerry from
The Super Terrific Happy Hour.
See, now, you should be doing
your own show in Japan.
Now, they get you.
What kind of show
am I gonna do in Japan?
All right, what did you do
with that pilot you did?
Yeah. The pilot.
Right. That had marvelous
production values.
And, you know, I do a lot
of business with Japanese TV.
They broadcast a lot of
American baseball.
They-- They got
an office here in New York.
Forget it.
The pilot was awful.
It failed.
It failed here.
Because here,
every time you turn on a TV,
all you see is four morons
sitting around an apartment
whining about their dates.
[SNAPS]
See...
George is right,
Jerry.
See, here, you're
just another apple.
But in Japan,
you're an exotic fruit...
like an orange,
which is rare there.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
JERRY [OVER TV]:
You had a date?
You went out with my butler?
Who said you could
go out with my butler?
Why do I need
your permission?
Because he's my butler.
[CHUCKLES]
So...what do
you think?
We're a bit
confused.
Why was this man
Jerry's butler?
Ah. Well, you see, the man
who is the butler, uh,
had gotten into
a car accident with Jerry.
And because, uh, he didn't
have any insurance,
the judge decreed
that the man
become Jerry's butler.
Is this customary
in your legal system?
No. That's what
makes it
such a humorous
situation.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
I'm sorry.
I'm sure
Mr. Seinfeld
is very funny
to Americans.
But I'm not sure
this, oh, butler show
would work
in Japan.
Oh, I, uh...
I disagree.
You've, uh-- You've been
living in America too long.
You've forgotten
what it's like
to have no oranges.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[JERRY
GASPS]
I'm sorry.
My hand is numb.
Yes. From endorsing
checks
for The Super Terrific
Happy Hour.
[LAUGHS]
You must go.
ELAINE:
Well, I think I'm on the outs with Brett.
I got shushed
during "Desperado."
What does he listen to,
the all "Desperado" station?
He is just in his own world
when he hears that song.
It's like I'm sitting there
in the car,
and he's...
out riding fences.
You know what you need,
is a song you can share.
Yeah. You're right.
We need to find our song.
Okay. So is there any song
that you feel
very strongly about?
I like "Witchy Woman."
"Witchy Woman"?
You know,
"Witchy Woman."
♪ Oh, oh, witchy woman ♪
Oh. Witch-eh Woman.
Hey, Elaine.
Hey.
Hey, how was the Rainbow Room?
Uh, well, we, uh--
We had to leave early.
There was a, uh,
slight monetary discrepancy
regarding the bill. Oh.
Uh, listen, uh, could I
borrow some pillows?
What for?
Yeah-- Well, uh, my Japanese
friends are gonna stay with me.
I thought they all had
suites at the Plaza.
Well, I'm sorry,
Jerry.
We all don't have checks
rolling in like you do.
Well, what about all that money
from the kimonos I wear?
Well, they ran out
of it.
I mean, Manhattan can be quite
pricey, even with 50,000 yen.
Fifty thousand yen?
Isn't that only
a few hundred dollars?
Evidently.
Oh, by the way,
tell Brett that his chest
of drawers are a big hit.
My guests are
very comfortable in them.
In them?
You have them
sleeping in drawers?
Jerry, have you
ever seen
the business hotels
in Tokyo?
They sleep in tiny
stacked cubicles all the time.
They feel
right at home.
This has international incident
written all over it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Good night,
Mr. Tanaka.
Good night.
Good night,
Mr. Oh.
Good night.
Good night,
Mr. Yamaguchi.
Oyasuminasai.
JERRY:
What is this?
Rice Krispies.
East meets West, Jerry.
Ah.
That's a lovely little
bureau-and-breakfast
you're running.
Well, I'm off to the bank.
Sayonara.
Konnichiwa.
[THE EAGLES' "WITCHY WOMAN"
PLAYING]
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
Elaine, I--
Shh, shh!
What do you think?
[TURNS RADIO OFF]
What are you doing?
That's "Witchy Woman."
I thought it could be
our song.
"Witchy Woman"
is okay for you,
but I've already
got a song.
Oh. Oh, well, then
how about "Desperado"?
We can share it.
No. It's mine.
[THUNDER
CLAPS]
Here you go.
Snap, crackle and pop.
Thank you
very much. Yeah.
Itadakimasu.
Good morning, Mr. Oh.
I gotta make up the drawer.
MR. OH:
Ugh. Come back in half-hour.
[GRUMBLES]
Hey, I'll
take one.
Well, look who's back.
Teddy. This is the guy says
he invented the twirl.
Jerry Seinfeld.
Teddy Padilac.
Long time, no see.
What do you got
in a push-button mini?
Same thing we had when
you bailed on us 15 years ago.
Bailed? Come on, you knew
I wanted to be a comedian.
Besides, we had some
good times.
Remember Tropical Storm Renee?
Oh, yeah, sure.
But where were you
during the poncho craze of '84?
I almost lost my house.
Umbrella, buddy?
Now we got that damn
urban sombrero to contend with.
Easy, Clicky.
I hear you're taking credit
for the twirl.
Oh, it was so many
years ago. Who cares?
I care. Clicky cares.
Look, could I-- Could I just
buy an umbrella?
Yeah, sure.
Two hundred dollars.
What?
Special price for a real
foul-weather friend.
Hey, George.
[CLAPS]
All right. How about
that tour, huh?
These guys are ready
to run the bases.
Kramer, it's--
It's raining. They got
the tarp on the field.
Uh, listen, George, uh, what
else can I do with these guys?
Now bear in mind, they're
a little light on the yen.
Well, I-- I-I got the pilot
of the Jerry show.
That's perfect.
How would you guys
like to watch
a Super Terrific Happy star,
Jerry Seinfeld?
Oh. Oh.
But we are also very hungry.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well...
you guys
just watch the tape,
and, uh, I'll
get you some food.
Go ahead. Yeah.
Sit down. Please.
KRAMER:
Hey! Peanuts!
George. George.
You got a minute?
Uh, George. Uh, did you call
some carpet cleaners?
Are they here?
Uh, they're in my office
right now.
They haven't said
anything to you?
About what?
What kind of a snobby,
stuck-up cult is this?
[HORN HONKS]
Hey, Jerry!
Oh, hi, Brett.
Haven't you ever
heard of an umbrella?
Uh, I didn't have
enough money.
Sure things will pick up
for you.
No, it's not that.
It's, uh...
Oh, no. Look at the checks.
Hours of hard work
ruined.
Oh, don't worry.
I can spot you the...
12 cents?
No. It's not the money.
It's my hand.
It's crippled from
writing and writing.
Nothing's working
for you, is it?
Not at the moment,
Brett.
I'd give you a ride,
but I got Karl Fardman here.
Thanks for
stopping.
Brett said you
ran away from him
as if he were
the boogity man?
Boogeyman.
Boogey?
I'm quite sure.
Anyway, any luck
getting together on a song?
No. He blew out
my "Witchy Woman."
And he won't share
"Desperado."
Hey, what do you think of
"Oye Como Va"?
Enh.
Well, I'm running
out of guys
here in this city,
Jer.
Hey. Great news.
I showed the pilot to
Kramer's Japanese friends.
They loved it!
Really? They bought
the butler character?
Did I tell you
that story's relatable?
That was
a great show!
That is why I'm
bringing it back to NBC.
NBC?
Nakahama Broadcast
Corporation.
Ah.
But they told us
we must go now.
Yeah. But now I have
my own market research.
Actual Japanese viewers...
[CLAPS]
...that loved the show.
I'm gonna talk to Kramer.
Hey, George,
do me a favor.
If they make you an offer--
whatever it is
--just take it.
Hey, by the way...
what'd you think
of Miss Yoshimura?
Who?
The network executive.
You think she
liked me?
[SHOUTING
INSIDE APARTMENT]
Yee!
Hey! Look at
who's here!
George, come on in.
Come on.
I want you
to come in here.
Come on in,
fat boy!
Get a good night's sleep.
All right, fellas?
Big day tomorrow!
[CHEERING]
All right!
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
JERRY:
Last one.
[GROANING]
Here you are.
[GASPS]
Ha-ha!
Where's the boys?
Uh, no, I let them
sleep in.
Yeah, I'm on my way to cash in
their plane tickets for them.
They need a little
food money.
The meeting starts
in 10 minutes.
No, well, I set
their alarm.
But they did have a lot
of sake in that hot tub.
I'm calling Jerry.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah?
Jerry!
The Japanese guys had sake
in the hot tub.
You gotta get 'em down here,
or I don't have
a focus group
to sell the pilot
to Japanese TV.
Uncle Leo?
Jerry!
All right, all right.
I'll wake 'em up.
Hm. Testy.
[CLUNKING, SHOUTING]
Hello?
MR. OH:
Mr. Jerry. Open the drawer, please.
It's stuck.
Ow.
Ah.
The steam from the hot tub
must have warped the wood.
MR. OH:
Pull harder.
I'm trying.
I can't get a grip.
My hand's had kind of
a bad week.
Very funny.
But no joking, please.
Uh, don't worry,
I'll get you out.
Brett, believe me,
you don't have to do this.
Elaine, I know
he'll appreciate this.
It's not as nice
as Kramer's cabinets,
but it's a start.
No, I promise you,
Jerry is not jealous
of Kramer's cabinets.
JERRY:
Move to the back of the drawers!
Jerry?
Jerry.
Not the Fardman!
[SCREAMS]
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
So, uh, gentlemen...
we have a deal?
Excuse me.
Did you hire
the Sunshine Carpet Cleaners?
Yes. To clean up
the coffee stain
left by Jerry Seinfeld.
Mr...
Mr. Wilhelm,
what are y--?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to clean
the carpets.
Most of the world
is carpeted,
and one day,
we will do the cleaning.
Him, you brainwashed?
What's he got
that I don't have?!
Mr. Wilhelm, listen,
you've been abducted.
Please, Mr. Wilhelm,
you gotta listen to me.
Wilhelm?
My name is Tanya.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[♪]
Brett, I'm--
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to hit you
in the head with...
an axe.
At least it was
just the handle.
Those beautiful cabinets.
What am I gonna tell--?
I can't remember his name.
Fleckman?
Calm down, Brett. Okay?
You could have a concussion.
Calm down.
♪ Desperado ♪
♪ Hm, hm, hm, hm ♪
ELAINE & JERRY:
♪ You better let somebody Love you ♪
♪ Let somebody love you ♪
♪ Before it's too... ♪
[SIREN WAILS]
His pulse is
fine.
Looks like a minor concussion.
Let me see what I can do
to relieve the swelling.
[THE EAGLES' "WITCHY WOMAN"
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
Doctor?
Doctor, I think
we're losing him.
♪ She got the moon in her eye ♪
[MACHINE BEEPS
RAPIDLY]