[♪]
Who was the last president
with a beard?
Nixon.
No, I mean a real thick beard.
His was thick.
I mean like a full, long beard,
like Smith Brothers cough drops.
Falkmore.
Who?
Artemis N. Falkmore.
You made that up, right?
Yeah. But it sounds
like a president name.
Yeah. Why do presidents
all have these bad names?
Woodrow, Grover, Millard.
The presidency attracts
the badly named.
Their ambition is based
on personal insecurity.
It's classic male
overcompensation.
Are you wearing lifts
in those shoes?
Cab.
[♪]
WOMAN:
So they have this clock now, where you punch in your age
and all your risk factors,
and it actually counts down
how much time
you have left to live.
What's the great moment?
On your deathbed,
they're pounding on your chest,
you're going,
"Ten, nine, eight--
I told you this thing was good."
I can't believe
this is our first date.
I know. How 'bout dessert?
I suppose I have to get
a piece of cake.
Why?
Today is my birthday.
What? Today?
Really?
Yep.
MEN: ♪ Happy Birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Lisa ♪
[♪]
GEORGE:
So she went out with you on a first date
and it was her birthday?
Yeah, and she picked the day.
Is she socially awkward?
No, she's great.
She's attractive and fun.
Well, maybe she decided
to celebrate her birthday
on the Monday
after the weekend.
She's not Lincoln.
Hey.
Anybody up for Lorenzo's pizza?
I'll pass.
Oh, really?
Hey, George, huh?
Pizza, yum-yum-yum.
Eh, I can't. I gotta go
down to the foundation.
I'm interviewing high schoolers
for the Susan Ross Scholarship.
Does it ever bother you
that this organization...
Nope.
...is beating the bushes...
No.
...to basically...
...give this money away...
No.
...to virtually anyone...
...as long as they're not you?
I'm fine with it.
[CHUCKLING]
Fine, I say.
[♪]
BOY:
And then I received
a 740 on the English
Achievement Test.
Quick,
what's your favorite animal?
I-- I don't know.
A frog?
Well, I-I--
Frog is wrong.
I see here
that you play the harp.
Tell me,
why do they have to tilt it?
Can't they just build it
on an angle?
Save you a lot of trouble. Heh.
Well, the modern-day harp
has been refined
over thousands of years
back to--
Yeah, yeah, we'll, uh--
We'll let you know.
I see your GPA is, uh, 4.0.
You like that, don't ya?
So, uh, Steven,
I see you're president
of the chess club.
State champs.
Who's your favorite
chess player?
[MUFFLED]
Nastercoff?
Right.
[MUFFLED]
Nastercoff.
What country is he from again?
[SIGHS]
I don't know.
I made it up.
I'm never gonna get
this thing.
Wha-- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[CHUCKLING]
What are you telling me for?
You really had me going there.
Yeah, sit down.
What do you want to do
when you grow up?
Well, I've been telling people
that I'd like to be
an architect.
[♪]
ELAINE:
So get this,
Mr. Peterman is finally
letting me do some real writing.
He's got this book deal
for his autobiography.
He's gonna let me
ghostwrite it.
That's great.
When it comes out,
I'll get someone
to ghost-read it.
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey. Oh, hi.
Hey.
So there I am at Lorenzo's,
loading up my slice
at the fixings bar.
Garlic and whatnot.
Mm-mm.
When I see this guy
over at the pizza boxes
giving me the stink eye.
So I give him
the crook eye back, you know?
And I notice
that he's not alone.
I'm taking on
the entire Van Buren Boys.
Van Buren Boys?
Yeah.
There's a street gang
named after President
Martin Van Buren?
Oh, yeah, and they're just
as mean as he was.
So I make a move
to the door, you know?
Vrrr. They block it.
So I lunge for the bathroom.
I grab the knob.
Occupato.
Then they back me up
against the cartoon map
of Italy,
and all of a sudden
they just stop.
What? What happened?
Because I'm still holding
the garlic shaker,
you know, like this:
I'm only showing eight fingers.
Well, what does that mean?
That's their secret sign.
See, Van Buren,
he was the eighth president.
They thought I was
a former Van B Boy.
Wow.
How was the pizza?
It was a little oily.
[♪]
Oh, Jerry,
can you hold on a sec?
I just wanna check my messages.
Oh.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, Melissa, Kim.
Ellen.
Hey.
You guys,
I want you to meet Jerry.
MELISSA:
Oh, we've heard a lot about you.
[CHUCKLES]
It is so sweet of you
to take her out.
Yeah, you don't even know
how much she needs this.
Is she coming off
a bad breakup?
No.
See ya.
Get your messages?
Yeah. No one called.
[♪]
JERRY:
They acted like it was
some act of charity,
just going out with her.
So she's the loser of the group.
Every group has someone
that they all make fun of.
Like us with Elaine.
There's no way Ellen
is the loser of that group.
Are you looking deep down
at the real person underneath?
No, I'm being as superficial
as I possibly can.
Well, stick with it.
Yeah.
I think I found someone
for the scholarship. Yeah?
I'm interviewing all these
annoying, little overachievers,
and finally this kid walks in,
Steven Koren, a regular guy.
Likes sports, watches TV.
Is he smart?
He knows how to read.
And he also knows
that finishing an entire book
doesn't prove anything.
But get this:
He's into architecture.
Hey, just like you
pretend to be.
Yes, with a little guidance,
Steven Koren is going to be
everything I claim to be,
only for real.
That's my dream, Jerry.
I had a dream last night
that a hamburger was eating me.
[♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Mr. Peterman,
thanks for having me over. I--
Your place isn't quite
what I imagined.
Oh, it's just a place to flop.
Well, ahem,
what part of your life
do you want to start with?
Foreign intrigue?
Exotic romances?
Oh, Elaine,
we've covered all of that
in the catalog, ad nauseam.
No, I would like this book
to be about my day-to-day life.
Oh.
Oh, damn, they changed
the cable stations again,
just when I finally
memorized them.
Well, Mr. Peterman,
do you want to--?
Two: CBS.
[CHATTER ON TV]
Get, um, started?
Three...
I don't know what that is.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's my damn
preview channel?
Well, I-I gotta tell you,
Mr. Peterman, I don't--
I don't know if I see
a whole book here.
Well, I'm sure
we'll come up with something.
What do you say you
and I order ourselves a pie?
Do you like Lorenzo's?
You know, a friend of mine
almost got beat up at that place
by the Van Buren Boys.
You don't say?
Yeah.
The only thing
that saved him is
that he accidentally flashed
their secret gang sign.
Well, that's pretty exciting.
Yeah.
Let's put that in the book.
But that didn't happen to you.
Well, so we pay off your friend,
and it becomes a Peterman.
Uh--
No, I-- I really don't think
you can do that.
Oh, damn,
I forgot to buy
plant food again.
I'll bet I got a coupon
for it.
You know what? Maybe
I better talk to my friend.
[♪]
Is that the same outfit
you were wearing yesterday?
No, this is brand-new.
Do you like it?
Actually, yeah.
Wait a second.
Is that the fork
that fell on the floor?
Are you using the fork
No, Jerry, the waitress
gave me another one.
I guess that's all right.
Is something wrong, Jerry?
No, absolutely nothing.
You're fantastic.
JERRY:
Hey, guys. Hey.
Kramer, George,
this is Ellen.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am happy to introduce you
to the first Susan Ross Scholar.
This is Steven Koren.
His GPA is a solid 2.0.
Right in that meaty part
of the curve.
Not showing off,
not falling behind.
George, the qualifications
for this scholarship
were supposed to be
largely academic.
I'm sure we're all aware
of the flaws and biases
of standardized tests.
These aren't standardized tests.
These are his grades.
Besides, Steven Koren
has the highest of aspirations.
He wants to be...
an architect.
Is that right?
STEVEN:
Actually,
maybe I could set my sights
a little bit higher.
GEORGE:
Steven, nothing is higher than architect.
I think I'd really like to be
a city planner, you know?
Why limit myself to one building
when I can design a whole city?
Well, that's a good point.
No, it's not.
Well, isn't an architect just
an art school dropout
with a tilting desk
and a big ruler?
It's called a T-square.
[WYCK LAUGHS]
You know, the stupidest guy
in my fraternity
became an architect after
he flunked out of dental school.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Congratulations, young man.
Thank you.
Susan would be very proud
of what you're doing.
STEVEN:
Thank you.
[♪]
KRAMER:
And they made it their sign
because Van Buren,
our eighth president,
was the man
they most admired.
[LAUGHS]
Kramer, my friend,
that is one ripping good yarn.
Uh, you know, if you liked
that one, I got more.
What are you looking for?
Uh, romance?
Uh, comedy? Adventure?
Erotica?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
No, uh, Kramer,
I don't think--
How much would you take
for the whole lot?
My whole life?
Name your price, man.
$1500.
I'll give you half that.
Done.
Kramer, my friend, you consider
Elaine at your disposal.
KRAMER:
Okay. Uh, well, I, uh...
I like to work in the evenings.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Would you please
just get on with the stupid
Bob Sacamano story?
Okay, well,
I'm on the phone with Bob,
and I realize
right then and there
that I need to return
this pair of pants.
So I'm off to the store.
What happened to Bob Sacamano?
Well, nothing.
His part of the story is done.
So I'm waiting for the subway.
It's not coming.
So I decided to hoof it
through the tunnel.
All right.
Now, that's something.
Well, I don't know
if I lost track of time or what,
but the next thing I knew--
A train is bearing down on you?
No, I slipped and fell in mud,
ruining the very pants
I was about to return.
[SMACKS LIPS]
I don't understand. You--
You were wearing the pants
you were returning?
[CHUCKLES]
Well, I guess I was.
What were you gonna wear
on the way back?
Elaine, are you listening?
I didn't even get there.
All right. Next story.
I think I've got enough
for one day.
Yeah, chew on that.
Yeah, I'll chew on that.
Oh, hey, listen.
By the way, uh,
I'm hosting
a little get-together tonight
in honor of my little
financial upturn.
Oh, thanks, I've got plans.
Yeah, Elaine, you should
be there to document it.
Oh, you're getting together with
some of your jackass friends?
You want me to take notes?
Yeah, but get there after 9.
You know, give the people
a chance to loosen up.
[♪]
JERRY:
So you're denying him the scholarship just because
he wants to be a city planner?
I was betrayed.
That kid was like a son to me.
And if there's one person
you should be able to hold down,
it's your own flesh and blood.
Like my father,
and my father's father
before him.
You know, maybe philanthropy
is not your field.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello. Oh, hi, Ellen.
Yeah, I called the hotel.
We're all set for the weekend.
Spending the weekend
with Ellen?
Vermont.
They said we can stay an extra
couple of days if we want to.
Four days at a beautiful
bed-and-breakfast.
I can't wait.
Buh-bye.
What?
What is this?
[DIAL TONE]
You wanna start?
Uh, no, no, no.
You go ahead.
I gotta get
my thoughts together.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Jerry, this whole
Ellen situation
has gone far enough.
What?
Jerry, she's a loser.
Where is this coming from?
She's great.
Why are you doing this,
Jerry?
Is it your career?
Things are gonna pick up.
There's nothing wrong
with my career.
I still like the Bloomingdale's
executive training program
for him.
I thought we weren't gonna
discuss that now.
Well, it's something
he should consider.
Of course he should.
But now is not the time.
Listen, all these issues
are interrelated.
All right. Excuse me.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
I'm not buying any of this.
All right, so, what are you
saying? That we're wrong?
Everybody's wrong but you.
You know, this is like
that Twilight Zone
where the guy wakes up
and he's the same,
and everybody else is different.
Which one?
They were all like that.
[♪]
[WHISTLING]
Why'd you take away
my scholarship, Mr. Costanza?
Well, Steven, I, uh...
These are my new friends,
the Van Buren Boys.
He became so disillusioned,
he had to join us.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh. Nice.
I want my scholarship back
so I can be a city planner.
What about architect, Steven?
City planner.
[♪]
MAN:
Great party, K-Man.
KRAMER:
Yeah, well, you got that straight.
Hey, Elaine, try the beef,
'cause that's real au jus sauce.
Real au jus sauce, huh?
I'll make a note of it.
Yeah.
Hey, Kramer.
Ramirez has never heard
your pants story.
Oh, okay.
Well, you know,
I had Bob Sacamano on the phone
and I suddenly realized that I--
Hey, Kramer, Kramer.
You can't tell that story now.
It belongs to Peterman.
W-what do you mean?
You signed the release.
Yeah.
He sat in mud, not you.
But I did sit in mud.
You didn't.
You never sat in mud.
I was all dirty.
It never happened,
you understand?
[ALL CLAMORING]
Hey, hey, all right. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, well, I--
Yeah, uh, the pants, uh-- They--
They, uh--
They fit, uh, well,
and so I decided
I wasn't gonna return 'em.
[LAUGHS]
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
Whoo.
It's getting late.
Huh?
Maybe we better get going.
You're gonna go now?
Hey, whoa. Come--
I don't--
Kramer, Kramer,
I-I got big trouble with the--
With the Van Buren Boys.
Now they're tough cookies.
I heard that you got on
their good side.
What'd you do?
Uh...
Uh, oh, nothing, nothing.
No, I certainly
don't have any stories,
if that's what you're implying.
[LAUGHS]
Do you know what those guys
are gonna do?
Yeah, well, uh,
you know, uh,
you didn't hear it from me,
but the Van Buren Boys,
they never hassle
their own kind.
You mean, like a former member?
[♪]
ELAINE:
These Kramer stories are unusable.
I mean, some of them
aren't even stories.
Look, this is the list
of things in his apartment.
Is my toaster oven on there?
How am I ever gonna turn
this into a book?
Well, just shape 'em,
change them. You're a writer.
Yes,
I'm a writer.
Make 'em interesting.
Interesting.
Of course.
People love
interesting writing.
Well, I gotta go to the airport.
I'm picking up my parents.
What? Weren't they just here?
Yeah, I'm flying 'em in
to meet Ellen.
I-I don't know where to turn.
I gotta see
what they think of her.
Maybe we can all
have dinner later.
I don't think so. I'm trying
to get 'em to fly right back.
Oh, hey. Hey, have I told you
about my bunions?
Oh, you're gonna love
this story.
So I line up my cold cuts
on the couch next to me,
but as I'm stacking 'em up,
they keep falling
into my footbath.
Kramer, this is awful.
We don't wanna hear
about this.
Damn!
What?
Oh, I bought a bunch
of bunion stories from Newman.
But they all stink.
How much did you pay for 'em?
Eight bucks.
I think I'm getting ripped off.
Newman!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Well, what didn't you like about the first chapter?
Well, it started out nicely.
I'm returning some pants,
a very identifiable problem.
I set off down a train tunnel.
Now, that's where the story
takes a most unappealing turn.
Oh, no, no, that's where
it gets interesting.
Don't you see? The-- The train
is bearing down on you,
you dive into a side tunnel,
and you run into a whole band
of underground tunnel dwellers.
It just seems so clichéd
and obvious.
It's not interesting writing.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Um...
How 'bout if instead
of diving from the train,
you, uh...?
I don't know.
You-- You slip and--
And fall in some mud and...
ruin your pants?
The very pants I was returning.
That's perfect irony.
Elaine,
that is interesting writing.
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]:
I have a Cosmo Kramer on line four.
Ha.
Peterman here.
Mr. Peterson,
you gotta sell me
my stories back.
You wanna know something?
I no longer need them.
No, no, Mr. Peterman,
why don't we keep them as a--
As a reference.
Nonsense.
I have Benes' wonderfully
imaginative mind
to spin my stories.
You take back your tales,
you vagabond.
KRAMER:
Yippee-yi-yea.
There you are, Elaine.
Go forth and create.
And by the way,
when you get to that chapter
about my romantic escapades,
feel free to toss yourself
into the mix.
[♪]
Hey, Van B Boys.
So, Mr. Costanza,
did you get my scholarship back?
Now, fellas, fellas, easy.
Wouldn't wanna beat up
on one of your own.
Is that right?
Then why don't you
flash us the sign?
Right.
The sign.
That's not the sign.
It was when I was bangin'.
All right,
if you are really one of us,
let's see you take the wallet
off the next guy who walks by.
Love to.
[KNUCKLES CRACK]
[♪]
And after college I got
my master's at the Sorbonne.
Sorbonne. Oh, hey,
that's in Paris.
Oh, Jerry, your parking meter
is about to expire.
Don't get up.
I've got change.
So, what do you think?
Jerry, she is fantastic.
I knew it. I'm not crazy.
She's so sweet.
And she's got
some body on her.
And smart,
like a computer.
And so much personality.
But it doesn't matter
what we think.
Do you like her?
Now I'm not so sure.
Well, she's 10 times better
than that awful Amber girl
that you were with.
Yeah, Amber.
I wonder if she's back
from Vegas.
[♪]
All right, no more stalling.
Next one or you're meat.
[SCOFFS]
All right. All right.
Seinfelds.
Hey, George.
Shh. Listen,
you gotta do me a favor.
Give me your wallet.
I'll give it back to you later.
How are your folks?
Trying to pick out a new couch.
You don't wanna know.
Give me your wallet
or I'll spill your guts
right here on the street!
What did you say?
Come on, hurry up,
old man.
I'm an animal!
You're being very rude.
Come on, Morty.
Please, please.
They're gonna hit me.
What? George Costanza,
what is the matter
with you?
Tell your parents we said hi.
[SCREAMING]
[♪]