[♪]
Boy, I really miss
the Bermuda Triangle.
I guess there's not much action
down there these days.
Oh, there's action.
There's plenty of action.
It's that damn alien autopsy
stealing all the headlines.
Yeah, tell me about it.
See, what they gotta do is lose
a plane or a Greenpeace boat.
See, that would get
the Triangle going again.
What keeps the water
in there?
I mean, why doesn't that
disappear?
Now what would be the point
of taking the water?
It's gorgeous water.
Do we own Bermuda?
No, it belongs
to the British.
Lucky Krauts.
So, what do you think
of that alien autopsy?
Oh, that's real.
I think so too.
[♪]
The doctor will be
with you in a moment.
ELAINE:
"Difficult"?
Elaine, you shouldn't
be reading that.
Now, tell me about this,
uh, rash of yours.
Um, well, it's-- It's...
You know, I noticed
that someone wrote in my chart
that I was difficult
in January of '92.
And I have to tell you,
I remember
that appointment exactly.
You see, this nurse
had asked me to put a gown on,
but it was a mole
on my shoulder
and actually I had specifically
worn a tank top
so that I wouldn't have
to put a gown on.
You know,
they're made of paper.
Well,
that was a long time ago.
How about if I just, uh,
erase it?
[CHUCKLES]
Now, about that rash?
But it was in pen.
You fake erased.
All right, Miss Benes.
This doesn't look too serious.
You should be fine.
What are you writing?
Doctor?
[♪]
Here you go.
Thanks.
I hope you got that
mustard stain out of your shirt.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Well...
[♪]
Jerry, what's the matter
with your stereo?
I don't know. What's the matter
I traded it to Lomez
for some steaks.
Hey.
Now, see, this is busted.
No, it works.
It's busted.
Watch out. Let me show you.
All you gotta do is--
You gotta jiggle it
with this screwdriver.
Smile.
What are you doing?
I met this, uh, woman Sheila.
She works down
at the one-hour photo place.
She's got
this incredible smile.
It's like she's got
too many teeth.
Oh, extra teeth.
I love that look.
And check this out.
I go to pick up my pictures,
and she says,
"I hope you got that mustard
stain out of your shirt."
What mustard stain?
Don't you see?
She's looking
at my pictures.
Why'd you take a picture
of a mustard stain?
It's got nothing
to do with this.
I see, she's looking.
Yes.
You gotta get
this thing fixed.
They've tried to fix it.
It keeps coming back the same.
You interested in a refund?
Well, I--
I can't get a refund.
The warranty
expired two years ago.
Would you be interested?
How you gonna--?
No, no. Would you?
I guess I would.
Yeah, yeah.
You are not gonna believe
what happened to me
at the doctor's office today.
Not the gown again?
No. No.
I was looking at my chart,
and it said
that I was difficult.
Why would they write that?
They've gotten to know you.
And then the doctor writes
more stuff down there,
and he doesn't even look
at my rash.
Find a doctor that doesn't
know you're difficult.
Oh, come on.
I'm not difficult. I'm easy.
Why? Because you dress casual
and sleep with a lot of guys?
Listen to me,
you little sh-- Smile.
[♪]
MAN:
Elaine, you, uh, really didn't have to put on the gown.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
I love these.
You know, in fact,
I've got one at home.
It's-- It's perfect when you
just wanna throw something on.
Hi.
Thank you.
Alrighty.
Let me just review
your history before we begin.
Oh, where did you get
my chart?
From your last doctor.
It's standard procedure.
You know, I can tell you
my whole history. Let's just--
Okay. Let's take a look.
Well, that doesn't look
too serious. You'll be fine.
Please, please. It--
But it's really,
really itchy.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, no.
[♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Seinfeld?
Yeah.
Got a package for you.
Sign here.
Oh, who's it from?
No return address.
What if I don't want it?
Are you refusing delivery?
Maybe I am.
Why would you do that?
I've never done it before.
Why start now?
Why not?
All right.
Why'd you refuse that?
Everybody loves a package.
I don't know.
It was weird.
Crazy printing.
I don't know who it's from.
So, what do you think?
It's a bomb?
It's not totally impossible.
[CHUCKLES]
The ego on you.
Why can't I be bomb-able?
Who's gonna bomb you?
An airline for all the stupid
little peanut jokes?
Oh, I suppose you think
you're bomb-able?
Couple people wouldn't mind
having me out of the way.
There's more than a couple.
Check these out.
I just picked them up
from Sheila.
She must have loved these.
You don't have a Mercedes.
I know. I just sort
of leaned on it
so it would look
like it was mine.
Driver seems
a little put out.
No, he was fine with it.
Check this out.
Is that Burt Reynolds?
Wax Museum.
Ah.
Oh, wha--?
What is this?
That is a lot of skin.
This must be Sheila
from the photo place.
You can barely see her face.
She must have slipped it
in here.
Ay-yi-yi.
Photo-store Sheila.
Well, hello,
photo-store Sheila.
All right.
I will see you boys later.
Where you going?
To ask her out.
No, no.
You're not playing
the game. What game?
She goes to these lengths
to entice you
and your only response is,
"Gee, I really like
your picture.
Would you like to go out
on a date with me, please?"
No good?
George,
it's the timeless art
of seduction.
You gotta join in the dance.
She sends you
an enticing photo,
you send her one
right back.
Oh, I don't know.
Well, as you know,
I've always been something
of a photog.
Oh, yeah, I like this idea.
[♪]
Hey, Danny.
Hello!
How are you?
Hey, Leo.
Hey, what's with your nephew?
He wouldn't accept the package.
Oh, he wants it.
He's just trying to be funny.
Yeah, I'll sign for it.
[♪]
ELAINE:
And then he started writing on my chart.
[SCOFFS]
Why don't you just get ahold of it
and change
what you don't like.
You can't change your chart.
It's your chart.
I'm in my personnel file
at work all the time.
You are?
Hey,
I've kept the same job
for over two years.
It's not luck.
Elaine,
have you ever sent a--
A racy photograph
of yourself to anyone?
Yeah.
I sent one to everyone
I know.
You remember my Christmas card?
Oh, right.
The nipple.
[CLEARS THROAT]
But, um, aside from that,
how did you feel
about Kramer's work?
Actually, I thought
he was very professional.
So it was a good experience?
Oh, yeah.
I liked the picture so much
I cropped out the nipple,
and I'm using it
for my health-club ID.
Nice.
Yeah,
it is nice actually.
ELAINE:
Please, I've gotta see Dr. Berg right away.
This rash is spreading.
He can't see you. He's busy.
Oh, come on.
Have some compassion.
Well, I hope
it's contagious then.
Come on. Move.
Oh, hi, Dr. Berg.
I--
I didn't know if--
The chart, Miss Benes.
Oh.
Oh, please, no more.
[♪]
Hey.
Where's Kramer?
He went to get
some steak sauce. Why?
Personal matter.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Jerry,
it's your Uncle Leo!
Hello!
Hello, Leo.
You don't have to yell.
I got your package.
How did you get
my package?
Leo's got your package?
What should I do with it?
I don't know
what you should do with it.
Tell him to open it.
I'm not gonna treat my uncle
like a bomb-defusing robot.
Jerry, your cousin Jeffrey
is in a Parks Department
production of The Mikado.
I want you
to come see it with me.
Open the package, Leo.
Okay.
LEO:
Opening!
[SOFTLY]
He's opening.
[EXPLOSION]
[♪]
ELAINE:
So it wasn't a bomb?
No. No bomb.
Well, then, what?
Oh, stupid Leo.
He was using one
of those oven cleaners.
He left the canister in there.
The pilot light was on.
The whole thing blew up.
But he's okay?
Yeah,
but the explosion singed off
his eyebrows, mustache,
everything.
He's all smooth now.
Looks like a seal.
Ew.
Yes. Hi, yeah,
I'm still holding.
Is this my stereo?
Oh, hey, you got it.
Hey, what happened to my stereo?
It's all smashed up.
That's right.
Now it looks like
it was broken during shipping,
and I insured it for $400.
But you were supposed
to get me a refund.
You can't get a refund.
Your warranty expired
two years ago.
So we're gonna make
the post office
pay for my new stereo now?
It's a write-off for them.
How is it a write-off?
They just write it off.
Write it off what?
Jerry,
all these big companies,
they write off everything.
You don't even know
what a write-off is.
Do you?
No, I don't.
But they do.
And they're the ones
writing it off.
I wish I had the last 20 seconds
of my life back.
ELAINE:
What?
What? He doesn't have
one appointment
this whole month?
Oh, come on.
I'm dying here, man.
Hello? Hello?
Still no luck?
Jerry, that was Dr. Zimmerman.
I'm at the end of the alphabet.
There's no, uh, Zorn
or Zutroff?
They're on vacation.
Every doctor in this city
seems to know who I am.
Hey, what about Dr. Resnick?
My Uncle Leo's going
to see him tomorrow.
Dr. Resnick.
He's not listed.
He's not that good.
Elaine said you were pretty good
at this stuff.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Elaine was a fun project.
I enjoyed working with her.
You don't have
your own camera?
Uh, no.
Oh, boy, look at this.
Yeah. Okay.
This looks good.
Very, very good.
All right. And I like
what you're wearing.
I feel fat.
No, no. You're stout.
The camera loves stoutness.
Look,
we're not gonna do anything
that makes you feel
uncomfortable.
The key word is "tasteful."
Now, I want to you relax
and have fun,
'cause you're a fun guy.
All right. Let's do it, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
[FUNK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKER]
Okay. Come on. Feel the beat!
[CAMERA CLICKING]
Feel the beat.
All right.
Now, you know,
you got some real strong pecs,
but it's hard to tell
under that T-shirt.
You want me to take it off?
Well, I don't know.
It's up to you.
You think it would be better?
It might be.
Whatever you want.
All right! Come on!
Yeah.
Ha, ha!
That's it.
Come on, George.
That's it. Come on.
Give it to me.
Come on. Work it!
Work it! Oh, yeah.
Hold it! Hold it!
Yeah, be a man.
Be a man!
Lover boy!
You are a lover boy.
Oh, yeah.
This can't miss.
[♪]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
MAN:
Is this Elaine Marie Benes?
Uh, yeah. Who's--?
Who's this?
We're with the American Medical
Association, the AMA.
Can you confirm the correct
spelling of your last name?
Is it B-E-N-E-S?
Yeah. Uh, wh--?
What is this about?
Goodbye.
Hello?
What?
Oh, uh--
Get off the line. We're trying
to make another call.
Oh, sorry.
[♪]
Elaine. Hello.
What are you doing here?
Leo, has the doctor
been in yet?
No, I'm gonna ask him
about my eyebrows.
Okay, listen, Leo.
You're hairless,
you're scared.
When the doctor comes in,
you just let me do
the talking, okay? Okay.
Leo. I understand
you had a little mishap.
It was a fireball.
I never should have
left him alone.
And who are you?
I'm his nurse.
Paloma.
You're not my nurse.
He has good days and bad.
Well, what seems
to be the problem?
Are my eyebrows
gonna grow back?
And he seems to have
a bit of a rash.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, there's been a bit
of that going around lately.
Will you excuse me
a minute, Paloma?
I'm just going to, uh,
get some ointment.
I don't like this.
This is too easy.
Elaine--
Shut up.
I think he's onto us.
Uh-uh.
LEO: Elaine,
what about my eyebrows?
Here. Here. Shhh!
JERRY:
I don't like this, Kramer.
Will it be much longer?
I'm sorry. It looks like
the claim has been red-flagged.
You're under investigation.
Investigation?
Hello, Jerry.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Kramer,
you, uh, might as well
run along.
Jerry may be a while.
Suspicion of mail fraud.
Mail fraud?
You're in a lot of trouble,
buddy.
[♪]
Okay, I've got your ointment.
Where's your, uh--?
Where's your nurse?
She left.
Whoa, whoa,
no need to get angry.
Calm down.
I am calm.
Leo, I don't care
for your demeanor.
Demeanor?
Well, now you're just
being difficult.
What are you writing?
[♪]
So I, uh,
really liked the pictures
I picked up here yesterday.
I'm glad, George.
And, uh,
here's a little roll
that I think you may enjoy.
Great.
Shall we say an hour?
Mm-hm.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNORTS]
Hey, Ron, I gotta go to lunch.
Could you do a roll?
No problem.
By the way,
you know that model
who's always in here?
She's missing one
of her lingerie shots.
Have you seen it?
No.
All right. All right.
Then let me ask you this:
don't you find it interesting
that your friend had
the foresight
to purchase postal insurance
for your stereo? Huh?
I mean, parcels are rarely
damaged during shipping.
Define "rarely."
Frequently.
Are we about
through here, Newman?
[♪]
It's pretty hot under
these lights, huh, Seinfeld?
Pretty hot.
Actually,
I'm quite comfortable.
Can I have a sip?
No.
Not gonna play ball, huh?
All right, admit it!
That-- That stereo
was already busted.
You can't prove anything.
Is this or is this not
your signature?
No, as a matter of fact,
it isn't.
[CHUCKLES]
"Uncle Leo"?
This case is closed
pending further evidence.
Jerry!
[♪]
Okay. Get in there,
get the chart,
and get out. You got it?
Yeah, no problem. Listen,
let me borrow your scarf.
What? This?
Yeah. It's nice. Yeah.
Here.
Yeah. All right.
So, uh...
One chart coming up.
Okay.
It's Bennett, right?
It's Benes, you jackass.
My last name is Benes.
Yeah.
Jerry. Jerry.
Jerry. Jerry. Jerry.
Jerry. Jerry?
[LAUGHING]
Jerry.
So I like
what you've done there.
May I help you?
Uh, yes, yes.
I'm, uh, Dr. Van Nostrund
from the clinic.
I'm gonna need
Elaine Benes' chart.
She's a--
A patient of mine and, uh,
I don't think
she's gonna make it.
It's very bad.
Very, um, very messy.
I see. And what clinic
is that again?
That's correct.
Excuse me?
From the Hoffermandorf
Neo Clinic
in Belgium.
Oh, really?
The Netherlands?
[♪]
Where's my chart?
Did you get it? No.
What? What happened?
I don't know.
Now they got a chart on me.
[♪]
I don't know
where they could be.
You can't find them.
[CHUCKLES]
That's marvelous.
The dance continues.
Well, if I find them
I'll call you.
Great. And maybe we could
go out and do something.
Sure.
Hello.
Hi.
So the little guy
finally asked me out.
Really?
Hey, I can't find
his photos anywhere.
You know what happened?
Some guy from the post office
confiscated 'em.
He left his card.
SHEILA:
"Newman"?
[♪]
GEORGE:
I don't know
what Newman wanted
to see me for.
Gentlemen. Gentlemen.
I'm so happy
to see you both.
There's just some
inconsistencies
I'd like to straighten out.
I'm clean, Newman,
and you know it.
Clean? Hardly.
[CLICKER SNAPS]
This doesn't look
like a man
who's happy with his stereo
performance, now, does it?
Where did you get that?
That's one of mine.
Looks like you're breaking
into it like an otter
cracks open a clam.
Well, I don't know about that,
but there's an explanation.
Yes.
It's called "mail fraud."
Ooh, how I've longed
for this moment, Seinfeld.
The day when I would have
the proof I needed
to haul you
out of your cushy lair
and expose you
to the light of justice
as the monster that you are.
A monster so vile--
Newman!
[SQUEALS]
There'll, uh...
be a small fine.
Okay.
Can we go now?
Not so fast, pretty boy.
There's more to
this sordid little affair.
[CLICKER SNAPS]
Oh, my God.
This photo clearly indicates
your involvement
in some ill-conceived
mail-order pornography ring.
As does this one,
[CLICKER SNAPS]
found in the same
disturbing packet.
Oh, my God!
We have a few questions
we'd like you to answer.
I have a few questions
of my own.
Hi. One of your mailmen--
Oh, my God. George.
Well, Sheila, listen,
it's not what you think.
I put my trust
in the wrong person.
GEORGE:
He said the key word was "tasteful."
The timeless art
of seduction.
[GEORGE SHOUTING]
[♪]
KRAMER:
Oh, gee.
That wasn't
such a long drive.
The dirt road
really hurt my back.
Okay, please, everybody
just stop complaining.
Smile.
We're good patients.
Okay, Miss Benes,
you wanna come on back?
Oh, I'd love to.
[PHONE RINGS]
Oh, just a sec.
ELAINE:
Okay. Hello.
Yes.
Well, as a matter of fact,
they're here right now.
I understand.
[♪]
[PIG SQUEALS]