Morning.
Hope you don't mind
baking-soda flavor.
Oh, baking soda.
Annoying little product.
"I can do this,
I can do that."
Why doesn't the stuff
just shut up?
Let me grab you
a towel.
Ugh.
[SPITS]
Oh.
Ugh. Ehh.
Ohh.
GEORGE:
So?
So? She used
the toothbrush.
You said you grabbed it
out of there real fast? Yeah.
So I'm sure whatever germs
it landed on were knocked out.
And by the time the rest
realized what was going on,
you had already grabbed it out.
How many years
of med school did you have?
Was she mad?
You didn't tell her.
Jenna's like me.
She's very...
Finicky?
Prissy?
Fastidious?
I'll take "fastidious."
What is that?
Oh.
Steinbrenner gave 'em to us.
In honor of Phil Rizzuto's
induction into the Hall of Fame.
Holy cow.
They don't have to
squeeze his head
to get him to say
"Holy cow", do they?
Just the last few innings
of a double-header.
Hey.
Look at this.
I'm in the passing lane of
the Arthur Berkhardt Expressway
going 70, and:
[IMITATES COLLISION]
Dragged this thing
for five exits.
Why didn't you
pull over?
Well, I was drafting behind
a semi. I didn't wanna lose him.
The infrastructure, Jerry.
It's crumbling.
Holy cow.
Oh, look at that.
Talking Nixon.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
MAN [ON PHONE]: China Panda.
Yeah, I'd like to
place an order.
Uh, yes, what you like?
This supreme flounder.
It says,
"First time served in America."
Is that true?
What number?
Forty-seven?
Yeah. First time.
What else?
Uh, that's it.
Address.
78 West 86th Street,
apartment 3E.
That's south side.
Sorry, we don't
deliver below 86.
I'm not below.
Yes, you are.
Street itself is boundary.
Your guy can't
cross to my side?
If we deliver to you,
then what?
85th Street?
Wall Street?
Mexico?
84th Street?
All right, fine.
I'll just cross and meet him.
Sorry. Food only for those
who live within boundary.
[TELEPHONE DIALING]
[RINGS]
China Panda.
[HIGH VOICE]
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Uh, I'd like to
place an order.
All right, what you like?
Well...
Well. I'm a papa.
Bring it on. Nothing's
throwing me at this point.
Well, as of today,
I am a proud parent
of a one-mile stretch of
the Arthur Berkhardt Expressway.
Oh, that
Adopt-A-Highway thing.
Yeah, I'm part of
the solution now, Jerry.
Yeah, I went down there, and
I checked it out this morning.
Here. Take a look.
Mile 114.
Oh. Looks
just like you.
Oh, I'm beaming, Jerry.
So, what do you have to do?
Pay to keep it clean?
Oh, no. They try to push you
into using their cleaning crew
with all their so-called
maintenance equipment.
That old scam.
That's why I'm doing
it all myself.
This parenting isn't about
delegating responsibility,
it's about being there.
At the side of the road
with a pile of garbage.
Quality time.
Keys. I can't find my keys.
You lost Phil Rizzuto's
head?
Have you seen him?
No.
Damn it.
KRAMER: Come on,
retrace your steps.
What'd you do today?
I got up, I was
supposed to go to work,
I came here instead.
All right.
They're not here. You'll
have to dig up your spare set.
I don't have
a spare set.
All my keys say
"do not duplicate."
So?
So you can't
duplicate 'em.
[JERRY & KRAMER LAUGH]
Sure you can.
Such a sweet
kid. Ha.
Oh. Oh. Hi.
China Panda?
Why are you
waiting on the street
and not in your apartment?
I...
thought that I would
meet you halfway.
Do you really live here?
Oh, yeah.
There you go.
You keep the change.
Bye now.
I'll--
I'll see you.
[DOORKNOB
RATTLING]
[GROANS]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
You know,
this isn't fair.
This is address
discrimination.
Well, I cleaned out their
whole dental-hygiene shelf.
So the plan is to
secretly sterilize her mouth?
By the time I'm through
with her mouth,
she'll be able to
eat off it.
Is it safe to drink bleach
if you dilute it?
No. Stings
the throat.
Anyway-- So I was
coming along here.
And I felt like
a piece of cake, you know?
So then I thought,
"It's morning.
I should really
have a muffin."
I like those
chocolate chip ones.
And then I figured,
well,
they're really
both cake.
So I, uh--
I sat on that bench
for a little while--
20 minutes or an hour
--and then I figured
I'd check and see
what you were up to.
Wait a minute.
The broad jump.
The broad jump over the pothole
on 86th Street!
Now I remember.
As I jumped over the hole,
I heard a jingling sound.
You didn't look down?
I was trying to
stick the landing.
I know it was
right around here.
No. No!
RIZZUTO HEAD:
Holy-- Holy cow.
Poor son of a bitch.
JERRY:
It's 100,000 revolutions a second.
It's the most powerful one
they make.
I feel like I'm
holding a blender.
The engine's made
by McDonnell Douglas.
No, no, you keep going.
It shuts off automatically.
Really? It does?
When the battery
runs out.
I was really happy
with my old toothbrush.
Oh, trust me, that one
was doing more harm than good.
Don't forget to use
the Plax too.
That stuff
tastes like bleach.
I don't know
anything about that. Huh.
Mm.
My mouth feels
so clean.
That's the idea.
[♪]
You know, maybe
we'd better not.
I-I think I'm
getting a little cold.
I don't wanna give you
any of my germs.
Oh.
Okay.
Thanks. I guess.
ELAINE:
You still couldn't kiss her?
She has
a taint.
I can't see it,
but I know it's there.
Oh. So now you're finding fault
on a subatomic level.
Maybe if I could
shrink myself down,
like in Fantastic Voyage,
and get inside a microscopic
submarine, I could be sure.
Although if there was
something there,
it might be
pretty scary.
Of course, I would
have that laser.
Jer...
do you see
where this is going?
Being really clean
and happy?
Jerry...
you have tendencies.
They are
always annoying,
but they were
just tendencies.
But now, if you can't
kiss this girl,
I-- I'm afraid
we're talking disorder.
Disorder?
And from disorder,
you're a quirk or two away
from full-on dementia.
Hm. That could hurt me.
Hey, there
it is.
Should we stop
and say hi?
Nah,
we've seen it. Yeah.
[HONKS HORN]
Hey, Jerry!
Yeah, I'll see you
back at the house!
Mile 114,
clean as a whistle.
[HORNS HONKING]
[TIRES
SQUEALING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Yeah?
Hi.
I'm your neighbor.
Uh, from-- From across
the street.
And, um...
Tsk. Ahem.
I was wondering,
if it wouldn't
be too much trouble,
if I could use
your apartment
to order some food.
What? W-what do you want?
You see, there's
this certain flounder.
And they won't deliver it
to my side of the street.
When-- When is that?
No, I just need them
to deliver it here.
And I have to be
kind of inside, is all.
Who are you with?
No, actually, I'm--
I'm just kind of hungry.
[CHUCKLES]
And--
Who let you in?
Well, the lock
was broken.
You just have to
jiggle it,
actually, to g--
But-- Hm.
I just need, like,
a half an hour to an hour.
[SIGHS]
JERRY:
What's with the signs?
Ah. you should see
the Berkhardt, Jerry.
My mile
is spotless.
I mean,
the big stuff was easy:
cinder blocks,
air conditioners,
shopping carts:
vrrt!
I just rolled them
into the woods.
Yeah, that stuff's
all-natural anyway.
Yeah.
Speed limit,
165 miles per hour.
See? They slipped
a one in there.
[LAUGHING]
Those kids with the spray paint.
God love 'em.
Hey, so? Keys?
No keys. And I've been
calling the city all day.
There's not a number to call
if you wanna make a pothole.
I guess they leave that
up to the general population.
I'll tell you this. If the real
Phil Rizzuto was down there,
this wouldn't be happening.
Hard to say.
Wait a minute.
You need some roadwork done?
I met some maintenance guys
today on the highway.
They could probably
help you out.
Really?
KRAMER: Oh, yeah.
I borrowed some cones
from them
when I was sweeping
my car-pool lane.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
JENNA: It's Jenna.
Ah, if you guys
wouldn't mind...
I would like to
ward off dementia.
You can hook me up
with them?
Oh, yeah. Give me
a ring tomorrow.
I'm gonna be at emergency
call box 784. [SNAPS]
Seven-eight-four.
Hey.
Hi.
How you feeling?
Good.
My cold's gone,
and I've been looking
forward to kissing you.
Which I'm ready to do now,
if you are ready.
Okay.
What?
Nothing. I just--
I, uh...
I bruised my lip.
I was drinking a Cel-Ray,
and I brought it up too fast,
and I banged it into my lip.
And then I knocked
your toothbrush
into the toilet.
And I wasn't able to tell you
before you could use it.
What?
I'm sorry.
When were you
gonna tell me this?
Obviously never.
I need
the yield sign.
Kramer...I'm kind of
in the middle of something.
Would you get these signs
out of here, please?
You could have
introduced me.
I wouldn't know
where to start.
Hey.
Jenna. Hey.
There.
Now something of yours
has been in the toilet.
What? Well, what did
you put in there?
Gotta run.
Oh, man.
JERRY:
Hello, Jenna? Did you dunk the spatula?
Was it the spatula?
Hello?
Damn it!
Didn't even
give you a hint?
No. Could be anything.
The whole apartment's
a biohazard.
You know what I bet it is?
Your remote.
Yes, that is a definite
possibility.
Or it could be
your Walkman there.
Are you just
screwing with me?
Yeah. I am.
Hey.
Hey. How's life on the road?
I'm making a difference,
Jerry. I don't doubt it.
You should see the smiles
on the drivers' faces.
I mean, you gotta
look quick...
but they're there.
This.
What's this?
You know those annoying little
bumps on the lane lines?
[IMITATES BUMPING CAR]
Isn't that some kind of
safety thing?
Well, I had to pull 'em up
if I'm gonna widen the lanes.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Well...you know how in planes
they got first class?
More legroom,
better ride?
Well, I'm bringing
that concept to mile 114.
How are you gonna
widen the lanes?
Well, you black out
lane lines one and three,
and a four-lane
highway
becomes a two-lane
comfort cruise.
So you got any black paint?
Yeah. In my tool shed,
next to the riding mower.
ELAINE:
Yeah.
I'd like an order
of supreme flounder,
number 47.
Yeah.
Apartment 1Q.
1Q? Whose apartment
is that?
That's the janitor closet...
across the street.
You're pretending to live in
a janitor's closet
just to get this flounder?
It's better than eating
it alone in the restaurant
like some loser.
That stuff is unbelievable.
I'd eat it out of
a dumpster.
[SNIFFS]
How do you know about it?
You're not in the delivery zone.
Well, Newman uses
his mail truck
to run fish for China Panda
on the weekends.
Well...
mine's coming in 10,
so I'll see you boys.
Now...
[CLAPS]
...where's that tool shed
of yours?
Hi. Sorry. I didn't hear you.
I was in the shower.
I'll see you.
You Costanza?
Yeah.
Thanks for-- Thanks for
coming by, fellas.
Yeah.
Got a set of keys
buried in the pothole.
[CHUCKLES]
What are the keys
doing in there?
Just need to, uh--
To dig them up.
You put 'em in there?
No, no. It's, uh--
It's a long story.
Just, uh, try to
get it up.
Bad place
to put your keys.
Yeah, I know that.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Could you start working?
Difficult job.
If you want those keys,
we're gonna have to
dig this up.
Oh, w-- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
[SNORTS]
Is this about money?
Yeah.
[SNORTS]
It's about money.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[MUMBLES]
Excuse me. what are you
doing in there?
Um, nothing.
I was just, um...
I wasn't in there.
You were hanging around
in there, lazing on the job,
when you should have been
downstairs in the basement
cleaning out those old carpets
and scrap wood.
Right. Because...
I'm the janitor.
Don't get smart with me.
Yes, ma'am.
[ALARM RINGING]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
If you're heading north on the Arthur Berkhardt,
whoa, Nellie.
For some reason
four lanes are converging
into two instantaneously
right at mile marker 114.
I don't know what that is,
but the A.B.E.'s
a parking lot out there.
Somebody screwed up
on that one.
[MOUTHS DIALOGUE]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Oh, it's you.
Is the flounder here yet?
No, it's not
here yet.
You want the tour?
There's this.
Nice.
French doors would really
open this place up.
Oh, but you have
a slop bucket.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
The fish.
Oh. What are you doing here?
Hey.
Oh, I was, uh--
I was waiting downstairs
for the jackhammer.
I just thought I'd drop by.
Kramer's guys?
Yeah. I got 'em down
to 50 bucks.
I just have to do
all the jackhammering myself.
Oh, that's nice. Kind of
a hard-labor fantasy camp.
Yeah, you know...
Ow!
Oh, man!
[JUNK
CLATTERING]
I, uh--
[ALL SIGH]
Oh. Sweet setup.
I--
Look, Elaine, do you have
any paint thinner?
I need like, uh, 40 gallons.
I'm plumb out.
Oh, damn.
If I don't get
that black paint off,
the city's gonna go ape.
I don't wanna lose my baby.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
WOMAN: Janitor!
Oh. It's Mrs. Allister.
Yeah, uh-- Yes, coming,
Mrs. Allister.
Okay, I've gotta get out.
Let's go. Let's go.
Here. Can you--?
You gotta move from the door.
[CLATTERING]
Hi.
I, um--
What can I do for you?
I told you yesterday
to haul that trash
out of the basement.
Yeah. I am so sorry.
Some of the children
have been playing near it
and putting it
in their mouth.
Well, a lot of it is vegetables.
[SCRAPING]
You mop it.
Get that stuff
out of there today,
or you'll be out of here,
understand?
Yes, ma'am.
JERRY: Stop pushing.
Ugh. Kramer
spilled ammonia.
I don't feel like eating.
I'm gonna
borrow this, huh?
Janitors' meeting.
JENNA:
So, Jerry...
why'd you call me?
Well, I thought
it's about time
we put aside all this silliness.
I know now that
you didn't
put anything
in my toilet bowl.
Did you?
Yes. I did.
Well, whatever.
So how have you been?
Good.
Steak knife?
It's just eating away at you,
isn't it?
No.
Hi.
Jerry, can I
borrow your car?
For what?
I have to haul some
dirty garbage to the dump.
Dirt? That's
all right.
Because there's
nothing wrong with dirt.
Well, actually,
it's pretty grimy.
Grime, grease,
filth, funk, ooze.
Whatever it is,
you take that stuff
and put it
right on
my leather
upholstery.
Well, I don't know
who you are,
but thanks for the car.
Sure. Bye.
Bye.
There.
You see?
I just lent her my car,
and she's gonna fill it
with all sorts of...
All right!
You win.
That car was my last
germfree sanctuary.
I slept there last night.
Now, for the love of God,
please, what is it?
What is it?
Toilet brush.
Oh!
All right.
I can replace that.
You wanna order dinner?
Yeah. Let's, uh,
go to your place.
Because I...
threw out
all my dishes.
[JACKHAMMER
DRILLING]
[GRUNTS]
That's true.
Mm.
But I'll tell you
this much:
I am never
going to let some
silly hygienic mishap
get in the way
of what could be
a meaningful,
long-lasting relationship.
[METAL DINGS]
[RUMBLING]
Do you hear
something?
[RUMBLING]
I don't know
what that could be.
[METAL GROANING]
RIZZUTO HEAD:
Holy cow.
JERRY:
Anyway,
I'm a new man.
And I'm looking
towards the future.
Clean, dirty...
whatever.
[EXPLOSION,
JENNA SCREAMS]
[WATER
RUSHING]
Holy cow.
Have a nice life.
Hey, look at this.
Wide lanes.
This is so luxurious.
Mm. Yeah.
[GRUNTING]
Bugger.
♪ You're once, twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
[METAL CLANGS, TIRES SQUEAL]
What the hell was that?
Double bugger.
NEWMAN:
♪ Yes, you're once ♪
♪ Twice ♪
♪ Three times a-- ♪
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Oh, the humanity!
[♪]
[NEWMAN SCREAMING]
Hey, buddy. What are
you doing out here?
Man, did you see
that fireball?
Ooh.
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Hey, I gotta skedaddle.
You want a lift?
Newman?
Newman!
All right, I'll meet you
at the coffee shop.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[♪]
[NEWMAN SCREAMING]