[♪]
Hey, you know what?
It says "no food or drink."
You can't take that in.
Wait,
I'll be right out.
Just wait a second. Come on.
I wanna go in.
I'm just runnin' in.
[MUMBLING]
Come on. Come on.
[MUMBLES]
[SIGHS]
You know what?
They don't have batteries here.
Let's go.
[GAGGING]
[♪]
GEORGE:
♪ Ba-da, ba-da-ba ♪
Hey, Georgie's movin' out!
Get out.
I'm out.
Fantastic apartment
right across from mine, huh?
I ca-- I can't wait
for you to see.
Is it better than mine?
Oh, yeah.
So it's a two-bedroom, one-bath
make-your-friends-hate-you.
You know what?
It's better than Elaine's too.
I gotta give her a call.
She's out.
Oh, right, the blind date.
Yeah, well, they like
to call it a setup now.
I guess the blind people don't
like being associated
with all those losers.
Aw, come on,
come check out my new place.
Take you two minutes.
I can't.
I'm meetin' Kramer
down at my Mini Storage.
You got any extra
furniture down there?
I need some more stuff
to fill that extra bedroom
with a walk-in closet.
Oh, this is really annoying.
[LAUGHS]
It's workin' already!
[♪]
[MAN COUGHING]
What is with that?
[COUGHS]
Well, it's coughing,
Jerry.
It expels the diseased germs
out of the body into the air.
Where is your key?
Yeah, well, uh...
Newman, he's, uh, got it.
You know, Kramer, I rented out
half of my space to you.
Yeah, and I rented out half
that space to Newman.
[COUGHING]
Mailbags?
He's storing mail in here?
Evidently.
[♪]
Excuse me, George?
Uh, no menus.
N-- No, I'm,
uh, Mrs. Ricardi,
president of
the tenants' association.
Oh, right.
[CHUCKLES]
Right. Hey.
Hey, I love the floors in here.
It's like a gymnasium.
Try and guard me.
Come on.
Aaah!
No, no.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, George...
unfortunately,
Clarence Eldridge, in 8C,
has decided
that he wants the apartment.
Yeah, but you--
You promised it to me.
Yes, but you see, Mr. Eldridge
is an Andrea Doria survivor.
And in light
of the terrible suffering
that he's already
been through,
we've decided
to give it to him.
Well, uh...
the Andrea Doria.
That was quite a fire.
Shipwreck.
I remember it.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Where is this guy? I hate this.
[SIGHS]
Should've brought
something to read.
"Cancer in laboratory animals."
Huh.
Excuse me. Elaine Benes?
Yeah?
An Alan Mercer called
for you.
He said he's sorry,
but he won't be able
to make it tonight.
He's been stabbed.
Stabbed?
More bread?
[♪]
Ya ate more bread?
That is not the point.
The guy was stabbed.
Did you find out
who stabbed him? Yeah.
It turns out
it was his ex-girlfriend.
Well, you're not goin' near
this hooligan anymore.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, think about it,
Jerry.
There must be something exciting
about this guy
if he can...arouse
that kind of passion.
I mean, to be stabworthy,
you know? It's, uh...
It's kind of a compliment.
Yeah, too bad
he didn't get shot.
He could've been the one.
[COUGHS]
Hey, how's everybody, huh?
Hey.
Ah. No expiration date
on this, huh?
[COUGHING]
There is now.
Kramer, you should get that
cough checked out by a doctor.
No, no, no.
No doctors for me.
Bunch of lackeys and yes men
all toein' the company line.
Plus they botched
my vasectomy.
They botched it?
I'm even more potent now.
Aw.
Hey.
Hey, how's
the new place?
Gone.
The, uh, tenant association
made me give it to this guy
'cause he was
an Andrea Doria survivor.
Andrea Doria?
Isn't that the one
they did the song about?
Edmund Fitzgerald.
I love
Edmund Fitzgerald's voice.
No, Gordon Lightfoot
was the singer.
Edmund Fitzgerald
was the ship.
You could fit 15 people
in that bathroom.
I think Gordon Lightfoot
was the boat.
Yeah, and it was rammed
by the Cat Stevens.
The Andrea Doria collided
with the Stockholm
in dense fog
12 miles off the coast
of Nantucket.
How do you know?
It's in my book:
Astonishing Tales of the Sea.
Fifty-one people died.
Fifty-one people?
KRAMER:
Mm-hm.
That's it?
I thought it was
like a thousand.
There were 1660 survivors.
That's no tragedy!
How--? How many people you lose
on a normal cruise?
Thirty, forty?
Kramer, can I take a look
at that book?
Oh, yeah. I also got
Astounding Bear Attacks.
Hey, before you go,
did you talk to Newman
about getting that mail out?
Oh, yeah.
No, he's not gonna do it.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[GUNFIRE OVER TV]
Newman?
I guess.
Listen, I want you
to get the mail out
of my storage unit.
Sometimes we don't get
what we want.
What're you talkin' about?
I didn't get my transfer.
Transfer?
To Hawaii.
The most sought-after
postal route of them all.
The air is so dewy sweet,
you don't even have
to lick the stamps.
But it's not to be.
So I'm hangin' it up.
You quit
the post office?
Kind of.
I'm still collecting checks,
I'm just...not delivering mail.
Well, get it out of my storage.
It's illegal.
And yet it's perfectly legal
to take a man's soul
and crush it out
like a stale Pall Mall.
Well, the law's the law.
[♪]
[COUGHING]
[COUGHS]
Oh.
Hold on there. It's--
It's a nasty cough
you got there, huh?
What cough?
[COUGHS]
[♪]
I love shrimp.
I'm a shrimp-eater.
You put shrimp in front of me,
and I'll eat it
till my stomach pops.
Oh.
No, it's okay. I'm...
still just
a little bit jumpy. Oh.
Between you and me,
what happened there,
with the stabbing?
Just...one of those things,
you know.
What, was she just so crazy
in love with you
she just couldn't take it
anymore, or...?
I don't know. Could be.
Alan?
Carol?
[SCREAMING]
Was that the one?
Was that the one
who stabbed you?
No, that was
a different girl.
[♪]
JERRY:
There was another crazed ex-girlfriend?
Right. So I called my friend--
You know, the one who set us up?
--I found out
he's a bad breaker-upper.
Oh.
Bad how?
You know
when you break up
how you say things
you don't mean?
He says the mean things
you don't mean,
but he means them.
I follow.
So, what are you gonna do?
Dump him.
I can't be with someone
who doesn't break up nicely.
That's one of the most important
parts of a relationship.
What's more important?
[SCOFFS]
[♪]
[COUGHING]
Hey.
What's with the dog?
Yeah, this is Smuckers.
I borrowed him.
Oh.
[COUGHS]
Yeah, we share
the same affliction. Mm.
So I'm gonna have a vet
check us out.
A vet?
Oh, I'll take a vet
over an M.D. any day.
They gotta be able to cure
a lizard, a chicken,
a pig, a frog,
all on the same day.
So...if I may jump ahead,
you're gonna take
dog medicine?
You bet we are.
How smart is that?
[COUGHS]
See ya.
[♪]
Ahoy, Mr. Eldridge.
I understand you were
on the Andrea Doria.
Yes, it was
a terrifying ordeal.
Well, I tell ya, I hear people
really stuff themselves
on those cruise ships.
The buffet, that's
the real ordeal, huh, Clarence?
We had to abandon ship.
Well,
all vacations
have to end eventually.
The boat sank.
According to this,
it took 10 hours.
It eased into the water
like an old man
into a nice warm bath,
no offense.
So, uh...
Clarence, how about, uh,
abandoning this apartment
and letting me shove off
in this beauty?
Is that what this is all about?
I don't think I like you.
It's my apartment,
Eldridge!
The Stockholm
may not have sunk ya,
but I will!
Ah!
[♪]
MAN:
What are the symptoms?
Uh, well, it-- It, uh,
hurts when he swallows,
especially when he drinks
orange juice.
I mean, uh, dog-food,
uh, juice.
And what's worse,
he has a nagging cough.
[COUGHING]
That's it. That's it.
Yeah, well, uh,
we've been seeing
a lot of this lately.
Been drinking from the toilet?
What?
No.
Ew.
That's disgusting.
[♪]
So that's it? We're--?
We're breakin' up?
What? Breakup?
We went out on one date.
Okay, yeah, sure,
fine, right, whatever you say.
All right. Good, good.
Okay, then, well...
So I'll see you around...
big head.
Pardon?
You got a big head.
It's too big for your body.
That's it?
[LAUGHING]
That's the best you got?
[ELAINE LAUGHING]
GEORGE:
So he's keepin' the apartment.
He doesn't deserve it though.
Even if he did suffer,
that was like 40 years ago.
What have you done
for me lately?
I've been suffering
for the past 30 years,
up to and including
yesterday.
If this board
is impressed with suffering,
maybe you should tell them
the astonishing tales
of Costanza.
I should.
I mean, your body of work
in this field is unparalleled.
I could go bummer-to-bummer
with anyone on this planet.
You're the man.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Jerry--
I'm with people.
I'll be with you
in a moment.
So you--? You want
a protein shake or something?
Ah, I guess I should
get moving on this, huh?
I'm gonna run.
All right.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
I need that mail. Where is it?
What's the difference?
The guy who had
the Hawaii transfer
got busted for hoarding
Victoria's Secret catalogs.
I-- I gotta deliver
that mail.
Well, go ahead.
There's eight bags of it.
Blast.
There's no way
I can handle eight
in addition
to my usual load of one.
I'll never get to Hawaii.
I'll be stuck in
this apartment building forever.
The dream is dead.
You givin' up that easy?
I usually do.
See ya.
Now, wait a minute, Newman.
You can't let this dream die.
You moving away
is my dream too.
What are you proposing?
Whatever it takes,
for as long as it takes me,
wherever it takes me,
so long as it takes you
away from me.
An alliance?
An alliance.
[BOTH LAUGHING SNIDELY]
Now get the hell
outta here.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Hawaii?
That's why you're
helpin' Newman with the mail?
Elaine, Newman is
my sworn enemy,
and he lives
down the hall from my home.
My home, Elaine!
Where I sleep,
where I come
to play with my toys.
Well, anyway, get this:
I spoke to Alan.
You know, I told him
I didn't wanna see him anymore.
Called me "big head."
[SCOFFS]
Big head?
It's almost a compliment.
It's one of the nicest things
anyone's ever said to me.
[RINGING]
Hello?
Hey.
Hey, George.
Yeah, listen, I, uh--
I can't make it later.
You can't make it?
Yeah, the, uh,
tenant association
has decided to hear
my side of the story,
so, uh, I gotta
kind of get ready.
I-I'll see you.
All right.
Is he not gonna go?
Doesn't look like
it's gonna happen. Aw.
All right, well,
I'll see ya.
All right.
[COUGHING]
Kramer, aren't you
takin' any medication for that?
[HOARSELY]
Yeah. Yeah, I got some pills.
They taste terrible.
Just swallow 'em.
Oh, my throat's too tender.
All right, sit down, sit down.
I don't want to.
Come on. Just sit down.
No, Jerry. What--?
Lay down.
What? Why?
Sit down.
Hey!
Lean your head back.
Open your mouth.
Open it.
Ugh.
What kind of pills
are these anyway?
[COUGHING]
"For Smuckers"?
"May cause panting
and loss of fur"?
These are dog pills.
We had the same symptoms.
But he's a dog.
You need to see a real doctor.
No. No-- No doctors.
All right.
Where you goin'?
I'm takin' the car. I gotta run
some errands. You wanna go?
I don't know.
Come on, you wanna go
for a ride, huh?
[JINGLING]
Come on.
Yeah.
[♪]
Lady, could you move
your head a little bit?
What?
Your head.
I can't see out the back.
Little more.
Thank you.
[♪]
KRAMER:
I don't see any tissues back here.
Wait a minute.
This isn't the way
to the park.
Where we goin'?
I recognize this block.
You're takin' me to the doctor.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So...
uh, Mom, Dad,
I was hoping
that you could help me
to remember my childhood
a-a little more clearly.
I feel a draft.
Let's change tables.
Get outta here.
We have a booth.
Frank, I'm cold.
Order a hot dish.
Why can't we sit
over there?
That's not a booth!
So who says we have to
sit in a booth?!
I didn't take the subway
all the way to New York
to sit at a table
like that!
Well, I didn't take a subway
to be in a drafty restaurant!
[CHUCKLES]
Mom...
Now, George, what do ya wanna
know about your childhood?
Actually, I think
I'm pretty clear on it.
Where's that breeze
comin' from?
Kramer, outta the car. Out, now.
No, Jerry!
All right. That's it, come on.
No! Jerry!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Hey. Hey, get back over here.
Kramer.
Get over here.
You are bad.
Bad neighbor!
Kramer!
[♪]
CLARENCE:
Just then,
a rescue ship emerged
from the fog and saved us.
[TAPPING]
It was--
It was the sweetest sight
my eyes ever saw.
Thank you, Mr. Eldridge.
The tenant board will now hear
Mr. Costanza's testimony.
[COUGHS]
[♪]
Newman, how'd it go?
Get it all delivered?
What happened?
Kramer bit me.
Bit you?
We had an argument about me
movin' to Hawaii,
and he locked on to my ankle
like it was a soup bone.
I'm hobbled.
I don't think I can do my route.
And they're awarding
the transfer in two days.
Well, what if I delivered it?
You?
[LAUGHING]
You can't deliver mail.
Why not?
I guess you're right.
It's just walking around
and putting it in the boxes.
Well, what am I gonna wear?
I can give you my uniform
from my rookie year.
I can't believe
I'm gonna be a mailman!
[♪]
Here you go.
Merry Christmas.
Mail on Sunday?
Oops.
[WHISTLING]
[♪]
I was handcuffed to the bed...
in my underwear...
where I remained for...
She certainly
seemed interested in me.
Though she was attractive,
she was also, in fact...
[TEARFULLY]
a Nazi.
The water that I had been
swimming in was...
very cold...
and when I dropped the towel,
there...
had been significant shrinkage.
My parents were looking at me.
So there I was...
[CHUCKLES]
...with the marble rye hanging
from the end of a fishing pole.
In closing, these stories
have not been embellished,
because they need
no embellishment.
They are simply, horrifyingly,
the story of my life
as a short, stocky,
slow-witted...
bald man.
Thank you.
Oh, also...
my fiancée died
from licking toxic envelopes
that I picked out.
Thanks again.
[SOBBING]
[♪]
JERRY:
Hey, I've been trying
to jam stuff in the box
like you told me,
but sometimes it says, like,
"Photographs: Do not bend."
"Do not bend."
[LAUGHS]
Just crease, crumple, cram.
You'll do fine.
[RINGS]
Hello?
This is he.
I don't understand.
Very well.
What?
That was the vice president
of the post office.
I didn't get the transfer.
They knew it wasn't me
doing my route.
How did they know?
Too many people
got their mail!
Close to 80 percent.
Nobody from the post office has
ever cracked the 50% barrier.
It's like
the three-minute mile.
I tried my best.
Exactly.
You're a disgrace
to the uniform.
You know,
this is your coat.
Damn.
[♪]
[CHIRPS]
He flew right into your head,
like he couldn't avoid it.
Really?
Never seen that before.
Bird into a woman's head.
[♪]
GEORGE:
There's no contest.
The guy had nothing.
The ship went down,
he got into a lifeboat.
Uh, come on.
Boy, he didn't know
what he was up against.
[LAUGHING]
When do you move
into the apartment?
Well, they're making
their decision today.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
Except that a...
bird ran into
my giant freak head.
What giant freak head?
The one that sits atop
my disproportionately puny body.
[TEARFULLY]
I'm a walkin' candy apple.
So it's actually
gotten to you?
You're playin'
right into his hands.
What?
Yeah, you're right.
All I have to do is call him up
and-- And sit down with him,
and show him
that it doesn't bother me.
You know, laugh it off.
Or jam a fork
into his forehead.
Either way.
All right.
[♪]
I want to apologize
for the--
Oh, please.
I hope we can get
past all this.
Oh, past? We're way past.
So you have a big head.
So what?
Goes well with the bump
in your nose.
What?
[♪]
Please, get help.
There's a crazy, bigheaded woman
beating up some guy.
Tell the police
it's the Old Mill Restaurant.
Hurry!
[COUGHING]
That's some cough
you got there.
[COUGHING]
I think he's trying
to tell us something.
What is it?
Trouble?
Trouble where?
Where's trouble?
[COUGHING]
Old...Mill.
Trouble at the Old Mill?
Oh, my God.
Good boy. Good boy.
Lead the way. Come on.
[♪]
Excuse me,
uh, what are you--?
What are you
doin' in there?
I'm movin' in.
Alan Mercer, new neighbor.
Uh, Elaine's "big head" guy?
They gave you the apartment?
Yeah.
Why? B-because, uh,
you were stabbed
and got coffee thrown
in your face and--? And--?
Oh, fork in the forehead.
That's why they gave you
the apartment?
No. Just gave
the super 50 bucks.
Whoa, wait a minute.
That is my apartment.
I earned it
with 34 years of misery.
Tough luck, chinless.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[♪]