Hey, if I were a gigolo,
how much you think
I could charge a night?
Here or in Japan?
What's the difference?
Well, the Japanese
are more enlightened.
They can, uh, see
beyond the physical.
Forget Japan.
How much would you pay?
[SIGHS]
Oh, I don't know.
A dollar.
I think I'm worth at least 300.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, I don't think so.
Hey, that's for all night.
I know.
You're demeaning me.
You're a gigolo.
Well, you hired me.
I'm the victim here.
Did I force you into this life?
Yes.
You and every woman like you.
Look how dark
it's getting already.
It's not daylight-savings
time yet.
When does it start?
I don't know. They just tell you
the night before.
Well, I'm sick of waiting.
I am springin' ahead
right now.
Oh, I'm sure that won't
cause any problems.
Oh, God, it's Mike Moffet.
Don't tell me you're still mad
at him for calling you a phony.
Jerry, that was
five years ago.
I'm not a phony. I don't want
anything to do with this guy.
Mike!
Mike.
Kramer, Jerry, how's it goin'?
Fine. And I'm not
just saying that.
Guess what.
I just started my own business.
I'm a bookie.
No openings in arson?
Either of you guys wanna place
a bet, I'm your guy.
No, no, no.
No bets for me.
I, uh--
I got a disease.
I'm feeling
a bit queasy myself.
Maybe I'll see you
in another five years.
Kramer, Jerry's still mad
about that phony thing?
Are you kidding?
It's all water
near a bridge. [HUFFS]
Oh, what time you got?
Oh, yes, uh...
It's, uh, almost 6.
Whoa, I'm really late.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Oh. These designs look great.
Peggy, you really saved me.
Oh, it was no problem.
Mr. Peterman
is gonna love 'em.
Thanks, Susie.
[♪]
ELAINE:
You won't believe this, but as I'm leaving,
she calls me Susie.
I don't see you as a Susie.
Sharon, maybe.
What am I, a bulimic,
chain-smoking stenographer
from Staten Island?
Who are you describing?
Someone I know.
Named Sharon?
I'd rather not say.
Hey.
Hmm. What's in the bag?
New tuxedo
for the Pinstripe Ball.
Steinbrenner is throwing
a huge party
at Tavern on the Green.
Kind of a Yankee prom?
It's not a prom.
It's a ball.
You taking Allison?
Yes, of course
I'm taking Allison.
This woman is genetically
engineered to go to a ball.
Tall, blond, lithe.
Live?
Lithe.
Oh, lithe.
Well, you two
will have a great time.
It can't be worse than this.
Wait till you see
the dress that she's got.
It's backless. Huh?
I'm finally gonna make
a great entrance.
Backless?
You gonna back her in?
Elaine, when a woman makes
a ball entrance, she twirls.
She's not gonna twi--
She'll twirl.
[♪]
That is what
Mr. Steinbrenner wants.
He wants everyone
to twirl around.
All right.
Great.
Hey, did you get your boss's
Knick ticket for Kramer?
Yeah, here.
Great.
Say, George--
Whew, courtside.
Is that the best you could do?
George, we need to talk.
What?
I really think we need to talk.
Uh-oh.
JERRY:
She wants to talk?
She doesn't want to talk.
She needs to talk.
Nobody needs to talk.
Who would want to?
She tried to end it
with me, Jerry.
What'd you do?
I told her I was out of soda.
I went out to get some,
and I never went back.
All night?
Yeah, I slept at my parents'.
And she wants
to break up with you.
[SNORTS]
Can you believe it?
I'm supposed to be having lunch
with her right now at Pomodoro.
Uh-oh. Everybody breaks up
at Pomodoro's.
So, what am I gonna do?
You really like this girl.
No, I like the ball.
This is my one chance
to make a great entrance.
My whole life, I've never made
a great entrance.
You've made some fine exits.
[MUTTERING]
So, what do you do?
You can't keep avoiding her.
Why not?
If she can't find me,
she can't break up with me.
And if we're still goin' out,
she has to go to the ball.
Hey. Oh, listen,
did you get my ticket
from Allison?
Yeah, right here.
All right.
Yeah.
Courtside. Whoa.
Don't let this girl get away.
She'll have to find me first.
Huh?
Oh, by the way,
you owe Mike $100.
What for?
I bet for you on tonight's game.
Yeah, if the Knicks beat
the Pacers by more than 35,
it pays 10-1.
Ooh-hoo.
That's some sweet action.
But I don't want
any sweet action.
Well, I couldn't do it.
I got a gambling problem.
So you put down my money?
[SIGHS]
You don't have a problem.
Not with that, no.
[♪]
Susie.
Susie!
Uh, hi, Peggy.
Um, look, I should have
said this yesterday--
Did you get this memo
from Elaine Benes?
Yeah, see--
You know, it's amazing
Peterman hasn't fired that dolt.
She practically ran the company
into the ground.
Well... Well, I thought
she did a pretty good job.
I heard she was a disaster, Suz.
Lookit.
It's not Suz, all right?
It's Susie.
My name is Susie.
[♪]
[PHONE RINGS]
GEORGE [OVER MACHINE]:
♪ Believe it or not George isn't at home ♪
♪ Please leave a message
At the beep ♪
♪ I must be out
Or I'd pick up the phone ♪
♪ Where could I be? ♪
♪ Believe it or not
I'm not home ♪
[BEEPS]
George, pick up. I know
you're screening for Allison.
Hey.
So coffee shop?
No, I can't.
She knows I go there.
It's not secure.
Hey, I got another call
coming in.
I gotta let the machine
get it. Bye.
[RINGS]
GEORGE:
♪ Believe it or not George isn't at home ♪
♪ Please leave a message
At the beep ♪
♪ I must be out
Or I'd pick up the phone ♪
♪ Where could I be? ♪
♪ Believe it or not
I'm not home ♪
[BEEPS]
ALLISON:
George, are you there?
I hate that stupid message.
I know you're avoiding me.
I'm at the office.
Please call me.
I've gotta talk to you.
[BEEPING]
Hi, Allison.
Oh, I guess
you're not at home.
I probably should have
tried you at the office.
Anyway, good to hear
from ya.
Really looking forward
to the ball.
[CACKLES]
ELAINE:
Can you believe this woman?
The nerve. Talking about you
behind your back,
and right to your face.
No. Suz.
I mean, Susie,
Suzanne, Susanna. Fine.
But there is no way
I'm gonna be a Suz.
No. No Suz.
I mean, what am I?
Some pom-pom wavin',
back-seat bimbo?
Who are you describing?
Someone I know.
Named Suz?
No, still Sharon.
Hey.
Hey, I thought you went
to the game.
No, I was kicked out
for fightin'
with one of the players.
Wait, wait, wait. Who?
Oh, Reggie Miller.
Cheryl Miller's brother?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
What happened?
Well, first of all,
for some reason, they started
the game an hour late.
And, uh, I don't know,
I was sittin' next to Spike Lee.
And he and Reggie were jawing
at each other. I got involved.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
What do you mean, "involved"?
Well, I ran out
onto the court
and threw a hot dog
at Reggie Miller.
Involved.
Then they threw me and Reggie
and Spike out of the game.
So that's it?
Well, you know, I felt
pretty bad about everything.
Then the three of us,
we went to a strip club.
Can you believe that?
I didn't know Cheryl Miller's
little brother
played basketball.
Knicks killed 'em, 110 to 73.
Well, without Reggie Miller,
it's a blowout.
No, Jerry, that's 37 points.
The Knicks covered. You won.
See, that's a cool G,
daddy-O.
Now, you gotta let it ride.
On what?
Come on, I don't wanna lose
this feeling.
Let's go to the OTB,
put money on the ponies.
Yeah, all right.
They just closed.
Oh, too bad.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Mr. Peterman, you wanted to see me?
Apparently,
Peggy down in Design
got into a little bit
of a tiff yesterday
with somebody named Susie.
Susie.
Yes.
And between you, me,
and the lamppost, and the desk,
Peggy says this Suz
isn't much of a worker.
It's Susie.
Nevertheless, Elaine,
the house of Peterman
is in disorder.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I wanna see you,
Peggy and Susie
right here in my office.
Uh, all--? All of us?
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Allison, hi.
Listen, I'm really sorry
about what happened
at the game last night.
Listen, could I have
that ticket tonight?
The Rockets are in town
and that Hakeem Olajuwon,
he's got a real attitude.
Kramer, have you seen
George around?
I can't get ahold of him.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, he visits the guy
across the hall from me,
like, every 10 minutes.
Oh, yeah?
♪ Believe it or not
George isn't at home ♪
MIKE:
Hey, Jerry.
Hey, Mike.
How 'bout those Knicks?
Yeah. How 'bout 'em?
Look, Jerry,
I can't pay you.
Why not?
'Cause I don't have
the money.
Mike, you say you're a bookie,
you take a bet
and then you can't pay.
I don't know, Mike, to me
it sounds a little, how you say?
Phony.
Just give me till Friday.
Please, please?
You know, you're supposed
to be the bookie.
Act like one.
I'm sorry.
Here, let me give you
a hand with that.
There's something wrong
with this trunk.
Oh, let me see.
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
GEORGE:
So, uh, Kramer, why'd you ask me out to dinner?
And why Pomodoro?
How could you say
that to me?
Allison spoke to me,
and, uh, she wanted me
to speak to you.
Uh-oh.
Now, we all know that this
relationship isn't working.
So Allison and I think
that the best thing to do
is just make a clean break.
Can't we discuss this?
We just don't think you're ready
for a serious relationship.
I didn't even know
you wanted to get serious.
So, what am I in this for?
You know, I'm getting
to a point in my life
where I need something more
than just...a good time.
Are you?
What, me?
No, no.
But she is.
I-- I can't believe
this is happening.
George, we're sorry.
We're through.
Kramer, please.
[SQUEALS]
KRAMER:
I'm sorry.
ELAINE:
Mr. Peterman, Peggy.
I guess we should
just get this over with.
Just hold on
a minute.
We're still one short.
Oh...
No, we're not.
Susie has been very rude to me.
PETERMAN:
Well, Elaine has nothing but good things to say about Susie.
Look.
We don't have to name names
or point fingers or...
name names.
Me and her have had
our problems.
She and I have had
You and I, and she and you.
Don't you drag me
into this.
This is between you
and her and her.
Yes.
And I am convinced
that if she were here
with us today,
she would agree with me too.
Who?
Her.
Where is she?
This is part of the problem.
I thought I was part
of this problem.
You're a huge part
of the problem.
But I think that at its core,
this is a Susie-and-Elaine
problem
that requires
a Susie-and-Elaine solution.
And who better
to do that than...
Elaine and Susie,
Susie and Elaine.
Well, now that we have
that cleared up,
why don't the three of us
have lunch?
What?
Oh. Oh, I'm coming.
I gotta go.
She is the best.
What was your name again?
[♪]
KRAMER:
Mike's outside. He wants to talk to you.
Then why doesn't
he just come in?
Because he's scared, Jerry.
Why is he scared?
Come on, Mike.
Did you do this?
Yeah, but--
Ah-ah!
You broke his thumbs.
It was an accident.
Is that what you call it
when somebody doesn't pay up?
I'll get ya the money,
Jerry.
I got $100 in my front pocket
if you wanna reach in.
I don't want it that way.
Okay, how about Mike
fixes your trunk,
we call it even,
nobody has to get hurt.
Fine.
Thank you, Jerry.
Thank you.
I won't forget this.
I'm gonna fix
your trunk good. Real good.
See, that was nice, Jerry.
Oh, by the way,
I broke your trunk.
Ah, it's just a car.
Hi.
Yeah.
It's funny running
into you here.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's funny.
You look good.
Do I? Thanks.
You too.
Oh, yeah.
[MUTTERING]
[CHUCKLES]
It's getting kinda late.
I really have to be going.
Yeah.
So it's nice seeing you again.
Hey, you know,
maybe I'll call ya sometime.
George, it's over.
It's just--
It's over.
What do you think, Jerry?
I don't know,
I just see you guys together.
[♪]
Stupid thumbs.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[YELPS]
Somebody help. Help!
JERRY:
So Peterman bought it?
I can't believe
you got away with that.
Well, I'm very fortunate
to be surrounded
by such stupidity.
Yeah,
I know how you feel.
Help!
[BANGING]
You hear something?
What?
Jerry.
Oh, the trunk's broken.
It's rattling.
Jerry, I don't know
how much longer
I can keep this up.
They're starting to give Susie
assignments now.
Well, there's only
one thing to do.
Eliminate her.
ELAINE:
What?
JERRY:
Get rid of Susie.
Make her disappear.
But I kind of like her.
She's gone.
Jerry--
Gone!
[JERRY LAUGHING]
The bumper sticker.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SOBBING]
Oh, God, I'm in trouble.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
GEORGE:
Kramer, open up. I know you're in there.
George?
Come on. It's 5:00
in the morning.
What's the matter with you?
It's only 4.
Huh?
I've been walking
around all night.
I've been thinking
about Allison and me...
and you.
Oh.
Come on, George.
Please, give me another chance.
I know I'm gonna
regret this.
All right.
Thank you.
I'm gonna make you both
so happy.
Okay. I'll see ya later.
Whoo!
PETERMAN:
Elaine, where's Susie?
I want her to head up our new
fingerless-glove division.
Oh, but I thought I was in line
for that assignment.
Mmm...nah.
All right, then, I was gonna
wait to tell you this, but...
last night, Susie...
She took her own life.
Oh!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
We're taking George back.
What?
He's gonna make us very happy.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Look at this turnout.
Where did Susie find the time
to meet all these people?
My real funeral's
not gonna come close to this.
Oh, my God.
Susie? How--?
I'm not Susie.
I'm Elaine.
But I've been
calling you Susie.
Oh, I hadn't noticed.
Excuse me.
I guess I never met Susie.
Suz?
I actually had a little thing
with her for a while.
Her too.
What can you say
about a girl like Susie?
[GRUNTING]
[♪]
Hey.
Where's, uh--?
Where's Allison?
No, Allison,
she didn't wanna come.
But you took me back.
Well, yeah, I did,
but she's a tough nut.
How do you like the tuxedo?
It's a rental,
but I've had it for 15 years.
All right.
Where are you goin'?
The ball, silly.
No, no, no.
You're not goin' in there.
George, I thought
you were gonna change.
For her, not for you.
Let's just try and have
a nice time for once.
And we'll talk about this
when we get home.
All right, look.
Wait. Wait. Kramer.
Wait. Wait a minute.
You are not going in there.
[CLOTH RIPS]
[GEORGE YELLS]
Wow!
What an entrance.
And, uh, who might this be?
Oh, I'm with him. Yeah.
And also much like me,
Susie hated going to the market.
Elaine, may I say a few words?
Oh, God, yes,
Mr. Peterman.
I don't think I'll ever be able
to forget Susie.
And most of all,
I will never forget
that one night
working late on the catalog,
just the two of us,
and we surrendered
to temptation.
And it was pretty good.
Yeah, but he didn't sleep
with both of 'em.
But I never heard
her cries for help,
and now Susie is gone.
MIKE:
Hold on! Hold on.
Susie didn't commit suicide.
She was murdered...
[CROWD MURMURING]
by Jerry Seinfeld!
Not only that,
I broke his thumbs.
[♪]
PETERMAN:
Elaine, guess what.
I've decided to form
a charitable foundation
in Susie's honor,
and as Susie's best friend,
I want you to be involved.
Mr. Peterman...
I'm Susie.
She's me.
I feel the same way.
And that's why this foundation
will meet around your schedule.
Nights, weekends,
every free moment you have.
Suz!