[♪]
Well, it's--
It's a magnificent stone.
They put it up
this morning.
Well...
It's just
a magnificent stone.
Jerry?
George,
we'll leave you alone
with her.
What?
I'm sure there are things
you'd like to say.
No, I-I'm--
I'm good.
Really. Jerry?
Jerry?
Thank you, no.
And then right after the, uh--
The All-Star break we--
We just swept the Orioles.
Four games.
In Baltimore.
So...
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
GEORGE:
Boy, that was awkward.
I don't mind
the cemetery.
In fact, now I see
why people like golf.
It's just nice to be outside
in a well-landscaped area.
What were you saying
to the Rosses over there anyway?
Oh, man, I don't know.
I-I told 'em, "Her death takes
place in the shadow of new life.
She's not really dead if we find
a way to remember her."
What is that?
Star Trek II.
Wrath of Khan.
Right. Kramer and I
saw it last night.
Spock dies. They wrap him up
in a towel and they shoot him
out the bowels of the ship
in that big sunglasses case.
It was a hell of a thing
when Spock died.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, the, uh--
The stone is up.
Paid my respects.
I guess that's it, huh?
So it's over?
I have mourned for three
long months, summer months too.
Anybody could grieve
in January.
It's-- It's time for George
to start being George again.
All right. So, uh,
let's do something later.
How about a movie?
Yes!
Nothing says "George"
like a movie. Ah, movie?
Yeah, you in?
No, no, no, I can't.
I got my martial arts class.
Well, George is going
to the movie!
So how's
your karate class going?
"Ka-ra-tay,"
Jerry, "ka-ra-tay."
It's the lifetime pursuit
of balance and harmony.
But with punching
and kicking.
Jerry.
Karate is not here.
It's here.
And here.
All right. I gotta go to
the airport and pick up Elaine.
What, she's been away?
She's been in Mexico
for six weeks.
I think you're wrong.
We just went to the fireworks
the other day.
That was July 4th.
All right,
I'm outta here.
And when I get back,
I don't wanna see you here.
Here, or here.
[♪]
ELAINE:
It was unbelievable.
Six weeks of traveling through
Mexico, all on Peterman's peso.
Wow, so did you get any good
ideas for the catalogue?
Oh, tons.
Anything you couldn't have gotten
tearing open a bag of Doritos
and watching Viva Zapata?
[CHUCKLES]
You don't respect my work
at all, do you?
No, I don't.
No.
So, what's been going on
around this dump?
How's your fiancée?
My what?
Jeannie? Your fiancée?
Oh, yeah. That.
Well...
All right. Spill it, Jerome.
There's really
not that much to tell.
About a month ago
we were here having lunch,
and all of a sudden
we both just blurted out:
BOTH:
I hate you.
See ya.
It was unprecedented.
I mean, it was the first
truly mutual breakup
in relationship history.
No rejection, no guilt,
no remorse.
You've never felt remorse.
I know.
I feel bad about that.
I bet your parents
were upset, huh? Eh.
You haven't told 'em yet,
have you? No.
[♪]
"So I pressed
through the rushes.
There below me, the shimmering
waters of Lake Victoria."
Oh, for the love of God, man.
Just tell me
what the product is.
It's a...washcloth.
No washcloths.
Well, Mr. Peterman,
I've got a really good idea
for a hat.
Oh, my neck is one
gargantuan monkey fist.
It combines the spirit
of old Mexico
with a little
big-city panache.
I like to call it
the "urban sombrero."
No, no.
No pears.
Mr. Peterman?
No apples.
ELAINE:
Um?
Where's my pineapple?
Are you okay,
Mr. Peterman?
Yes, yes, go on.
Go on. Go on.
Well, see, it's
businessmen taking siestas.
[GROANING]
You know, it's the, uh--
It's the urban sombrero.
Mr. Peterman?
[♪]
Hey, Jerry,
I'm feeling somethin',
somethin' I haven't felt
for a long time.
Pride?
No.
Autonomy, complete
and total autonomy.
Well, you're
your own boss now.
I wanna go
to a tractor pull.
Go ahead.
I am staying out
all night.
Who's stopping you?
I wanna bite into
a big hunk of cheese,
just bite into it
like it's an apple.
Whatever.
JERRY:
Oh, God.
GEORGE:
What?
It's Dolores.
Who?
Mulva.
Jerry, hi.
Hi, Dolores.
George, you remember
Dolores.
Hi.
I heard you got engaged.
Yes, Dolores, I did.
It didn't work out, though,
Dolores.
Oh, that's too bad.
You know, we should
get together some time.
See ya.
Bye, Dolores.
I thought Mulva hated you.
Yeah, so did I.
You know what?
I bet it was
the engagement.
I've shown I can go
all the way.
All the way?
Not our all the way.
Their all the way.
I got the stink
of responsibility on me.
Yeah, you were engaged
for, like, a minute.
I was engaged
for a year.
You stink worse
than I do.
I'm feeling
somethin' else here, Jerry.
[♪]
WOMAN [OVER SPEAKER PHONE]:
Elaine, Mr. Peterman on line one.
Hello, Mr. Peterman,
how are you feeling?
Elaine, I'll be blunt.
I'm burnt out. I'm fried.
My mind is as barren
as the surface of the moon.
I can run that catalogue
no longer.
What? Who's gonna do it?
What about you?
Me? Why me?
Why, indeed.
Mr. Peterman, you can't leave.
I've already left, Elaine.
I'm in Burma.
Burma?
[LAUGHS]
You most likely
know it as Myanmar.
But it will always
be Burma to me.
Bonne chance, Elaine.
You there, on the motorbike,
sell me one of your melons.
Mr. Peterman?
Where?
Burma.
Isn't it Myanmar now?
Jerry, he wants me
to run the catalogue.
I mean, it's crazy.
I can't be in charge.
No, certainly not.
I mean, I can't
give people orders.
No one's gonna
listen to you.
I am not qualified
to run the catalogue.
You're not qualified
to work at the catalogue.
Hey.
[GROANING]
What's wrong?
Oh, Peterman ran off to Burma.
And now he wants me
to run the catalogue.
Where?
Myanmar.
Is that the discount pharmacy?
Well, I'm just gonna
tell him no.
I can't run the catalogue.
Whoa, whoa, "can't"?
When did that word
enter your vocabulary?
What, is the job
too difficult?
What, you don't have
enough experience?
You're not smart enough?
Where's your confidence?
Elaine, let me tell you
a story.
When I first started
karate...
"Ka-ra-tay"?
Yeah, I had no support.
Not from him,
not from Newman, no one.
First time I sparred with
an opponent I was terrified.
My legs,
they were like noodles.
Then I looked inside,
and I found my katra.
"Katra"?
Yeah, your spirit,
your, uh, being.
That part of you
that says, "Yes, I can."
Sammy Davis had it.
So I listened to my katra,
and now:
[TRUMPETS]
I'm dominating the dojo.
I'm class champion.
Well, you know, I--
I have watched
Peterman run the company.
Sure, you have.
I know how to do it.
Mm-hm.
Pair of pants,
stupid story, a huge markup.
I can do that.
You follow your katra
and you can do anything.
[LAUGHING]
Now get out of here.
Okay.
That kid is gonna be
all right.
No, she's not.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
BOY:
Come on, Kramer.
Hey there.
Come on.
Mom's down in the car.
Okay, Joey.
You guys have class
at the same time?
No, we're in
the same class.
You're in the same class?
He almost beat me.
Kramer,
you're fighting children?
We're all at the same
skill level, Jerry.
He's 9 years old.
You don't need karate.
You can just ring his neck.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
I got car pool.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Thanks for the juice box, Mrs. Z.
Hey, can we stop for ice cream
on the way home, Mom?
Mmm, I don't know about--
ALL:
Please!
Please,
please!
All right.
ALL:
Yeah!
[♪]
DUGAN:
You're taking the job?
You got that straight.
Now, I want four new ideas
from each of you by 6:00.
No, make that six ideas
by 4:00.
All right. Let's move.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Are you prepared for kumite?
BOTH:
Yes, sensei.
Fighting stance.
[BOTH GRUNT]
Begin!
Ha-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
[♪]
[YELLING AND GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[KRAMER YELLING]
[GONG BONGS]
Winner.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
It's open.
Rosses.
Hello, George.
[STAMMERING]
Come in. Come in.
We, uh, tried to call,
but the line was busy.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Sure, here.
Uh, sit down,
please.
Uh... Uh, cheese there?
We know the last three months
have been hard on you.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Very, very hard.
And they've been hard
on us too.
It's a terrible tragedy
when parents outlive
their children.
Yes, I agree. I-- I hope
my parents go long before I do.
That's why we decided
to create a foundation
to preserve Susan's memory.
Oh, that's wonderful.
And, of course, we want you
to be an integral part.
Yes, integ--
H-how int--? How integral?
You'll be on the board
of directors.
Great.
[CHUCKLING]
Great!
Oh, oh, oh, gosh,
you know, it's just...
My duties with the Yankees,
you know--
MRS. ROSS:
Oh, don't worry, George.
The foundation will revolve
around your schedule.
Evening, weekends,
whenever you have free time.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Well, it wouldn't have
without your friend Jerry's
inspirational words.
He said to us, "She's not
really dead if her shadow is--"
Uh, what was it, dear?
Something about a way,
wasn't it?
And a light and a--
[CHUCKLES]
Who the hell knows.
MR. ROSS:
But what's important is that your relationship with Susan
doesn't have to end.
MRS. ROSS:
So will you be sure to thank Jerry for us?
The second I see him.
[♪]
Hey.
How's your day? Good?
Actually, yeah.
I'm meeting Mulva here
in a few minutes.
So, uh...
Wrath of Khan, huh?
Yeah, was that a beauty
or what?
What was that line again?
Something about...finding
your way in a shadow?
No, no, no, it's,
"She's not really dead
if we find a way
to remember her."
That's it.
That's the line...
that destroyed my life.
Problem?
The Rosses have started up
a foundation, Jerry,
and I have to sit
on the board of directors.
Hey, board of directors,
look at you.
Yeah, look at me.
I was free and clear.
I was living the dream.
I was stripped to the waist
eating a block of cheese
the size of a car battery.
Before we go any further,
I'd just like to point out
how disturbing it is that you
equate eating a block of cheese
with some sort
of bachelor paradise.
Don't you see? I'm back in.
All because of Wrath of Khan?
Yes!
Well, it was the best
of those movies.
Khan!
[♪]
George?
Oh!
I'm Wyck Thayer, chairman
of the Susan Ross Foundation.
Wink?
Wyck.
Now, as you know, the, uh,
Rosses had considerable monies.
Well, I-- I know
they have some monies.
They had more than some monies.
Many, many monies.
And they planned, uh,
to give a sizable portion
of their estate to you
and Susan after the wedding.
So if Susan and I had--
I mean, if the envelopes
hadn't, uh...
Then we...
Yes.
And now?
Not.
It's all been endowed
to the foundation.
Even this townhouse.
This townhouse?
Yes, this would have been
your wedding gift.
And now?
Not.
Also endowed.
George, I know how much
Susan meant to you.
This can't be easy.
You know, it really can't.
[♪]
DOLORES:
So who broke it off?
Well, that's the thing.
It was mutual.
Oh, come on. Everybody knows
there's no such thing
as a mutual breakup.
Tell me the truth.
I am.
It was the world's first.
[SIGHS]
You know,
when I heard you got engaged,
I thought maybe you'd matured,
but obviously
there's no growth here.
Well, I can't argue
with that,
but the fact remains
I was completely...
Mulva.
[RINGING]
[LOCKS TURNING]
Hello.
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
Please hold for Elaine Benes.
Oh, I don't believe this.
Jerry?
JERRY:
Hey.
Hey, guess who just finished
laying out her first issue
of the J. Peterman Catalogue?
How's it look?
It's a peach.
What's that?
I say, it's a peach.
Let me ask you something.
When I told you
my breakup was mutual,
did you believe me?
No, no, no.
It's weak.
No one's gonna buy it,
and you shouldn't be selling it.
I gotta do some research here.
Hey, hey. Me, talkin'?
You know,
between you and me,
I always thought Kramer
was a bit of a doofus.
But he believed in me.
You did not.
So as I see it,
he's not the doofus,
you are the doofus.
Oh, I'm the doofus?
Yes.
You, Jerry, are the doofus.
You know, it occurs to me
that Kramer is
at "ka-ra-tay" right now.
Well, maybe I'll just go
down there
and thank him in person.
Yeah, that's what
I was thinkin'.
[♪]
[YELLING]
Kramer?
Ahh!
Oh, hey.
What are you doing?
Oh, well, I'm dom--
I'm dominating.
You never said
you were fighting children.
Well, it's not the size
of the opponent, Elaine.
It's, uh...the ferocity.
This is what you used
to build me up?
This is where got
all that stupid katra stuff?
No, no, no, that's from,
uh, Star Trek III.
The Search for Spock.
Search for Spock?
Yeah, yeah, I know. Jerry will
tell you that the Wrath of Khan
is the better picture,
but for me, I--
You doofus!
CHILDREN:
Wow.
[♪]
Okay, question number eight:
what if I told you my fiancée
left me for another man?
Does that make me more likable,
less likable, as likable?
Let's start over here
this time.
More.
Less.
Same.
Are we about through here?
[♪]
I thought you said your mom
was meeting us in the alley.
Ah, she had a little
change of plans.
[♪]
What's going on?
Hey, Timmy, Clara.
That was some kind of workout
we had tonight, huh?
Now we finish it.
Huh? Wha--?
BOY:
Get him.
Ah! Ahh! Mama!
[♪]
JERRY:
Dad, I wouldn't eat anything
you caught in that pond
out in front of the condo.
All right. Look, Elaine's here.
I gotta get going.
Uh, by the way, uh...
I'm not getting married.
Tell Mom. Bye.
[PHONE RINGS]
So...
Did you stop by the dojo?
Yup.
How's your
confidence level?
Shot.
Self-esteem?
Gone.
Doofus?
Yo.
All right. So what?
You put out the catalogue.
How bad could it be?
What is that?
The urban sombrero.
I put it on the cover.
Well, nobody sees the...cover.
What happened to you?
Whew. I got whupped.
You should have seen the rage
in their little eyes.
And those tiny little fists
of fury.
Oh.
What is that?
It's the new cover
of the J. Peterman catalogue.
It is Elaine's choice.
Let's congratulate her.
Whoa.
This is all your fault.
You told me
I could run the company.
Well, then I was way off!
Well, I'll see ya.
Vaya con Dios.
Man. I gotta go lay down.
Are you and George
going out a little later?
No, he's still stuck
at the foundation.
You know, you oughta go
down there and help him out.
He's a widower.
Widower? Wait a second.
[♪]
Okay, let's see.
The beach house, 48 acres--
Ooh, Southampton.
That should fetch
a fair price.
Would I have had access
to that?
Course.
Would have been yours.
And now?
Not.
[PHONE RINGS]
Got it.
Hello.
JERRY:
Hey, Georgie.
I'm doing some research
down at the coffee shop.
Your story's the one.
My story?
Yeah, your widower story's
tested through the roof.
When are you getting
out of there?
Um. Excuse me, Wyck,
are we, uh, almost done here?
[CHUCKLING]
No, no, not even close.
I can't go.
What do you mean,
you can't go?
There's two really cute girls
sitting at the counter,
eating grilled cheese.
Cheese, George.
Cheese.
Okay, next item,
Susan's doll collection.
Estimated value: 2.6 million.
What do you say we go
through this doll by doll.
[♪]
It was nothing unusual.
Every afternoon
for the last 24 years,
I'd shut the door to my office
and sneak a little shuteye.
No one was the wiser.
But then my wife gets me
this urban sombrero.
The next thing I know,
my ass is out on the street.
I tried one too.
I woke up and found my walking
papers tacked to the brim.
Stupid J. Pendleton.
It's "Peterman."
It's J. Peterman.
I never thought
a hat would destroy my life.
[♪]