[♪]
Uh-- Uh, excuse me?
Be with you
in a minute.
No, you should have
come last night.
It was fun.
Um, I just have a question.
I know.
The margaritas
in that place
are so strong.
Hello.
I'd like to buy
these huaraches.
[SIGHS]
So...
what else is going on?
Hee-hee!
Hey!
Listen. I'll call
you back.
Yes?
What can I do for you?
Nothing.
You just lost
a customer.
WOMAN:
Ready to go? I don't wanna miss the previews.
Me neither. I love
the previews.
In fact, I enjoy being
the theater cutup.
Last week after a preview,
I yelled out, "Must miss!"
I think that I was
in that theater.
That-- That was really funny.
Yeah, I got a good laugh.
Ha!
Let me just check
my messages before we go.
[DIAL TONE HUMMING]
GEORGE:
So you're on the speed dial?
After two dates.
What number?
Seven.
Wow! You know,
it's a pain to change that.
You gotta lift up
that plastic thing with a pen.
[INDISTINCT
SINGING]
Oh, hey, buddy. Hey.
Hey.
Is it all right if I keep these
here for a while?
I'm having a New Year's Eve
party.
You're gonna keep these here
for eight months?
No, Jerry.
New Year's Eve, 1999.
The millennium.
I told you about that.
Y-you're gonna leave
these chairs here
for two and a half years?
You're not gonna see 'em.
I got a case of party poppers
I'm gonna keep in front of 'em.
It's all right.
Hey, so get this.
I got a call this morning
from one of the Mets'
front-office guys.
They wanna take me
out to lunch.
What for?
I'm on a winning
ball club, Jerry.
They probably wanna
pick my brain.
Really. Why do you think
they're taking you out to lunch?
I have no idea.
All right. I have had it
with those Mayans.
I don't mind the Mayans.
You know that store,
Putumayo?
I was trying to buy
these huaraches,
and this saleswoman
just completely ignored me.
Oh, are we talking
huaraches?
I know a great store
for huaraches.
No, no.
Not Putumayo.
Cinco de Mayo.
Yeah, Marcelino,
he turned me onto it.
And he's 1/64
Mayan.
I'm starting to get a little
nervous about this lunch.
What did you have?
Elaine.
I'm gonna...
keep these here too, huh?
They'll be all right.
Kramer, these balloons
aren't gonna stay filled
till New Year's.
Oh, those aren't
for New Year's.
Those are my everyday
balloons.
MAN:
George, we'll be blunt.
The Mets need somebody
to head up scouting.
And we think that someone
might be you.
Head of scouting?
Interested?
I'm still here.
Now, unfortunately,
league rules prevent us
from making you an offer while
you're still under contract.
Do you understand
what we're talking about?
So you're talking--
No, no.
We're not talking.
We're just...
talking.
So you need me...
to get fired?
We didn't say that.
We couldn't say that.
Because even if we did--
We couldn't say that we said it.
You see what
we're saying?
But you are still paying
for this lunch?
We didn't say that.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
There's a lot of chairs
and balloons in my apartment.
How about I make it up
to you with dinner?
Someplace nice this time?
Yeah, I'm sorry about that
Mongolian barbecue last night.
I had heard good things.
I don't know.
It got a two in Zagat's.
Let me just, uh,
check my messages.
Maybe a nicer girl called.
[PHONE DIALING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
Hello.
Hello?
Who is this?
Jane. What number
did you dial?
Seven.
Hey!
See these?
Cinco de Mayo!
Sales commission,
bye-bye-o!
GEORGE:
♪ Meet the Mets ♪
♪ Come on in
And greet the Mets ♪
[LAUGHS]
Good meeting?
There was no meeting.
But it was
quite a meeting.
You are looking
at the next director
of Mets scouting.
The only thing is
I have to
get fired from
the Yankees first.
You can do that.
Of course.
But I really wanna leave my
mark this time, you know? Uh-
I wanna walk away
from the Yankees
with people saying:
"Wow!
Now, that guy got canned."
So you wanna go out in
a final blaze of incompetence.
Yeah. Remember that summer
at Dairy Queen,
where I cooled my feet
in the soft-serve machine?
Yeah.
Think people will
still be using napkins
in the year 2000?
Or is this mouth-vacuum thing
for real?
So, George...
Yeah.
I had, like, a so-so date
with Valerie.
Now I'm number nine
on the speed dial.
So?
So I used to be seven.
I dropped two spots.
What? She's ranking you?
Yeah, the speed dial's like
a relationship barometer.
What is a barometer
exactly?
It's pronounced "thermometer."
You know, in the year 2000,
we'll all be on speed dial.
You just have to think
of a person,
they'll be talking
to you.
It'll be like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm getting a call here."
"Hey, it's Newman."
"Hey, how you doing, Newman?"
[MOUTHS]
I'm not here.
"Oh, you wanna
talk to Jerry?"
VALERIE:
Oh. Flowers.
You didn't
have to do that.
I mean, the dinner
and the play
and the hansom
cab ride.
Well, I just wanted to--
You forgot the gift certificate
to Barnes & Noble. Oh.
--you know,
make a good impression.
I'm gonna go put these
in some water.
I like the way
you think.
[GIGGLES]
Oh, my God.
Number one.
Seinfeld, you magnificent
bastard.
GEORGE:
Sorry I'm late, but look what I found
in the Yankee Hall of Pride
display case.
[CHUCKLES]
Isn't that Babe's Ruth
uniform?
Is it?
Eh. Strawberries,
anyone?
Aw, it's good.
Ooh. Juicy this time of year.
Heh-heh.
Gotta get the good ones.
Oh, that's bad.
That's bad.
KRAMER:
So, Jerry, my millennium party's really coming together.
Will people be able to breathe
underwater in the year 2000?
Some of us.
I don't want to exclude anybody.
Hola.
Shove it.
What is all this?
I got all of this junk
at Cinco de Mayo
because I was trying
to show Putumayo
how much business
they'd lost.
I mean, I've been
dancing and strutting
in front of their store
for two days.
Oh, no wonder we're
getting so much rain.
Elaine, I'm having
a millennium party,
so save the date.
Hey, you know what? Newman
sent me an invitation already
to his party.
Newman?
Yeah.
"Come celebrate the millennium
with 'Newmannium.'"
Newman.
Hi, Valerie.
You're not Valerie.
I'm her stepmother.
Drive.
It's taken me 13 years
to climb up
to the top of
that speed dial,
and I don't intend
to lose my spot to you.
But I-I never--
You just stay away
from that phone.
GEORGE:
You wanted to see me, sir?
I heard about what happened
at the meeting this morning.
Oh, yes. I already
packed up my desk, sir.
I could be out of here
in an hour.
And I have to tell you
it's exactly what
this organization needed.
If we wanna look
to the future,
we've gotta tear down
the past.
Babe Ruth was nothing more
than a fat old man
with little-girl legs.
And here's something
I just found out recently.
He wasn't really
a sultan. Huh?
What do you make
of that?
Hey. check
this out.
Lou Gehrig's pants.
Not a bad fit.
You don't think
that nerve disease of his
was contagious, do you?
Oh. Better take
them off.
I'm too important
to this team.
Big Stein can't be
flopping and twitching.
Hey. How about
some lunch?
What are you
going for?
JERRY:
You know, uh, Valerie,
I, uh, couldn't help but notice
that I'm on your speed dial.
You deserve it.
But I--
I can't help thinking
that maybe there's
someone in your life
who deserves it more.
Someone you've known,
you know...
more than a week.
My stepmother got to you,
didn't she?
What? No.
[GROANS]
I can't believe
she did this again.
That's it.
She's off the speed dial
completely.
Yikes.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Well, I just got
your invitation
to the Newmannium
party.
You just got it?
Damn, the mail is slow.
You knew I was having
a millennium party,
but you just had to throw yours
on the same day.
I have done nothing
unethical.
Well, you're gonna have
to cancel it,
because I've told everybody
about my party.
Cancel?
Think again,
long shanks.
I started planning this in 1978.
I put a deposit down
on that revolving restaurant
that overlooks Times Square.
And I booked
Christopher Cross.
Well, what am I
gonna do?
I got
over 200 folding chairs
and quite a bit of ice.
What kind?
Cubed.
That's good stuff.
And you can never have
too much ice.
All right, I'll tell you
what I'll do.
You can cohost
the party with me. Mm-hm.
Under one condition.
No Jerry.
Jerry is not invited.
I got to invite Jerry.
He's my buddy.
That he may be,
but he's out of my life
starting in the year 2000.
For me, the next millennium
must be Jerry-free.
JERRY:
How could they not fire you?
Gee. Never thought
I'd fail at failing.
Oh, come on, now.
Feel like I can't do
anything wrong.
Nonsense.
You do everything
wrong.
Everything?
Everything.
You really think so?
Absolutely.
I have no confidence in you.
All right.
I guess I just have to
pick myself up,
dust myself off...
and throw myself
right back down again.
That's the spirit.
You suck.
I know.
No, no, no, listen to me.
I work in fashion.
Together we can drive
Putumayo out of business
and make Cinco de Mayo
numero uno...
de Mayo.
Do you need some help
with something?
You? What are you
doing here?
I own this store.
No, you don't.
You own Putumayo.
Unless you own
both stores.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm Gladys Mayo.
Ah, this really
sticks in my craw.
Well, Mrs. Hamilton,
it's certainly nice that
you and Valerie
patched things up
so we could all
get together like this.
Where is Valerie?
I'm sure
she'll be along.
Have some wine, Jerome.
Okay.
You know, Jerome,
I can understand
what Valerie sees in you.
So attractive...
so strong,
so comedic.
Mm. Good.
Jerome...
I have a deliciously
naughty idea.
What?
Why don't I put you
on my speed dial?
I don't know, Mrs. Hamilton.
That doesn't sound--
Don't be such
a child, Jerome.
How's number three sound?
Valerie's not
coming over, is she?
Seven, four--
No.
--two.
Stop. Stop. This isn't right.
What about Valerie?
I won't tell if you don't.
Oh, my--
[LAUGHS]
Jerry.
Newman.
It's 2000.
Newmannium!
Oh, Jerry.
[WHIMPERS]
MALE ANNOUNCER [OVER TV]:
All right, Yankees 2, Orioles nothing.
Wait a minute.
A short, stocky bald man
is streaking across the field.
Oh, my God, George.
No, check that.
He's not streaking.
He's wearing
a flesh-toned body stocking.
Apparently, he's
a bit bashful,
and oddly,
no one seems upset.
Kramer, look.
It's George.
Everyone loves him.
Yeah, I know.
Listen. Jerry.
I can't let you come
to my New Year's party.
All right.
It's killing me.
Newman's got the jump
on the invites
and will crush me
if I try to go it alone.
No problem.
You're right.
I won't do it without you.
Oh, I feel so ashamed
I even thought of it, huh?
[DOOR OPENS]
Elaine, you can't go
to Newman's Newmannium.
Okay.
No, no, no. You gotta spend
New Year's 1999
with me and Jerry.
Fine.
Oh, come on!
All right.
Yes! All right.
So it's you, it's me,
and it's Jerry, huh?
Yeah. Now things are starting
to snowball, huh?
I'll tell Newman
I don't need him.
So I'll, uh, see you two
in the 21st century.
Okay. Kramer. Kramer.
Wait a minute.
Do you still have
that pricing gun? Yeah.
Okay. I need you to help me
put Putumayo out of business.
Can do.
What are you doing
with a pricing gun?
That place is about to have
the sale of the century.
Nothing over 99 cents.
Still a rip-off.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Jerry, I was just
at my stepmom's house,
and I saw that you were
on her speed dial.
Uh, well, she, uh,
probably just wanted
to be able
to keep tabs on you.
[CALL WAITING BEEPS]
Hold on a second.
Hello.
Hi, Jerome.
Oh, Mrs. Hamilton,
this is a very bad time.
I've got Valerie
on the other line.
Just a second.
Hello.
That's her, isn't it?
Well...
Tell her I don't want you
on her speed dial.
Hang on.
She knows about
the speed dial, Mrs. Hamilton.
You gotta get me
off this thing.
I won't until
she puts me back on hers.
Hang on.
She wants to be
back on yours.
Fine. But only
if you're off hers.
Hang on.
Fine.
If I'm off yours.
No. Still me.
Sorry. Hang on.
Fine,
if I'm off yours.
I won't do it.
It's my speed dial,
and I don't trust her.
Please, Mrs. Hamilton,
this is very awkward
for me.
All right.
I'll hide you in one of
the emergency buttons.
Great. Bye.
She said
she'll do it.
Great.
[CALL WAITING BEEPS]
Hang on.
Hello.
Jerry.
I can't get fired.
Hey, Body-Suit Man.
What's up?
MAN 1:
Hey!
MAN 2:
Hey, look who it is.
Body-Suit Man.
ALL:
Hey!
Hi.
Mm.
[COUGHS]
Hi. I'm, uh,
H.E. Pennypacker.
I'm a wealthy
American industrialist, uh,
looking to open a silver mine
in the mountains of Peru.
And before I invest millions
in a lucrative mine, I--
I'd like to go
a little native, uh...
Get the feel
of their condiments,
their unmentionables.
You know, the real, uh,
gritty-gritty.
Um, let me show you
what we have.
No, no. I think I can just
browse around on my own.
Mmm,
Machu Picchu. Hm.
Are these free?
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
[COUGHING]
Some of those
are women's clothes.
Oh, not a problem.
[PRICING GUN CLICKING]
Attention, Steinbrenner,
and front-office morons.
Your triumphs mean nothing.
You all stink.
You can sit on it
and rotate!
This is George Costanza!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
I fear no reprisal.
Extension 5170.
Ocupado.
Come on. What is
taking you so long?
All right, I broke
the price gun,
so I had to move to plan B.
Plan B?
Yeah.
There is no plan B.
I took these out of every single
garment in the store.
What?
They're desiccants.
See, they absorb moisture.
These clothes won't last
five years without 'em.
[GROANS]
That's not gonna do anything.
Patience.
All right, forget it.
What?
You have screwed me again,
Pennypacker.
Ladies, care for
some chips?
Well, I don't mind
if I do.
Mmm. Well, I've, uh--
I've changed
my mind. I--
I think I'm going to build
a roller coaster instead.
Mmm.
I heard what you did
in the parking lot, big boy,
and it is in-ex-cus-a-ble.
Personally insulting me,
my staff.
I cannot believe that you,
Body-Suit Man,
could perpetrate
such a disloyal deed.
It breaks my heart
to say it.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I love it. You're--
Wait! Wait,
Mr. Steinbrenner.
George doesn't deserve
any of the blame
for what happened in
the parking lot today, sir.
If there's anyone
to blame here, it's me.
What are you
talking about?
You popping pills?
Got the crazies?
No, no.
No, no, no, sir.
I ordered George to drive around
insulting people today.
Because I'm tired of
all your macho head games.
He's lying, sir. I'm tired
of all your macho head games!
Macho head games?
He's just being
loyal to me, sir.
Wilhelm,
you're fired.
I owe you an apology,
Body-Suit Man. Streak on.
Now, if you gentlemen
will excuse me.
I'm not going to
the game today.
I'm gonna go
outside
and scalp
some tickets.
Owner's box. That's gotta bring
in 40 bucks, no problem.
Mr. Wilhelm,
what was that?
I wanted to get fired.
George...you are looking at
the new head scout
of the New York Mets.
♪ Meet the Mets
Meet the Mets ♪
♪ Come right out
And greet the Mets ♪
I mean, I don't know
what Elaine is so upset about.
I mean, without desiccants,
those clothes
will be noticeably musty
in five years.
She never sees the big picture.
[POUNDING AT DOOR]
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
What did you say
to Elaine?
I just got her cancellation
in the mail.
Oh. Well, I guess she found
someplace better to go.
Well...it's her mistake,
because she is going to miss
the party of a lifetime.
Well, maybe so.
But come midnight,
when she's looking for someone
warm and cuddly to kiss,
I guess you'll be
caught
between the moon
and New York City.
All right.
Come back
to my party...please.
Jerry too,
of course.
You don't wanna do your act
or anything, do you?
No.
All right, then.
I guess I can accept
a little Jerry
if it gets me a...
lot of Elaine.
Deal?
To the Newmannium.
To the "Kramennium."
By the way, Newman,
I'm just curious.
When you booked the hotel,
did you book it
for the millennium New Year?
As a matter of fact,
I did.
Oh, that's interesting,
because as everyone knows,
since there was no year zero,
the millennium doesn't
begin until the year 2001.
Which would make
your party one year late.
And thus...
quite lame.
Ohhh.
[SQUAWKS]
[♪]
I don't feel well
at all.
I feel all dried-out
inside.
Oh.
I'll call for help.
Okay.
[DIAL TONE HUMS,
PHONE DIALS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Who's this?
It's Jerry. Who's this?
Ugh.
It's Valerie. Ugh.
Oh, hi, Valerie. What's up?
I'll tell you what's up.
[GROANS]
My stepmother is violently ill,
so I hit the button
for Poison Control
and I get you.
Wow. Poison Control.
That's even higher
than number one.
Hello?
[♪]
[NEWMAN SQUAWKS]