[♪]
[SIGHS]
Well, that was all right,
huh?
Yeah.
Well, um, good night.
Yeah, good night.
Boy...
[♪]
[GRUNTS]
Believe this...
[♪]
HELEN:
Jerry, we can only stay four days.
Well, I'm upset,
but we'll make the most of it.
Helen, did you pack
my travel gym?
Yes. Oh, your father bought
a exercise device
off television.
He does it every morning at 4.
Only 25 minutes a day,
and you can attach it
to any doorknob, heh.
JERRY: Ah.
So I guess your travel miles
are about to expire?
Well, actually, Jerry, we wanted
to talk to you about something.
Am I finally getting
a baby brother?
Jerry, be serious.
How would you feel
if we sold the Cadillac?
What? The--? The Cadillac
I bought for you?
It's too much car, Jerry.
Oh, come on. You love that car.
What about the Northstar system?
I don't think
we even use it.
Well, it's a gift, and I--
I want you to keep it.
We already sold it.
Why--? Why didn't you tell me
before you sold it?
We had a buyer, and we couldn't
get a free flight until now.
Well, we could,
but we wanted the bulkhead.
Oh, my God.
[DOOR OPENS]
Ah, well...
Man, that Emily
is wearin' me out.
Kramer...
No, no, no,
it's not the sex, Jerry.
H-hey, Seinfelds.
Hi, Kramer.
Hiya, Kramer.
We're in the middle
of a discussion.
Oh, yeah? What about?
Jerry's upset.
We sold the Cadillac.
What'd you get for it?
Jack Klompus
gave us 6 grand.
[WHISTLES]
You sold my Cadillac
to Jack Klompus?
And we want you
to have the money.
I don't need the money.
What are you talking about?
You had a check bounce
at the bodega.
Oh, is that
what this is all about?
I bounce a check
and you sold a Cadillac?
Well, also, Jerry, we read
an article in the Sun-Sentinel.
It says that standup comedy
is not what it used to be,
what with Def Jam and all.
Yeah, that Def Jam
is a force.
Jerry, you know,
I hear wonderful things
about Bloomingdale's
executive training program.
Oh, my God.
KRAMER:
You've given this comedy thing your best shot.
Yeah, you had some
good observations,
but it's over.
Now, this Bloomingdale thing:
[CLICKS TONGUE]
That could be the next wave.
[GROANING ANGRILY]
[♪]
GEORGE:
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, a pound
of Arabian Mocha Java, please.
So you understand
how my Peterman stock options
are gonna work?
I'm going to the bathroom.
It's just very interesting.
Yeah, when it's your money,
it's fascinating.
Hm.
Arabian Mocha Java.
Mm.
Oh, um, I got it.
That Arabian
is strong coffee.
It's PLO blend.
Oh, I got your coffee.
Oh. Oh, here, let me, uh--
Nah, nah, it's on me.
Oh, man. Okay, listen, guys,
I'm gonna be late.
I'll see you, okay?
Yeah.
Bye.
Mm.
You see what just happened here?
What?
She treated me
to the Arabian Mocha Java.
And you misinterpret
this how?
She's stickin' it to me that
she makes more money than me.
I'm sure she was just being nice
buyin' you the coffee.
No, not nice.
Stickin' it to me.
You're crazy.
Stickin' it to me, Jerry.
George.
Sticking it!
[♪]
GEORGE:
So you're buying the car back for your parents?
I'm flying down
to Florida tomorrow.
Your parents'll never
let you do it.
They lie to me
about selling the car,
I'll lie to them
about buyin' it back.
They think they can dump
6 grand on me? Think again.
What kind of money
you think your parents have?
Excuse me?
I bet they have more money
than mine.
Come on. Your parents
have money. You think?
When do they ever spend money?
Never.
What are their expenses?
Nothing.
Where do they go on vacation?
Nowhere.
How much do you think
they have?
Few hundred grand?
You're saying I stand
to inherit $300,000?
Is that what you're saying?
You may not see it
for 20 years.
Twenty years? That long?
Does your father eat
bacon and eggs every day?
Unfortunately, yes.
How's your family history?
I have an aunt that died at 7.
Really?
Aunt Baby.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Elaine, uh, you got a moment?
Yeah, Kramer, come on in.
I, uh, need to speak to you
about some lady problems.
Okay...
You know,
after I have sex with Emily,
uh, I don't want her
in the bed anymore.
Ah, yeah.
Yeah, because she's throwin' off
my whole sleep.
She's got the jimmy legs.
Jimmy legs?
The-- Uh, jimmy leg.
Oh.
So, uh... Well, uh,
maybe I should just be honest
with her, huh?
Tell her after sex
you just want her out of there?
Well, I'd say it nicely.
I don't think so.
Well, you know, I really like
this girl. And I--
You know, I think if I could
work out this one thing--
Yeah, I gotta be honest
with you, Kramer.
You might be more than
just a couple of tweaks away
from a healthy relationship.
Well, you're not exactly
zeroing in yourself, lady.
All right, get out.
Get out!
[♪]
JERRY:
So listen, I've gotta go down to Atlantic City.
I'm performing
at Bally's.
You just heard
about this today?
They had a cancellation,
and they instantly called me.
Who canceled?
Carrot Top.
I told you:
My career's fine.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I've been, uh, thinkin' about the family.
Tell me, uh, about Aunt Baby.
She's deceased.
Yeah.
Um, why did she die so young?
She had problems.
Internal.
Is that common in our family?
Well, your Uncle Moe,
he died a young man.
Also internal problems.
It's that temper on your side.
They're yelling and yelling
and then one day,
they're all gone.
FRANK:
What about your side?
Your cousin Heddy.
She was sickly
from the moment I met her.
Don't you talk about Heddy!
So I guess
you two are the lucky ones.
So far.
Frank,
if Aunt Baby were alive today,
how old would she be?
She'd never make it.
[♪]
EMILY:
So let me get this straight.
You enjoy the lovemaking--
Shh. Shh.
Well, do you?
Oh, yeah.
Like strawberry pie.
Okay, but you have a problem
sharing a bed with me.
I know it's not
what the ladies like,
but without
some solid sack time,
I'm a zombie.
I don't know.
Oh, come on, man.
Meet me halfway.
You're not easy, Kramer.
I know.
[♪]
JACK:
So to what do I owe
the pleasure
of this unannounced visit?
I wanna buy back
the Cadillac.
You wanna buy it back? Why?
You got drugs hidden
in the trunk? Heh-heh.
I'm kidding.
All right.
I'll give you 9000 for it.
Nine thousand for a Cadillac?
It's got no miles on it.
You bought it for six.
You're not me.
How much do you want for it?
The Kelley Blue Book value:
$22,000.
Fourteen thousand.
Done.
But I get
to drive it tomorrow,
because Doris
wants to go to Naples.
You need a pen?
Still works.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Hey, uh, where's Jerry?
He's performing at Bally's
in Atlantic City.
Oh, okay.
Yeah,
I need his shoeshine kit.
He always hides it from me.
Yeah, Bally's?
Yeah, Jerry Seinfeld's room,
please.
You know that number?
I used to have a problem.
Well, what do you mean,
he's not registered?
Well, S-E-I-N-V--
HELEN: F.
F-E-L-D.
Uh, F-E-L-D.
Well, I think you're wrong.
All right,
you have a lucky day too.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
He's not there?
No, they never heard of him.
[♪]
This is so nice of you to take
us all out to dinner, George.
Well, as much as I enjoy
all the good-natured ribbing--
[CHUCKLES]
--nothing really
makes me happier
than spending money
on the people I care about.
Where's Jerry?
Oh, he'll be here.
By the way,
Elaine, thank you
for laying out
for the Arabian Mocha Java.
George, you didn't have
to do this.
[SNICKERS]
I'm president of a big company.
I can afford
to buy you coffee.
President?
Yeah.
Hey, look, he's back! Hey.
Hey.
I got your message so I came
straight from Atlantic City.
Kramer called Bally's.
You weren't registered.
[CHUCKLING]
Well, I can't stay under my own name.
I was registered
under "Slappy White."
Mom.
Dad.
Well, look who's here, heh.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Seinfelds.
What--?
What are you doing here?
We're having
an upscale dinner.
What?
Well, after talking to you,
we realized we may not
have much time left.
So we're blowing it all.
Look, George,
it's a Pierre Cardin.
[♪]
That was all right.
[SIGHING]
Yeah.
Well, I'll see ya.
[♪]
[CLATTERING]
[SOFTLY]
Who's that?
[♪]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
[LOUDLY]
Jerry.
I had a little mishap
with the car.
I'm down here
in Alligator Alley.
You better get down here.
Uh, all right.
Who was that?
That was the Golden Nugget,
also in Atlantic City.
They heard such good things
about my show at Bally's,
they want me for tonight.
So I'll have
to repack and go.
That didn't sound
like the Golden Nugget.
I'm worried. What happens
if we have to support Jerry?
I'll have to go back to work.
Where would you work?
Maybe I should talk to Elaine.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Well, Mr. Seinfeld,
I-- I'm not sure
I understand
why you want a job here.
What's not to understand?
Well, for one thing,
you live in Florida.
I'm very comfortable
working out of the house.
I have a phone.
We have a Kinko's nearby.
You know,
I think that my résumé
speaks for itself.
Where is your résumé?
I don't have it.
I'll mail you one.
Uh, all right, Mr. Seinfeld,
uh, what kind of a position
did you have in mind?
You sell clothes, don't you?
Yeah.
Well, I sold raincoats
in the garment center
for 38 years.
In 1949--
All right.
All right. All right.
You come in tomorrow.
We'll find something
for you to do.
You won't regret this,
Miss Benes.
What time should I be in?
I get up at 4.
I could be here
as early as 4:25. Uh...
[MOUTHS]
No.
Oh, Elaine,
this dry air is curing me
like a Black Forest ham.
Mr. Peterman? You're back.
[DOOR OPENS]
Who's Mr. Fancy?
[♪]
I-- I-- I was thinkin' maybe
I should spend the night.
Oh, that's sweet,
but actually, I...
I think I'd prefer it
if you left.
What?
Well, you were
completely right.
I sleep so much better
when I'm alone.
And you scream
in your sleep.
I do?
There was a man.
He was trying to get
into my apartment last night.
He was jiggling the doorknob
for 25 minutes.
[SIGHS]
Come on.
It was probably the wind.
No, no.
No, it was a fearless
cat burglar.
Now, listen, you gotta
let me sleep here. I'll--
You know, I'll stay over here
on my side, and I'll--
I'll stuff a sock
in my mouth.
'Cause I don't
wanna sleep alone.
Well, I do.
[♪]
What took you so long?
I live in New York.
What the hell happened?
This thing is a--
Is a behemoth.
What did you do?
I was--
I was making a--
A simple lane change.
I-- I put on the blinker,
and-- And it took off on me.
And next thing you know,
I was submerged.
I'm telling you, Jerry,
I'm very lucky
that those crocs
didn't get me.
You are such an idiot.
Well, we gotta get
the car cleaned up
for my parents.
Do whatever you want.
It's your car.
My car? You drove it
into the swamp.
It drove itself
Besides, I think
I lost my pen too.
You know, that almost makes
this all worthwhile.
[♪]
Why is there a Cadillac
parked in front of the house?
That's your mother's new car.
You bought that?
It's a coupe de elegance.
[CHUCKLES]
Your father wanted a Mercedes,
but I won't ride
in a German car.
Morning.
[SIGHING]
Oh, boy.
What the hell
is goin' on here?
I had some trouble
at my place.
So I need a little company
at night to sleep.
[CHUCKLES]
George,
your mother and I--
And Kramer.
--have been talking.
Oh, God.
Uh, George,
your parents can't blow
their savings
in this community.
It's low-rent.
We feel that Florida
is really the place
where they should be.
You can drop a grand
in Disney World like that.
Wait a minute. You're thinkin'
of movin' to Florida again?
Well, it's either that,
or we stay here near you
and just sit
on the money.
What do you think
we should do, Georgie?
[♪]
PETERMAN:
So anyway,
effective immediately,
Miss Benes will return
to her old position
at her original salary,
and I, of course,
will return to mine.
Kudos, Elaine, on a job...
done.
What about my stock options?
I think not.
Now, down to business.
I have had this vision
of a diaphanous
rumrunner scarf.
Well, we could fly some fabric
in from our silk factories
for about $1000 dollars a bolt.
A thousand?
I know a couple of Chinamen
over there on 43rd Street
that'll do it for half that.
It's, uh, Asian Americans.
What?
Who are you?
Don't worry--
Morty Seinfeld.
I cut velvet for 40 years
with Harry Alper.
Okay, Mr. Seinfeld,
this is not--
PETERMAN:
Elaine, did you hire this man?
No, no-- Well, I mean,
you know,
he's more like an intern,
you know, at best.
[♪]
ELAINE:
So if your parents move to Florida, you're poor.
But happy.
Obviously.
And if they stay,
you're rich, but...
Obviously.
It's quite a dilemma.
You know, I have a bit
of a dilemma of my own.
No, no.
No, no, no.
We're stayin' on me.
We haven't solved
anything yet.
All right. This is easy.
Just let 'em go.
So now, listen--
What do you mean?
They're spendin' all my money.
All right. Then they stay.
So let me ask you a question--
Could you put
a little thought into this?
Jerry's gone.
You could humor me.
He humors me.
Speaking of Jerry,
his father is driving me
so crazy down at Peterman's.
Know what I do when one of these
guys is breathing down my neck?
What?
You schedule a late meeting.
Huh? What does that do?
These old guys,
they're up at 4 a.m.
By 2:30, they're wiped--
How did we get back on to you?
I gotta go.
You know I got nothin'
outta this.
[♪]
Hey, Frank.
Yeah.
Hey, you got two beds
in here.
That's right.
That's me on the left.
So you sleep
in separate beds.
Thirty years ago
we came to an agreement.
It was the only way
I could get some rest.
Really?
Estelle's got
the jimmy arms.
You can get that
in your arms?
Like you wouldn't believe.
[♪]
JACK:
Jerry, it's getting late.
You, uh, cleaned up the car.
You made all your phone calls.
Why are you still here?
Well, I, uh, maxed out
my credit cards.
And I don't have enough cash
for a hotel room.
So...
You are, uh,
thinking of staying here?
Well...
You've got some nerve.
I almost break my neck
in that deathtrap of yours,
and now you ask me
for a favor?
Didn't like that crack
about the pen?
I did not.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Well, I've given this a lot of thought,
and I've gotta say--
[DISHES RATTLE]
As much as I'd like to see
the two of you livin' it up
in a warm,
tropical setting,
I--
I would just miss you
too much.
So I've decided
I want you to stay.
It's too late.
We bought a condo
at Del Boca Vista.
We're leaving tonight.
You said it was my call.
We were just being nice.
Cosmo, are you sure
you're gonna be
all right here alone?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I got Emily
comin' over tonight.
You're lettin' him
have a woman over?
He's not family.
It's different psychologically.
[♪]
PETERMAN:
And so I made
an explosive
out of chickpeas.
And I stopped
that great rhino
right in his tracks.
Well, it's getting late.
Why don't we, uh--?
Mr. Peterman, that can't
have been the only time
that you faced mortal danger.
[CHUCKLES]
Funny you should ask, Elaine.
Look, if we're gonna stay here
until all hours of the night,
can't we at least
get some food here?
It's only 5:15.
So later on that same day,
I developed a great hankering
for some wild honey.
Okay, I'm done.
I'll be back
in the morning
when he's close to finished
with this story.
PETERMAN:
Morty.
My stories are what sell
these clothes.
Cheap fabric
and dim lighting:
That's how you move
merchandise.
Okay. You're out.
Ach, I never knew
what the hell I was peddling
with those stupid cartoons
and that paper book anyway.
[♪]
I don't know
why I let you talk me
into that corned beef
at Snitzers.
No one held a gun to your head.
Yeah.
Don't forget: We're eating
at the Fidermans' tomorrow.
Now why do I have to go?
They're your friends.
You like 'em.
I've had it with 'em.
[WATER RUNNING]
Then we won't go.
Okay, okay. What time?
Eight-thirty.
Mm.
[BURPS, SIGHS]
That was all right.
[♪]
ELAINE:
"One bright note in today's market
"was the stock
of retailer J. Peterman,
"whose founder's
surprise return generated a rise
of 12 and a half points."
Mm-mm-mm.
That means if you still had
those stock options...
[WEAKLY]
Yeah.
That's a shame.
What are you,
stickin' it to me?
What?
I think
you're stickin' it to me.
Elaine, I'm sure George
is just being sympathetic.
Stickin' it!
You're not alone.
I'm practically broke.
Really?
No.
But...
I did blow over 20,000
on that Cadillac.
[CHUCKLING QUIETLY]
Delicious.
Well, you seem happy.
Hey, the folks
are 1200 miles away.
I'm baskin'
in the buffer zone.
Another piece of pie here!
So were your parents shocked
to see the Cadillac?
Actually, I haven't heard
from them yet. Hm.
When are we gonna
tell Jerry?
I don't wanna worry him.
We'll tell him
next time we go up.
He thought he could buy back
that Cadillac for us?
He's not getting away
with that.
HELEN:
Besides, that condo was too much house.
[♪]
How many times
can you check the car?
I saw a bum sleeping
in the Cadillac the other day.
Why would someone break
into a car to take a nap?
They don't nap.
They make it their home.
They urinate in there!
You're driving me crazy!
That's it!
We're going back to Queens.
Where's my hat?
No!
[♪]