Oh, hang on,
let me just pick up a paper.
Excuse me.
Would you mind watching my bag
for a minute?
Yeah, no problem.
Let's go.
Well, I gotta watch
this guy's bag.
For how long?
Well, I'm sure he'll be back
in a second.
Hm, nice stuff.
Come on.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Would you, uh, would you mind
watching my bag for a second?
Why? So I can stand here
like an idiot
not knowing
if you'll ever come back?
Where are you going?
I'm gonna be this guy's friend.
JERRY:
New clothes?
Yeah, I did some shopping.
Some, uh, new-clothes shopping.
Oh, uh, can I borrow your menu?
Strange, for new pants
there's noticeable wear
on the buttocks of those chinos.
Wait, those are the clothes
from the bag.
The guy never came back.
He asked you to watch them,
not wear them.
I'm still watching 'em.
You look like a tourist.
All right, all right.
Let me ask you something.
When do you start to worry
about ear hair?
When you hear, like,
a soft rustling.
Puberty that never stops.
Ear puberty, nose puberty,
knuckle puberty.
You gotta be vigilant.
All right. Let me ask ya this:
You know where
Walker Street is downtown?
I got a league meeting there.
Oh, right, the new job.
Yeah.
How is it?
I love it.
New office, new salary.
I'm the new Wilhelm.
So who's the new you?
They got an intern
from Francis Lewis High.
His name is Keith.
He comes in Mondays
after school.
Hey, Alex.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Have you ordered yet?
No.
I'll be right back.
Where are you meeting
these women?
When they get off the bus
at the Port Authority?
Right here, George. In here.
Try opening this up.
You'll find the biggest
dating scene in the world.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[♪]
Hey.
Hi.
Where's Jerry?
Oh, well, uh,
he's in the shower.
Ya want me to get him?
No, no, no, no. Um...
Actually, I kind of need
to speak to you.
Oh, uh, well, let's sit down.
Kramer, ahem,
remember that whole deal
with you
selling Peterman your stories
for his book,
and then he gave 'em back
to you?
Vaguely.
Well, um, ahem,
I was kind of, uh, heh-heh,
short on material
and, uh, I put 'em
in the book anyway.
You put my life stories
in his autobiography?
Kramer, listen,
it is such a stupid book.
It doesn't matter.
No, no. Sure it matters.
Wow.
I've broken through, huh?
Yeah, I'm part
of popular culture now.
Listen, I'd like to thank
Mr. Peterman.
He's doing a book signing
at Waldenbooks this afternoon.
Waldenbooks.
Oh, that's a major chain, huh?
Hey, Jerry,
I'm going to Waldenbooks.
JERRY:
Oh, get out! Get out!
What?
I don't wanna live like this!
All right, let's go, huh?
[♪]
ELAINE:
Mr. Lippman.
How are you?
Well, I'm not bad. Not bad.
What are you doing here?
I work for Pundit Publishing.
This is our book.
Oh.
If you can call it that.
Why is it every, uh,
half-wit and sitcom star
has his own book out now?
Hey, buddy. Remember me?
You're that gangly fellow
we bought the stories from.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm just here
to do my part.
What's your name,
darling?
Who are you?
Oh, I'm, uh--
Let me use your pen,
will ya?
I'm the real Peterman.
All right, playtime's over.
Relax, man.
There's enough juice here
to keep us all fat and giggly.
I can't believe somebody
pulled the top off this muffin.
That was me. I'm sorry, I--
I don't like the stumps.
So you just eat the tops?
Oh, yeah,
it's the best part.
It's crunchy. It's explosive.
It's--
It's where the muffin
breaks free of the pan
and sort of...
does its own thing.
[BOTH LAUGH]
I'll tell ya, that's a
million-dollar idea right there.
Just sell the tops.
Okay. Let's go, slim.
That's enough.
I have a right to be here.
Come on.
These are my fans.
Hey, you're hurting my elbow!
Try looking up,
hayseed.
You wanna sightsee?
Get on a bus.
WOMAN:
Please don't think all New Yorkers are so rude.
Oh, well, actually I'm, uh--
I'm Mary Anne.
I work for the New York
Visitors Center.
Where are you visiting from?
Little Rock, Arkansas.
Ooh.
[HUMMING]
Hm.
That looks new.
[♪]
KRAMER:
So get this:
Peterman has his henchmen
forcefully eject me
from the book signing.
Like I'm some sort of maniac.
Yeah, that-- That's too bad.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
No, no, no, no.
Don't give me that.
I know you.
Something's wrong.
What is it? What happened?
I did something stupid.
What did you do?
Well, I was shaving...
Yeah.
...and I noticed an asymmetry
in my chest hair.
And I was trying to even it out.
And the next thing I knew:
Gone.
Don't you know
you're not supposed
to poke around down there.
Well, women do it.
"Well, women do it."
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'll pick you up a sundress
and a parasol,
and you can just sashay
your pretty little self
around the town square.
Well, what am I gonna tell Alex?
Now, you listen to me. You don't
tell anybody about this.
No one. Ya hear me?
Mm-hm.
Hey.
Jerry shaved his chest.
Hey!
Oh, I forgot.
Wait, never mind.
[♪]
You couldn't pay me enough
to ride a horse in this city.
I mean, it's hard enough
to cross the street
in a pair of sneakers,
let alone six feet in the air
on a jittery,
glassy-eyed dinosaur.
How about the beach
this weekend?
Uh, well, you couldn't
pay me enough
to go to the beach
on a weekend.
I mean,
it's hard enough to park--
All right, all right.
Wow, is that
a Mexican hairless?
I love those.
Oh, hairless.
This is where it's at.
It's so much
smoother and cleaner.
Really?
Um, excuse me.
Are you eating a muffin top?
Yeah, a muffin-top store
just opened up down the street.
A muffin-top store?
What did I just say?
[♪]
ELAINE:
"Top of the muffin to you"?
[DOOR CHIMES RING]
Top of the muffin to ya.
Elaine.
Mr. Lippman?
JERRY:
So you're pretending to be a tourist?
It's beautiful.
She makes all the plans.
I'm not from around here,
so it's okay if I'm stupid.
And she knows
I'm only in town visiting,
so there's no messy breakups.
How do you explain
your apartment?
I got a hotel room.
You moved into a hotel?
Well, I don't know anyone here,
Jerry.
Where else am I gonna stay?
So get this:
We're in the park today.
Alex goes wild
for this hairless dog.
So?
So I figured since she likes
one hairless animal,
why not another?
Oh, really?
Yes.
Oh, you tell her you shaved it?
Are you nuts?
I don't want her to think
I'm one of those
low-rise briefs guys
who shaves his chest.
[HORN HONKS]
Hey, Jerry!
I'm starting
a Peterman Reality Bus Tour!
Check it out!
[LAUGHS]
Reality tour?
The last thing this guy
is qualified
to give a tour of is reality.
This was my idea.
You stole my idea.
Elaine, these ideas are all
in the air.
Oh.
They're in the air.
Oh, well, then, if that air
is comin' outta this face,
then it is my air and my idea.
You want a muffin or not?
Peach.
[♪]
So I've noticed you don't have
much of an accent.
Yeah, my parents have it.
Sometimes it skips a generation.
So I was thinking maybe tonight
we could go back to my hotel.
I got SpectraVision.
First five minutes free.
Look, George,
I'm really enjoying
spending time with you,
but I'm not sure
this is gonna work out.
At some point you're going back
to your job at Tyler Chicken
and your three-legged dog,
Willy.
Right. Yeah.
And I'm still gonna be here.
Well, what if I told ya
I'm thinking of moving here?
[LAUGHS]
George, no offense,
but this city
would eat you alive.
[♪]
JERRY:
You're moving to New York?
That's fantastic.
I can see you all the time now.
Eat me alive, huh?
We'll see who can make it
in this town. Ha, ha!
What is it she thinks
you can't do?
Find a job, get an apartment.
How did ya do those things?
Never mind, they're done.
All I have to do now
is redo 'em.
You know, if you take everything
I've accomplished
in my entire life and condense
it down into one day,
it looks decent.
Well...
Hey.
What were you doing
with that bus yesterday?
Here you go. Here you go.
Check it out.
"The Real Peterman
Reality Bus Tour."
I'm confused.
That Peterman book
is big business.
People wanna know the stories
behind the stories.
Nobody wants to go
on a three-hour bus tour
of a totally unknown person's
life.
I'm only charging 37.50,
plus you get a pizza bagel
and dessert.
What's dessert?
Bite-size 3 Musketeers.
Just like
the real Peterman eats.
He eats those?
No, I eat those.
I'm the real Peterman.
I-I don't--
Wait a minute.
I think I understand this.
J. Peterman is real.
His biography is not.
Now you, Kramer, are real.
Talk to me.
But your life is Peterman's.
Now, the bus tour,
which is real,
takes you to places that,
while they are real,
they are not real in the sense
that they did not really happen
to the real Peterman,
which is you.
Understand?
Yeah, it's 37.50
for a 3 Musketeers.
There you go.
[♪]
LIPPMAN:
Elaine, I'm in over my head.
Nobody likes my muffin tops.
So? What do you want
me to do about it?
You're the muffin-top expert.
Tell me, uh,
what I'm doing wrong.
Mr. Lippman,
when I worked for you
at Pendant Publishing
I believed in you, you know,
as a man of integrity.
But when I saw you in that
paper hat and that apron--
What if I cut you in
for 30 percent of the profits?
Deal. Here's your problem:
You're making just
the muffin tops.
What do you mean?
Ya gotta make the whole muffin.
Then you...
pop the top...
Uh-huh.
...toss the stump.
Taste.
Hm?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
So, what do we do with the bottoms?
Give them to a soup kitchen.
It's a good idea.
And one more thing.
Uh, do you really think
we need the exclamation point?
Because it's not,
"Top of the muffin to you!"
No, no, it is.
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry.
What's this?
Lady Gillette?
Oh, what's going on?
Hey.
What?
Jeez.
Can't I get a moment's peace?
What are you doing to yourself?
I can't stop.
Oh.
Alex thinks
I'm naturally hairless.
What? You can't keep this up.
Don't you know
what's gonna happen?
Every time you shave it,
it's gonna come in thicker
and fuller and darker.
Oh, that's an old wives' tale.
Is it?
Look at this.
What is--? What is that?
KRAMER:
Look at it! Look at it!
It's all me.
I shaved there
when I was a lifeguard.
Oh, come on. That's genetic.
That's not gonna happen to me.
Won't it? Or has it already
started to happen?
Wow, look at this,
we're cleaning up.
Oh, Reuben,
get me another tray of, uh,
low-fat cranberry, please.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Excuse me.
I'm Rebecca DeMornay,
from the homeless shelter.
Oh, hi.
Are you the ones leaving
those muffin pieces
behind our shelter?
You've been enjoying them?
They're just stumps.
Well, they're--
They're perfectly edible.
So you just assume that
the homeless will eat them?
They'll eat anything?
No, we just thought--
I know what ya thought:
"They don't have homes.
"They don't have jobs.
"What do they need
the top of a muffin for?
They're lucky to get
the stumps."
If the homeless don't like 'em,
the homeless don't
have to eat 'em, okay?
The homeless don't like them.
Fine.
We've never gotten so many complaints.
Every two minutes:
"Where's the top of this muffin?
Who ate the rest of this?"
We were just trying to help.
Why don't you drop off chicken
skins and lobster shells?
I think I might.
MARY ANNE:
I can't believe
you found something so quickly.
How much are you paying?
Twenty-three hundred.
Ouch. A month?
Yeah.
Well, I guess that's all right
for now.
But if you stay here more
than a few months,
you're a real sucker.
Yeah, well, I, uh,
I got lots of other stuff
to show you too.
Wait till you see
the plum job that I landed, huh?
Yeah, we should let this place
air out anyway.
Smells like the last tenant
had monkeys or something.
[♪]
Okay, coming up on the right,
if you glance up,
you'll just make out
my bedroom window.
It's the one that's covered
in chicken wire.
Hey,
if you're the real Peterman
how come you're wearing
those ratty clothes?
What?
Well, they're--
They're not very romantic.
Well, that's your opinion.
Can I have another 3 Musketeers?
They're rather small.
Forget it.
Okay, uh, Newman's postal route
is around here somewhere--
MAN 1: Who's Newman?
MAN 2: Who cares?
Hey, fake Peterman,
let me off.
I-I'm nauseous.
Can I have his candy bar?
Yeah-- Yeah!
Everyone just settle down.
Okay, we got three hours left
on this thing,
and I can't drive
and argue with you rubes
all at the same time.
Okay, uh,
Lomez's place of worship
is right
on the right here.
[♪]
JERRY:
Why do I have to go on the tour?
Jerry,
you're a minor celebrity.
You know,
if you go on this thing,
it could create a minor stir.
Come on, you can bring that
little girlfriend of yours,
and I'll only charge ya
60 bucks.
Hey.
How's business?
Oh, I got stump trouble.
The sanitation department
won't get rid of them all.
I can't get a truck to haul
this stuff until next week.
Meanwhile, I'm sitting
on a mountain of stumps.
Mm-mm-mm.
All right.
I gotta hose the puke
off the floor of the bus.
Bus? Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Bus? You got a bus?
Yeah. Yeah.
You got any room on that thing?
There are a few seats available.
Do you think you could
transport some stumps for me?
I-- I-I'll make it
worth your while.
Well, if they don't mind
sitting in the back.
No, they don't.
Are they war veterans?
MARY ANNE:
Wow! This is your office?
Whoa, hello. Sorry, George.
Didn't know you had
a girl in here.
Leave a signal on the doorknob
like a necktie
or a sock or somethin'.
Come on, help me out.
Mr. Steinbrenner, I would like
to thank you for taking a chance
on a hen supervisor
at Tyler Chicken
like our boy George here.
Oh.
Hen supervisor
from Tyler Chicken?
Yes, very nice for her
to have met you, sir.
Wait a minute, George.
Be right with ya.
Look, M-- Mr.Steinbrenner--
Moonlighting for Tyler Chicken.
Pretty impressive, George.
Days with the New York Yankees,
nights in Arkansas
with a topflight bird outfit.
And a hen supervisor, to boot.
I am blown. Blown away.
Blown, George. Blown!
You know,
when you make a pizza bagel
you really shouldn't use
cinnamon raisin.
You also shouldn't use
a doughnut.
[BANJO MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKER]
All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Peterman
Reality Tour.
MAN [OVER TAPE]:
Turn music off.
Kramer, can we just go?
And go we will.
What is this? Pizza pound cake?
Well, we have a bonus
ultra-reality stop today.
We're gonna be hauling muffin
stumps to the local repository.
We're going to a garbage dump?
And we're off.
[BANJO MUSIC RESUMES]
You know, I never thought
he'd be able to re-create
the experience of actually
knowing him,
but this is pretty close.
[GEARS GRIND]
[♪]
Don Tyler?
George Steinbrenner here.
I wanna talk
about George Costanza.
I understand he's been dividing
his time between us and you.
I cannot have that.
Well, I don't know who he is,
but if you want him that bad,
I'm not giving up that easy.
Oh, is that so?
Playing a little hardball, huh,
Donny boy?
How about this:
You give me Costanza.
I convert your concessions
to all chicken, no charge.
Instead of hot dogs,
chicken dogs.
Instead of pretzels,
chicken twists.
Instead of beer,
alcoholic chicken.
How do you make
that alcoholic chicken?
Ah, they ferment,
just like anything else.
That stuff sounds great.
All right, I'll have Costanza
on the next bus.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where do you think
you're going?
Well, I was gonna dump this.
It doesn't look like garbage.
Well, it's muffin stumps.
Where are the muffin tops?
This is a garbage dump.
Just let me dump it.
Can't do it.
What is this, a joke?
That's what I like to know
about it.
You have a pretty heavy beard,
don't you?
What's that?
Well, look. It's almost time
for you to shave again.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, yeah.
Well, maybe I will take it up
with Consumer Affairs!
Well, ha, ladies and gentlemen,
you are in for
an additional treat.
Uh, we're going to extend
the tour at no extra charge.
Where
are we going?
I don't know.
Uh, no more questions.
[BANJO MUSIC RESUMES]
[♪]
[COUGHS, VOMITS]
[HORN HONKS]
So the New York Yankees
traded you
for a bunch of Tyler Chicken?
Dogs, twists...
some kind of fermented
chicken drink.
Hey, aren't you the guy
I asked to watch my clothes?
What clothes?
These clothes.
The ones you're wearing.
Kramer, how much longer?
What?
My chest hair's growing back,
and it's itching me like crazy.
I can't let her see me
scratch it.
Well, don't worry.
I...
I got a good feeling
about this dump.
I tell you, man, I'm losing it.
I can't sit
on this bus anymore.
[DOG BARKS]
I think I'll go play
with that dog.
I don't know where the tops are.
[♪]
Jerry, what's the matter?
[HEART BEATING]
Ahh.
[HOWLS]
That feels good.
Oh, hey,
you looking for George?
Yes.
He's been in the bathroom
a while.
You might wanna check on him.
Jerry, you gotta bring me
some clothes down here.
I lost my job with the Yankees.
I'm standing in a men's room
on 43rd Street in my underpants.
I told you this city
would eat you alive.
And I think my relationship's
in trouble.
So, what is this guy again?
They call him a cleaner.
He makes problems go away.
[DOOR CHIMES JINGLE]
Hello, Elaine.
Where did you get the car?
It's a rental.
Where are they?
In the back.
All right.
I'm gonna need a clean
eight-ounce glass.
What is going on here?
If I'm curt,
then I apologize.
But as I understand it,
we have a situation here.
And time is of the essence.
[♪]
Mm.