You know that manslaughter is
the least serious
murder charge?
You don't say.
Manslaughter.
Literally, the slaughter
of a man.
Sounds brutal,
doesn't it? Heinous.
Yet it's the most socially
acceptable form of murder. Huh.
So you think we should
change the name.
Yes, I do.
How about, uh...
"inadvertent life-ending"?
Uh... "unintentional
snuff-out."
How about "I can't believe
it's not murder"?
Oh, boy. I was up
till 4 in the morning
watching that Omen trilogy.
Mm.
Mm. That's
good stuff.
Devil? Pshht.
Forget about it.
Well, he was
the devil's son, right?
I thought he was
the devil's helper.
Well, he's pretty scary
for a helper.
I can't keep doing this
to myself. I'm exhausted.
Can't you grab
a nap at work?
Not with that big glass window
looking out onto the hall.
And I love a good nap.
Sometimes it's the only thing
getting me out of bed
in the morning.
I'll see you.
Bye.
So what are you
doing now?
I'm gonna take a little stroll
through the park.
With a gentleman caller?
Yes, his name is Hal.
The walking date
is a good date.
You don't have to look
at the person.
Hey, it's the next best thing
to being alone.
Hi.
Shower?
Yeah.
Oh, pool.
I just swam 200 laps.
You are
kidding.
Hey, look at those babies, huh?
Wow.
They're prunes.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, I saw Conrad
going up to your place.
Oh, yeah,
that's right.
Those new kitchen cabinets.
How's that coming?
Slow. I gotta hold
this guy's hand
on every little
decision.
Hey, Kramer, listen.
You've seen The Omen, right?
What exactly
was that kid?
Oh, Damien?
Mm-hm.
Nothing. Just a mischievous,
rambunctious kid.
[LIGHT SNORING]
WILHELM: Uh, George.
Have you seen that
American League directory?
It's, um, a big green book.
Right here.
Ha, ha.
Thanks, kiddo.
[SIGHS]
You know Twinkies
aren't cooked?
[GASPS]
It looks cooked.
It's dark on the bottom.
That's just the way it is.
It's a substance.
Well, I don't care.
They're delicious.
You wanna sit down?
Oh, I don't sit
on park benches.
They're very bad
for the back.
Really?
I threw my back out about 15 years ago.
Ever since I've been
very careful.
I buy all of my furniture
at an ergonomic store.
Oh, those places have
the stupidest names.
Like, uh--
Like, Back in Business.
Or Good Vertebrations.
Not this one.
It's called
the Lumbar Yard.
MAN:
Hey, Jerry.
Jerry? Are you okay
with this hinge?
Yeah.
I can get you any kind you want, you know.
Four holes,
two holes,
bronze, no hinge
at all.
You know, why don't we just go
with the one in your hand?
Ugh-- Well,
these are different.
Drop one.
Left.
Ugh.
Jerry...
Look at my eyes.
Hm, a little less
beady today.
Because I'm refreshed.
I finally found a way
to sleep in my office.
Under the desk. Heh?
I lie on my back, I tuck in
the chair, I'm invisible.
Sounds like a really
cool fort.
Hey, Jerry. Do you want
a flat edge on this molding,
or do you want me to
uh, bevel it?
I'll tell you what I'd like
you to do with it.
Hey, uh, Conrad, is it?
Conrad, Connie or Con.
Whatever you prefer. [CHUCKLES]
Listen, let me
ask you a question.
Could you, um, expand
the space underneath a desk?
You know, give it
a little more head room?
George, he's
kind of tied up here.
What? It would have to be
a night job anyway.
You don't normally work
after dinner, do you?
There is no normal.
Whatever Jerry wants.
He wants me here late,
I'm here late.
He wants me early,
I'm early--
You know,
why don't you just
work on George's
project for a while.
Whatever
you want.
So how was, uh, Wednesday
in the park with Hal?
Eh. It was okay.
He's coming over later
to watch a movie.
Hey, listen. What's
better for your back:
couch cushions or
a folding chair?
I don't know.
[SIGHS]
Maybe we'll just stand
and watch the TV.
[KNOCK
ON DOOR]
Um, I gotta go.
Somebody's at my door.
Yeah?
MAN:
Delivery.
Elaine Benes?
Yeah.
We're from the Lumbar Yard.
We got your mattress.
Mattress? I-- Oh, I didn't
order a mattress.
Who sent this?
"Hal Kitzmiller"?
You think it might be possible
to add a little shelf,
like, uh,
for an alarm clock?
What about,
maybe that big?
I don't know.
Maybe like this? Like that?
Yeah, like that.
I can do that.
Great. Heh-heh.
You know, this could
sound crazy but...
what do you think about
adding a drawer for,
like, a blanket?
Blanket or a quilt?
Blanket.
About that thick?
Maybe like this.
Like that?
Yeah, like that.
That's what you want?
That's what I want.
CONRAD:
Hey, George.
You want
this cup holder, uh--
You want it mounted
on the left,
or the right,
or the middle? Whatever!
[DRILLING]
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
This is unbelievable.
This is better than
my bed at home.
All right.
It's been a long night.
You go home
and get some sleep.
That's what you want?
That's what I want.
Morning, George.
Morning,
Mr. Wilhelm.
[SIGHS]
Phew. I got pool
problems, Jerry. What happened?
Well, I had been swimming
for three hours,
and I was in
a real groove,
so I decided
to keep going.
But at 10, they start
the aquacise.
Thirty-five geriatrics
throwing elbows.
It was like I was
swimming through
a flabby-armed
spanking machine.
Well, how long
did that last?
Half-hour. Then
diving class started.
Well...that got
a little messy.
I gotta find
a new place to swim.
Because that pool
can't hold me, Jerry.
How was
the movie?
I cancelled.
Hal sent a mattress
to my apartment.
The nerve of
that guy.
Why?
He's got a back problem.
So you think
he was expecting
a roll in the
supportive hay?
After one date.
What's that guy's
last name again?
Kitzmiller.
Oh, that's right.
So what are you gonna do
with the mattress?
I don't know.
Chuck it?
Oh, wait, wait. No, no, no, no.
I'll take it.
Yeah, why don't you
come over.
See if it fits
in my bedroom.
Oh. All right.
Yeah, 'cause my old one sprung a leak.
You have a waterbed?
Sand. It's like
sleeping on a beach.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Hi.
Oh, hey.
Hi, Con.
How you doing?
Hi. Jerry,
I'm sorry I'm late.
George and I, we've been--
We've been up all night long.
Uh, I can make up the time
to you any number of ways.
How about this?
Finish this thing up today.
Couple questions for you--
No. No more questions.
Just figure it out
for yourself and get it done.
All right, Jerry.
But I can figure it out myself
any way you want.
[THREATENINGLY]
Just...
do it.
Costanza?
Where's Costanza?
Excusez-moi?
Have you seen Costanza?
I've seen him
around.
Hmm. He was humming
this song yesterday.
I can't seem to
get it out of my head.
I gotta know
the name of that.
♪ She's a heartbreaker
Love taker ♪
♪ Brubaker, run this prison
Like a man, oh, oh ♪
Something like that.
It's a very catchy tune.
Very, very catchy.
Well, you know what?
I'm just gonna sit here
and wait for that guy.
What is this,
People?
Hm. "The Most Beautiful
People" People.
Connie Sellecca.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Nothing wrong that, ah?
HAL:
Elaine, you're taking this totally the wrong way.
That's not what I intended.
Well, what did you
intend, Hal?
I just wanted you
to have the comfort
and support you deserve.
That's why I had the mattress
custom-designed for you.
Custom-designed?
They adjust the foam density
and the spring tension
to your body type.
I estimated
your height and weight:
5'8", about 110 pounds?
Oh, well, that is
the nicest thing
anyone has ever
done for me.
So you do like
the mattress?
Oh. I love it.
I'm glad I...
kept it.
And over there,
that's Brooklyn.
That's where
Spike Lee lives.
Hm.
Hey.
There's a man swimming
in the water.
No. That's probably
just a dead body, son.
You see, when the mob
kills someone,
they throw the body
in the river.
All right?
KRAMER:
Jerry!
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Well, my swimming pool
problems are solved.
I just found myself miles
and miles of open lanes.
What is that smell?
That's
East River.
You're swimming in
the East River? Yeah.
The most heavily-trafficked,
overly-contaminated waterway
on the Eastern Seaboard?
Technically, Norfolk
has more gross tonnage.
How could you swim
in that water?
I saw a couple of
other guys out there.
Swimming?
Well, floating.
They weren't moving much,
but they were out there.
ELAINE:
Hey, Kramer. It's Elaine.
Thanks for bringing
my mattress back.
And I guess I'll just get
my spare key from you whenever.
All right. Bye.
Ooh. This is
a good mattress.
[SNIFFING]
Ugh. Ugh.
STEINBRENNER:
Where the hell is this guy?
I'm waiting here
three and a half hours.
Should I go?
No way, Jack.
I'm not humming it
to the guy
at the record
store again.
Mr. Steinbrenner?
That's what they call me.
Your grandchildren
are here to see you.
Oh, well. Send them in.
BOY: Grandpa, Grandpa.
Send the tykes in.
KIDS: Grandpa, Grandpa.
Hey, you little kids.
[BARKS]
Who-- Who are you
people?
Come here. Come here.
[KIDS YELLING]
How about a ride on the
Stein-pony express? Get up here.
What's your name?
Shorty?
Mel?
Are you Mel?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
[WHISPERS]
Jerry. Jerry.
I'm trapped under my desk.
Steinbrenner's in the room.
You gotta help me.
Who is this?
[WHISPERS]
Jerry!
Hi.
Go away. Shh.
Bye-bye. Shh.
Get away.
Hi, I'm Brian.
Beat it, Brian.
[WHISPERS]
Beat it! Beat it!
Why don't you
just have him paged?
Because he'll see
the extension's
coming from my--
Back off. C-- Come on.
Come on.
Won't you do something?
Call in a bomb threat.
A bomb threat?
Why would I call in
a bomb threat?
Just call.
I'm thinking I should have
some reason.
[WHISPERS]
Jerry!
Hey, you kids are up
on all the new tunes.
Tell me if this one
rings a bell:
♪ Heartbreaker
Love taker ♪
♪ Shoemaker, won't you fix
My shoes for free ♪
Huh? Anything?
Shorty? Girl?
Mr. Steinbrenner.
We just received a call.
There's a bomb
in the building.
Thank God.
A bomb in the building!
Oh, my God. Quick.
Everybody under the desk.
George, can you imagine
what went through my mind
when I saw there
wasn't going to be
enough room under that desk
for me and my babies?
I'm sorry, sir.
You know what
I think?
I think you knew about
that bomb ahead of time.
What?
You had a premonition
about the bomb.
You climbed under that desk
because you have ESP.
Quick, George. Put
a thought in my mind.
Mmm...
Meatballs. Huh?
Unbelievable.
You're a wonder, George.
Anyway...
this terrorist had
a very specific demand.
No more cheap adjustable hats
for Hat Day.
He wants fitted hats,
just like the players wear.
Jerry. Jerry.
Yeah.
What the hell
is this? Wh--
Where are you?
Over here.
You can see right through here.
What is this?
It's like you're selling
movie tickets back here.
I think it's kind of cozy.
All right. You are not
gonna believe
what Kramer did to
my mattress.
I can't-- I can't talk
to you like this.
So Kramer completely
funked up my mattress.
Does it smell like
the East River?
Yes, it does.
How did you know?
Because Kramer's been
swimming laps
between the Queensboro Bridge
and the Brooklyn Bridge.
Oh, great!
[EXHALES]
Oh, man. I'm on
the wrong floor again.
[GASPS]
Hey!
Thanks for ruining
my mattress. It reeks.
Hey, you know what
I think it is?
I think it's that
East River.
I think it might be
polluted.
Well, you really did it
to me this time, Seinfeld.
What the hell
happened here?
Hey.
L-l-look how
obtrusive it is.
It is obtrusive,
isn't it?
It's very
obtrusive.
I-I don't think
it's that bad.
Well, can I get
a stool in here?
No, the stools go over there.
No, no, no.
That's no good.
I'm leaving.
Yeah, I'm with stinky.
I'm going back
to my place.
Fitted Hat Day?
That's what you asked
Steinbrenner for?
Hey, they're actually
doing the fitted hats? Cool.
Guess who he put in charge
of Fitted Hat Day?
Me.
Hey, look at you.
Yeah, look at me.
Now, I gotta figure out
the different head sizes
of 59,000 different people!
What if a pinhead shows up?!
I gotta be on top of that!
No knockoffs. I want the ones
like the real players wear.
Forget the fitted hats!
I'm not doing it!
And you're gonna call
Steinbrenner back
and cancel
the whole thing!
Could you at least
get a hat for me?
Fine. What size?
Seven and five-eighths.
Seven and five-eighths!
Why are you
shouting?
I don't know!
It's this place!
I'm very
uncomfortable here!
HAL:
So you're liking the mattress?
Oh, I'm j--
Loving it.
Ah, you know,
we should, um...
uh...
[SIGHS]
...get going.
What is that smell?
What smell?
[SNIFFS]
I think it's
the mattress.
Did something
happen to it?
No. No.
Oh. Oh, you know what
that is?
Um...
I went clamming the other day,
and I forgot
to hose off my boots.
Clamming?
Yeah, I clam...
and scallop.
I clam and scallop.
[CHUCKLES]
Huh.
[TENTATIVE KNOCK]
Yes, yes, come in.
Come in.
Sir. I just got a call
from the terrorist.
I told him to call here
if you have a moment.
Hey Costanza, let me
ask you something.
Is it "February"
or "Febuary"?
Because I prefer "uary."
And what is this "ru"?
[PHONE RINGS]
Let me put that
on speakerphone for you, sir.
Hello, uh, bomber?
Yeah, this is
the terrorist bomber.
You know, Costanza is busting
his hump on those hats.
JERRY [ON PHONE]:
Yeah, about those hats,
I think maybe I changed my mind.
You don't want them?
They're gone. Goodbye.
Good thinking, sir.
Now, what do you want
instead?
What?
You're the terrorist.
You gotta want something.
Uh, I guess it would be nice
if you called ticket holders
if a game is
gonna be rained out.
All right. George, you can
handle that. [DIAL TONE]
Costanza, what the hell
are you doing?
We have to stand tough, sir.
That's why I had to
hang up the phone.
When someone's unstable,
you don't stir the pot, George.
Know what
I'm gonna do?
Run around the stadium
and close the windows.
That's what
I'm doing, pal.
And I'll tell you
something else:
I am very nervous!
I liked that
stuffed crust pizza.
Cheese-in-crust pizza.
It's just more
cheese.
Let me tell you something.
It'll be years before they find
another place to hide
more cheese on a pizza.
Kramer!
Oh, hey.
God, hi.
Hi.
Oh, this is Hal.
Hal, Kramer.
Kramer, Hal.
Hal, uh...
Langerhans.
Kitzmiller.
Ooh, yeah. Kitzmiller.
That's right.
You taking
a dip?
Oh, I'm dipping, yeah.
That smell.
Well, listen, I gotta
get to the pier. It's, uh--
Ferry traffic gets really bad
around 4:30, but, uh--
Look, I still got your key
to your apartment, and I'll, uh,
give it back to you
as soon as I can.
Ooh, baby.
[CHUCKLES]
[ALARM RINGING]
[SIGHS]
[ALARM STOPS]
Lunch.
Kramer.
Hey.
Can I talk to you a minute?
Yeah, sure. Sure.
Uh--
Um. Oh, boy.
Kitzmiller.
Ye-- That's it. Heh.
You and Elaine are pretty close.
Oh, we go back
a ways. Heh.
And you've, um--
How do I put this?
You've been in her bed.
That's right.
But this isn't
still going on?
No, no, no.
She put a stop to that.
That's all
I needed to know.
So you actually
swim in this thing?
Oh, yeah.
[SNAPS]
Exercises every muscle
in the body.
It's great
for the back.
Great for the back.
Right.
Four hours in this chop,
and I'm a full inch
taller.
Giddyap.
[SPLASH]
STEINBRENNER:
♪ Heartbreaker Brubaker ♪
Hey. Hey, George.
I remembered that tune.
George? George?
[CLOCK TICKING]
Hm. What's that ticking?
Uh, oh-- Oh.
Mm-- My-- Oh--
[BABBLING]
Fire in the hole!
ELAINE:
Ugh! I can't believe the Lumbar Yard
wouldn't pick this up.
Ugh!
[SIGHING]
Ugh.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
[GROANS LOUDLY]
CONRAD:
You want it back the way it was?
Yeah. That's right.
You know, I don't get you,
Seinfeld.
You want something one day,
the next day you don't like it.
I mean, come on, man,
make a decision.
[PHONE RINGS]
One second.
Hello?
Jerry. You gotta
help me.
I threw my back out.
So just lie down.
I am lying down.
I am trapped
under a funky mattress.
You gotta go get a doctor,
or at--
At least come over and...
roll this thing off of me.
All right. I'll--
I'll be right there.
Uh, Conrad...
I gotta go.
Stay, go. Huh. Whatever.
Hey, Kramer.
What's going on, huh?
I told my chiropractor
how great
swimming in the river
made my back feel. Yeah.
He recommended it
to all his patients.
Agi-gi-gi-gi--
Step aside.
He just sunk like a stone,
didn't he?
Sir, uh, I-I'm sure
it's not a bomb.
Yeah, don't be
so brave, George.
You mess with them, and
they're messing with you.
All right, boys,
send it in.
Wait. What's that thing
straight ahead?
Is that's anything?
Is that Mothra?
Okay, let's check
the desk.
That's where I heard
the ticking.
Search each of
those drawers,
starting with
the top one.
Mm.
Tsk. It's just
empty calories
and male curiosity,
eh, Georgie?
Looks like there's
more compartments underneath.
Compartments underneath?
Probably where it is.
Okay, boys. Let it rip.
I'll tell you what,
George.
Starting tomorrow,
no more desks.
Just a Lucite table
and four legs.
KRAMER:
Hey!
Hey, watch where
you're kicking!
You people find
your own river! Ah!
Ow, jeez!
I'm so sor--
Kramer.
[COUGHING] Elaine.
Hi. I am
loving this.
Hey, I'll meet you
at the coffee shop.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[SCREAMS]
Hey, Connie.
Jerry around?
No.
And I prefer Conrad.
So I heard what happened
to the desk.
I tell you, there was
something so reassuring
about that cozy little space.
Yeah, well, whatever.
See you.
Ahh. Back to normal.
Not bad for 4000 bucks.
Can't believe I got the low-fat.