[SIGHS]
All right,
you're on a desert island.
You can bring five books.
Which five do you take?
I gotta read five books?
All right, one.
Come on.
Ah, I got it.
Three Musketeers.
You've read that?
No, I'm saving it
for the island.
All right, let's start
this whole thing over. Ahem.
Best Chamberlain:
Wilt, Richard, or Neville?
To the desert island?
Okay.
Richard.
You know, he was
in The Three Musketeers.
Exactly. Save me having
to read the book.
What's going on
over there? [SIGHS]
I don't know.
I gotta see somebody.
[♪]
So, uh, Marcy, you should have
seen me in the hot tub today.
[CHUCKLES]
Why?
I was naked.
Oh, George.
[LAUGHS]
I saw it.
How'd he look?
Okay.
I wouldn't see it again.
You know,
a friend of mine thought
she got Legionnaires' disease
in a hot tub.
Really, what happened?
Uh, yada, yada, yada.
Just some bad egg salad.
I'll be right back.
Nice girl.
Lovely.
I notice she's big
on the phrase, "Yada, yada."
Is "yada yada" bad?
No, "yada yada"'s good.
She's very succinct.
She is succinct.
Yeah, it's like
you're dating USA Today.
Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, Tim.
George,
you know Tim Whatley.
Yeah, dentist to the stars.
Ah!
What's up?
I'll tell you what's up.
I'm a Jew.
Excuse me?
I'm a Jew. I finished converting
two days ago.
Oh, well,
welcome aboard.
Thanks.
So I'll see you tomorrow?
Yeah, I have a cavity,
lower left.
Were you just
at the health club?
Oh, yeah.
We must have just missed you.
Ah, well, I didn't do much.
I just sat in the sauna.
You know, it was more like
a Jewish workout.
[LAUGHS]
I'll see you.
[♪]
JERRY:
Elaine, the guy's Jewish two days.
He's already making
Jewish jokes.
So what?
When someone turns 21,
they usually get drunk
the first night.
Booze is not a religion.
Tell that to my father.
Anyway, guess what.
Beth Lookner called me.
Ooh, Beth Lookner.
I'm still waiting out
that marriage.
What are you talking about?
That marriage ended
six months ago.
She's already remarried.
Where was I?
It was when
you were engaged.
Oh, I gotta get
on that Internet.
I'm late on everything.
Anyway, so Beth
and her new husband, Arnie,
have listed me as a reference
for an adoption agency.
They're trying to get a baby.
Oh, God, a baby.
That can add two years
to a marriage.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Oh! Elaine, all right.
Who looks better in this shirt,
me or Mickey?
We're double-dating tonight.
If we wear the same shirt,
we'll look like idiots.
Hm. Turn around.
Well, you're both so...
striking.
Yeah,
tell me about it.
We just picked up two women
at The Gap.
How did you decide which one
of you would date which girl?
[♪]
MARCY:
So I'm on Third Avenue,
minding my own business
and, yada, yada, yada,
I get a free massage
and a facial.
Wow.
What a succinct story.
[CHUCKLES]
So I'm surprised
you drive a Cadillac.
Oh, it's, uh-- It's not mine.
It's my mother's.
Oh.
Are you close with your parents?
Well,
they gave birth to me and...
yada, yada.
Yada what?
Yada, yada, yada.
[♪]
[CLEARS THROAT]
It's a nice place.
Really nice.
I like your shirt.
Oh, thank you.
It's a hundred percent cotton.
And some wool.
Mm.
Well, you, uh--
You two seem to have
the same taste.
Well, I like it too.
Oh, well,
I have the same shirt.
Yeah, well, I'm wearing it.
Well, I like your shirt too.
Oh.
Well, so do I.
Did I mention
I'm a serious actor?
Really?
I enjoy polo.
[IN UNISON]
Oh.
I like the beach.
My aunt has been, uh,
ill of late.
I own a tuxedo.
Anything to drink?
Uh, some wine perhaps?
I like merlot.
I love merlot.
I'm crazy about merlot.
I live for merlot.
We're out of merlot.
[DISHES CLATTER]
[♪]
We'll clear out
so you can do your interview.
Okay.
Make us sound good.
Oh, come on.
[LAUGHTER]
Bye.
Bye, Beth. Bye, Arnie.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Nice people.
So do you, uh, know Beth
and Arnie pretty well?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Do you socialize
with them often?
Yeah, yeah,
we go out to dinner a lot,
usually Chinese.
Well, sometimes Thai.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
And we go to the movies.
Arnie's a real film buff.
Uh-huh.
Uh, actually, I remember
this one time, um...
Heh.
This is funny.
[CHUCKLES]
Um,
we-- We went to see
the movie Striptease.
I don't know if you've
saw-- Seen it.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway.
Um-- And it was during
the opening credits, you know,
it was before the movie
had even started.
And I was whispering something
to Beth
and Arnie leans over to me
and he goes,
"Would you shut up?!"
[SCOFFS]
I mean, he barely even knew me.
Where did he get off--?
But they're great people.
[♪]
Oh, you're in here.
What are you doing here?
I knew you had an appointment.
Well, this is very awkward.
I'll leave
when the guy comes in.
Hey, I gotta tell ya.
I am loving
this yada yada thing.
You know, I can gloss over
my whole life story.
Look at that.
Hey. Hey, don't play with that.
That's going in my mouth.
What is this thing?
Woo!
Oh. All right. That's enough.
Just get going. Get outta here.
All right. Hey, Tim.
Hey.
Ooh, quick question.
Is it normal for your teeth
to make noises
like a hissing or a chirping?
George.
Uh...
Fine, I'll make
an appointment.
[SCOFFS]
All right. It is...
[SNAPS FINGERS]
cavity time.
Ahhh.
Ahh. Here we go.
Which reminds me,
did you hear the one
about the rabbi
and the farmer's daughter, huh?
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
"Those aren't matzo balls."
[CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
What?
Tim, do you think you should be
making jokes like that?
Why not?
I'm Jewish. Remember?
I know, but--
Jerry,
it's our sense of humor
that sustained us
as a people for 3000 years.
Five thousand.
Five thousand, even better.
Ahhh. Ahhh.
Okay.
Chrissy,
give me a shtickl of fluoride.
[♪]
And then he asked the assistant
for a shtickl of fluoride.
Why are you so concerned
about this?
I'll tell ya why.
Because I believe Whatley
converted to Judaism
just for the jokes.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
WOMAN:
Would you be interested in a subscription
to the New York Times?
Yes.
Well,
I don't believe that.
If you had gotten
in the back seat of the car,
we could've figured
this thing out.
Well, why were you holding
the door open for?
Not for you.
Who holds a door open for a man?
Well, I thought it was
a nice gesture,
but I guess I was wrong!
Let's just put their names
in a hat.
I don't even know their names!
Look, why don't you take
the one that was on the left?
I'm not sure she's my type.
Oh, everybody's your type.
What the hell
does that mean?
You've been married
three times.
That's it.
It's go time.
All right.
Take it easy.
Easy, easy.
Hey, hey, hey!
No, come on, let him go.
You wanna throw? Let's throw!
Hey, hey!
Hold on a second.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
All right, look.
I got an idea.
Why don't you just show up early
for your next date,
sit across
from each other,
and see who the girls
sit next to.
That's not bad.
All right.
So we let the girls decide.
Yeah, why should we
knock ourselves out?
Yeah, I wanna wear that shirt
next time.
No one wears the shirt
'Cause they already saw it.
We'll look like idiots.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Well, we, uh...
We were engaged
to be married, um...
We bought
the wedding invitations and, uh,
yada, yada, yada.
I'm still single.
[LAUGHS]
So, what's she doing now?
Yada.
I get it.
Well, I--
I love talking to you.
[CHUCKLING]
Me too. [LAUGHS]
So speaking of exes,
Mm.
my old boyfriend
came over late last night
and yada, yada, yada.
Anyway,
I'm really tired today.
[♪]
Beth, Arnie.
Hi. What's up?
Well, our adoption application
was denied.
Really?
The adoption agent seems to feel
that Arnie has a violent temper.
Oh.
So we're just asking
our friends
what they may have said
to the adoption agent.
Well, I...
Uh, you know, I just told them
what kind people you are
and, uh...
how Arnie's a big movie buff
and yada, yada, yada.
That is it.
[♪]
How you doing?
I have some discomfort
in my molar.
You like Tootsie Rolls,
don't you?
Father Curtis,
why don't you come in?
Father Curtis, good guy.
Oh, which reminds me.
Did ya hear the one
about the pope and Raquel Welch
on the lifeboat? Hm?
Huh?
I'll tell ya later.
[CHUCKLES]
Whatley.
[♪]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What are they doing here?
I told you we should've
got here a half-hour early.
All right. Okay, now,
what are we gonna do?
All right, all right.
Don't panic.
Let's just decide now.
Which one do you want?
All right,
I'll take Julie.
I knew you wanted her.
That's who I wanted.
All right. I'll take Karen.
No. You think I'm falling
for that?
I'll take Karen.
Fine. I'll take Julie.
All right. Which one is Julie?
I don't know.
Why don't we just grab a chair?
You first.
No, you first.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
How you doing?
Good evening.
KRAMER:
Stop.
Well, you ladies look lovely
tonight.
[♪]
So Whatley says to me,
"Hey, I can make Catholic jokes.
I used to be Catholic."
Now, see, I don't think
it is a Catholic joke.
I think it's more
of a Raquel Welch joke.
What was it?
"No, I said,
'Hand me the buoys.'"
[LAUGHING]
"Buoys."
[LAUGHS]
Don't ya see
what Whatley is after?
Total joke-telling immunity.
He's already got
the big two religions covered.
If he ever gets
Polish citizenship,
there'll be no stopping him.
So, what are you gonna do?
I think this Father Curtis might
be very interested to hear
what Whatley has the pope doing
with Raquel Welch.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, Beth, Arnie, it's Elaine.
Um...
Thought you guys might wanna
have lunch. Give me a call. Bye.
They're not getting a baby,
so you're taking them to lunch.
I thought it would be nice.
Poor Beth.
Hey, Arnie's just as upset.
Oh, screw him.
Listen to this.
Marcy comes over
and she tells me
that her ex-boyfriend
was over late last night
and yada, yada, yada,
"I'm really tired today."
What do you think
she was tired from?
Well, obviously the yada yada.
You don't think
she'd yada yada sex?
I've yada yada-ed sex.
Really?
Yeah. I met this lawyer.
We went out to dinner.
I had the lobster bisque.
We went back to my place.
Yada, yada, yada,
I never heard from him again.
But you yada yada-ed
over the best part.
No, I mentioned the bisque.
Well, I gotta do something.
George is already in there.
[MOUTHING DIALOGUE]
No, Mickey and I.
We can't work it out.
You know, I'm thinking of asking
that Karen out by myself.
She's the one.
You were leaning towards Julie.
Well, I was. But the one
I thought was Julie
turned out to be Karen.
[TRILLS]
Ba-ba-ba!
[♪]
GEORGE:
Well, it was a hell of a yada yada.
He's moving to Seattle.
He wanted to say goodbye.
I was just getting out
of the shower
and yada, yada, yada--
All right. Enough. Enough.
From now on, no more yada yadas.
Just--
Just give me the full story.
Okay. Well,
when I got out of the shower,
I was dripping wet--
Not that story. Another story.
Tell me, uh,
about the free facial.
Okay, well, like I said,
I was on Third Avenue
and I stopped by
a large department store.
Which one?
Bloomingdale's.
Very good. Go on.
[CLEARS THROAT]
And--
Oh, I stole a Piaget watch.
What's that?
And then I was on such a...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
...high that I went upstairs
to the salon on the fifth floor
and got a massage and a facial
and skipped out on the bill.
[LAUGHS]
Shoplifting.
Well, what about you?
You-- You told me
that you were engaged.
What was the rest of that?
[♪]
[ORGAN PLAYING]
Um, excuse me, Mother?
Sister.
Sister. Right.
Do you know when
Father Curtis has office hours?
Well, not until tomorrow.
Oh.
I really need to speak with him.
You know that's a kneeler.
Oh.
Tell me your sins, my son.
Uh, well, I-I should mention
that I'm Jewish.
Oh, that's no sin.
Oh, good.
Anyway, I-- I wanted to talk
to you about Dr. Whatley.
I-- I have a suspicion
that he's converted
to Judaism purely for the jokes.
And this offends you
as a Jewish person?
No, it offends me as a comedian.
And it'll interest you
to know
that he's also telling
Catholic jokes.
Well, um--
And, I mean--
And they're old jokes.
I mean, the pope
and Raquel Welch in a lifeboat.
I haven't heard that one.
Oh.
Oh, I'm sure ya have.
They're out on the ocean
and yada, yada, yada and she--
And she says,
"Those aren't buoys."
[LAUGHING]
Father.
One second.
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Well, if it would make you
feel better,
I could speak to Dr. Whatley.
Uh, I-- I have to go back
and have a wisdom tooth removed.
Good luck.
You know the difference
between a dentist
and a sadist, don't ya?
Um--
Newer magazines.
[CHUCKLES]
That's funny.
Now, if you would excuse me.
Jerry,
I gotta talk to you.
[♪]
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
Hi.
Hey, Kramer.
Uh, got a minute?
Uh, actually,
my parents are over but--
Would you like to meet them?
Yeah.
Uh, Mom, Dad.
Oh. Hi.
[MUMBLING]
[♪]
Elaine, I have to ask you
about something. What?
The yada yada.
The yada yada?
What exactly happened
down there?
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I talked to him
and blah, blah, blah.
He asked about you guys
and da, da-da, da-da.
More questions.
Blah, blah, blah.
All right. Shut up.
Shut up?
Again you are telling
me to shut up? What?
You yelled at me
that time at the movies.
That's why you're not
gettin' the baby.
And you told that
to the adoption guy?
[TSKS]
Slipped out.
Oh, God.
What am I gonna tell Beth?
Well, Arnie, look,
I'll go down and talk
to this adoption guy,
and I'll make sure that it all
gets straightened out.
All right, just don't
screw it up this time!
See, again you're yelling.
Not a fan of the yelling.
[♪]
[GROANS]
Are-- Are you about done?
Oh, I'm just getting warmed up.
Because I'm just a sadist
with newer magazines.
Huh?
Father Curtis told me
your little joke.
I really didn't appreciate it.
Well, what about
all your Jewish jokes?
I'm Jewish.
You're not a dentist.
You have no idea what my people
have been through.
The Jews?
No, the dentists.
You know, we have the highest
suicide rate of any profession.
Is that why it's so hard
to get an appointment?
[♪]
So I'll, uh...
I'll see you
tonight, huh?
Okay.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Date with Karen?
No, Julie.
She's the one.
What happened to Karen?
Well, Mickey and her
have a lot more in common.
Her parents are little people.
Oh, small world.
So little people can have
"non-little-people" children?
Oh, yeah, and vice versa.
Yeah, Mother Nature's
a mad scientist, Jerry.
So you won't believe what
happened with Whatley today.
It got back to him that I made
this little dentist joke,
and he got all offended.
Yeah.
Those people...
can be so touchy.
"Those people."
Listen to yourself.
What?
You think that dentists are
so different from me and you?
They came to this country
just like everybody else
in search of a dream.
Whatley's from Jersey.
Yes, and now he's
a full-fledged American.
Kramer, he's just a dentist.
Yeah,
and you're an anti-dentite.
I am not an anti-dentite.
You're a rabid anti-dentite.
Oh, it starts
with a few jokes and some slurs:
"Hey, denty."
Next thing you know,
you're saying they should have
their own schools.
They do have their own schools.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Oh, come on.
One little baby,
whatever you have in stock.
Miss Benes, please.
Lookit, lookit, Brian.
These people are getting
a baby,
period.
Now, we can do this
the easy way, or...
we can do this...
the fun way.
[♪]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Jerry, I'm sorry
to bother you,
but you always said
that you'd be there for me.
What's wrong?
I'm thinking of leaving Arnie.
Talk to me.
He met with Elaine,
and I asked him what happened.
And he yada yada-ed me.
But could--
Could they be having an affair?
Well, I wouldn't put anything
past anybody.
But we just got married.
Well, obviously
that was a mistake.
You need to forget
about Arnie.
The important thing
is you're moving on.
Why would Elaine
do that to me?
Forget about Elaine.
Let's just focus on us.
Come on, big hug.
Hey, Jerry.
Where's Kramer?
I've got exciting news.
I'm in the middle
of something.
Karen and I
are getting married.
Oh, congratulations.
Her marriage just fell apart.
How many is that for you?
Two.
Heh-heh, you're a lightweight.
Come on, honey.
[♪]
[ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
This church give you
any ideas?
Hey, Jerry.
Hey.
[CHUCKLES]
What are you doing here
with Beth?
[WHISPERS]
Beth and Arnie broke up.
So they don't want
a baby?
[SCOFFS]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I think
I'm gonna be sick.
Hey, where's Marcy?
She, uh, went shopping
for some shoes for the wedding
and, uh, yada, yada, yada,
I'll see her
in six to eight months.
Hey, Kramer,
over here.
I'd just as soon
not sit next to you.
Kramer.
Oh, look, there's Mickey
and his parents.
ELAINE:
Oh, a nice-looking family.
JERRY:
Very handsome.
How you doing?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Hey, Kramer.
You must be so proud.
We never thought
he'd settle down.
Well, not again.
Poor Mickey.
Excuse me.
I can't take this.
Hi, Mr. Abbott.
That's Dr. Abbott,
D.D.S.
Tim Whatley was
one of my students.
And if this wasn't
my son's wedding day,
I'd knock your teeth out,
you anti-dentite bastard.
What was that
all about?
Oh, I said something
about dentists,
and it got blown
all out of proportion.
Hey, what do you call a doctor
who fails out of med school?
What?
A dentist.
[BOTH LAUGH]
That's a good one.
Yeah.
Dentists.
Yeah, who needs 'em?
Not to mention
the blacks and the Jews.
[♪]
[ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's Beth?
She ran out
to get her head shaved.
[MUFFLED]
We are gathered here today
to unite this couple
in the bonds of holy matrimony.
Those wisdom teeth are tough
to get out. Mmm.
Marriage is not an institution
to be entered into lightly.
Yada, yada, yada.
I pronounce you man and wife.
[ORGAN PLAYING MENDELSSOHN'S
"WEDDING MARCH"]
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
I really wanted you.