[♪]
Now, I wouldn't walk over there.
Why not?
Because it's the most dangerous
part of the sidewalk.
Cab hops a curb: whack!
You've had
your last egg sandwich.
What about over there?
You know, air conditioners
fall out all the time.
I'd much rather get hit
by an 80-pound air conditioner
than a 2-ton cab.
No, no.
Cab's coming up right here.
Set of plastic hips,
prosthetic legs,
a monkey to answer the phone,
I'm back in business.
I'd much rather
take one in the head,
like I did in '79.
You were living
in the Village then, right?
I don't really remember.
[♪]
Toxic-waste green.
That is disgusting.
You know,
revulsion has now become
a valid form of attraction.
Well, then,
you're driving me wild.
I had 'em done for the big
Peterman bash I'm throwing.
Why are you having a party?
Oh, I drive
my people hard,
and then I reward them.
Like with dogs.
Yeah, exactly.
Party?
Yeah.
Food?
Mm-hm.
Bar?
Yeah.
George?
He's gonna show up anyway.
George, I just don't
want you interfering.
How could
I possibly interfere?
Isn't that
what Jack Ruby said?
[♪]
Ooh.
These are fantastic.
Fantastic.
You know, I'd love to, uh,
get a jump on the next batch.
Where do you come out of?
She's been ignoring
this section all evening.
[SNORTS]
Uh, quesadilla?
Uh, no, thanks.
Hi, uh, my name is George.
Anna.
I, uh, don't recall
seeing you around the office.
Do you work
in the mailroom?
Not quite. I, uh--
I'm a friend of Elaine Benes.
Oh, that's nice.
Excuse me.
So...
How 'bout leading us
in a toast?
Oh, sure.
Hey, guys,
I wanna make a toast.
Um...
Here's to those
who wish us well,
and those who don't
can go to hell.
[ALL LAUGHING]
["SHINING STAR" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKER]
Mm. All right.
Who's dancing?
Come on, who's dancing?
You want me--?
You want me to get it started?
I'll get it started.
All right. Woo!
Woo!
ELAINE:
Come on, guys. What's the holdup?
Sweet, fancy Moses.
[♪]
Hey.
You get the tickets?
Who needs two?
Oh, mamacita!
Let me see 'em.
Special sneak preview
of Death Blow.
Death Blow.
When someone tries
to blow you up,
not because of who you are,
but because of different
reasons altogether.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah? Come on up.
GEORGE: Up.
Hey, Jerry,
you think you could get an extra
ticket for my friend Brody?
Know what I had to go
through to get these?
I know, but he's a big fan
of the genre.
You know, I'd consider it
a personal favor to me.
Yeah, I guess I do owe you.
Yeah.
Uh, listen, you want me to stay
here till George gets up?
No, I'm okay.
There's no problem, really.
I'm fine.
He's right in there, boy.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, how was the party?
The food was good.
Yeah,
so I didn't miss anything?
Well, actually,
you did miss one little nugget
of entertainment.
Have you ever seen Elaine dance?
Elaine danced?
It was more like a full-body
dry heave set to music.
Did she do the little kicks
and the thumbs?
Wait, you mean
you know about this?
For some time.
It was about five years ago.
[BAND PLAYING UPBEAT TUNE]
Woo!
I never knew what to say
to her about it.
It was one of those problems
I hoped would just go away.
Well, sometimes
you can't help these people
till they hit rock bottom.
And by then
you've lost interest.
Hey, you gotta take a ride
with me later.
I borrowed my father's car,
'68 GTO!
What made him get that thing?
Well, during that period
when my folks were separated,
he went a little crazy.
Not a very long trip.
Yeah, Brody's in.
I don't even have
the extra ticket yet.
Well, you better get
on the horn.
[♪]
ELAINE:
I'm telling you, Jerry, I'm gettin' a vibe.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say that the staff
completely lost respect for me.
JERRY [ON PHONE]:
How could that be?
Well, Jerry,
I mean, it's like
the feeling is palpable.
Think it could have something
to do with the party?
No, George was there.
He said he had a great time.
It's George. I bet you
this is somehow George-related.
Oh, what are you talking about?
He's like a virus.
He attaches himself
to a healthy host company,
and the next thing you know,
the entire staff is infected.
Now you're talking crazy.
All right. Then, Jerry,
if that's not what it is,
you tell me.
What is it?
Uh...
[POPPING]
There's my call waiting,
I gotta get going. Bye-bye.
[DIAL TONE]
You have a minute
to approve some copy?
Oh, yeah. Sure, sure.
So, uh, did you have a good time
at the party last night?
It was a real kick.
Hey, did you happen
to speak to my friend George?
As a matter of fact,
I did.
Aha.
Well, listen, you would be wise
to keep your distance from him.
Why? He seems harmless.
Oh, he's not.
He's very harmful.
Really?
Oh, trust me.
He's a bad seed,
he's a horrible seed.
He's one of the worst seeds
I've ever seen.
And you two are friends?
Yeah, we're good friends.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So this, uh, Anna
called me
from out of the blue.
Really?
I thought you were rebuffed.
With extreme prejudice.
Maybe Elaine put in
a good word for you.
No, no, no.
See, that's just the thing.
Anna told me that Elaine said
I was one of the worst seeds
she'd ever seen.
Interesting.
She doesn't care for you.
Then a stern warning.
Suddenly a phone call.
Seems Elaine's made you
the bad boy.
And Anna digs the bad boy.
I'm the bad boy.
I've never been the bad boy.
You've been the bad employee,
the bad son, the bad friend.
Yes. Yes, yes.
The bad fiancé, the bad dinner
guest, the bad credit risk.
Okay, the point is made.
The bad date, the bad sport,
the bad citizen.
The bad tipper.
[♪]
JERRY:
Boy, half of show business is here.
Oh, there's Brody.
Psst! Brody, over here.
Hey, Kramer.
Yeah.
And, uh, you must be Jerry.
Thanks for the ticket.
That's quite a feedbag
you're working on there.
[CHUCKLING]
It's for all of us.
Is there a problem?
Brody. Brody, come on,
he's just kidding.
He's a joke maker.
Tell him, Jerry.
I'm a joke maker.
All right, here we go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Death Blow.
[SOFTLY]
Hey. Hm?
What the hell is he doing?
Relax, he does that
all the time.
Does what?
He's making a copy of the movie
for sale on the street. Hm?
May I see you outside
for a moment, please?
I wanna watch the movie--
Outside!
JERRY:
Come on!
Hey, have you seen Anna?
She just left to meet
your friend George.
To meet George?
I knew it. Where did they go?
The park, why?
Don't you see?
George is in the bloodstream.
You stay away from him too.
[♪]
What do you mean,
bootlegging the movie?
It's a perfectly
legitimate business.
It's not legitimate.
It's a business.
Where did you meet
this guy?
He's a friend of a friend.
You know Corky Ramirez
up on 94th Street?
One day he and I
are playing Pachinko--
Kramer.
[EXPLOSION, GUNFIRE]
Man, we're missing
the deathblow!
I don't believe it.
[♪]
You know, I'm not supposed
to be talking to you.
No one's putting
a gun to your head.
Do I, uh, scare you?
No.
A little.
Nice car.
Yeah.
[SNIFFS]
She's a sweet ride.
Is that your orthopedic
back pillow?
Maybe.
Well, is it, or isn't it?
I guess not.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Stay away from her.
Hey,
I didn't do nothing.
Get in the car.
But--
You heard me, young lady.
Get in the car.
And you! You should know better.
I don't want you infecting
my staff.
Lighten up.
[♪]
Go get 'em, Death Blow.
MAN:
So, Death Blow, we meet again.
Are you okay?
[GROANS]
I got a cramp.
Well, it's no wonder.
You ate that entire bag
of candy.
[GROANS]
There it goes again.
[WHIMPERS]
Kramer,
you gotta drive me home.
Hey, what is going on
over here?
Jerry, finish shooting
the movie for me.
Are you nuts? There is no way
I'm holding that thing.
Jerry,
the man is in pain.
If he hadn't licked
his fingers
before reaching in the bag,
we would have eaten some.
Serves him right.
What are you,
some kind of tough guy?
Okay.
Let's everybody just relax.
Jerry,
take the camera.
All right, I'm--
I'm taking the camera.
All right, come on, let's go.
Thanks, buddy.
Oh, man.
[♪]
Hey.
So how was the rest
of Death Blow?
How was the rest of Death Blow?
Yeah,
who got the final deathblow?
I thought that Hawaiian guy
had it coming to him, huh?
You make me get a ticket
for this friend of yours,
and then the guy forces me
to bootleg a movie at gunpoint?
He's quite a character,
isn't he?
He came by here last night
at 3:00 in the morning
to pick up the tape.
I was scared out of my mind.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
I'll get it.
Yup.
It's Brody.
Yeah, come on up.
It's Brody, he's coming.
What? Are you crazy?
I don't want to see
this guy again.
Jerry, you did him a favor.
He probably wants to thank you.
What if I didn't do it right?
Well, it's your first time.
He'll understand.
People with guns
don't understand.
That's why they get guns.
Too many misunderstandings.
Hey, Brody.
Hi.
Jerry, I have to talk to you
about the tape.
Yeah.
I've never seen
such beautiful work.
What?
You're a genius.
The zoom-ins,
the framing,
I was enchanted.
Well...
I did the best I could.
I got another project for you.
Here, go ahead.
It's a movie called
Cry, Cry Again.
I was gonna give it
to one of my other guys,
but it's an arty movie
and quite frankly,
they don't have the sensibility.
[PAGER BEEPS]
May I use your phone?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
It's under the couch.
Look at you.
You got another gig, huh?
I don't want another gig.
I'm not doing this.
But you have a gift.
Look, Jerry, this is not
your little comedy act.
We're talking
feature films here.
federal crime here.
I'll expect that tape
by 3:00 tomorrow.
May I borrow this, please?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Oh, you need a glove?
Nah.
"I pressed
through the rushes,
"and there the native dancers
whirled before me.
"Limbs flailing,
arms akimbo,
feet kicking up dust."
What? What is so funny?
Sorry, I got hung up.
Oh.
At Yankee Stadium.
This? It's mine.
Oh, really? Because it looks
a little big for you.
It looks like something
a short, stocky,
slow-witted,
bald man might wear.
He's not stocky.
Who did that?
Who did that!?
[♪]
[LAUGHING]
[CRASHING NOISE]
[CHUCKLING]
The French guy fell off his bike.
Oh, man,
that's precious.
[♪]
JERRY:
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
What were you thinking
when you shot this?
What? That's fine.
Do you even know what
this scene is about?
Yeah, it's about a guy buying
a loaf of bread.
No. Bread is his soul.
He's trying to buy back
a loaf of his soul.
Wha--? When?
There's no way you're giving
this tape to Brody
and telling him I shot it.
Why? He's not gonna know
the difference.
I don't care about Brody.
I was up on 96th Street today.
There was a little kid,
couldn't have been more
than 10 years old.
He was asking a street vendor
if he had any other bootlegs
that looked as good
as Death Blow.
That's who I care about.
The little kid
who needs bootlegs
because his parent
or guardian won't let him see
the excessive violence
and strong sexual content
you and I take for granted.
So you'll do the movie?
KRAMER [ON TAPE]:
Oh. Oh, man. I sat in gum.
I have to.
But I'm gonna need
to storyboard this whole thing.
Where are my Magic Markers?
Right here.
Well, I have lost
complete control of my staff.
Why did I let George go
to that party?
I mean, we were having
so much fun.
I mean, we were wining,
we were dining, we were dancing.
Whoa, whoa.
Please stop.
What?
This...thing.
It's dancing.
No, no.
That ain't dancing, sally.
I dance fine.
You stink.
He doesn't know
what he's talking about.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Jerry?
I'm a good dancer, right?
I forgot to make my bed.
Jerry, do I stink?
All right!
You're beyond stink!
But I really enjoy dancing.
And that's not helping either.
That's why you're having
trouble with your staff,
not because of George.
It's that bad?
Have you ever seen yourself?
Uh-- Uh, please, please.
Not in my home.
I gotta throw this stuff
in the laundry.
I'll be right back.
[♪]
SECRETARY [OVER PHONE]:
I have George Costanza still holding.
George, hi.
Um, I have Anna here.
There's something I want
to say to both of you.
Yo, Anna.
Hi, George,
what are you up to?
[CHUCKLES]
You don't wanna know.
[GIGGLES]
Uh, well, listen,
I feel really horrible
about trying
to keep you two apart,
and I just wanted
to apologize.
Wha--? What--?
What are you talking about?
Well, George, I just want you
to hear me say to Anna
that you're a good
and decent person.
GEORGE:
Pick up the phone, Elaine. Pick it up.
I never should have given Anna
the impression...
Pick it up!
...you're a bad seed.
I mean, you're a fine seed.
Elaine, get off the speaker!
What?
You are ruining everything.
What? I'm-- I'm trying to help.
Why are you being so difficult?
Yeah, yeah. That's it.
More of that.
Difficult,
I'm a difficult seed.
George,
I don't have time for this.
Anna, do you want
to talk to George?
Um, no, I don't think so.
No, she doesn't want to.
Okay. Bye, George,
we'll see you.
GEORGE:
I'm a bad man!
[♪]
So where's the tape?
Oh, no, I didn't shoot this one.
I'm just scouting the location.
I need the tape.
You'll get your tape.
But here's what I need.
I'm gonna need three cameras,
two on the floor,
one in the balcony,
and I want headsets
for the guys running 'em.
I want to be able
to talk to 'em.
Are--? Are you out
of your mind?
Kramer, I-- You know...
Yeah.
I know, Jerry, it's okay.
Yeah, uh, look, Brody,
Jerry wants to do the bootleg.
He's dying to do it,
but if you don't make him happy,
the work suffers
and then nobody's happy.
Just shoot the damn thing
so I can get it out
on the street!
All right, that's it.
I can't work like this.
Jerry--
I'm off the project!
Jerry!
I want the tape.
Yeah, I-- I know.
[♪]
Well, I'm the good boy again.
Can you believe that?
They think they can get anyone
to shoot these bootlegs.
Anna actually has respect
for me now.
[CHUCKLES, SNORTS]
It's all over.
Eh, the whole business
has changed.
It's all about money now.
The sad thing is,
it's the kids that suffer.
Listen, man, you gotta shoot
this movie for me.
Brody, he's a reasonable man,
but he's insane.
Kramer, I'm not doing
this anymore.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
It's illegal,
it's dangerous...
Did you say dangerous?
I'm a bootlegger!
You're a what?
Bootlegging a movie, baby.
Isn't that illegal?
I could do hard time
for this one.
And community service.
Is this your FiberCon?
Get out of my way!
[♪]
Jerry,
George got arrested.
What?
Yeah.
He went down at the Beekman.
He tried to lam,
but they cheesed him.
Oh, now I see.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
It's Brody. I'm coming up.
What are we gonna do?
Well, uh,
I gotta give him something.
Come on.
Where's that tape I shot?
Uh, I think that's it.
Let's check it out.
[SERENE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Sweet, fancy Moses.
Jerry, she taped over
the whole ending.
Where's the tape?
Uh, well, it's--
Is that it?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Here it is, Brody.
One copy of Cry, Cry Again.
How'd it turn out?
Great.
Great, yeah.
Although the, uh, whole story
kind of comes apart
at the end there.
Yeah, out of nowhere
there's this lone dancer
who appears
to be injured.
Yeah. I-it's a disturbing image.
Yeah, so you cry,
and then when you see
the dancing,
you cry again.
[♪]
It's all right, George.
You'll just pay a fine,
and that'll be it.
Why did the policeman have
to yell at me like that?
Anna.
Thanks for coming
to pick me up.
I can explain everything.
All right.
We'll talk about it
at the office.
Okay, where's my boy?
Oh, my God.
I'm sitting at home,
reading a periodical,
and this is the call
I get?
My son is a bootlegger?
Ow, Dad!
Who put you up to this?
Was it her?
All right. Wait, I think
you've got it backwards.
My George isn't clever enough
to hatch a scheme like this.
You got that right.
What the hell
does that mean?
That means whatever the hell
you want it to mean.
You saying you want
a piece of me?
I could drop you
like a bag of dirt.
You want a piece of me?
You got it!
[♪]
But he's an old man, Elaine.
Well, he wrote the check,
and I cashed it.
Look, here's that bootlegged
Death Blow that I shot.
Oh, Cry, Cry Again,
I want to see that.
No, you don't.
You shot Death Blow?
Yeah.
It was brilliant.
Thank you.
You were big.
I'm still big.
It's the bootlegs
that got small.
How are things at the office?
Back to normal?
Yeah, pretty much.
Although I still get the vibe
every once in a while.
Oh, I wouldn't worry
about it.
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ You're a really big
Shining star ♪