[♪]
You know, I can now bite
my fingernails so evenly
that I don't even need
to use a clipper anymore.
But it's a pleasure
to use clippers.
Why gnaw away
like a mental patient
when we have
this elegant device?
What if you're in prison?
They don't give you clippers?
No, it's like a weapon.
You know what's really a weapon?
That big toenail.
You let that grow
for a month,
take it in the shower,
it's like a shiv.
I love prison.
It is fascinating.
Yeah...maybe someday.
[♪]
You want me to find
a poem about Susan?
May she rest in peace.
Well, we think
it would be a nice touch
for the foundation literature.
You have a favorite poet,
George?
I like, uh, Flavman.
Pardon?
Flavman.
Well, you should choose the poem
since you knew Susan best
at the time
of her unfortunate--
Ahem. --accident.
[♪]
JERRY:
He cleared his throat?
Yes.
So?
He did it right as he said,
"Her unfortunate accident."
Not getting it.
Jerry, a throat clear
is a non-verbal
implication of doubt.
He thinks I killed Susan.
Oh, help me, Rhonda.
What time is it?
One-fifteen.
Right now?
I gotta go meet Pam.
Oh, the bookstore girl.
How's that going?
Okay.
I'm just not gaga over her.
For once, I'd like to be gaga.
Where's Elaine?
She's having Carol,
Gail and Lisa over.
You know,
they all have kids now.
What's with all
these people having babies?
Perpetuation of the species.
Yeah, right.
By the way,
just for the record--
No, I did not!
All right.
CAROL:
But because it comes out
of your baby,
it smells good.
Well, that's--
That's sweet.
Being a mother has made me
feel so beautiful.
Elaine,
ya gotta have a baby.
Oh, hey, you know,
I had a piece
of whitefish
over at Barney Greengrass
the other day, and I--
Elaine, move to Long Island
and have a baby already.
I really like the city.
The city's a toilet.
When's the last time
you saw my little Adam?
Uh, it was in the Hamptons.
Ah, I have pictures.
Oh, no, no, that's okay. It's--
Look at him,
just look at him.
[♪]
So Elaine was telling me
about this piece of whitefish
she had the other day.
Do you really think I'm wrong
about this Wyck guy?
You know, if you really
wanna test him out,
why don't you try
the Jerry Lewis trick?
Jerry Lewis?
I heard when Jerry Lewis
left a meeting
he'd purposely leave a briefcase
with a tape recorder in it.
Then after five minutes,
he'd come back for it,
listen to what everyone
said about him.
That's pretty paranoid.
Yes, it is.
I like it!
I thought you might.
[♪]
Oh. Hi.
I'm Pam.
You must be Kramer.
Jerry has, uh, told me
a lot about you.
[MOANS]
Well, uh, I'm supposed
to meet Jerry.
It's my day off.
I work in a bookstore.
[MOUTHS]
Books.
Oh! Careful!
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
Hi.
That's okay.
Kramer let me in.
If we rush,
we can still make the movie.
It was really nice meeting you.
[SQUEALS]
KRAMER:
I'm in trouble, buddy.
I just met a woman.
Go on.
Well...
she's Jerry's girlfriend.
Ah, yes,
forbidden love.
She works in a bookshop.
Her name is Pam.
Pam.
I don't know the woman,
but she sounds quite fetching.
I can't even speak
in front of her.
Jerry!
What could she possibly see
in Jerry?
Oh!
She has delicate beauty.
Jerry wouldn't know delicate
if it bludgeoned him
over the head.
And yet, he's my friend.
And therein lies
the tragedy.
For I believe,
sadly for you,
that there is but one woman
meant for each of us.
One perfect angel
for whom we are put
on this earth.
Oh, that's beautiful, Newman.
One winsome tulip
we ceaselessly yearn for
throughout our dreary
workaday lives,
and you, my friend,
have found your angel.
I can tell.
For my heart has
also been captured
by a breathless beauty
whom I fear
I will never possess.
I thought we were talking
about me.
Oh, right.
Kramer, you have
to confront Jerry.
Confront Jerry?
I can't.
You must.
I won't.
You will!
[AS CAROL]
"Elaine, you gotta have a baby."
Ehh.
Where are
the poetry magazines?
[NORMAL VOICE]
The New Yorker has poetry.
Yes, The New Yorker.
Why do you invite
these women over
if they annoy you
so much?
Well, they're my friends,
but they act as if having a baby
takes some kind of talent.
Come on.
You wanna have a baby.
Why? Because I can?
It's the life force.
I saw a show
on the mollusk last night.
Elaine, the mollusk travels
from Alaska to Chile
just for a shot
at another mollusk.
You think
you're any better?
Yes, I think I am better
than the mollusk.
Excuse me,
I couldn't help overhearing
what you were saying.
Oh, I'm sorry--
No, no.
I think I agree with you.
I mean, all this talk
about having babies.
Yeah, like you must procreate.
Besides, anyone can do it.
Oh, it's been done
to death.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I, uh, should have a poem very soon now.
Are you okay, George?
[CLATTERING]
No, no.
Not really.
Ever since Susan passed on
I have good days and bad.
Some days I--
I'm haunted by one word:
why?
Why Susan?
Why wasn't it me
licking those invitations?
Why am I still here?
But I gotta run, uh...
[♪]
Now, the stock options
for this year look, uh, quite--
Briefcase.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
[♪]
So, Kevin,
if I don't want children,
does that make me
a bad humanitarian?
Not at all.
I mean,
when you get to know me,
you'll see that I'm
a pretty good humanitarian.
You are doing a wonderful job,
by the way.
WAITRESS:
Thanks a lot.
Right? Am I right?
Yeah.
Kramer.
Kramer, come here,
look at my new friend Kevin.
Oh, you got a little, uh--
You got--
Wha--? Oh, yeah.
I just had, uh,
two double-fudge sundaes.
Oh, are you all right?
Yeah, I'll be okay.
You know, Jerry has one of those
every time he bombs on stage.
Well, I'm sure he'll be sharing
his next one with Pam.
Oh, no, that won't last.
What do you mean?
He's not gaga.
[GIBBERS]
[♪]
Let me tell you something.
That Jerry Lewis?
You wonder how these people
get to the top?
It's ideas like this.
Brilliant! Ha, ha.
Look at this.
What the hell happened?
The whole side
is damaged here.
And the lock is broken.
How long did you
leave it there?
Five minutes.
What the hell happened here?
Play the tape.
Maybe we'll get a clue.
I have to rewind it first.
[CLICKS]
All right. All right.
MAN [ON TAPE]:
Did anyone notice George's fingernails?
WOMAN:
Oh, my, yes.
They look like they were
eaten away by weevils.
WYCK:
It's getting warm in here. Open the window.
Hey, what are you doing?
WOMAN:
Dear God!
[LOUD THUD, RECORDING ENDS]
Is that it?
It stopped dead.
What do you make of it?
I don't know.
Jerry,
uh, can we talk?
Kind of busy here.
I'd like to talk to Jerry
in private.
Why can't I stay?
Because it doesn't concern you.
Well, if it doesn't concern me,
then I can stay.
So, what's on your mind?
It's Pam.
Pam? What about Pam?
I love her, Jerry.
You what?
I love her.
Is that right?
Oh, she's-- She's real.
She can bring home the bacon
and fry it in the pan.
What does that mean?
Oh, and that voice.
What about her name?
Pam?
Oh, it's a beautiful name.
Pam.
Pam?
Pam!
She's got really nice hair.
Oh, it's incredible.
Although, I might replace
her tortoise clip
with one of those
velvet scrunchies.
I love those.
You've got really
specific tastes.
Oh, I know what I want, Jerry.
She's got nice calves.
Oh, she's a dreamboat,
but you don't like her.
Maybe I could. You're making
some good points.
No, you can't, Jerry.
But I might.
Oh, no, you don't.
Why not?
The voice, the calves,
the bacon.
What?
I think I can. I even like the name. Pam.
Huh? Huh?
Pam. Pam.
[♪]
So now he wants her
more than ever.
Blast!
What am I gonna do, huh?
Don't despair, my friend.
Ow!
[GRUNTS]
I won't allow your love
to go unrequited,
not like mine.
What, again with you?
Sorry.
But love is a spice
with many tastes.
A dizzying array
of textures and moments.
If only I could say things
like that around her.
Yes.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Well, I hear three distinct sounds.
A low rumple,
followed by
a metallic squink--
Yes, yes, I heard the squink.
Followed by
a mysterious...galonk.
It's a real baffler,
isn't it?
Well, one question
does come to mind.
Have you considered
just asking 'em what happened
to the briefcase?
They would never tell me,
Elaine.
First of all,
they probably think
that I killed Susan.
Besides, I don't even think
they like me.
That Pam.
I am gaga over her.
Gaga? When did that happen?
Yesterday, 6-ish.
Huh.
Well, maybe we should double.
I'm pretty gaga myself.
You just met
the guy yesterday.
Yeah, but we have
a common goal.
A barren, sterile existence
that ends when you die?
[GIGGLING]
Yeah.
You really believe this guy
doesn't want to have kids?
Of course.
JERRY: Elaine,
a guy will say anything
to a woman.
Oh, please,
he wouldn't say that.
Elaine, I once told a woman
that I coined the phrase:
"Pardon my French."
I once told a woman
I don't eat cake
because it goes right
to my thighs.
Once told a woman
I enjoy spending time
with my family.
[♪]
NEWMAN:
With your looks and my words
we'll have built
the perfect beast.
All right.
Oh, hi, Kramer.
[SOFTLY]
Hi, how are you?
I'm great.
I too am well.
Do I smell Pantene?
Do I smell?
Pantene!
Uh, Pantene?
PAM:
Oh!
My shampoo.
Yeah, yeah, you know,
it is Pantene.
I got a free sample of it
in with my junk mail.
Well, there really is
no junk mail.
Everybody wants a check
or a birthday card, but--
It requires just
as much manpower to deliver
as their precious cards--
Newman.
[GRUNTS]
What?
Uh, human. Human.
It's human to be moved
by a fragrance.
That's so true.
Her bouquet cleaved
his hardened--
Shell.
Shell
And fondled his muscled heart
He imbibed her glistening spell
Just before the other shoe fell
Kramer, that is so lovely.
It's by a-- An unknown
20th century poet.
Oh, what's him name?
Newman.
[♪]
KEVIN:
Elaine, you changed my life.
Oh, Kevin,
you can go on and on
about how you don't want kids,
and it-- It sounds--
It sounds really nice,
but the truth is, I don't know
if you mean it or not.
I got a vasectomy this morning.
Although,
I have a hunch you mean it.
[♪]
JERRY:
I just came by to tell you
I'm really, really happy
about this relationship.
Really happy.
Oh, well, that's--
[CLEARS THROAT]
Nice.
JERRY:
A velvet scrunchie.
Kramer.
[♪]
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
How's Pam?
Pam? What do you care?
Well, ta-ta.
[GIGGLING]
Wait a minute.
[♪]
All right, Newman,
this is it.
Steady, Jerry.
Steady.
You wouldn't wanna lose
your cool now.
Why not?
Because right now
I'm the only chance
you've got.
[GIGGLES]
[SWALLOWS]
Come on.
[♪]
I can't believe
I'm losing Pam.
I know how you feel,
for I too have a woman
for whom I pine.
I thought
we were talking about me.
Right.
Anyway,
I don't need your help.
Oh, don't you, joke boy?
[DOOR OPENS]
You really think
you can manipulate
that beautiful young woman
like the half-soused,
nightclub rabble
that lap up
your inane "observations"?
All right, Newman.
What do I have to do
to get you to stop
pulling the strings
for Kramer?
Well, there is
a little something
you can do for me.
Come on, out with it.
It's about Elaine.
Elaine?
What does she have to--?
Oh, no.
You dated her.
Give me some inside information.
Anything I can use.
Well, I know she doesn't
wanna have kids.
[♪]
I thought you'd be a little
more enthusiastic about it.
I know. I-- I don't want--
[CLEARS THROAT]
Kids.
What was that?
Well...
Kevin, maybe I have
a little doubt.
I mean,
nothing is 100 percent.
This is.
Oh, boy, I always do this.
What?
I get all jazzed up
about something,
and I go way too far with it.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Like last summer,
I'm watching TV
and I saw one
of those jet skis.
Huh.
Four thousand dollars later
and it's sitting in my garage.
You know,
that's weird actually,
'cause I'm sort
of the same way.
I mean, once,
for, like, no reason,
I flattened my hair
and I had all these strands
hanging in my face all the time.
Sometimes I think
I do want kids.
Maybe a lot of kids.
Sometimes I think about
wearing my hair real short.
Yeah, I think
I like short hair,
really short.
Yeah.
[♪]
This is a crude mockup
of the conference room.
One-fourteenth scale.
When did you build
this thing?
Yesterday.
Took the day off.
Now, from the time
that I left the room--
Wait. That's you?
Yeah.
I think the M&M
should be you.
All right, whatever!
Now, whatever caused
the damage,
it was jarring enough
to completely stop the tape.
And?
Okay.
That's what we know.
But we already knew that.
Well, yeah.
Just give me some idea
what you think it could be.
I don't know
if you're ready for it.
Please.
I believe that I'm about
to become the target
of a systematic process
of intimidation
and manipulation,
the likes of which--
Hold it. You're right. I'm--
I'm not ready for this.
[INTERCOM BUZZING]
Yeah?
It's Pam.
Come on up.
All right, it's Pam.
You gotta get going.
I'm not through here,
Jerry.
I'm gonna keep on
investigating.
This thing is like an onion.
The more layers you peel,
the more it stinks.
What was that?
We were just playing.
Listen,
I had a long talk
with Kramer today.
Uh-huh?
Well, the thing is I, uh--
I think I have
a little crush on him.
I'm so happy.
My world suddenly has meaning.
This is the man
you have a crush on?
Well, I have feelings
for both of you.
You have feelings for him?
We're soul mates.
Why can't I be
a soul mate?
Jerry,
you really think
that Pam would want you
to be the father
of her children?
Children?
Who said anything
about children?
I don't wanna have children.
[♪]
GEORGE:
There are some people in this room
who would've been very happy
to never see...
this briefcase again.
There are people
in this room
who think they can destroy
other people's property
and get away with it.
Well, let me tell you something
about those people.
They weren't counting
on this brain!
And this tape recorder.
George--
You'll have your turn!
The truth must be heard.
[CLICKS]
WYCK:
Hey, what are you doing?
WOMAN:
Dear God!
[LOUD THUD, RECORDING ENDS]
[CLICKS]
That's all there was,
and yet it speaks volumes.
A low rumple,
a metallic squink,
a galonk,
and someone crying out,
"Dear God!"
Let's start with, uh...
With you, Wyck.
George,
Quinn here was moving a chair.
He lost his balance
and dropped it.
It must have fallen
on your briefcase,
which for some reason,
contained a running
tape recorder.
All right then.
We've gotten
to the bottom of that.
[♪]
Uh--
What are you guys
doing here?
We're getting vasectomies.
[LAUGHING]
Why?
I'm doing it for you.
What?
What'd you do
to your hair?
I cut it.
It's a little short.
You think?
What are you doing here?
Kevin's having
his vasectomy reversed.
Reversed?
[GASPING]
[♪]
He imbibed her glistening spell
Just before the other shoe fell
Is that a Keats poem?
No, it's a Newman.
[QUIETLY]
Newman.
Well, I gotta run.
Does anyone think George
might have murdered Susan?
Oh, yeah, I just assumed
he murdered her.
Of course
he killed her.
So it's not just me then.
All right.
Back to business.
[♪]