[♪]
What happened? We were
supposed to go the auto show.
I waited for you.
You never came.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got really busy.
How long did you wait?
Five minutes.
Five minutes?
That's it?
No difference.
You never showed up.
[SCOFFING]
Well, I could have.
I mean, last week we waited
for that friend of Kramer's
for like...
40 minutes.
Well, we barely
knew the guy.
So the longer you know someone,
the shorter you wait for them?
That's the way
it works.
When did you tell George
to be here?
I told him to meet us
in 10 minutes.
How long has it been?
About five.
That's enough.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Early. All right.
[SNIFFLES]
Cold.
So I noticed you bounced
a check at the bodega.
How did you know about that?
Marcelino.
He taped it up
on his cash register
with all of
the other bad checks.
He can't do that.
It's the only way
you'll learn.
Oh, these eggs
are disgusting.
Boy, this chicken should be
ashamed of himself.
Fantastic thing.
Fantastic.
What happened?
[CHUCKLES]
Well, first,
I'm brushing
my teeth,
and this piece
of apple skin
that must have been there
for days...
[SNAPS]
...comes loose.
Fantastic.
Then...I'm at
the foundation--
You're still doing that?
Sometimes.
Once in a while.
When you feel guilty.
No. Occasionally
I forget to let
the machine pick up.
Anyway, they made
this large donation
to a woman's prison,
and I get to go down there
and check it out.
Hm.
That's caged heat.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
What are you gonna do there?
Nothing really.
Just, uh, you know,
stroll around
the cellblocks,
maybe, uh, take in
a shower fight.
Heh, heh, heh.
Hey, you know
you got a bounced check
hanging up in the market
over on Columbus?
Yes, I know. I know.
I noticed you chose
the, uh, clowns-with-balloon
check design.
It was a mistake. The bank
sent me the wrong ones.
Hey. Look who's here.
Hey, Kurt, this is Jerry
and George and Kramer.
Hey.
Hey, Kurt. Taste these eggs.
Uh, no. I only eat
cage-free, farm-fresh.
Yes. These are
sweatshop eggs.
Uh, I gotta call
the office, honey.
Will you order for me?
I'm a honey.
[CHUCKLES]
He's pretty
great, huh?
Is he from the future?
No. He just
shaves his head.
I think it's
pretty gutsy.
Listen, sweetheart,
let me tell you
a little something
about guts.
This is guts.
What? Clinging to
some scraps?
These are
not scraps.
These are historic
remains
of a once-great society
of hair.
Oh. Did you guys stop
at the bodega today?
[LAUGHING]
Some moron bounced a clown check.
Again, I'm really sorry
about the check, Marcelino.
People seem to like
the clowns.
Look, let me
just give you the 40,
plus another 20
for your trouble.
Okay.
Aren't you gonna take
the check down?
Sorry, no.
Store policy.
But it's your bodega.
Even I am not
above the policy.
WOMAN:
And those are our tennis courts.
Tennis courts?
W-w-what about
the yard?
Where do they have
the gang fights? Hm.
There's no fights here,
Mr. Costanza.
This is a minimum-security
facility.
Hm.
What about a hole?
Do you ever put anybody
in the box?
No.
This prison stinks.
And finally, the library,
which has just been refurbished,
thanks to your
generous donation.
This is Celia Morgan,
our librarian.
Nice to meet you.
I'll be in my office
if you need me.
Thanks, warden.
Betsy.
So are you the head
of the foundation?
Well, let's just say
it wouldn't exist without me.
So you two, uh,
shop at the same store? Heh.
No, it's standard issue.
Oh, my God.
You're in jail?
[GIGGLING]
That is so cool.
JERRY:
You asked her out?
Well...
not out.
She's
a prisoner.
How could you ask her out?
Why not?
I remember when
you wouldn't
date that girl
from Queens
'cause you didn't want to
go over the bridge.
It was different.
I'll say.
Jerry, I like being
with her.
Plus, I know where
she is all the time.
I have relatively
no competition.
And you know
how you fear the pop-in?
The pop-in.
Yeah-- No pop-in.
No, "In the neighborhood."
No, "I saw your light was on."
And the best part is,
if things go really well...
Conjugal visit?
Don't jinx it.
Don't.
Hey.
GEORGE: Hey.
What's up?
George is dating
a convict. Oh.
What's she in for?
Embezzlement.
Sounds like a nice girl.
Jerry, is it all right if I put
some stuff in your fridge?
'Cause mine's full.
Yeah, sure. You don't even
have a fridge, do you?
Well, not here.
Okay.
Kramer...
Wait a minute. Wait.
What the hell is that?
Well, it's
chicken feed.
I sense something
is afoot.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bought a chicken.
Allow me.
Yeah.
Why?
Cage-free,
farm-fresh eggs.
Allow me.
What are you?
An idiot?
No.
KURT:
Hold it. Hold it. Hold it.
Here. I got it.
Catch.
Hey. Driver's
license.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh...
my God.
What?
Your hair.
It's so thick
and lustrous.
I mean, it-- It was.
Well, it still is.
I shaved my head
for my swim team.
I just liked the way
it looked, so I kept it.
Are you saying that
I could be dating
this hair?
I mean...
with you under it?
[ROOSTER CROWING]
Wha--?
[ROOSTER CACKLING]
Hey.
Is that your chicken
making all that noise?
Oh, Jerry loves
the morning.
Who?
Little Jerry Seinfeld.
I named my chicken
after you.
Thanks. That's very sweet.
But that is not a chicken.
Of course it is.
I picked it out myself.
Well, you picked out
a rooster.
Well, that would
explain
Little Jerry's
poor egg production.
[CACKLING]
This was fun.
Yeah.
I had a great time.
Five minutes,
Mr. Costanza.
The whole hour just flew by.
[CHUCKLES]
GUARD: I'll get that.
Oh. Thanks, Bobby.
Well...
I guess I'll see you
in four days.
Yeah. Go out and have
a ball with the guys.
I'll be waiting
right here for you.
Of course you will.
You're the best.
Mm.
[PHONE RINGS]
JERRY:
Hello.
HELEN:
Jerry.
Leo told us he saw
your bounced check.
Are you having
money problems?
I'm not having
money problems.
Enough with the comedy.
You're very clever.
You should look
into advertising.
He never even called
Ed Roydlick.
They were looking
for someone.
I'm not calling Ed Roydlick.
I'm doing fine.
HELEN:
That's it.
I'm gonna send you $50.
You are not sending me $50!
[DOOR CLOSES]
We're sending you $50.
Morty, get me an envelope.
I swear to God,
if you send me $50,
you are gonna be
so sorry.
I don't see
envelopes.
They're right
in front of you.
Oh, for heaven's sakes.
Let me show you.
Ma. Ma.
Ma!
Oh!
[SIGHS]
How are the folks?
Good.
So...movie tonight?
I thought you were, uh,
going out with Celia.
I did. I'm back.
I love this relationship.
I feel so liberated.
Having her
in jail?
Yeah, the only thing
that bothers me
is I'm just coming up
with this now.
Yeah, dating
a convicted felon.
I don't know
how you missed it.
Here. Take a look
at that.
Oh.
Kurt's an organ donor.
No. He's not bald.
Look. He's got
a full head of hair.
So he just shaves
his head for no reason?
That's like using a wheelchair
for the fun of it.
And he's growing it in
just for me.
It's mine.
It's all mine.
It's just hair.
No, it's not
just hair. Look.
It's brown.
It's chestnut
with auburn highlights.
So?
You know, you're
not around women.
You don't know how important
a man's hair is.
I'm sorry, George,
but it's true.
I knew it.
[CACKLING]
Hey.
Hey, Kramer.
Yeah.
Yeah, nice rooster.
What's his name?
Ah, well, this is
Little Jerry Seinfeld.
Does he bounce checks?
[LAUGHS]
Come on. Look, can't you
take Jerry's check down?
Sorry, Kramer.
Can't help you.
[DOG BARKS, ROOSTER CLUCKS]
Hey. Hey, Jerry.
Come on.
[DOG WHIMPERS]
Oh, sorry.
I like the way
he handles himself.
Oh, yeah.
[CACKLING]
ELAINE:
Oh. It's coming in already.
Yeah?
Wow.
You have some very nice
little seedlings here.
[CHUCKLES]
Huh.
What?
Well, it doesn't seem to be
coming in so good
over here...
Or here.
What do you mean?
Well, I-- I don't know.
How--? How long
have you been
shaving your head for?
About three years.
Uh-huh.
Oh, my God!
I'm going bald!
CELIA:
George. I'm so glad to see you.
Heh-heh. Hey, I brought you
some cigarettes. Ha.
You buy yourself
something nice, huh?
Good news.
I'm up for parole.
Parole.
That's dynamite.
JERRY:
So Marcelino's gonna take down the check?
Yeah. Well,
it comes down
if Little Jerry Seinfeld
wins the cockfight.
Great.
What?
Well, Marcelino,
he has cockfights
in the back of his store.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. So he says
if Little
Jerry Seinfeld wins,
the check comes down.
Kramer, cockfighting
is illegal.
Only in the United States.
It's inhumane.
No, it's not
what you think it is.
It's two roosters
pecking at each other.
What?
Yeah.
Well, I thought
they wore gloves and helmets.
You know, like
American Gladiators.
No, Kramer, Little Jerry
could get hurt.
Yeah, well, I left him
with Marcelino.
My Little Jerry.
[YELLS INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, did you get
Little Jerry? Is he okay?
Oh. Well, he's
more than okay.
He won.
You let him fight?
I couldn't get there
in time to stop it.
But you should've seen
Little Jerry, Jerry.
Flapping his wings
and strutting his stuff.
He was pecking
and weaving
and bobbing
and talking trash.
He didn't even
have to touch him.
The other rooster
ran out of the ring.
The whole fight
lasted two seconds.
How long do they
usually last? Five seconds.
And Marcelino says he's
taking your check down today.
Great.
Hey.
Celia is up
for parole.
Hey, Little Jerry
won his cockfight.
What?
Who?
I'm too tired.
Okay,
well, listen, uh,
I want you to
come by later, all right?
We're having
a victory party. Okay.
It's over, Jerry.
She's getting out.
I'm so sorry.
She's been locked up
for two years.
She's gonna want to
make up for lost time.
Dinners, movies...
talking.
In other words,
a normal relationship.
Ha-ha.
And that's no good.
I've tried it
straight, Jerry.
We've all seen the results.
[SIGHS]
Think for me...
sick is the only way
to go.
Well, she'll still be an ex-con.
It's not the same.
Hey, if you two
were meant to be together...
I'm sure the cops
will pick her up on something.
ELAINE:
Kurt?
What's with the sweats?
Aren't we going out?
I don't care.
You, uh...
got a big stain
on your shirt.
Oh, yeah. A meatball
fell out of my sandwich.
You already ate?
It's from yesterday.
Jerry. You missed a hell
of a cockfight last night.
Then what is my check
still doing up?
We had a deal.
Now we have a new deal.
New deal?
When Little Jerry Seinfeld
is mine,
the check will be yours.
This is outrageous!
Pack of Juicy Fruit.
Eighty-five cents.
Eighty-five cents?
That is outrageous.
JERRY:
Kramer, Marcelino wants us
to sell him
Little Jerry Seinfeld.
Well, that's
out of the question.
But, Kramer, cockfighting
is an illegal
and immoral activity.
Yeah, if you've got
a loser.
But Little Jerry
was born to cockfight.
No. No more cockfighting.
Let's just sell him
to Marcelino, the cockfighter,
and be done with it.
I think you're jealous.
Of what?
Yeah!
Yeah, you see
in Little Jerry Seinfeld
the unlimited future
you once had.
Now, just because
Jerry Seinfeld is a has-been,
don't make Little
Jerry Seinfeld a never-was.
Kramer, give me
that rooster.
No more!
You hate him
because he's doing more
with your name
than you ever will!
[STAMMERS]
George, Celia has listed you
as a character reference.
Whatever
you can tell us
would certainly
be helpful
in her getting
parole.
Well, anything
I could do to help. Um...
She's a wonderful girl.
Very smart.
Very, uh, crafty.
Does she have any plans
after she's released?
Plans. Schemes.
She, uh-- She keeps talking
about getting back together
with her old friends,
you know.
"The gang,"
she likes to call them.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, they're, uh--
They're hatching something.
You can count on that.
MARCELINO:
Jerry.
Tomorrow night's
fight night.
Where's my rooster?
Kramer won't sell.
Well, tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna take down
your check anyway.
Oh. Well, thank you,
Marcelino.
Well, perhaps someday
you will do me a favor.
And that day is today.
Little Jerry Seinfeld
must go down
in the third round
of tomorrow's
main event.
You want Little Jerry
to take a dive?
Shh. Not so loud.
First of all,
I don't think you can
make a rooster
take a dive.
Can too.
Second of all,
Jerry Seinfeld,
big or little,
doesn't go down for anyone,
anywhere, at any time.
Now, I'd appreciate it
if you'd please leave.
Big Jerry is making
a big mistake, Jerry.
We'll see
about that.
Kramer, I'm coming up.
We got a cockfight to win.
KRAMER:
Okay.
Elaine said you would be
the best person I could talk to.
Yup. Classic
horseshoe pattern.
I've seen
a lot of this.
Oh, God.
No, no, Kurt.
Wrong attitude.
You should be happy now.
Happy? Why should
I be happy?
You've still got
pretty good coverage.
Once the enemy advances
beyond this perimeter...
well...
then you won't be
Kurt anymore.
What will I be?
[GROANS]
How long do I have?
Fourteen months.
Maybe 10.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes.
Live, damn it.
Live every precious moment
as if this was the last year
of your life.
Because in many ways...
it is.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
[SIGHS]
Celia, what--? Wh--
What are you doing here?
Well, I didn't get
my parole, so I busted out.
And-- And you just
decided to pop in.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Kurt.
Elaine. Will you marry me?
Oh, yeah.
Boy, he's looking good,
huh, Jerry?
Yeah. All right.
I think that's
enough for today.
[CACKLING]
Little Jerry is a lean,
mean pecking machine. Yeah.
What are you doing with that?
Yeah, I'm just
gonna heat this up.
Make a little hot tub
for Little Jerry.
Hey, Kramer.
Be careful.
Yeah. Right.
Hey.
Hey. Guess what.
Little Jerry
ran from here
to Newman's
in under 30 seconds.
Is that good?
I don't know.
Where have you been?
Celia broke out
of prison.
I'm sitting in my home.
She shows up at the door.
Oh, my God.
The breakout pop-in.
Yeah.
Jerry, listen to this.
I've discovered something even
better than conjugal-visit sex.
Fugitive sex.
Now it's like every time--
George. This is a little
too much for me.
Escaped convicts,
fugitive sex.
I got a cockfight
to focus on.
ELAINE:
Hey, hey, Kurt. Slow down.
I can't just marry you.
Whim, bam, boom.
I mean,
I need some...
fiancée time.
I need some make-
my-girlfriends-jealous time.
Plus, you want to
get to know me.
Yeah. Yeah, that too.
Well, how much time?
We--
[GASPS]
I don't know.
A year?
No, no, no,
it has to be now.
[SIGHS]
Could I see the ring again?
So you're actually
considering it?
Well, it will be
a couple of years
before he's
completely bald.
Those will be
good times.
Marriage is
a big step, Elaine.
Your life will
totally change.
Jerry, it's 3:30
in the morning.
I'm at a cockfight.
What am I clinging to?
Oh. Hey.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
Where's Celia?
She didn't
want to come.
She's not really
into sports.
Mm.
Hey, how's he doing?
He's got
a big sweat going.
Oh. This came for you
Express Mail.
It's from
your parents.
Hi.
ELAINE: Hi.
"Fifty dollars."
I don't believe this.
There's Marcelino.
Look at the size
of his bird.
That looks like a dog
with a glove on his head.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
KURT:
Hi. Is George back from the cockfight yet?
You know, I've gotta thank him.
He changed my life.
No. Must've been a good fight.
He's not back yet.
Ah. Damn.
Sorry to bother you,
Mr. Costanza.
Well, well, well.
Look who's here.
Oh, man.
Mr. Costanza.
You're under arrest
for aiding and abetting
a known fugitive.
[ CHUCKLES]
Save it.
We know you're bald.
We know it's you.
Let's go.
Muchas gracias.
Okay. I got
the whole scoop.
Marcelino flew the bird
in from Ecuador.
He's 68-0.
He's a ringer.
Where's the tamale guy?
[BELL RINGS,
CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Little Jerry's
gonna get his clock cleaned.
I've gotta get him
out of there.
[♪]
[IN SLOW MOTION]
Little Jerry!
[SLOW MOTION]
Kramer!
Stop the fight!
[SLOW MOTION]
Tamale!
[ROOSTER PECKING,
KRAMER YELLING IN PAIN]
Why? Why did you get into
a fistfight with the cop?
You were innocent.
They thought I was George.
I'm not that bald.
And I have too little time left
to take that kind of crap,
so I slugged him.
But how long are you
gonna be in here for?
Well, my lawyer says 14 months.
But with good behavior,
maybe 10.
[SIGHS]
So 10 to 14 months?
Yeah.
Tsk.
[♪]