[♪]
A dollar eighty-nine.
Why is this $1.89?
Why is there no
haggling in this country?
We like to think
we've progressed
beyond a knife fight
for a citrus drink.
Not me.
Everything should be negotiable.
Restaurants too?
Absolutely.
Are you telling me
there's no room to move
on pasta?
All starches are a scam.
Yeah, especially ziti,
with that big hole.
Uh, excuse me.
How much is this?
A dollar nineteen.
I'll give you a quarter.
Get the hell out of here.
Tell him 40 and no fork.
Thirty.
That's it. You leave
and never come back.
How about we leave
and come back in a week?
Deal.
All right. See?
We got something there.
[♪]
Oh, check it out.
Wow,
JERRY:
Kenny Rogers Roasters finally opened.
Hey, look at the size of that
neon chicken on the roof.
No. Rogers can't sell chicken
around here.
We got chicken places
on every block.
He is the Gambler.
Well, I gotta meet Newman
at the pet store.
Helping him
pick out a turtle.
Try and stay calm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey. Jerry?
Seth.
Wow, what has it been,
like, five years?
At least.
You wanna grab lunch?
Uh, I'm actually
headed back to the office.
Seth, it's me.
What's more important
than catching up
with an old college buddy?
Well, I am supposed
to be in this meeting.
Blow it off.
Remember poli-sci?
How many of those did we go to?
All right, I guess I can go.
All right. All right.
Hey, whatever happened
to Moochy?
He's dead.
Is that right?
I still don't know how you can
call lunch with me
a business expense.
What do you think
of the catalog?
Stinks.
There, we just talked business.
We have the down comforter
and the cookware you liked.
Oh, great. Put it all
on the Peterman account with the other stuff.
You know what else we have
you might like?
I'll take it.
Hey, you like?
I think it looks
very nice on you.
Really?
Hm.
Elaine, huh?
Peterman account?
Why not?
And some hair
for my little friend here.
So how's
your standup career?
Good. As a matter of fact,
I almost had my own show
in Japan.
You speak Japanese?
No.
So you would have done it
in Japan, but in English?
I don't know.
So, what's this job of yours?
Big investment firm.
Mm.
We just got
the Citibank account.
In fact, today was our
first big meeting with them.
The meeting you blew off?
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Wasn't that kind of important?
[♪]
ELAINE:
And I bought a whole new set of cookware
and a water pick.
You use a water pick?
Sure. Water pick,
floss, Plax, brush, Listerine.
So you go into the bathroom 11,
you're in bed by, what, 2?
Oh, at the latest.
Oh, hang on a second.
I got another call.
Hello?
Good day, Miss Benes.
It's Roger Ipswich.
Oh, hey, how are things
doing in Accounting?
Miss Benes,
I notice you've been charging
quite a bit of merchandise
on the Peterman account.
Well, I am the president.
Yes, and we're all
very impressed.
Nevertheless,
the expense account
is for business purposes only.
Well...
Well, isn't the president
allowed to do anything
that they want?
No.
I'll be in your office
first thing tomorrow.
Good day.
Hello?
Anybody?
[♪]
[SHIVERS]
Hey.
Why didn't you get
the big one?
This hat just bottles in
the heat.
I don't even need a coat.
It's unbelievable.
I don't believe it.
And I got a date
with the saleswoman.
She got a little Marisa Tomei
thing going on.
Ah. Too bad you've got a little
George Costanza thing going on.
I'm going out
with her tomorrow.
She said she had
some errands to run.
That's a date?
What's the difference?
You know the way I work.
I'm like a commercial jingle.
First, it's a little irritating.
Then you hear it a few times.
You hum it in the shower.
By the third date
it's:
♪ By Mennen ♪
How do you make sure you'll get
to the third date?
If there's any doubt,
I do a leave-behind.
Keys, gloves, scarf.
I go back to her place
to pick it up--
[SMACKS LIPS]
--date number two.
That is so old.
Why don't you just show up
at her house in a wooden horse?
[♪]
♪ By Mennen ♪
What the--?
[BUZZING]
Wh-what's goin' on in there?
What?
That light.
Oh, the red.
Yeah, it's the chicken roaster
sign.
You know, it's right across
from my window.
Can't you shut the shades?
They are shut.
Oh, by the way,
your friend Seth, he stopped by.
Oh, yeah? What'd he have to say?
Yeah, he was fired.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Well, as you can see,
the comforter
I expensed is actually
the Aristotle goose-down tunic.
[CHUCKLES]
What do you think?
Another bull's-eye.
Hm.
Well, Mr. Ipswich,
since every one of my expenses
was obviously
for a legitimate
business purpose...
I just need to see the sable hat
you purchased yesterday.
The hat? Why do you need
to see the hat?
It cost $8000.
What? Oh.
Ooh.
[♪]
Seth, if you knew the meeting
was so important,
why did you go
to lunch with me?
We're old college buddies.
I only knew you through Moochy.
Hey, Jerry, don't worry
about it, all right?
The important thing is,
is we got a chance to catch up.
Mind if I, uh,
grab the want ads?
Um, actually, I haven't read
Tank McNamara yet.
[BUZZING]
How's life on the red planet?
I...
It's killin' me.
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
All I can see
is that giant red sun
in the shape of a chicken.
Well, did you go down to
the Kenny Rogers and complain?
Oh, they gave me the heave-ho.
You know,
I don't think that Kenny Rogers
has any idea
what's going on down there.
What are you doin'?
Getting some cereal.
That-- That's tomato juice.
That looked like milk to me.
Jerry, my rods and cones
are all screwed up.
All right, that's it.
I gotta move in with you, Jerry.
I don't know, Kramer.
Uh...
My concern is that...
living together
after a while, we...
might start to get on
each other's nerves a little.
Listen to me,
I got a great idea.
You're a heavy sleeper, right?
Why don't we switch apartments?
Or I could sleep in the park.
You could knock
these walls down,
make it an eight-room
luxury suite.
Jerry, these
are loadbearing walls.
They're not gonna come down.
Yeah, that's no good.
I may have to drive that place
out of business.
Well, how are you gonna do that?
Like we did in the '60s.
Takin' it to the streets.
[BUZZING]
[♪]
HEATHER:
Thanks, George,
but I got it from here.
Oh, no, I'm in already. Come on.
So, uh, you wanna
get together tomorrow?
No, I'm gonna be pretty busy.
What about this weekend?
I'm gonna be busy for a while.
Okay.
Uh, see ya.
Hey.
You forgot your keys.
Th-those aren't my keys.
Well, they're not mine.
Oh.
[LAUGHS]
They are my keys.
How weird.
[PHONE RINGING]
Goodbye, George.
Yeah, bye.
George, bye.
Hello?
You are not gonna
believe the date I just had.
♪ Costanza ♪
[♪]
ELAINE:
What do you mean, you don't have the hat?
I left it at Heather's.
Are these alive?
No, dead.
George, I need
that Russian hat back.
All right, all right.
I'll call Heather.
You'll get your hat back.
I will get a second date.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, watch the magic.
[BEEPING]
Dial nine, Merlin.
[SIGHS]
[RINGING]
HEATHER: Hello?
Heather, hi, it's, uh--
It's George Costanza.
Oy.
Uh, listen, uh,
I don't mean to bother you,
but, uh, silly me, I--
I think I may have left my hat
in your apartment,
so I thought
I'd just come by later
and pick it up.
You didn't leave a hat here.
I'm pretty sure I left it, uh,
behind the cushion
of the chair,
accidentally.
No hat.
George, I've gotta go.
Uh, you know what,
maybe I'll just come--
[DIAL TONE]
Um-- Um, hey, hey.
[♪]
Seth?
Jerry, hi.
What do you think?
I think you're takin' the trash
out for this chicken place,
but that couldn't be.
Yeah, I'm the new manager.
But you were an executive.
This is fast food.
Not fast food.
Good food quickly.
Hey, next time lunch
will be on me, huh, Jer?
KRAMER:
Hey!
Stay away from the chicken!
It's bad!
Bad chicken! Mess you up!
That's not going to be
good for business.
That's not gonna be good
for anybody.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Jerry, I'm so glad we switched apartments.
It was the perfect solution.
Look, Kramer,
if I'm gonna live over there,
you gotta take
some of this stuff out.
I mean, this thing
is really freaking me out.
I feel like it's gonna
come to life
in the middle of the night
and kill me.
What, Mr. Marbles?
He's harmless.
And one other thing,
I don't want Newman
using my--
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Oh, no.
Nice place you got here, Kramer.
Yeah.
A man could really
get some thinking done.
Well, don't get
too comfortable.
As soon as Seth gets a real job,
you two are going back
in that chicken supernova.
What's that, Rogers chicken?
Oh, get that out of here.
I don't know. The man makes
a pretty strong bird.
Yeah, but I'm boycotting.
What is that, hickory?
Yeah.
It's the wood
that makes it good.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Let me--
[GROWLS]
Oh, stop it.
What's the matter with you?
Mm.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Can I help you?
Hi, yeah, I'm Elaine Benes.
We met at Barney's.
I'm a friend
of George Costanza's.
[SIGHS]
Hi.
Um, whether you're
aware of it or not,
George had this
pathetic little plan
to leave something behind
so he could try and weasel
a second date.
Really?
I know. He-- He has
a real confidence problem.
Well, not really--
George.
Anyway, I know you told him
that you didn't have the hat
because you didn't
wanna see him again,
and more sympathetic
I could not be,
but I really do need to have
the hat back.
Look. I don't know
what to tell you,
but there's no hat here.
I mean, maybe the maid took it.
I had people over, but--
Well, that makes sense.
Well, then you wouldn't mind
if we took a second look around?
Be my guest.
Good to see you again.
[♪]
She's bluffing.
[SIGHS]
She's got it stashed away
in there somewhere.
This is an absolute
disaster.
Oh, I don't know.
Check this out.
You stole her clock?
Well done.
Yep.
This is one for our side.
[♪]
[BED CREAKING]
[BUZZING, CREAKING]
What is that creaking?
It's like I'm
in the hold of a ship.
I've gotta relax.
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
Hello?
Is somebody there?
[FEET PATTERING]
M-- Mr. Marbles?
[♪]
ELAINE:
So I told Ipswich
I'd have the hat
by this afternoon.
What am I gonna do?
You should sleep with him.
[BUZZING]
Hi, buddy.
I'm on no sleep, no sleep.
You don't know what it's like.
All night long,
things are creaking and cracking
and that red light
is burning my brain.
You look a little stressed.
Oh, I'm stressed.
So, Kramer,
what am I supposed to do?
If I don't have
that fur hat by 4:00,
they're gonna take me down
like Nixon.
You know my friend
Bob Sacamano?
I thought he was
Kramer's friend.
Well, he called last night about
3 a.m., and we got to talkin'.
He sells Russian hats
down at Battery Park,
40 bucks.
Forty bucks?
Are they sable?
No, but the difference
is negligible.
Oh, yeah, I like this idea.
All right.
Let's give it a shot. Let's go.
Giddyup.
It's getting cold.
That was a close one.
Why do we have to
keep this from Jerry?
If Jerry finds out I'm hooked
on Rogers chicken,
I'm back in there
with the red menace.
[♪]
IPSWICH:
Miss Benes, the hat you charged to the company was sable.
This is nutria.
W-- Well, that's a, um--
It's a kind of sable.
No, it's a kind of rat.
That's a rat hat?
And a poorly made one,
even by rat-hat standards.
I have no choice
but to recommended
your prompt termination
to the board of directors.
Nothing short of the approval
of Peterman himself
will save you this time.
But-- But he's in
the Burmese jungle.
And quite mad too,
from what I hear.
Wait a minute.
Can I fire you?
No.
[♪]
KRAMER:
So Heather called?
Yeah, but get this.
The message said,
"Call me if you have the time."
[CHUCKLES]
If I have the time? You get it?
No, but is this all
very exciting.
She knows that I have her clock.
I know that she has my hat.
I think she's getting ready
to make an exchange.
Well, there is the possibility
that you've gone right out
of your mind.
I've looked at that.
It seems unlikely.
Well, I'd look again.
So how come you didn't call
Jerry about all this?
Jerry. I can't talk
to Jerry anymore.
Ever since he moved into
that apartment, he's too much...
like you.
Mm.
That's a shame.
[♪]
Seth, you're the manager.
Can't you turn off that sign?
Jerry, I lied.
I'm just an assistant manager.
Number 67,
family feast.
Number 67. Right here.
Right here.
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry.
And don't forget
your steamed broccoli.
Hold it.
Broccoli?
Newman, you wouldn't
eat broccoli
if it was deep-fried
in chocolate sauce.
I love...broccoli.
It's...good for you.
Really?
Then maybe
you'd like to have a piece.
Gladly.
[RETCHES]
Vile weed!
It's for Kramer, isn't it?
I knew it.
The greasy doorknob.
The constant licking of the fingers.
He's hooked on the chicken,
isn't he?
Yes! Yes, now, please,
someone, honey mustard.
[COUGHS]
[♪]
Newman, what took you--
Hey, buddy.
That was good.
Expecting Newman?
That's funny,
because I just
happened upon him
down at the
Kenny Rogers Roasters.
[SCOFFS]
Oh, Kenny Rogers.
Oh, boy, I hate that place.
He was buying
quite a load of chicken,
almost enough for two people.
Oh.
As long as one of them's
not him.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah.
Oh, hey, you know,
Elaine, she stopped by.
Yeah, dropped off
that Bob Sacamano hat.
Yeah, oh, she's upset with him.
Yes, sirree.
Yeah, well,
thanks for stoppin' by.
I sure do miss my apartment.
Maybe I'll switch back.
Oh, you don't wanna
think about that.
No, sir.
Otherwise, I'd have no choice
but to put that banner back up
and, uh, yeah,
run that Rogers
right out of town.
I don't think you will.
As a matter of fact,
I'll save you the trouble.
I'll do it myself.
Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
Put the banner up.
Doesn't matter to me.
All right.
No, Jerry.
I need that chicken!
I gotta have that ch--
Now, you leave
those roasters alone!
Kenny never hurt anybody!
You got a little problem.
Oh, I got a big problem, Jerry!
[♪]
Here. Kneel here.
What?
Kneel.
Kneel? Okay.
[WATER SPLASHING]
Elaine.
Mr. Peterman.
[SPEAKING IN FAKE FOREIGN
DIALECT]
You speak Burmese?
No, Elaine, that was gibberish.
Ah.
So did you have any
trouble finding the place?
No, you're the only...
white-poet-warlord
in the neighborhood.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you an assassin?
I work for your mail-order
catalog.
You're an errand girl
sent by grocery clerks
to collect a bill.
Well, actually, um,
I do have a bill here.
If you could just sign
this expense form,
I think I could still make
the last fan boat out of here.
I'd be happy to, Elaine.
Ah. Here.
But I will have to see
this hat.
Right.
[♪]
So how do you want to do this?
All right, George,
I'll be honest.
The first time we went out,
I found you very irritating.
But after seeing you
a couple of times,
you sort of got stuck
in my head.
♪ Costanza ♪
[GIGGLES]
So you--
You really don't have my hat?
What?
Uh, let's go do somethin'.
What's in the bag?
Oh, That's--
That's a sandwich.
[ALARM RINGING]
Uh...
Damn salami.
My clock.
[ALARM STOPS]
You stole it?
That damn delicatessen.
That is the last time
they screw up one of my orders.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[SIGHS]
Hey, Seth.
Man, it is coming down
hard out there.
Oh, gross.
That's not gonna be
good for business.
good for anybody.
[♪]
[SIGN BUZZING]
[SIGN CLICKS, POWERS DOWN]
Kenny?
[♪]
Kenny.
JERRY:
Home at last.
Ah.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Is someone there?
[FEET PATTERING]
[WHISPERS]
Mr. Marbles.
This is the urban sombrero.
I put it
on the last catalog cover.
[WATER DRIPPING]
[WHISPERS]
The horror.