[♪]
All right,
how 'bout this one?
Let's say you're
abducted by aliens. Fine.
They haul you aboard
the mother ship,
take you back to their planet
as a curiosity.
Now, would you rather be
in their zoo or their circus?
I gotta go zoo.
I feel like I could set
more of my own schedule.
In the circus, you get
to ride around on the train,
see the whole planet.
I'm wearing a little hat.
I'm jumping through fire.
Putting their little
alien heads in my mouth.
At least it's show business.
Yeah.
But in the zoo, you know,
they might put
a woman in there with me
to, uh, you know,
get me to mate.
What if she's got
no interest in you?
Well, then I'm pretty much
where I am right now.
Just got to take a ride
on a spaceship.
[♪]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
George, why couldn't I use
the bathroom in that store?
Kramer, trust me, this is
the best bathroom in midtown.
[WHIMPERS]
He knows.
It's right in there,
on the left.
Exquisite marble,
high ceilings,
and a flush
like a jet engine.
[WHOOSHES]
Now, listen, um,
you better not wait.
I'll catch you later.
You sure?
He knows.
Wow.
Nice.
Why don't you try
your engagement story?
Won't work.
Are you sure?
He knows.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Look, Kevin,
I really like you--
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
--but, um,
maybe we'd be better off
just being...friends.
Friends?
Yeah. I mean--
Oh, God.
This tuna tastes
like an old sponge.
Friends. Yeah.
Why not friends?
I might like to try that.
Like you and Jerry.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
KRAMER:
Whew!
This damn thing
is jammed again!
You know
what happens with these?
The rollers,
they get flat spots on 'em.
[BEEPING]
Huh?
Hey, Leland wants everyone in
the conference room right now.
Come on, let's go.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay.
ELAINE:
Remember I was telling you about Gillian,
my friend who writes
for the L.L. Bean catalog.
I really think
you should give her a call.
I don't know,
do you have it--?
Not bad.
Wha--? What does she--?
I put her stats on the back.
Pretty impressive.
Serious boyfriend, '92 to '95.
Uh-huh.
Owns her own car.
Yup.
Favorite president,
James Polk. Hmm.
Let me see that.
So how'd it go
with Kevin?
Did you steel-toe
his ass back to Kentucky?
You are not gonna
believe this.
I told him that I just
wanted to be friends.
He's fine with it.
He really wants
to be friends.
Why would anybody
want a friend?
[GROANS]
It's really not
that bad, actually.
He said he'd go with me
to the Museum of Miniatures.
This is something
you would never, ever do.
I mean, all that stuff
is so small.
Stupid.
You know, if I told
my engagement story
to that receptionist,
but told her
this was my fiancée...
What?
Don't you see?
Women like that
are like members
of a secret tribe
living in a forbidden city.
People like me have not been
inside in thousands of years.
But with this,
it's like I've already been
with one of her own.
My hand's been stamped.
I come and go as I please.
Well, you've cracked it.
I warned the queen
you were getting close,
and now it looks like
we're gonna have to move
the whole damn
forbidden city.
Can I keep this?
No, I need it.
Thanks.
[♪]
Hi. I'm, uh--
I'm here to see
a Mr. Art Vandelay.
I'm sorry, sir,
there is no Mr. Vandelay here.
Well, let me-- Heh.
Let me just, uh,
check and make sure
I have the right name.
Ha, ha, ha.
I seem to-- Oh, I--
Oh.
Oh, she's beautiful.
Who is she?
Well, if you must know,
she was my fiancée, Susan.
May she rest in peace.
I am so sorry.
She was lovely.
I'm Amanda.
I'm George.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Good work today, K-Man.
Well, you know
what they say:
You don't sell the steak,
you sell the sizzle.
[LAUGHS]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
In that case,
make mine a double.
[♪]
WOMAN:
Jerry?
Gillian. Hi.
It's very nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
She had man-hands.
Man-hands?
The hands of a man.
It's like a creature
out of Greek mythology.
Oh.
I mean, she was, like, part woman,
part horrible beast.
Would you prefer it
if she had no hands at all?
Would she have hooks?
Do, uh...
Do hooks make it
more attractive, Jerry?
Kind of cool-lookin'.
Okay, listen,
you're picking me up
from White Plains
tomorrow, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, I got five
huge boxes of buttons.
Well, if you need
an extra set of hands,
I know who you can call.
Jerry!
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
Kramer?
Hey, buddy. Hey.
It's 8:00 in the morning.
What the hell is going on?
Breakfast.
I gotta be in
at Brandt-Leland by 9.
Why?
Because I'm working there,
that's why.
How long
have I been asleep?
What--?
What year is it?
Look, Jerry, I don't know
if you've noticed,
but lately I've been
drifting aimlessly.
Now that you mention it...
But I finally realized
what's missing in my life.
Structure.
And at Brandt-Leland,
I'm getting things done.
And I love the people
I'm working with.
How much are they paying?
No, no, no, no.
I don't want any pay.
I'm doing this just for me.
Clearly.
So, uh, what do you do
down there all day?
TCB.
You know,
taking care of business.
Ah! I gotta go.
All right, then.
I'll see you tonight, huh.
Forget my briefcase.
Well, what do
you got in there?
Crackers.
[SHEENA EASTON'S "MORNING TRAIN
(NINE TO FIVE)" PLAYING]
♪ And then
He takes another home again ♪
♪ To find me waiting for him ♪
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ My baby takes
The morning train ♪
♪ He works from 9 till 5
And then ♪
♪He takes another home again ♪
♪ To find me waiting for him ♪
♪ He takes me to a movie
Or to a restaurant ♪
I'm gonna go that way!
[ALL LAUGHING]
JERRY:
So the picture worked. Amazing!
Hey, she wants me
to dress, uh, smart casual.
What, uh--?
What is that?
I don't know,
but you don't have it.
Right. Bye.
Where were you today?
What?
Pick up.
Damn.
So? Where were you?
Uh, here, I guess.
And, uh, I went out
and picked up a paper.
I had to ask Kevin...
to leave his office
and come and pick me up.
Well, what are friends for?
Yes.
And he is a friend, Jerry.
He's reliable,
he's considerate.
He's like your...
exact opposite.
So he's Bizarro Jerry.
Bizarro Jerry?
Yeah, like Bizarro Superman.
Superman's exact opposite,
who lives in the backwards
Bizarro World.
Up is down, down is up.
He says hello when he leaves,
goodbye when he arrives.
Shouldn't he say "badbye"?
Isn't that the opposite
of goodbye?
No, it's still goodbye.
Does he live underwater?
No.
Is he black?
Look, just forget
the whole thing, all right?
[SIGHS]
Wow, man.
What a day.
Could I use a drink.
Tough day
at the office?
People kept coming in,
and that phone
just wouldn't stop.
[EXHALES]
Well, we better get going
if we're gonna go
to that, uh, 7:00
Hall of Fusion.
Yeah, well,
count me out.
I'm swimming in it.
Old man Leland
is busting my hump
over these reports.
If I don't get 'em done
by 9, I'm toast.
[COUGHS]
All right,
I have to go.
Whew.
Oh, and, uh, listen.
Uh, could you keep it down
to a low roar?
Some of us have to work
in the morning. Thanks.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
GEORGE:
This is a fantastic place.
I always thought
it was a meat-packing plant.
Hey, Amanda.
These are my friends.
Annabell, Justina and Mickey.
We used to model together.
Oh, modeling.
What's that like, fun?
[CHUCKLES]
GEORGE:
Stupid. Stupid. Stupid!
So, Mickey,
how was Paris this time?
A bore.
You know who used
to love Paris?
My, uh,
dead fiancée, Susan.
In fact, I think
I may have a picture of her.
Wow.
She was beautiful.
Do you wanna dance?
Would you like
some bread, Jerry?
No. No, thanks,
I'm just not hungry.
Well, then,
at least drink your beer.
[SQUEAKS]
[SOFTLY]
It's not a twist-off.
You have a little something
on your face.
I can get it.
No, no. No, no.
You're missing it.
It's higher.
It's an eyelash. Make a wish.
I don't want to.
Make a wish.
Okay.
Didn't come true.
Don't you just love lobster?
[♪]
KEVIN:
That Museum of Miniatures was amazing.
I know, it was so tiny.
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
Elaine, sit down.
These are a couple
of my friends.
This is Gene,
and this guy
we just call Feldman.
Bizarro World.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Jerry, it was incredible!
Models as far
as the eye could see.
Then it does exist.
Yes, the legends are true.
When are you going out
with this girl again?
I'm not.
I'm inside the walls.
So you're gonna burn
that bridge.
Flame on!
So when are we going?
Well, it's...
It's a pretty
fast-paced crowd.
What would you wear?
That?
You know, I'm the one
who's actually dating
the woman
in the picture.
Yeah.
But I was engaged to her.
I got it.
You got it last time.
Don't worry
about it.
This is unbelievable.
Say, Elaine.
What do you think
of an alarm clock
that automatically tells you
the weather when you wake up?
Well, I gotta say,
I think that
that is a fantastic idea,
Feldman.
Nah, I-- I don't--
It's not practical.
Well, see you later,
Elaine.
Feldman and I gotta get
down to the library.
What are you gonna do
down there?
Read.
Hello.
[♪]
So, uh, Gillian's
coming over later.
I'm gonna end it.
Uh-huh.
Those meaty paws.
I feel like I'm dating
George "The Animal" Steele.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll chain her
to the refrigerator
and sell tickets.
That's nice.
Kramer, put the paper down.
You never listen
to me anymore.
We hardly even talk.
Well, we're talking now,
aren't we?
I see you for 20 lousy
minutes in the morning.
Here we go.
And when you come home
at night,
you're always exhausted.
We never do anything
anymore.
What are you starting
with me for?
You know this is
my crazy time of year.
It's your third day.
I gotta go to work.
We'll talk about this later.
Well...
Call if you're gonna be late!
What?
What is going on
with you two?
Oh, I don't wanna
talk about it.
All right, listen.
Have you seen my addre--?
Ah, there it is.
Okay. I got it.
I'll see you later.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait a second.
Where you going?
I hardly ever see you anymore.
Well, I--
I guess I've been at Reggies.
The Bizarro coffee shop?
Kevin and his friends
are nice people.
They do good things.
They read.
I read.
Books, Jerry.
Oh.
Big deal.
I can't spend
the rest of my life
coming into this
stinking apartment
every 10 minutes
to pore over
the excruciating minutiae
of every single daily event.
Why not? Like yesterday,
I went to the bank
to make a deposit,
and the teller
gives me this look--
I'll see you later, man.
I gotta go.
The whole system
is breaking down!
[♪]
[HAIR DRYER BLOWING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Amanda, hi, yeah.
Listen, you know,
I'm thinking we might just
be better off
being friends.
Yeah. Yeah. You know what?
I can't even really talk
about it right now.
Bye-bye.
No. No!
Friends? Just friends.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, do you still wanna
see a movie later?
I wish I could,
but we're friends.
I'm just gonna go wash
my hands.
Good idea.
[PHONE RINGS]
There's a beach towel
on the rack.
Yeah.
Jerry!
Jerry, my--
My hair dryer
ruined the picture.
Now I need one
or I can't get back
into the forbidden city.
Who is this?
Jerry! I need you to get
another picture of man-hands.
I'm begging you.
If I get it for you,
will you take me to that club
and show me a good time?
Yes, yes, all right.
Anything.
Okay.
[WATER RUNNING]
Got it.
[WHIMPERING]
[♪]
Jerry.
Hey, Jerry?
I'm right here.
Oh, hey.
You're late.
Yeah, well,
I got held up, you know.
What happened to your hand?
Like you care.
Work piled up,
I lost track of the time.
Oh, sure, sure.
You and your work.
Elaine's off
in the Bizarro World,
George only calls
when he wants something,
and I'm left sitting here
like this plate of cold chicken.
Which, by the way...
[CLATTERS]
...was for two.
What, you cooked?
I ordered in.
It's still effort.
Oh, jeez.
What's wrong?
It's my stomach.
You're probably
getting an ulcer.
This job is killing you.
It's killing us.
You know what?
You're right.
These reports, they can wait
a couple of hours.
What do you say
we go out tonight?
Any place you want.
The coffee shop?
You got it, buddy.
I'll call George.
[♪]
Hey, isn't
that Elaine?
Maybe she can get me
a picture of man-hands.
Elaine!
GEORGE: Laney!
KRAMER:Elaine!
JERRY: Elaine?
KEVIN: Hey, Elaine.
Hi. Over here.
[♪]
Jerry, George, Kramer,
this is Kevin,
Gene and Feldman.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Nice to meet you.
This is
really weird.
Uh, could you guys excuse us
just for a moment?
Sure.
Thanks.
What? What do you guys want?
Elaine, I've got to have
another picture of Gillian.
I tried to get him one,
but man-hands almost ripped
my arm out of the socket.
You could have gotten one.
I could not.
[GROANS]
Guys...
I gotta go.
Take it easy.
Elaine?
Can I come?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
We've already got a George.
[♪]
KRAMER:
What did you wanna see me about, Mr. Leland?
Kramer, I've been reviewing
your work.
Quite frankly, it stinks.
Well, I, uh...
I've been having trouble
at home, and, uh...
I mean, uh, you know,
I'll work harder.
Nights, weekends,
whatever it takes.
No. No, I don't think
that's going to do it, uh...
These reports you handed in,
it's almost as if you have
no business training at all.
I don't know
what this is supposed to be.
Well, I'm, uh...
Just trying to get ahead.
Well, I'm sorry.
There's just no way
that we could keep you on.
But I don't even
really work here.
That's what makes this
so difficult.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, I'm George.
Are you sure
you're supposed to be here?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I used to come here
all the time with my fiancée
back when it was
a meat-packing plant.
Here's her picture.
What'd you do? Cut this out
of a magazine or something?
What?
That's me.
It's from a Clinique ad I did.
[CHUCKLES]
Look at that.
Let's go. Private party.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
ELAINE:
It's Laney.
Hi, Elaine.
Hi, Kevin. Oh!
Oh-ho.
Ohhh.
Come on in.
Okay.
Hi, Gene.
What's up?
Just reading.
Aah.
Hey, what are you doing?
Eatin' olives.
Ever hear of asking?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Who is it?
Feldman,
from across the hall.
Hold on.
Hey.
Hey, Kevin.
Hi.
Look who I ran into.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Kevin.
Hello, Vargas.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Wanna catch a ball game
this weekend?
Great.
Okay, great.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Vargas.
Well...I got 'em.
All right!
Hey, Elaine,
Feldman was able
to get us all tickets
to the Bolshoi.
[GASPS]
Fourth row,
center.
Get out!
Aah!
What's the matter
with you?
Oh, Kevin.
I'm so sorry.
Is there anything
I can do?
Haven't you done enough
already?
I'll just...
It's--
It's locked.
[♪]
So this is it, huh?
But it was--
It was here, I'm telling you.
It wi-wi--
It was really here.
There--
There was a bar and a--
And a dance floor.
I guess the DJ booth
was over there
behind the bone saw?
Let's get
out of here, George.
[♪]
At work today, I discovered
there's a pay phone
in the lobby
that has free long distance.
Oh, so, what did you do?
I called the phone company
and immediately reported
the error.
Nice.
[DOORBELL RINGS,
KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Who is it?
Feldman,
from across the hall.
Hold on.
Kevin.
Brought you some groceries.
Again?
Feldman, you didn't have
to do that.
Hey, what are friends for?
You know,
I may not say this enough,
but you two are
about the best friends
a guy could have.
Oh...
Me so happy.
Me want to cry.
[♪]