[♪]
MAN:
Well,
if the big man wants
a new scoreboard,
I don't wanna be the one
to tell him no.
No one in the park is gonna be
able to see it from there.
Well, why don't we just put
a monitor in the skybox?
Hey, George...
the ocean called.
They're running outta shrimp.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪]
[MUTTERING]
"The ocean called.
They're running out
of shrimp."
Got your shrimp.
Oh, yes!
That's what I should
have said!
Damn it!
[♪]
JERRY:
"The ocean called.
They're running
out of shrimp"?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
but then I said
to him:
"Oh, yeah? Well,
the jerk store called,
and they're runnin'
outta you."
Really? That's great.
[CHUCKLING]
You said that to him?
Well, actually, I-- I thought it
up on the way over here.
Oh, that's not quite the same.
No, no, it's not.
You don't know this guy.
It would have been so sweet.
I'm gonna grab a can of balls.
All right.
[EASTERN EUROPEAN ACCENT]
Hello. My name is Milos.
How can I help you?
I need a can of balls.
A can of balls
for the nice guy.
All right-- Uh...
You don't plan to hit these
balls with that racket, do you?
[♪]
Checking out the staff picks,
Miss Benes?
Oh, ha-ha, hey.
Yeah, yeah.
This Vincent guy,
he is the best.
He and I have
the exact same taste in movies.
Well,
Vincent is an art-house goon.
I stick to the Gene rack.
Gene? Oh, he's so stupid
and mainstream.
I've seen all of these,
so I went with the Kramer pick.
The Other Side of Darkness.
Huh, I never heard
of that one.
Yeah, it went straight
to video.
That makes me the premiere.
[♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
KRAMER:
Jerry? You ever seen the movie
The Other Side of Darkness?
JERRY: No.
It's about this woman
in a coma.
Well, I couldn't finish
watchin' it, so...
I want you to read this.
"I, Cosmo Kramer,
"having just seen the movie
The Other Side of Darkness
"and not wanting to be in a coma
like that lady in the movie,
"hereby want Jerry Seinfeld
to remove my life support,
"feeding machine, lung blower,
Mm-hm.
et cetera, et cetera,
et cetera."
Can you do that for me,
buddy?
Well, I don't know if what
you have here constitutes
a legally binding document.
Well,
I'm gonna type it up.
Yes, well, of course,
but even so,
you may wanna talk
to a lawyer.
Yeah, well,
Jackie Chiles,
he put a restraining order
on me.
I'm not allowed within 200 feet
of his office.
I couldn't even give him
his Christmas present.
Oh, hey,
new racket, huh?
Yeah, I wasn't
gonna get it,
but this guy, Milos,
who runs the pro shop,
he really recommended it.
In fact, it's the only racket
he plays with.
Uh, you're not gonna need
this anymore.
Hey, this is the Z page
of my address book.
Oh, yeah,
I put all your Z's
on the weights-and-measures
page.
Pfoof!
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING
OVER TV]
[SOBBING]
[SIGHING]
Oh.
Oh, bravo, Vincent.
[SNIFFLES]
Bravo.
[PHONE RINGS]
[BEEPS]
What?
MAN [OVER PHONE]:
Did you enjoy the movie?
Who is this?
It's Vincent.
Of Vincent's picks?
The same.
[♪]
JERRY:
He called you?
He must have gotten my number
off the computer.
We ended up talking
for like two hours.
To a guy you've never met?
Mm.
Your screening process
is getting ever more rigorous.
I'm trying
to meet him.
He's never
at the video store.
Ahem, they said he sets
his own hours.
MAN:
Little help!
Hey.
Yeah.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, my God, that guy is terrible.
Mm-hm.
Hey, how come we played
at this crummy place
instead of your club?
George used up
all my guest passes already.
Oh.
[MAN GRUNTS]
Come on.
MAN: Thank you.
[PANTING]
Here you go.
Milos?
Oh, hey.
How you doin'?
Okay.
Uh, we should, uh,
wrap it up here.
[CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY]
[♪]
ELAINE:
So he was bad.
What do you care?
Elaine, I paid $200
for this racket,
'cause he said it's
the only one he plays with.
He could have played
just as well with a log.
Hey.
All right, I, uh--
I talked to this lawyer,
Shellbach.
Now, he's gonna set me up,
but you gotta come with me
to be the executor.
The executor of what?
Kramer wants to die
with dignity.
There's a feather in your cap.
I don't wanna be a vegetable,
Elaine. I just want out.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Sometimes in life,
the gods smile upon you,
my friends.
Did you get someone to take
that Canadian quarter?
I got another meeting
with Reilly.
A whole new audience,
and I bet I can get him
to try that line again.
Who's Reilly?
George was scarfing shrimp
at this meeting,
and this guy says:
"Hey, George,
the ocean called.
They're runnin'
outta shrimp."
[LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
Think that's funny?
Listen to the comeback:
"Oh, yeah?
Well, the jerk store called.
They're runnin'
out of you."
[CHUCKLES]
What? You gotta
be kidding me.
How 'bout this one?
How 'bout:
"Your cranium called.
It's got some space to rent."
[CHUCKLES]
It's good.
What does that mean?
Hey, here you go:
"Hey, Reilly, the zoo called.
You're due back by 6."
No.
No, no, no,
you're not helpin' me.
Look,
just tell him you had sex
with his wife.
That'll get him.
I'm not lookin'
for another line!
I got the line!
Look, George,
just think about it, you know?
You're married,
how would you feel
if somebody says to you
that they had sex--?
All right!
You see?
This is why I hate writing
with a large group.
Everybody has their own
little opinions,
and it all
gets homogenized,
and you lose the whole
edge of it!
I'm goin'
with "jerk store."
"Jerk store"
is the line.
Jerk store.
Yes.
Why?
Did you take this out
of the garbage?
It's still got some spring
in the strings.
Oh, Jerry,
this is a piece of junk.
How are you gonna be
the executor of my living will?
You-- You see,
you can't let go.
Trust me, Kramer,
given the legal opportunity,
I will kill you.
I wish
I could believe you.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Hey, Elaine, do you have some
free time tomorrow afternoon?
Me?
Yeah, because you're perfect.
You're a calculating,
cold-hearted businesswoman.
And when there's dirty work
to be done,
you don't mind stompin'
on a few throats.
[GIGGLING]
Oh, come on.
[♪]
MAN:
Situation number four:
You're breathing
on your own,
you're conscious,
but with no muscular function.
Well, would I be able
to communicate?
I don't see how.
Ach, I don't like
the sound of this one.
Yeah. Yeah,
let's pull the cord, huh?
Yank it like
you're startin' a mower.
Moving on.
You have liver, kidneys
and gallbladder,
but no central nervous system.
Well, I gotta have
a central nervous system.
Okay.
One lung, blind,
and you're eating
through a tube.
Nah, that's not my style.
Boring.
All right. You can eat,
but machines do everything else.
Hm.
Uh--
[SOFTLY]
What? I'd stick.
Yeah, yeah, stick,
'cause I could still go
to the coffee shop.
That's right.
[♪]
Hello, Milos.
Jerry.
Thank God
you got my message.
Thank you so much
for coming down here.
Um, listen--
You know, I spent $200
on a racket
because I thought you knew
what you were talkin' about.
I--
You can't even play.
Believe me,
it is Milos' great shame,
but, Jerry, I could lose
my business if anybody find out.
How would you like
extra year membership
on the club?
Free. No charge.
You could do that?
Jerry, for you,
anything. Heh.
Game, set and match, huh, Milos?
Uh, Jerry,
I'm so sorry.
They tell me there is no way
they can do it.
Um, is there anything else
I could do for you?
Anything at all?
I-- I--
I refund your money.
You know what, Milos, I don't
even care about the money.
I just feel like I was taken
by the worst tennis player--
Shh! Shh! Shh!
[WHISPERING]
I-- I make it up to you.
Yeah, you make it up to me.
Tennis, anyone?
[GIGGLES]
[♪]
ELAINE:
Oh.
This is the one
Vincent told me about.
The Pain
and the Yearning.
"An old woman experiences
pain and yearning."
A hundred
and ninety-two minutes?
[WHISTLES]
That's a lot of yearning, huh?
Yeah.
You know,
these movies are great,
but they are just
so emotionally exhausting.
Yeah, well,
what you need
is some summertime
adolescent high jinks.
Really?
Let's see
what Dr. Gene prescribes, huh?
Oh, here.
Yeah, Weekend at Bernie's II.
Now, that's an hilarious
premise. Huh.
Well--
Yeah, get it.
Yeah, I could use a chuckle.
Huh? Yeah.
What are you gettin'?
Uh, nothin'.
I'm gonna finish watching
The Other Side of Darkness.
Oh.
How much you got left?
Yeah, about two hours.
Oh, yeah, she shot
in that coma pretty quick.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[♪]
Bernie is dead, you morons.
Just because he's wearing
sunglasses, he looks alive?
Ugh.
How long is this weekend,
anyway?
Ugh.
[RINGS]
[BEEPS]
Hello?
VINCENT [OVER PHONE]:
How's the movie, Elaine?
Vincent?
A Gene pick. How could you?
I thought
we had something special.
No, i-it doesn't mean anything.
I-- I'm not
even gonna rewind it.
[DIAL TONE]
Vincent?
[♪]
MAN:
All right.
Let's get to it.
Wa-- Wait a minute.
What--? What about Reilly?
Reilly doesn't
work here anymore.
What? I--
I didn't hear about that.
Well, we only wake you up
for the important meetings.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪]
[EASTERN EUROPEAN ACCENT]
Hello.
Didn't I see you
at the pro shop yesterday?
I think so. I'm Patty.
Milos gave me your address.
I hope you don't mind me
waiting for you here.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, that Milos.
Well, what should we do?
Um, care for a cup of coffee?
Why don't we just go up
to your apartment?
All right.
Gotta be an easier way.
WOMAN [OVER TV]:
Doctor, how's her coma?
MAN:
Oh, exactly the same.
Wait a minute.
She's coming out of the coma.
Mrs. Albright, can you hear me?
Are you okay?
ALBRIGHT:
I feel so rested and refreshed.
Get me a toothbrush.
[♪]
So you play tennis?
Enough talk, Jerry.
Not for me.
I love chatting.
Oh, shh.
No!
No, I can't do this.
I can't go through with this.
Not even for him.
Who?
[SOBBING]
Milos, my husband.
Your husband?
[♪]
GEORGE:
And so concerned
was he that word of his poor
tennis skills might leak out,
he chose to offer
you his wife
as some sort of medieval
sexual payola.
He's new around here.
So...details.
Well, I didn't sleep with her.
Because of society, right?
Yes, George,
because of society.
So how did the big meeting
turn out?
Reilly is no longer
with the club.
You believe that?
Ah, you're better off.
Now you can just let it go.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm gonna let it go.
You never really had
the right comeback, anyway.
Are you insane?
"Jerk store" would have
smoked that guy!
Smoked him, I say!
Hey, oh, Jerry,
listen, uh...
You know, I saw the rest
of that movie,
The Other Side
of Darkness.
The coma lady wakes up
at the end.
Oh, I wanted to see that.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
I didn't know it was possible
to come out of a coma.
not to know that.
GEORGE:
How was Eric Roberts as the husband?
Oh, unforgettable.
Oh!
I gotta find Elaine.
You know,
she's gonna pull my plug.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[♪]
What?
Betrayed?
Oh, Vincent,
I'm so sorry, I--
Hey, hey, listen, uh,
Elaine,
I've changed my mind
about the whole coma thing.
Yeah, I decided
I'm up for it.
Kramer, do you have any idea
what you've done?
Excuse me.
What are you doin'?
Wha--?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Vincent stopped making picks.
Well, how am I gonna know
what movies to see?
We have a wide variety
of Gene picks.
Gene's trash.
I'm Gene.
Hi.
[♪]
JERRY:
Milos, I can assure you,
I had no intention
of telling anyone
about your unbelievably
bad tennis playing.
Thank you,
but unfortunately,
I have much larger problems
to fry.
My wife, she has no respect
for Milos anymore.
I guess
that's a risk you run
when you dabble
in the flesh trade.
Patty, she-- She loves tennis
as much like I do.
W-would you--? Will you
let me beat you in tennis?
That is the only way
that I c-can show her
that I'm still a man.
Well, I'll do it as long as
there's no other girls around.
I mean,
I wanna be a man too.
[♪]
JERRY:
So you hurt Vincent's feelings?
Look what came
in the mail today.
What's this?
It's the play button
off his VCR.
Boy, look how far back
it goes.
It's like a tooth.
So guess where
Mr. Ocean Phone turned up.
He's workin' for Firestone
in Akron, Ohio.
Ohio?
Yup.
I'm leavin' first thing
tomorrow mornin'.
You're flying to Akron
just to zing a guy?
Don't you understand?
It's not about him.
To have a line as perfect
as "jerk store"
and to never use it.
I-I couldn't live with myself.
See,
there are no jerk stores.
It's-- It's just
a little confusing, is all.
It's smart.
It's a smart line,
and a smart crowd
will appreciate it.
And I'm not gonna dumb it down
for some bonehead mass audience!
Not you.
[♪]
WOMAN [OVER TV]:
Oh, brittle bones.
How I long to be rid
of the pain.
[PHONE RINGS]
[BEEPS]
Hello.
Elaine, it's Vincent.
Vincent. Where are you?
I have to meet you.
No, I can't bear
to have anyone see me.
Vincent, listen, I won't judge
you the way everyone else does.
You're-- You're strange
and beautiful and sensitive.
Now, let's have a look at ya.
All right.
But can you bring me
a few things from the store?
I haven't been out
in a while.
[HORNS HONKING]
Well, go around,
you bunch of crazies.
Maniacs are gonna get us
all killed.
[♪]
WOMAN:
Hi, can I help you?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I'm Cosmo Kramer.
Yeah, I had an appointment
to annul my living will.
Oh, Mr. Kramer,
Yeah.
you had a 10:30 appointment.
It's 2:00.
W--
Mr. Shellbach
had a tennis lesson.
Wha--?
He's gone for the day.
[♪]
Too good.
Another game for Milos!
[LAUGHING]
You're on fire today.
Hey, Patty,
look at this guy.
He's awful.
[MILOS LAUGHING]
He's not a man,
this Jerry.
He's not even married
like I am.
Hey, uh, Milos, I don't mind
rollin' over here,
but could you lighten up
on the "not a man" stuff?
Hey, everybody, look!
The little chicken girl
wants me to ease up.
He can't handle this.
He cries like a woman.
[LAUGHING]
[♪]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hello? Vincent?
Elaine?
I got what you asked.
Just leave it
and go.
Well--?
Well, can I come in?
No, go away, now.
No, no, Vincent, I...
Oh, don't shut me out.
I-- I just-- I know
you feel what I feel. I--
Excuse me,
can I help you?
VINCENT:
Oh, damn it.
Uh-- Um, I'm here
to see Vincent.
Well, I'm his mother.
Vincent, what's goin' on here?
No, my acne!
Acne?
What do you have here?
Vodka, cigarettes, fireworks.
What kind of a sick woman
brings this to a 15-year-old?
We have the same taste
in movies.
Did he send you part
of our VCR?
Here.
WOMAN:
Vincent!
[♪]
Look at the big baby.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, big baby,
are you wetting yourself?
Maybe it is time
for you to be changed.
[MILOS LAUGHING]
I told you to cut it out.
[GRUNTS]
[QUIETLY]
Come on, what are you doing?
[CHUCKLING]
The baby got lucky on that one.
Shellbach. Hey.
[GRUNTS]
Racket?
[GASPS]
[♪]
So, George...
you're proposing
a Snow Tire Day
at Yankee Stadium?
As long as they don't
throw them on the field, heh.
Help yourself to some shrimp.
I brought enough for everybody.
I have to say, this--
This proposal doesn't make
a whole lot of sense.
Well, you never know.
Let's see how many
I can fit in my mouth.
You know, George...
the ocean called.
They're running
outta shrimp.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, yeah, Reilly?
Well, the jerk store called.
They're runnin' outta you.
What's the difference?
You're their all-time
bestseller!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Yeah? Well, I had sex
with your wife.
[CHUCKLING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
His wife is in a coma.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
How's he doin'?
He's been sleepin' a lot.
He's still groggy.
Oh.
Well, I thought a movie
might cheer him up.
I got him a Gene pick.
What happened to Vincent?
I'm kind of...off of him.
Uh, outlet?
Ah.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
"My wife's in a coma."
Yeah? Well, the life-support
machine called, and...
Stupid.
Wait.
Yes!
That's what I should've said!
[YELLS]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
You're meat, Reilly!
You just screwed yourself!
[LAUGHING MANICALLY]
[♪]