You know at the movies
they show
that little ad
for the concession stand?
Where the cartoon
candy's dancing,
and the Milk Dud's
playing the banjo?
Oh, he's wailing
on that banjo. Yeah.
I just don't understand
the Raisinets.
The sax player?
Yeah.
The box of Raisinets runs up to the concession stand,
buys another box
of Raisinets.
So?
Box of Raisinets eating
another box of Raisinets?
It's perverse.
No. He's not gonna
eat them.
He's buying them for
his Pepsi girlfriend.
And why is
he dating a Pepsi?
They're not having
children.
They're
musicians.
Musicians.
Get a real job.
What do you want?
Oh, I've had everything
on the menu.
Uh...
surprise me.
Neil. Neil.
Oh. I am sorry.
I am supposed to
meet my boyfriend here.
He looks
just like you.
Really.
Yeah.
Like me?
Uh-huh. Sorry.
He-he.
Like me?
But how?
Here's your halibut
omelet.
Surprised?
Yes. Yes, I am.
KRAMER:
Look what I got for you for your Florida trip.
Crazy Shirts was
closing them out.
I got a dozen
for a buck.
I saved a fortune.
Look at that.
There
you go.
Oh.
"Number-one dad."
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
Ooh, and it's a medium. Perfect.
KRAMER:
Hey. Hey.
You ready?
Almost.
Okay, so look, uh,
when you're in Florida,
can my cigar guy
drop off some Cubans
for me at your parents'?
I'm helping my parents
move into their new condo.
I'm gonna be busy.
Oh, come on, man.
Help a brother out.
All right.
Yeah.
I owe you one.
We're even.
Hey, Jerry...
figure this out.
I'm in the coffee shop,
and this beautiful girl
I could never even talk to
mistakes me
for her boyfriend.
That's a nice four seconds.
I look just like him.
I, me...this.
This is what
her boyfriend looks like.
How is that possible?
Maybe he has money.
Maybe he doesn't.
Maybe he and I
are exactly the same,
except for one minor,
yet crucial, detail.
You never know.
Sometimes you do.
Maybe it's some--
Some small thing I could change.
Like a mustache
or, uh...
wearing a top hat.
Or a monocle.
Or a-- Or a cane.
Who's she dating?
Mr. Peanut?
You could do a lot worse
than Mr. Peanut, my friend.
So, what do
you wanna see?
How about
Sack Lunch?
The English Patient?
It's up for
all those Oscars.
Oh, Come on, Blaine.
I mean,
look at the poster
for Sack Lunch.
It's a family
in a brown paper bag.
Don't you wanna know
how they got in there?
[CHUCKLES]
No.
Oh.
Sold out.
Oh. Uh, two for
The English Patient.
So do you think
they got shrunk down,
or is it just
a giant sack?
Uh, hi.
Um, remember me?
I-I-- I'm the guy
that looks like Neil.
Hi.
Ahem.
Is Neil here?
Oh, no. He got
held up at work.
Oh, that's too bad.
I-- I kinda wanted to meet him,
seeing as we look so similar.
Huh. Well, you know, you don't
look that much like him.
Oh.
Of course not.
No, you're
a little taller.
You look like you're
in better shape than Neil.
Do you work out?
Listen, I--
I'm--
I-I don't mean
to seem forward,
but is-- Is there any way
that I could possibly
have Neil's phone number?
What is everyone
talking about?
"The English Patient,
it's so romantic"?
God, that movie
stunk.
I kinda liked it.
No, you didn't.
Elaine, Blaine.
Did you just see
The English Patient?
Didn't you
love it?
No.
How could you not
love that movie?
How about, it sucked.
That Ralph Fiennes.
I would give up
my firstborn for him.
Uh. He's getting
the short end of that stick.
Jerry, this is
Del Boca Vista's
new physical
fitness room.
They got
medicine balls.
You can bike ride.
Anything you want.
StairMaster?
What?
Nothing.
See what I'm wearing?
Oh. Did you get that
out of my bag?
No. Your mother found it.
Son...this is
the most wonderful
and thoughtful thing
you've ever done for me.
You know, I bought you
a Cadillac.
Twice.
Oh. Here he is.
This is the man
I wanted you to see.
Izzy Mandelbaum.
IZZY: Hey there.
He's 80 years old,
but strong as an ox.
Watch this.
[EXHALES]
See that?
You couldn't do that.
I could.
I choose not to.
Hey, Morty.
Who's this?
This is my son, Jerry,
from New York.
He thinks he can lift
more than Izzy.
I-I didn't
say that.
Hey, Izzy.
This kid says he can
lift more than you can.
Hey, your kid's
pretty funny, Morty.
He should be a comedian.
Actually, I am
a comedian.
That's not so funny.
You think you're better
than me, huh?
Izzy used to work out
with Charles Atlas in the '50s.
1850s?
Well, that's it.
It's go time.
Let's see you lift that.
Mr. Mandelbaum--
Come on, come on.
Pump it.
All right.
Eh. Wrong
attitude.
You're not bringing
that trash
into
my house.
There. All right?
Step aside,
string bean.
I'll show you.
I'm gonna take it up
a notch.
[CRACK]
Uh. My back.
[GROANING]
Somebody
call an ambulance.
There's already
an ambulance here
for Mrs. Glickman.
There's room
for one more.
Hey. One for
Sack Lunch.
It's good,
right?
Yeah. Good.
Hey, what are
you guys doing here?
We just saw
The English Patient again.
It's even better
the second time.
They make it longer?
Forgot
my umbrella.
Blaine.
Elaine.
You said you were
busy tonight.
Well, to tell you
the truth, Elaine...
I don't know if I can
be with someone
who doesn't like
The English Patient.
It's just a stupid movie.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Come on, Blaine.
Let's go.
Enjoy Sack Lunch.
I will.
HELEN:
How could you do that to Mr. Mandelbaum?
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
He egged me on.
You should be more mature.
He's 80.
Okay. Tomorrow Jerry and I
will visit Izzy and apologize.
Now, good night.
You're not sleeping
in that shirt.
It's too tight.
This shirt will never
leave my body.
Good night.
All right, 7:30,
got the place to myself.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Jerry Seinfeld,
please.
Oh, you must be
Kramer's guys. Come on in.
You got the cigars?
What cigars?
Kramer said to
bring him back some Cubans.
We are
the Cubans.
[CHOPPING VEGETABLE]
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah, hello.
Jerry's place.
They're real Cubans?
They're human beings
from Cuba?
I said Cubans.
What did you think I meant?
Cigars!
Jerry, Cuban cigars are
illegal in this country.
That's why I got
these guys.
You're making
your own cigars now?
Yeah, yeah. I got investors
all lined up.
Hold on a second.
Hi, Dad.
Who are they?
They're Cuban
cigar rollers.
Don't tell
your mother.
What is that
bubbling sound?
Are you making
your tomato sauce?
Yeah, hot and spicy.
You're not wearing
a shirt, are you?
Yes, I am.
What color is it?
Oh.
Damn it.
You know, you--
You could have
just given me
Neil's number.
You-- You didn't have to
take me out to dinner.
I wanted to give it
to you in person.
Oh.
You know, I don't have to
be up in the morning,
and I know a great
breakfast place
right around the corner.
Does Neil like to
eat a big breakfast?
Why don't you come in?
We'll talk about it.
I really should get going.
I-- I wanna be home
in case Neil calls.
Well...
good night.
I'll see you.
WAITRESS:
Rough night?
Ugh. You wouldn't
believe it.
My boyfriend
dumped me. Ugh.
My friends,
who I don't even like,
they won't talk to me,
all because I don't like
that stupid
English Patient movie.
Really? I thought
it was pretty good.
Oh, come on.
Good? What was
good about it?
Those sex scenes.
I mean, please.
Give me something
I can use.
Well, I liked it.
Hey.
You f-- You forgot
about my piece of pie.
Hello?
You know, sex in a tub...
that doesn't work.
This is quite
a condo.
The Mandelbaums own
the Magic Pan restaurants.
The crepe place?
Yeah. This is all
big crepe money.
There's crepe money?
What are you doing here?
Oh, Mr. Mandelbaum,
I wanted to come by
tell you how sorry I was
that you hurt yourself.
What the hell is that?
What?
That shirt.
You think that you
are the number-one dad?
This was a gift
from my son.
Oh, I see how it works now.
He knocks me
out of commission...
so you can strut around
in your fancy number-one shirt.
Well, I'll show you
who's number one.
Mr. Mandelbaum,
please.
It's go time.
[CRACK]
[MOANS]
My back.
I can't move.
Call an ambulance.
I think I saw one
a couple doors down.
JERRY:
So she wanted you to come up,
but you left
because you thought
some guy might be
calling you?
Some guy. Some guy?
Neil.
I have got to
find out how
he could get a girl
like Danielle.
George, you've
got Danielle.
Forget about Neil.
You've "out-Neiled" him.
So I'm Neil.
How did I do that?
I don't know,
but you better keep it up.
I'm gonna go meet
Danielle.
There's a new Neil
in town. Ha-ha.
[PHONE RINGING]
Try take
a vacation.
I come back, the whole
operation's in shambles.
Hello.
Hey, Jerry.
Number one here.
Did you go see Izzy
at the back specialist?
I will. I just
walked in the door.
You have to go see him.
Ma.
Helen, will you stop
bothering him?
Jerry, that shirt
has gone right to his head.
Number one,
signing off.
Jerry...
I just picked up the Cubans
at the bus station.
[DISTRESSED]
What's going on?
What?
They're not real Cubans.
They're Dominicans.
So?
So, Jerry, if my investors
don't get Cubans,
the whole deal's off.
What's the difference?
Jerry, once you've
had real Cubans,
there's just
nothing else like it.
We're talking
about people, right?
Yes. Yes. The quality,
the texture,
the intoxicating aroma.
These guys
don't have it.
I thought they smelled
pretty nice.
Jerry, your palate's
unrefined.
Is not.
Is too.
I'm not having
this conversation.
Are too.
Am not.
PETERMAN:
Another productive meeting.
By the way, I saw
that English Patient
film last night.
It was extraordinary.
Oh, yes.
It was so romantic.
It ravished me.
Elaine, what did you think?
Well, uh, act--
Actually
I haven't seen it,
so...
I couldn't tell you
whether I...
liked it,
or whether it really sucked.
You haven't seen it?
No.
That's it. Drop everything.
We're going right now.
JERRY:
Again, Mr. Mandelbaum,
this back specialist
is supposed to be the best.
If there's anything else
I can do,
don't hesitate to, uh,
try and find my number.
Uh-- Oh, wait.
How about that, huh?
The "World's Greatest Dad."
My son made it for me.
That's very nice.
The best in the world.
Which means I'm better
than just number one.
Well, I don't know
how official
any of these rankings
really are.
Hi, Son.
Hi, Daddy.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
This is your son?
I got married
in high school.
Hey, who are you?
This is
Seinfeld's kid.
Oh, you think
you're tough,
picking on
an old man?
Maybe you'd like to
try taking on
somebody
your own age.
Hm.
You got any kids?
Oh, you think
you're better than me?
Go ahead. Pick out
anything in the room here.
I'll lift it up
over my head.
Look. No one is
lifting anything.
The television.
Mm.
[CHUCKLES]
This one's for you, Pop.
It's go time.
[CRACK]
Oh. My back!
Call an ambulance!
We're already
in a hospital.
MAN:
All right, partner. Let's get down to business.
Okay. Well, I'll, uh-- I'll
get the Cubans. All right.
They're right out here.
[BABBLING
SPANISH]
Yeah, here they are.
They're Cubans.
Real Cubans.
You wouldn't be trying to sell
old Earl Haffler
Dominicans in a Cuban wrapper,
now, would you?
Oh, come on.
Look at these boys.
If they were
any more Cuban,
Castro would have
smoked them himself.
We're talking about
people, right?
I think so.
I thought he quit
smoking cigars.
Well, yeah. Yeah.
But they also rolled
for his brother...
uh, Dennis.
Dennis Castro?
Uh-- Uh, Dwayne.
Get the hell out
of my office.
What?!
You know,
Neil called me today.
Really?
Yeah, he's pretty upset
I broke up with him
to go out with you.
Well, I guess
I showed Neil who's Neil.
He wanted to get together
tomorrow and have coffee.
Coffee?
I can beat that.
Move in with me.
What?
It beats the hell
out of coffee.
[CHUCKLES
UNCOMFORTABLY]
And I thought
I knew what love was.
Yep.
JERRY:
You asked her to move in with you?
I gotta stay
one step ahead of Neil.
What if it's
Neil Armstrong?
Then I'm going to Mars.
What if it's Neil Diamond?
Oh, shut up, Jerry.
Just shut up.
All right, I gotta go back
to the hospital.
What? To see the old guy?
No, I got into a thing
with the son,
and now he's laid up too.
How old's the son?
I think he's the same age
as the father.
What is with this family?
Don't know. It's like,
if one of them dies,
the other one wants to
bench-press the casket.
Hey, Jerry.
[STUTTERING]
You cold?
No.
[STUTTERS]
It's them, right?
Something wrong
your chin? [STUTTERS]
There.
Where?
No, no, no. Don't look.
Don't look.
Over there.
The Dominicans.
Aren't they supposed to be
rolling cigars?
Well, it didn't
quite work out,
and now I've got nothing
for them to do.
So?
So I taught 'em
all about Cuba,
and they really
took to it.
You know, Marxism,
the workers' revolution,
the clothing.
Boy, they seem pretty angry
about something.
Yeah. I'm
a little worried.
When there's no work
and the people get restless,
who do you think
they come after?
El presidente.
[POUNDING
TABLE]
I swear to you,
I didn't know
the TV was bolted
to the table.
I bet you pulled
that trick
on my daddy
in Florida.
He couldn't handle
the weight.
Oh, so now you think
you're better than me?
You think you're
better than him?
Look, let me just state
for the record,
I think you're both
better than me.
Okay.
My boys.
My dad.
My grandpa.
Oh, come on.
[WHIMPERS]
What happened to him?
He was trying
to lift the TV.
That TV?
Oh, no.
It's go time.
[CRACK]
[MOANS]
Why didn't
anybody tell me
it was
bolted down?
Well, I still thought
you could do it.
Me too.
[IN UNISON]
Mandelbaum, Mandelbaum, Mandelbaum.
Fellas, fellas, fellas.
Look, I gotta go.
Oh, yeah,
that's right, go.
Put us all in the hospital.
And you ruined
our business
with all your macho
head games.
I didn't ruin
your business.
Yes, you did.
There's nobody there now
at the Magic Pan
to roll the crepes.
We gotta close it up.
Don't you hire people
to do that?
Each crepe has to be
hand-rolled
by a Mandelbaum.
That's what puts the magic
in Magic Pan.
So you just need some guys
that could roll them?
Yeah.
[SNAPS]
I think I can help you out.
I'll see you later.
Hey. I can't
see the TV.
Here.
You think you're better
than us, don't you?
Huh?
Elaine, I hope you're
watching the clothes
because I can't take my eyes
off the passion.
No.
No, I-- I can't
do this anymore.
I can't.
It's too long.
Quit telling
your stupid story
about the stupid desert
and just die already.
Die!
ALL:
Shh!
Elaine, you don't
like the movie?
I hate it!
ALL:
Shh!
Oh, go to hell!
Well, why didn't you
say so in the first place?
You're fired.
Great. I'll wait
for you outside.
JERRY:
He was gonna fire you?
Well, the only way
I could talk him out of it
was that I agreed to go
and visit the Tunisian desert.
Tunisia?
That's where
they filmed the movie.
It's supposed to
inspire me.
Well, that doesn't
sound so bad.
I have to live
in a cave.
Oh.
These Dominicans
really know
their way
around a crepe, huh?
Look at that.
Looks like they're
rolling a Double Corona.
Just a cigar made
out of Bisquick, huh, Guillermo?
I'm very happy
with George.
I'm sorry, Neil.
It's over.
Come on, let's just
eat our crepes.
Ah! My face!
Ooh!
Ah!
Neil!
What are they-- Why are
the crepes spraying?
Dominicans are
rolling them too tight.
Well. That's why
you gotta get real Cubans.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[MAN SCREAMS]
Danielle.
Where's Neil?
Is this him?
Yeah.
That blueberry crepe
burned him pretty badly.
Whose cane is this?
It's Neil's.
Cane.
I knew it.
So...
we meet at last.
I admire your skills...
Mr. Peanut.
Well, Danielle, uh,
we should get going.
I-- I got a key
made for you.
George, I can't
move in with you. What?
I'm sorry. But I'm taking
Neil to a clinic in England.
N-no. No.
You can't leave me.
Uh-- Marry me.
I'll burn myself.
I'll burn my parents!
Sorry, George.
George...
I win.
STEWARDESS:
Ladies and gentlemen, in just one moment
we'll be showing
our feature presentation...
No, no, no, no, no.
...the comedy hit,Sack Lunch,
starring Dabney Coleman.
[GASPS HAPPILY]
All right.
Oh, this is shaping up.
MAN:
Excuse me, please.
Oh, sure.
Oh.
Ladies and gentlemen,
because we have been exploited
by your Magic Pan
crepe restaurants,
we are hijacking
this plane to Cuba.
Everyone stay in your seats.
And shut that movie off.
Oh, nuts.
MANDELBAUMS [IN UNISON]:
Mandelbaum, Mandelbaum.