I can't believe
the Yankees really fired me.
Ah, you had a good run.
Took them
to the World Series.
I gotta give the players
most of the credit for that.
Don't sell yourself short.
You made all those flight
arrangements, hotels, buses.
No, I don't know
who was doin' that.
So when you actually did work,
what is it that you did?
I'll tell you,
they had a pastry cart
you wouldn't believe.
Here we go.
Your latte.
Your cappuccino.
Maybe I should ask her out.
She is a good waitress.
It's true.
Maybe I'll take her
to the Tonys.
You're goin' to the Tonys?
Yeah, I wrote some jokes
for the show,
and they gave me
two tickets.
Well, why didn't you ask me?
I know a million theater jokes.
Uh, what's the deal with
those guys down in the pit?
[SNORTS]
They're musicians.
That's not a joke.
It's a funny observation.
Hm. Severance package?
The Yankees are giving me
three months' full pay for doin' nothin'.
Well, they did it for
three years. What's another few months?
I'm gonna do somethin'
with these three months.
Like what?
I'm gonna read a book,
from beginning to end,
in that order.
I've always wanted
to do that.
I'm can learn to play Frolf.
You mean golf?
Frolf. Frisbee golf, Jerry.
Golf with a Frisbee.
This is gonna be my time.
Time to taste the fruits
and let the juices drip
down my chin.
I proclaim this
"The Summer of George."
[INSECT BUZZING]
[GRUNTS]
Whoa.
Jeez!
Hey, Jerry!
[GRUNTS, SHRIEKS]
[♪]
And then Peterman ate it.
[CHUCKLING]
I never told him.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Who is that?
That's Sam,
the new girl
in Accounting.
What's with her arms?
They just hang
like salamis.
She walks
like an orangutan.
Better call the zoo.
[CATERWAULS]
What?
[HISSES]
Catty.
[♪]
ELAINE:
It's like she's carrying invisible suitcases.
Like this?
Yes, exactly.
That is so strange.
Right.
So why am I the one
who gets:
[CATERWAULS]
You know? I mean, they were
being just as catty as I was.
It's a double standard.
Oh, and what about
ladies' night?
Women admitted free before 10?
That is so stupid.
[CATERWAULS]
[SIGHS]
Hey, The White Shadow is on.
Boy, you're really
packin' it all in.
Hey, Jerry, my vacation
has just started.
I need a day or two
to decompress.
Besides, I did plenty today.
Like what?
I bought a new recliner
with a fridge
built right into it.
Hey, Jerry, you got any TUMS?
Stomachache?
Ah, I drank too much water
in the shower.
Ah, top of the fridge.
Hey.
Hey, George, I'm taking
that waitress to the Tonys.
Shadow.
Oh, the Tonys?
I'll see you there, buddy.
You're going to the Tonys too?
Yeah, roger that.
Where are you sitting?
Uh, well, all over the place.
Yeah, I'm a seat-filler.
They don't like
to see empty seats on TV.
Somebody gets up,
I park my caboose in their spot
till they get back.
How did you get that job?
Yeah, Mickey, he hooked me up.
He's a member of the academy.
What academy?
Well, he didn't say.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Nice tuxedo.
Thanks.
It's a breakaway.
Should we go?
Absolutely.
Lyle, we're going.
All right.
Jerry, this is Lyle.
Hey, how you doin'?
Okay.
Bye.
Mm.
Have a good time.
Thanks...
Lyle.
[♪]
Are you leaving?
'Cause I got you covered.
I-- I'll just go ahead
and get in there.
Just-- Just a min--
What are you doing?
My job. What are you doing?
You know, they--
They catch the two of us on TV,
you might have
a little explaining to do.
So you and Lyle
are roommates?
No.
Gay?
What?
Is he gay?
No.
Are you sure?
I think I would know.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKER INDISTINCTLY]
This is a new one.
Turkey jerky?
Go ahead, take a pull.
More for me.
ANNOUNCER: Scarsdale Surprise...
[GASPS]
ANNOUNCER:
And the Tony for best musical
is awarded to...
Scarsdale Surprise.
Lewis Lexton Graham,
Douglas Ewing,
Benjamin London,
Polly Kennedy, producers.
[FANFARE PLAYING]
Whoa-ho-ho!
[FANFARE PLAYING OVER TV]
[SIGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
Kramer?
Thank you and bless you all.
This truly has been
a Scarsdale Surprise.
[LAUGHS]
[BAND PLAYING JAZZ TUNE]
[♪]
SAM:
Elaine, am I crazy?
I just get the feeling that...
Dugan and the others
are making fun of me
all the time all the time.
Well, you might wanna think
about, uh, maybe, um...
moving your arms a little
when you walk.
My arms?
You know,
sort of swing 'em,
so you're not lurchin' around,
you know,
[CHUCKLING]
like a caveman.
I'm a caveman?
No, no, no, no, no, it's--
It's just that--
[TEARFULLY]
Everyone told me what a catty shrew you were.
You're horrible.
[♪]
GEORGE:
She had a dude?
Yeah, when I went to pick
her up, there was this dude.
How do you know
it was her dude?
Think it could've been
just some dude?
Sure, dudes in this town
are a dime a dozen.
I reckon.
Or maybe
she just wanted to go
to the Tonys.
I tell you what.
You ask her out again.
No Tony, just Jerry.
That way you know if the dude
is her dude
or just some dude.
Dude.
Yeah.
[SIGHING]
All right, that's enough. I gotta go home and take a nap.
It's 10:30 in the morning.
What can I tell ya,
I'm wiped.
So has the Summer of George
begun,
or are you still, uh,
decomposing?
Decompressing.
Ooh, well, good morning,
gentlemen,
and Tony says hello to you.
[LAUGHS]
You didn't give
that thing back?
Jerry, it was a whirlwind.
They whisk us backstage.
The media is swarming.
Champagne is flowing.
Woo!
I can't describe
how great it is to win.
That's because
you didn't win.
Scarsdale Surprise.
That-- That's the musical
about the Scarsdale
diet doctor murder.
Featuring the mind-blowing
performance
of Miss Raquel Welch.
You haven't even seen it.
Ah, Jerry, I'm not gonna let you
bring me down off this high.
Ah, I've been partyin'
all night.
I saw the sun rise at Liza's.
Wha--? Minnelli's?
No.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Sam, listen.
I am so sorry
about the other day.
No, don't apologize,
Elaine.
I was thinking that maybe, um,
I should swing my arms
a little bit more.
See, yeah, I mean,
that's all I was saying.
How's this?
Or this?
Or this? Or this?
Well you, uh--
--seem to be gettin'
the hang of it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Sorry, I'm running late.
I just lost track of time.
No rush.
[LAUGHING]
Hey, Jerr, what's up?
I have absolutely no idea.
[♪]
JERRY:
Can you believe she expected me
to squire her
around town
while the dude sits at home
in swaddling clothes?
Do they make swaddling clothes
for adults?
It's like she split the role
of boyfriend into two jobs.
Except the dude's playing
the showroom,
and I'm stuck doin'
food and beverage.
Hey, buddy.
Who's that?
It's Kramer.
Hey, Kramer.
George says hi.
Hi, George!
How's that Tony?
Why don't you
just come over here?
Why can't I do this
on the phone?
What's Kramer doin' now?
He's lookin'
in the refrigerator.
[CHUCKLING]
Kramer.
Anything good in there?
Any Popsicles?
I cannot do this.
So, what's George doing?
He's not doin' anything.
Goodbye.
I'm gonna grab a bite to eat
at Sardi's.
You wanna go?
Are you takin'
the Tony to Sardi's?
The Tony is taking me
to Sardi's.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[FLATLY]
Oh, hello.
Well, I'm going.
Congratulations.
Well, thank you.
Yes, thank you so much.
I have so many people
I wanna thank.
I don't wanna forget anyone.
All right. All right.
[PHONE RINGING]
I said no.
Jerry, I just wanna
let you know,
Lyle and I
are completely over.
I'd rather be with you.
Just me? No...
dudes or fellers?
What do you think?
I can start right away.
[PHONE RINGING]
But not here.
JERRY [OVER SPEAKER]:
Leave a message.
GEORGE:
Jerry, what's happenin'?
Jerry, come on,
pick up the phone.
[♪]
So, I said to him,
"Arthur, Artie, bubele,
"why does the salesman
have to die?
"Change the title.
"The Life of a Salesman.
That's what people
want to see."
Excuse me,
Mr. Kramer.
My name is Lewis Lexton Graham.
I'm one of the producers
of Scarsdale Surprise.
Oh, hey. Yeah. Yeah-- Lew!
We need to talk.
[♪]
PETERMAN:
Elaine,
what did you wanna
talk to me about?
This. My office.
Sam trashed my office.
Well, I see
what's going on here.
I am smack-dab in the middle
of a good old-fashioned
catfight.
Mr. Peterman,
this is not a catfight.
This is violent,
psychotic behavior,
directed at me all because
I told her to swing her arms.
Woof.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you mean:
[CATERWAULS]
Yes, that's the one.
Good day, Elaine.
Oh, no, please,
Mr. Peterman.
She's crazy.
♪ Crazy for feelin' ♪
♪ So lonely ♪
[♪]
JERRY:
I can't believe
how much we did
this afternoon.
I have a friend,
today would be his whole life.
Now, what time are you
picking me up tonight?
Huh?
You got reservations at Sfuzzi,
didn't you?
Oh, yeah, Sfuzzi. I--
I gotta do that.
Should I wear the outfit
I bought?
Sure.
Which one?
The one with the, uh...
With the...
[MURMURS INDISTINCTLY]
If I'm gonna get my hair cut,
I better go now.
Call me when you get home.
I won't be there, but leave
a message so I know you called.
Okay. Okay.
Do you mind?
No,
I'll grab 'em, yeah.
Hey. I've done
that today.
[SIGHS]
What, you lose your remote?
Nah, cable's out.
What's with you?
You look, uh, dead.
It's Lanette.
I need, like, an assistant
or an intern or somethin'.
[SNORTS]
Relationship intern, huh?
Hey, what if the two of us
teamed up?
Not...?
No, no.
No, because that's--
No.
Listen,
we're always sittin' here.
I'm always helpin' you
with your girl problems.
You help with my girl problems.
Where do we end up?
Here.
Exactly,
because neither one of us
can handle a woman
all by ourselves.
I'm tryin'.
I've tried.
We don't have it.
But maybe the two of us,
working together
at full capacity,
could do the job
of one normal man.
And each of us would only
have to be, like, a half-man.
That sounds about right.
[♪]
We understand
how excited you are
to have this very,
very prestigious award.
But you didn't have
anything to do
with the actual production.
[LAUGHING]
No.
I'm afraid there is no way
we can allow you
to keep this Tony.
What?
Unless--
Anything.
Are you familiar with our star,
Raquel Welch?
Oh, she's fantastic.
She's a train wreck.
There's a big tap-dance number
before Jean Harris leaves
the Madeira School
to confront Dr. Tarnower.
It is a gut-wrenching scene.
Yes.
But Raquel Welch doesn't move
her arms when she tap dances.
It's very distracting.
There is a lot of this...
in tap dancing.
So you'd, uh, like me
to teach her how to dance?
No, we want you to fire her.
[♪]
JERRY:
Why do they want you
to fire Raquel Welch?
Because they're
terrified of her.
I heard from someone they cut
one of her lines.
She climbed up a rope
on the side of the stage
and started droppin' lights
on people's heads.
A story like that's
gotta be true.
She seems very nice.
Jerry, you're not
in show business.
You don't know
what these people are like.
I'm in show business.
Oh, come on.
What am I gonna do?
She's gonna eat me alive.
Well, I got a tape
of Fantastic Voyage,
if you think that'll help.
[BLURTS]
I'll take it.
Jerry, that crazy
straight-arm woman
down at Peterman's
trashed my office.
And then listen to this.
This is the message
she left me.
SAM:
Elaine, I am going to find you.
If not in your office,
then in the Xerox room,
or the small conference room
next to the kitchen,
[YELLING]
or the kitchen--
I mean, she must have
a blueprint
of the building
or something.
Did you tell Peterman
about this?
Well, I tried.
But he thought
it was some sort
of a catfight.
Catfight?
Okay. Why?
Why do guys do this?
What is so appealing to men
about a catfight?
[GIDDILY]
Catfight.
Because men think
if women are grabbin'
and clawin' at each other,
there's a chance
they might somehow kiss.
[BABBLING EXCITEDLY]
[♪]
You got the tickets?
Yeah.
Two for the 7:15
of Lenore's Promise.
What, are you wearing
a green sweater?
I like it.
Lanette doesn't.
Here's your blue one.
It's her favorite.
What?
Just put it on!
Oh.
All right.
Now, remember
she got her nails done today,
so remark on how
you like the color.
And if you need me, you beep me.
All right?
Okay.
Here, here. There you go.
There you go.
All right.
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Ah, go get 'em.
You're a tiger!
Hey, George, one second.
Uh, she's having
a party Friday.
She wants me to take care
of the invitations.
A little notice
would have helped.
How many people?
Thirty-five.
And, George,
on the invitations--
Yeah, I know. I know.
Don't skimp. Go, go.
Right on time.
I like that.
I like your nails.
That is a great color.
Love the sweater.
This old thing?
[♪]
GEORGE:
Hi, I, uh, need some party invitations.
Okay. Have you been
in here before?
About a year ago.
Wedding invitations.
Right. How'd that
all work out?
No complaints.
Well, they're arranged according
to price, and as I recall...
Actually...
I'll take these
nice glossy ones.
[♪]
WOMAN:
You are a fraud, Dr. Tarnower.
You haven't even been
to Scarsdale.
[KNOCKING]
Miss Welch. Hi.
Who are you?
Uh, well, I'm, uh--
I-- I'm Cosmo Kramer.
I'm, uh, one of the producers.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello. Sidney.
No. No, I told you
I don't wanna do that.
If you bring it up again,
I'll feed your genitals
to a wolf.
Kids.
[SIGHS]
You're still here?
Well, uh...
Uh, Miss Welch I--
I do need to talk to you
about a-- A little problem
regarding your, uh...
Your performance.
What kind of problem?
Uh, well, it seems that, uh,
due to the, uh...
The v-vagaries of the, uh,
production parameters,
uh, vis-à-vis the, uh,
fragmenting of the, uh...
The audience
due to cable television,
uh, carnivals, uh, water parks--
Out with it.
Well, you're fired.
You don't use your arms
when you tap dance.
You're like a gorilla.
Gotta go.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[♪]
MAN:
A little help?
Hey, Frolf?
Yeah.
You know, we need a fourth
for the back nine. You want in?
JERRY:
What's the deal with airplane peanuts?
[POP]
Yeah, sure.
Come on.
[♪]
JERRY:
Well, I'm ready.
Let's towel it up.
Jerry, where are
those invitations
you were supposed to get?
If they don't go out today,
they're useless.
But we're in towels.
Jerry.
All right,
one second.
He Frolfs.
Pshh! He scores!
[PHONE RINGING]
GEORGE: Hello.
Where are those invitations?
You were supposed to leave them
with her doorman.
Did you shave your chest hair?
[HIGH VOICE]
No.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Did you at least pick them up?
Yeah, yeah, super glossy,
the best they had.
All right, well,
get 'em over here pronto.
We're at towels here,
George.
All right. All right.
Keep your towel on.
What?
It's a joke.
All right. That's not bad.
Now, get over here.
[♪]
♪ Bum-ba
Ba-da-bum-ba-- ♪
[GRUNTS]
Ow.
SAM:
--if not in your apartment,
then in the laundry room,
or the ATM in the building
across the street,
or the watch shop!
Can't you do anything
about this?
I mean, this woman
is a psycho.
[CATERWAULS]
[SIGHS]
Look, just because I'm a woman
doesn't mean--
[CATERWAULS]
[MEOWS]
I don't move my arms
when I dance?
That's my signature.
Would you just keep an eye out
for this woman?
She's about, I don't know,
yay high,
and, uh, heh, she doesn't swing
her arms when she walks.
What do you mean?
Like this.
[LAUGHING]
What the hell is that?
Are you making fun
of my dancing?
[GASPS]
Aren't you Raquel Welch?
You know who I am.
Now, what are ya doin'?
Uh, n-nothing.
I just wasn't moving my arms.
Mm-hm.
That's it. You're goin' down.
[ELAINE SHRIEKING]
Ooh, catfight.
[ELAINE AND RAQUEL SCREAMING]
[♪]
KRAMER:
So how's George?
I don't know.
They won't tell me anything.
Oh, jeez.
What's that?
[TEARFULLY]
Tony.
What happened to you?
Yeah, Raquel Welch.
Yikes.
[BABBLES]
[SIGHS]
What happened to you?
Raquel Welch.
The woman is a menace.
Yeah.
I bumped into her
on the street.
It got pretty ugly.
Hm.
A catfight
with Raquel Welch.
[BABBLES EXCITEDLY]
Catfight.
My God, George.
I slipped
on the invitations.
How's the towels?
They're back
on the rack.
Even with the two of us?
I think we're still
a man short.
Mr. Costanza...
Your legs have sustained
extensive trauma.
Apparently, your body was
in a state of advanced atrophy
due to a period
of extreme inactivity.
But with a lot of hard work
and a little bit of luck,
I think there's a good chance
you may, one day, walk again.
Well, that's good news.
ELAINE:
Wow,
invitations again.
[SCOFFS]
Oh, yeah,
that's weird.
All right. Well...
Well.
[SIGHS]
You wanna grab some coffee?
Yeah, coffee.
I-- I'd like to get
some coffee. Okay.
JERRY:
Mm-mm-mm.
This was supposed to be
the Summer of George!
[WEAKLY]
The Summer of George.
[♪]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[WOMEN CHATTERING]
Summer of George.
Swing them.
Right? Okay?
Sort of swing them.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
Swing them.
[SIGHS]
Just swing them.
I can't do it.
Okay? It's hard.
Come on. Okay?
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah--
Yes.
[GASPS]
There's still
a little summer left.
[GEORGE GRUNTING]