[♪]
Man, I'm starving.
How can you be hungry
after what you ate
at that Mets game?
'Cause ballpark food
doesn't count as real food.
Right. It's just an activity.
It's like that paddle
with the ball and rubber band.
You know, my friend Bob Sacamano
made a fortune off of those.
See, he came up with the idea
for the rubber band.
Before that,
people would just hit the ball
and it would fly away.
I can't believe you all
made me leave
before the end of the game.
Oh, come on, Jerry,
it was nine to nothing.
We were getting
shellacked.
Those nachos
are killing me.
I thought you were hungry.
It's complicated.
Jerry, you're gonna
miss the exit.
Keep your shirt on,
I got it.
Watch out for that maroon Golf.
Oh, boy.
Look at this guy.
He's trying to box me out.
I'll tell you when you can go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Now, now, now, now.
No, no, no.
Now. Go, go.
No, no. Wait.
Wait. Now, now, now.
Jerry, go-- Ah.
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[HORN HONKING, MOUTHED SPEECH]
Oh, calm down,
maroon Golf.
He thinks I cut him off.
He accelerated.
You want me to moon him?
Ooh, let's moon him.
Roll up your window. Let's do
a pressed ham under glass.
Oh, no, I couldn't do that.
Look at this, look at this.
He's giving us the finger.
Oh, all right.
Okay.
[♪]
So I saw that new movie
about the Hindenburg.
Oh, yeah,
what's that called?
Blimp: The Hindenburg Story.
How was it?
I found it morose.
Why dwell on
these negative themes?
Yeah, they should
make a movie
about all the Hindenburg
flights that made it.
Anyway, right in the middle,
the ship blows up.
Burning debris, bodies falling,
and then just as
this eerie silence
settles over the airfield,
I yelled out,
"That's gotta hurt."
The place went nuts.
Imagine the laugh
you could have gotten
if you had yelled that out
at the actual disaster.
Yeah.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
Why are we slowing down?
What is that music?
What's with
all these flags?
Oh, no.
JERRY AND ELAINE [IN UNISON]:
It's the Puerto Rican Day parade.
Ohhh, the city shuts down
Fifth Avenue.
They never
let anyone through.
We are never
getting home.
I'll check it out.
Ahem.
Ahhh.
Mucho tráfico.
Yep. Ungh!
Yep, the streets
are all blocked.
I think every Puerto Rican
in the world is out here.
Well, it is our day.
Whoo.
Wrong car. Sorry.
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
The Mets score two in the eighth inning.
See? If we had stayed,
we could have seen those runs.
I could've had
some ice cream.
That might have calmed down
the nachos.
I'm gonna miss
60 Minutes.
You know I hate
to miss 60 Minutes.
It's part of my Sunday
weekend wind-down.
I don't know how you can unwind
with that clock ticking.
It makes me anxious.
All right, gentlemen.
I scouted it out. I think
we can get out over there.
JERRY:
But that's a one-way street coming this way.
Besides, how am I gonna get
all the way over there?
Just inch over.
You worm your way.
Just do it, Jerry.
Ugh, this exhaust.
I'm gonna throw up.
You know, you should
make yourself throw up.
Huh?
You know you're going to.
All right, I'm worming.
Hey, Jerry. You know who the
grand marshal is of this thing?
None other than
Miss Chita Rivera.
JERRY:
They're not letting me in.
GEORGE:
My hand is out.
Well, I think we're gonna need
more than a hand.
They have to see
a human face.
You sure you want
his face?
No, no, no.
It was Maria Conchita Alonso.
This guy's giving me the
stare-ahead.
JERRY:
The stare-ahead, I hate that.
I use it all the time.
Look at me.
I am man!
I am you!
[MOUTHED SPEECH]
All right, he's letting you in.
Thank you.
[QUIETLY]
Freak.
[MOUTHED SPEECH]
Oh, I know who it is:
Stacy Keach.
JERRY:
One more lane to go.
All right. We're here.
Oh, look who's here.
My old buddy.
Black Saab.
Maroon Golf.
Where you going, black Saab?
You seem to be a tad askew.
Could you move your car
back a little?
Oh, sorry.
I seem to have cut you off.
All right. I think
I know where this is going,
and I am going
somewhere else.
You can't do that.
You can't just leave the group.
I've been trying to leave
this group for 10 years.
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
Well, that's rude.
Can you believe her?
Yeah.
I'll see you later.
Well, where you going?
The movies.
Blimp is playing right there.
You're going to that again? Why,
just to do that stupid line?
It's a performance, Jerry.
Like what you do.
That's not what I do.
Isn't it?
Maybe a little.
Ah, hell, I guess it is.
You know, actually, Jerry,
you haven't worked
a room that big in a while.
[♪]
Look at that guy's dog.
[SCOFFS]
I hate it when their ears get
flipped inside out like that.
Why doesn't he fix it?
Hey!
Fold your dog's ear back!
[SIGHS]
Ohhh!
This isn't moving.
[HUFFS]
I could walk
faster than this.
No, you can't.
Yes, I can.
Here.
I'm outta here.
Oh.
Now it's moving.
Oh, yeah, I knew it.
Hey! Hey!
Where to?
That's cute.
That's really cute.
[TIRES SQUEALING,
HORNS HONKING]
[SIGHING]
Come on.
All right.
Bye again.
Hey. Taxi!
Taxi!
[♪]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ladies.
I, uh--
I haven't seen this before.
Oh, what is that dot?
Ooh, I think someone has one
of those funny laser pointers.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER FILM]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[♪]
Give me a box of those,
and one of those.
Ahem. Excuse me. Are you
the guy with that funny laser?
The laser's not funny.
I'm funny.
Yeah.
The thing is, I, uh,
had this little zinger
of my own I wanted to try.
Uh-huh.
It's right
in the explosion scene,
so if you could just leave me
a little window...
You know, my, uh-- My aunt had
a thing removed with a laser.
[CHUCKLES]
All right, I don't wanna
interrupt your meal, so...
[♪]
ANNOUNCER:
What a comeback for the New York Mets.
Six runs in the bottom
of the ninth...
I've gotta see this game.
If it wasn't for this guy,
we could get out of here.
This traffic's a killer,
ain't it?
You wanna get outta here?
Here's what we do.
We leave the car here.
We take the plates off,
we scratch the serial number
off the engine block
and we walk away.
Walk away?
Well, you've got insurance.
You tell 'em
that the car was stolen,
and then you get
another one free.
Isn't there a deductible?
All right,
what is your deductible?
I don't know.
Yes.
Because they've already
deducted it.
From what?
The car.
Which we're leaving,
so the net is zero.
See, you pocket the money,
if there is any,
and you get a new car.
We're not leaving the car.
All right.
If you refuse to grow up
and scam
your insurance company,
you'll have to work this out
with maroon Golf.
Absolutely not.
He sped up.
ANNOUNCER:
Swing long, lined hard toward left center field.
That's in the gap,
that's a base hit...
I'm ready to talk.
[♪]
Hey, there's
that laser guy again.
He's funny.
I never meet anyone funny.
I know.
A sense of humor
is so much more important to me
than looks,
or hair.
Mm-hm.
[♪]
That's gotta hurt!
It's gotta hurt!
[MAN COUGHS]
Hurt!
Because...
[YELLS]
Damn you, laser guy!
You had to grab it all
with your lowbrow laser shtick.
You're just a prop comic.
Where's the craft?
Look, it's on the bald guy.
[LAUGHTER]
FRIEND:
I am so glad we came to this showing.
[♪]
Whew. Okay, here's the deal.
He wants you to acknowledge
that you cut him off
with an "I'm sorry" wave.
What's that?
You raise the hand,
lower the head.
"I'm sorry. The buttons
are really big on the car.
I don't understand it.
I haven't read the manual. Ooh."
You get my drift.
Okay.
"Hallelujah. Praise the Lord."
But I'll take it.
Yes. All right, Lamar,
back it up a little bit
so we can get out now.
All right. At last, we're
finally getting outta here.
What's that on your forehead?
Uh, probably chocolate.
I-is that one
of those laser pointers?
Hey, Jerry, crank up the Floyd.
It's a George Laserium. Ha-ha!
All right, stop it.
Stay away from my breasts--
Chest!
See you around,
maroon Golf.
And by the way, that was
an "I'm not sorry" wave.
What was that?
I'm glad I cut you off,
because black Saab rules!
So long, jackass.
Elaine?
Jerry?
Jackass.
So I'm a jackass now?
[♪]
So if everyone would just put
their cars in reverse
at the same time,
we can do this.
All right,
on the count of three.
Can everyone hear me?
Hey, Amigo,
are you paying attention?
Buenos días, my friend.
Not you.
The guy in the Amigo.
Uh, well...here.
Here is good.
Oh, yeah, sure. Now--
Now I'm gonna be stuck here.
But you knew the way to go.
You went to college.
Hey, I went to Tufts.
It was my safety school.
So don't talk to me
about hardship.
Boy. Ha!
Can you believe this mess?
Elaine, why did you have the cab
come down this street?
We were almost out.
So that was your girlfriend
that blocked you in.
That's real good.
I'm not his girlfriend.
Well, actually, we used to date,
but not anymore--
Elaine, he doesn't need--
LAMAR: Used to date.
So I guess you found out
he's a jackass.
'Cause that's what's
gonna happen.
Oh, he's giving you
a mustache. Where is this guy?
No, don't. Don't look around.
That's what he wants.
All right, well,
I'll see you.
Hey, George, I think there's
a sniper looking to pop you.
This thing can't
hurt me, can it?
I mean, it is a laser.
What if it hits my eye?
I don't know.
I can't be blind, Jerry.
The blind are courageous.
You'll be fine,
as long as it
doesn't hit you right
in the pupil,
'cause then the whole ball
will go up like the Death Star.
Th-doo!
All right, I gotta
go find a bathroom.
Hold it, George.
Don't move.
It's right
between your eyes.
Oh, my God.
Hey, there's the soda guy.
Hey, jackass,
get me a Diet Dr Pepper.
JERRY:
All right.
[CROWD CHEERING, MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, hey, hey.
What--? Oh! Oh.
Oh, this is nuts.
I can't get across anywhere.
Well, none of us can.
We're trapped.
Hey.
Hey, everyone,
this way.
I think we can get out
through here.
Oh, I don't know
if that's such a good idea.
Look. No one knows how long
this parade is gonna last.
They are a very festive people.
All I know
is that it's Sunday night,
and I have got to unwind.
Now, who's with me?
Father?
None of us saw
the nylon flap.
That might mean something.
All right.
All right. Come on,
come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
But it's dark.
Get in there.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yes, uh, I'm interested
in the apartment.
Yes, come in, come in.
Okay.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I'm Christine Nyhart.
Ooh.
Delicious to meet you.
Heh.
Did the broker
send you over?
Yes, most likely.
Yes, I'm, eh,
H.E. Pennypacker.
I'm a wealthy industrialist
and philanthropist
and, uh, a bicyclist.
And, uh, yes,
I'm looking for a place
where I can settle down
with my, eh, peculiar habits,
and, eh, the women
that I frequent with.
[SNIFFING]
Mmm. Mombasa, huh?
The asking price is
a million and a half dollars.
Oh, I-- I spend that much
on aftershave.
Yes, I buy and sell men
like myself every day.
Uh, now, I assume that there's
a waterfall grotto?
No.
How about a bathroom?
It has four.
Yes. And, eh, where would
the absolute nearest one be?
Just down the hall.
Oh.
[STEEL PAN MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh. Oh.
Don't worry, we'll get you home
to your husband soon.
I'm not married.
Well, I, for one,
really respect that.
Oh. Thank you.
Hey. Guess who's not married?
[MOUTHED SPEECH]
Is the boyfriend
still in the picture?
Come on, Father,
you can make it.
No, I can't.
I've got a bad hip.
Go on without me.
No, I won't.
Leave me. You must.
All right. Take it easy.
All right, we can move faster
without Father O'Gimpy.
PRIEST:
I heard that.
[♪]
You know, I don't think
I've ever seen a man
driving
a Saab convertible.
Still haven't.
[SARCASTICALLY]
Ho-ho.
What seems to be the problem,
officer?
They're for protection, Jerry.
Can you tell where I'm looking?
At me?
No.
Well, it's back.
Bring it on, baby.
What if it gets in the side?
Side?
Yeah.
Wouldn't it just
bounce back and forth
between your cornea
and the mirror?
Faster and faster,
getting more intense, until--?
All right.
Oh, it's in your eye now.
What?!
[YELLING]
KRAMER:
Hola, Jerry.
I'm into this Puerto Rican Day.
The sights, the sounds.
The hot spicy flavor of it all.
It's caliente, Jerry.
You know, the Mets
got men on base.
Yeah, I know.
I was watching the game.
You were watching? Where?
Oh, that was a strike.
Did you see that?
Would you like to see the rest
of the apartment, Mr., um...?
Uh, Varnsen. Kel Varnsen.
Actually,
this room intrigues me.
Why is it called
the TV room?
Well, it's--
Balk? How was that a balk?
You have any snacks?
Mr. Varnsen, if you like
the apartment,
I should tell you
I've also had some interest
from a wealthy industrialist.
Not Pennypacker.
You know him?
I wish I didn't.
Brace yourself, madam,
for an all-out bidding war.
But this time,
advantage Varnsen.
[♪]
Wait a second.
What?
I think I see
where that laser guy is.
No, don't look,
don't look.
Oh, yeah,
that's him.
Okay. I'm gonna
sneak up on him.
Now the hunted
becomes the hunter.
[♪]
[GROANS]
We should be able to get across
right through here.
[GASPS]
It's a dead end.
Oh, no. I thought--
You thought?
We're gonna die in the dark.
I knew it, I knew it.
We're gonna die.
Get ahold of yourself!
ELDERLY WOMAN:
Ohhh.
Sorry.
Somebody help us!
Mira, mira,
Stacy Keach!
ELAINE:
Look down here. Help!
There's people down there.
Hold on!
Let us out.
There's an unmarried
pregnant woman down here.
PREGNANT WOMAN:
Don't judge me.
Help us up
so we can cross the street?
No, no, you can't cross here.
There's a parade.
But we've come so far.
We just wanna unwind.
Yeah, what can I tell you?
[WOMAN GROANS]
Wanna make out some more?
Oh, God! Let us out!
[♪]
Got it! Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
That wasn't a laser pen.
No.
It's just a pen.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, that's funny?
No, you have, like,
a dot on your face.
Whoever's doing that
is very clever.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
[♪]
Come on, man.
You need to lighten up.
Yeah, a feeling like this
only happens once a year.
Yeah, it's like this every day
in Puerto Rico.
Yeah, see, now you're getting
the spirit of it, huh?
[LAUGHING]
[SNIFFS, YELLS]
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
Hey. There's a guy burning
the Puerto Rican flag.
Who? Who is burning the flag?
Oh, no.
Him?
That's not very nice.
It was an accident.
Do you know
what day this is?
Because I know
what day this is.
They know
what day this is,
so I was wondering
if you know what day this is!
Because
it's Puerto Rican Day.
Maybe we should stomp you
like you stomp the flag.
What do you think of that?
All right, look.
I just have one thing
to say to you boys.
[HIGH-PITCHED]
Mama!
CEDRIC: Get him.
[KRAMER YELPING]
[♪]
Right this way,
Mr. Vandelay.
Well, this is
a lovely apartment. Lovely.
The kids
are gonna go crazy.
[CHUCKLES]
I, uh-- I wonder if I could
see the bathrooms. Ahem.
Preferably one
with some paint thinner
and, eh, some rags?
It's down the hall.
Oh, hello...
Art.
Mr. Vandelay,
of course.
You two know each other?
Mr. Pennypacker.
Uh, yes, uh...
Oh, yeah, I wanted to, uh,
stop by and make sure
that my shark tank fits--
Uh, hello.
Mr. Pennypacker,
this is Mr. Vandelay,
and you know
Mr. Varnsen.
Varnsen.
Pennypacker.
Vandelay.
Pennypacker. Varnsen.
Wait a second.
Mr. Pennypacker,
if you're here,
and Mr. Vandelay
is also here,
then who's watching
the factory?
The factory?
The Saab factory?
Jerry, that's in Sweden.
ANNOUNCER [OVER TV]:
The guy in here...
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
My car.
Yeah. You know, it's like this
every day in Puerto Rico.
Jerry,
the Mets lost.
I love a parade.
[♪]
GEORGE:
How do you suppose they did that?
KRAMER:
Well, there's no logical explanation.
All right, well,
shall we go home?
Well,
what about my car?
Well, Jerry,
you can't deduct it now.
Hey, there's Elaine.
Hey.
Well, you look, eh...
relaxed.
Well, it is Sunday night,
and you know
how I like to unwind.
LAMAR:
Hey, black Saab.
Looks like that building
cut you off.
[LAUGHS]
See you around.
Well, at least he didn't--
LAMAR: Jackass.
[CAR LOCK BEEPS]
Somebody remember
where we parked.
KRAMER:
Well, this was a fun day. It's nice to get out.
[♪]