[♪]
What is Holland?
What do you mean,
what is it?
It's a country
right next to Belgium.
No.
That's the Netherlands.
Holland is
the Netherlands.
Then who are the Dutch?
You know, I cannot
stand this thing anymore.
I know. I hate it too.
I feel like
an out-of-work porn star.
I told you, we should've
taken some kind of vacation.
Well, why didn't we?
Because you said
this would be better.
Remember?
"A vacation
from ourselves."
That's what you said.
What if we
grew muttonchops? No.
Buzz cuts?
Parachute pants!
Stop it, George.
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
You've gotta get a job.
[WHIMPERS]
Damn it.
[♪]
Hey, hey, hey.
Check me out. Huh?
No more crutches.
That must be a relief.
Yeah. With crutches,
everyone has questions.
Not with the cane?
Nah. With crutches,
it's a funny story.
With a cane,
it's a sad story.
You through with those?
That is a sad story.
Hey, you should've
been here tonight.
Some guy from NBC
saw my set.
He wants me
to do a showcase.
I might have another shot
at a pilot.
All right!
We're back in!
We? No.
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen, Kenny Bania.
Thank you.
Hey, Jerry,
did you see me up there?
I was killin', Jerry. Killin'.
I killed.
You killed?
Killed.
I'm gonna go
pick up some chicks.
Good-lookin' ones too.
Hey, what's your name?
Yeah, he killed.
Because I killed first
and warmed up the crowd.
He's like that fish
that attaches himself
to the shark.
And you're the shark?
Yeah, I'm the shark,
and he's the fish
eating my laughs.
I don't know how a fish
could eat laughs.
Well, I'm glad
I brought it up.
[♪]
So you got any
shredded coconut?
We're not doin' that anymore.
Uh-- Right-- Yeah--
Oh, my God.
What?
I got a job interview.
They wanna see me
this afternoon.
So what's this job?
Oh, it's beautiful.
It's in sports.
Knicks? Rangers?
Playground equipment.
Welcome back to the show.
Ah-ha-ha!
Yeah, this is better.
Yeah.
So you got
any shredded coconut?
No.
I gotta hobble.
Ya-ta-ta-ta-ta!
I gotta switch
shaving creams.
I'm gettin' no protection.
What kind do you use?
Whatever you get.
Look, postcard from Elaine
from Europe.
Oh. Don't tell me
she's draggin'
another poor guy
across Europe.
Remember David Puddy?
Oh, the face-painting
auto mechanic.
So she's
dating him again, huh?
Oh, I guess
she's batted around,
and she's back
at the top of the order.
Boy, a month in Europe
with Elaine.
[WHISTLES]
That guy's comin' home
in a body bag.
[♪]
Well, let's see.
I've got a 10 kroner,
a 5 kroner,
A 20 kroner--
No, wait.
That's another
10 kroner.
"Femty kroner."
How much is that?
We have to break up.
What?
I can't take this anymore!
I don't wanna hear
how interesting
the change
with the hole in it is!
If you tell me what time
it is in New York again,
you are going home
in a body bag!
Well, what about you?
What do you think
the Gap in Rome has that's
not in the Gap on Broadway?
Okay. All right. Listen.
Forget about the Gap
because we are through!
Fine.
Fine!
Okay.
Terminal three.
Have
a nice flight.
MAN [OVER P.A.]:
Ladies and gentlemen,
our flight time with stopovers
will be approximately 22 hours.
[SNIFFLING]
Hey, you gonna bust out
that drink cart or what?
[♪]
KRAMER:
Hey, what are you doin'?
I'm taking this lace out.
It came undone and touched
the floor of a men's room.
That's the end of that.
Did you see Bania's set
last night?
'Cause I read on the internet
he killed.
"He killed."
He only does well
when he has me for a lead-in.
He's a time-slot hit.
Jerry, you gotta
give him some credit.
I mean, you're just
being totally ridiculous.
I'll see you later,
buddy.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait a minute.
What, what, what?
Do I have to ask?
Well, I ran out of butter,
so I had to borrow yours.
Anything else, Mr. Nosy?
Why are you
buttering your face?
I'm shavin' with it.
Oh, Moses,
smell the roses.
No, Jerry,
it's vastly superior
to any commercial
shaving cream.
I mean, the shave
is close and clean,
and the natural emollients
keep my skin silky-smooth.
Now, feel my face.
No.
No, feel it.
I don't want to.
Feel it.
Feel it!
That is close.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I got the job?!
George, everybody here
at Play Now
is very impressed
with you,
but I'm sure you've
heard that before.
Well...
no.
I don't want you to think
that anyone's going to
treat you any differently
just because of your,
uh, ahem, handicap.
Handicap? Oh.
I'm not handicapped.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry.
Differently, uh...
um, advantaged?
See, I--I didn't
mean that.
Of course,
you will have
your own private,
fully equipped bathroom.
When do I start?
Oh, whenever you feel
that you're able.
Uh, ahem, you
need a hand here?
Yeah, what the hell?
[♪]
JERRY:
You got the job?
GEORGE:
Jerry, it's fantastic.
I love the people there.
They treat me so great.
They think
I'm handicapped.
They gave me this incredible
office, a great view.
Hold on.
They think you're handicapped?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well,
because of the cane.
You should see the bathroom
they gave me.
How can you do this?
Look, Jerry, let's face it.
I've always been handicapped.
I'm just now getting
the recognition for it.
Name one thing I have
that puts me
in a position
of advantage, huh?
There was a guy that worked
at the Yankees, no arms!
He got more work done than
I did, made more money.
He had a wife, a-a family!
Drove a better car than I did.
He drove a car with no arms?
All right, I made up
the part about the car,
but the rest is true.
And he hated me anyway!
You know how hard it's getting
just to tell people I know you?
I love that bathroom.
It's got
that high, high toilet.
I feel like a gargoyle perched
on the ledge of a building.
Hey.
They hooked me up.
What's with all the butter?
I'm shaving with it, and
you know what I discovered?
You can eat it?
No.
My face feels so good,
I'm gonna use it
all over my body.
Oh, my God,
it's Bania and Jenna!
Who?
The toothbrush in the toilet bowl.
Hey, Jerry!
This is Jenna.
Pretty good-lookin',
huh?
Uh, Jerry is the guy
that I dated right before you.
Oh.
This is awkward.
JENNA:
Don't worry, Kenny.
After dating Jerry...
you're a pleasure.
I don't believe this.
You miss her, don't you?
No!
He's ridin'
my coattails again.
He's gettin'
everything off of me.
First laughs, now ladies.
You miss her.
[♪]
PUDDY:
You know, I think, ultimately,
I'm upset with myself.
I knew what I was
getting into.
She's a bitter,
unstable person.
I mean,
the sex was good,
which I'm sure
was fine for her...
but I need more.
Hey, you believin' this?
Excuse me.
I-I was--
I was sleeping.
Well, you missed
quite a performance.
That's my apple juice.
[SHEENA EASTON'S
"MORNING TRAIN" PLAYING]
♪ My baby takes
The mornin' train ♪
♪ He works from 9
Till 5 and then ♪
♪ He takes another
Home again ♪
♪ To find me
Waitin' for him ♪
♪ My baby takes
The mornin' train ♪
♪ He works from 9
Till 5 and then ♪
♪ He takes another
Home again ♪
♪ To find me
Waitin' for him ♪
[LOCKS CLICKING]
[SNIFFS]
Someone's cookin'.
Hello, Jerry.
[FLATLY]
Hello, Newman.
You know, old friend,
sometimes I ponder
this silly gulf between us,
and I say why?
Are we really so different?
For what is--?
I'm not the one
doin' the cooking, Newman.
Damn you, Seinfeld!
You useless pustule!
Well, somebody's got
somethin' on the griddle.
Maybe it's Kramer.
Nah, he's up on the roof
gettin' some sun
with the butter.
Oh, no!
[SNIFFS]
Butter?
This is
the femty kroner.
Ohhh.
You know,
my last boyfriend,
he had a real kroner
comprehension problem.
You know what I mean?
A real cement-head.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
David,
you are so funny.
Yeah, I know.
Hey. What are
you doing?
It's a long flight,
Elaine.
I had to get on
with my life.
By making time with some floozy
across the aisle?
Yeah, that's right.
What's going on over there
with you and, uh...
Vegetable Lasagna?
This guy?
Oh, he's an idiot.
He doesn't mean
anything to me.
I can
hear you.
Well, she doesn't
mean anything to me.
If it were up to me,
we'd be together.
Well, maybe I feel the same way.
Okay.
Okay, so now what?
Let's make out.
Kramer!
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I think I cooked myself.
Look at your skin!
Oh, stick a fork in me, Jerry...
[WHIMPERS]
I'm done.
[♪]
Whew.
I'm fried.
Technically,
you're sautéed.
So, what're you
doin' for that?
Well, I just gotta keep my skin
moist so I don't dry out.
Is that what
the doctor said?
No. I read an article
in Bon Appetit magazine.
I'll see you, man.
See you.
Hey, Kramer.
Hey, buddy.
[SNIFFS]
Mmm. Game hen?
Kind of.
Nice limp. You bringin'
your work home with you?
No, I fake limp on my right.
This is a real limp because
I sprained my ankle.
What happened?
Well...
I was butterin' myself up
for a nice shave--
Oh, not you too.
I must've dripped some
on the floor,
and I slipped, and...
You know what's good for that?
Relish.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Yeah, this is Jerry Seinfeld.
What?!
No!
No, no, no!
Thank you.
I don't believe this.
They've added Bania
to the network showcase,
and he's goin' on
right after me.
Well, so what? He's got
a couple of good jokes.
Oh, like what, Ovaltine?
Why do dogs
drink out of the toilet?
Shopping carts
with one bad wheel?
[SNICKERS]
That's true.
That always happens to me.
You think that's funny?
I don't know, I like stuff
you don't have to
think about too much.
You like Bania's act.
You're a closet Bania fan.
Maybe I am.
Oh, I'm gonna puke.
Puke! That's a funny word,
"puke."
[LAUGHING]
Puke.
Ah, you don't have to
think about that.
I can't believe
we broke up like that.
It was stupid.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Do you want
something to read?
No, I'm good.
Are you gonna
take a nap or--?
Nah.
You just gonna
sit there,
staring at the back
of the seat?
Yeah.
That's it!
I cannot take this!
I mean, look at this.
Nothing has changed.
We've been back together
two hours,
we're having the same problems
we had 12 hours ago!
Oh, tell me about it.
I don't know why
I ever took you back.
Oh, please! I took you back!
You know it, I know it,
Vegetable Lasagna here
knows it.
Please, please.
I don't want to get involved.
Oh, I hope a giant mountain
rises out of the ocean,
and we just ram
right into it,
and end this whole thing!
Oh, God.
Ow!
Owww!
How much longer you gonna be?
I'm starvin' here!
Well, just a few more squirts...
'cause I gotta stay juicy.
That smell...
it's still with you, huh?
Oh, yeah.
It's baked on in.
Hey, put another
stick of butter in.
Yeah, yeah.
Would ya?
Yeah. Stir it up
so it'll melt.
Fine.
Oh, yeah.
Ooh, that feels good.
Yeah.
Now I'm simmering, huh?
I-I'll meet you
at the coffee shop!
MAN:
Good morning, George.
GEORGE:
Good morning, sir.
Is there something wrong
with your other leg?
No, no.
Just the old handicap acting up.
But your cane's
on the wrong side.
Oh, well, that's, uh...
That's just 'cause we're
standing on opposite sides.
Huh?
Yeah. See, when we met,
I was over there,
and you were over here,
so the image was reversed
like in the mirror, you see?
See, this looks right
to you, doesn't it?
Uh...yeah, I guess.
But...see, here.
Right.
Wrong.
Right. Wrong.
Will you stop it, George?
J-j-just stop it!
I think I can see
what's going on here.
[HORN BEEPS]
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[HORN BEEPING
"SHAVE AND A HAIRCUT"]
Well, you're not gonna
believe what happened.
You mugged Stephen Hawking?
Play Now thinks I've
got problems in both legs.
My own personal Rascal,
Jerry.
On the house.
Well, it must be
comforting to know
you'll be going
straight to hell
at no more than
three miles an hour.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Jerry.
Hey, Lanie.
How's the trip goin'?
Oh, it's awful.
This trip was
a huge mistake! Huge!
Please stop shouting!
I can't take it!
Who's that?
It's Vegetable Lasagna.
Who?
Vegetable Lasagna!
My name is
Magnus.
Shut up, or I'll
snap you in half
and stuff you
in the overhead!
Uh, get me some
duty-free Kahlua.
How's the trip?
Sounded good.
Well...gotta motor.
Hey, if you got any juice left,
you might wanna roll by
the big showcase tonight.
Oh, you still goin' on
in front of Bania, huh?
That's right,
and I'll tell you what.
I'm feelin' a little off.
What're you talkin' about?
You're not!
That's right.
I'm takin' a dive.
You're throwin' the set?!
I'm layin' down!
Then we'll see
how he does up there
without all the assistance.
Listen, Jerry,
with all due respect,
Bania's voice is the voice
of a new generation.
My generation!
We're four months apart.
Nevertheless!
His time has come.
[REVVING]
Now, if you will kindly
help me unwedge my front wheel,
I'll be on my way.
[HORN BEEPS]
[BEEPING CONTINUOUSLY]
[♪]
Butter.
Kramer.
Hey, buddy.
Ah!
[♪]
KRAMER:
Jerry, what are you doing?
George tells me
you're gonna throw your set?
That's right, Choochie.
Let's see how Bania does
without the cushy time slot.
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen, Jerry Seinfeld!
If you'll excuse me...
Whoa, man!
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
JERRY:
Hey, everybody! Who's ready to laugh?
Oh, man.
And what's the deal
with lampshades?
[LAUGHING]
Yeah!
I mean, if it's a lamp,
why do you want shade?
[GUFFAWING]
And what's with
people gettin' sick?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I mean, what's the deal
with cancer?
MAN:
I have cancer!
Uh-oh. Tough crowd.
[♪]
[WHISTLING]
Hey! Hey!
You dented my ride!
What you got there,
the, uh, four volt?
[CHUCKLES]
I did you a favor.
How about I do you a favor
upside your head?
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Hey!
Get the bikes!
[♪]
[AUDIENCE BOOING]
Ouch.
Well, that wasn't so bad.
What are you talkin' about?
I bombed!
Well, you had some good stuff.
The cancer bit.
It was edgy,
not my sort of thing,
but some of those people out
there, they really liked it.
Like who?
Well, that guy
who yelled out.
He had cancer.
And laughter
is the best medicine.
Hey, sorry, Kenny.
I guess you got your work
cut out for you.
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen, Kenny Bania!
Jeez!
Where were you?
Jerry, he could've
used your laugh.
He was a big turkey
up there.
Turkey?
A big fat turkey.
I'm sorry I missed that.
Let me tell ya,
he worked so hard,
and then
he just blows--
What is this, oregano?
Look at me!
I'm all covered in
oregano and parmesan,
and it's stickin' to me
because of the butter!
Look at me!
Yeah.
Hold this.
What is this?
Parsley?
Yeah.
Ah, the sweet stench
of failure.
KRAMER:
Ah, he bit me!
[KRAMER & NEWMAN GRUNTING]
[CRASH & CLATTER]
KRAMER:
Get off me!
[TENSE ACTION THEME PLAYING]
[HORN BEEPING]
Come on!
[MOTOR STOPS WHIRRING]
You stupid
two-hour battery!
Now I got ya!
Ah!
George?
Your legs!
Are you
a religious man, sir?
No.
Eat hickory!
Ah!
Hey, Jerry.
Did you see it?
Ouch.
Kenny!
There you are.
Jay Chermack and
Stu Crespi from NBC.
Listen, Kenny,
really funny out there.
What?
That thing you did
having the two guys
running through?
I love stuff you don't have
to think too much about.
Give us a call.
We wanna be in
the Kenny Bania business.
By the way, Jerry,
the suspenders?
A little hacky.
How about that, Jerry?
First you had a pilot on NBC,
and now I'll have one.
Looks like
I'm followin' you again.
Oh, I'm gonna puke.
Puke.
That's a funny word.
Can I use that?
[♪]
David, this has been
the worst month of my life,
and if I never see you again,
it'll be too soon.
Ditto.
Oh, that's original.
Go to hell.
86th and Broadway, please.
I'm sorry, lady.
There's a cab shortage.
The transit police are
makin' everyone share.
Oh, no.
Hello!
I'm sorry.
[GROANS]
ELAINE:
Nooooo!