[♪]
Any second now.
The light is on!
Melissa, waffles are ready.
MELISSA:
Oh, fantastic. I'm starving.
How about that?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[♪]
She ate breakfast naked?
She didn't even
want a napkin.
I've had bedroom naked.
I've had
walk-to-the-bathroom naked.
I have never had
living-room naked.
Oh, it's a scene.
It's like you're living
in the Playboy Mansion!
Did she, uh--?
Did she frolic?
I don't really
have enough room.
Yeah.
Hey, Laney, Puddy.
Hey.
Hi. Hi.
I gotta make a pit stop.
Okay.
Back together?
His apartment
was being fumigated,
so we thought
we'd give it another shot.
Oh.
So guess
who called me last night.
Jason Hanke.
Stanky Hanke? Heh.
What did he want?
He called to apologize
for standing me up
five years ago.
Why now?
AA. It's one
of the 12 steps.
Oh.
Step number nine is:
You have to apologize
to everyone
you've ever wronged.
[GEORGE CHORTLES]
I can't wait for Hanke
to come crawling back to me.
Still with
the neck hole?
Still upset. Very upset.
What neck hole?
Remember that New Year's party
he threw a few years ago?
He had that
very drafty apartment,
you know,
I think on 9th Avenue.
Faster.
I asked if I could
borrow a sweater.
A cashmere sweater.
I said preferably cashmere,
for warmth.
So in front
of the whole party, he says,
"No. I don't want you
stretching out the neck hole."
[LAUGHING]
Oh, yeah, sure,
laugh it up.
Everybody else did.
Well, it's funny.
I mean,
you have a big head.
[ELAINE LAUGHING]
Or is it 'cause
of your neck?
No. I think the head does
most of the stretching.
Regardless...
I had to walk around
for the rest of the party
in some cheap
MetLife windbreaker.
Now it is payback time.
I really think
it's the size of your neck.
It's my head!
[LAUGHING]
[♪]
Hey.
Isn't this great?
Since those nerds
in Accounting moved,
you and I are the only ones
who use this bathroom.
Yeah. Great.
[♪]
KRAMER:
You went to the coffee shop without me?
I told you, I just wanted
to hop in the shower.
That was an hour ago.
What were you doing in there?
Showering.
How long does it take you?
Ten minutes.
Ten minutes?
That's kooky talk.
Hey, Elaine, how long
do you spend in the shower?
Ten minutes.
Let me smell you, huh?
All right. Whiff away.
[SNIFFING]
Hey. That's not bad at all.
Hup.
Wh-wha--
That's it.
Okay.
So get this:
I'm in the bathroom
at work today,
and I see Peggy
using a seat protector.
So?
We're the only women
on the floor.
I mean,
we're like roommates.
Would you use a seat protector
if you had a roommate?
[SODA FIZZES]
Oh, gee--
I think the damage
is probably already done.
All right. I'll get that.
Well, maybe she just
practices good hygiene.
Yeah, you're right.
She's probably one of those
neurotic clean freaks.
Mm.
Well, here's my shower routine.
Maybe I can make
some changes.
Wash cloth mittens
and maybe some liquid soap
and just-- Pow! --focus.
[♪]
JERRY:
"Zephyr"?
That is not a word.
Do you challenge?
No, I do not challenge.
Sixty-six points. Ha-ha.
I'd accuse you
of cheating,
but I don't know
where you'd hide the tiles.
You want some ice tea?
Sure.
[COUGHS]
Wrong pipe.
[COUGHS & GASPING]
[♪]
GEORGE:
So she coughed.
Coughing...naked?
It's a turn-off, man.
Everything goes
with naked.
When you cough,
there are thousands
of unseen muscles
that suddenly
spring into action.
It's like watching
that fat guy
catch a cannonball
in his stomach in slow motion.
Oh, you spoiled,
spoiled man.
Do you know how much
mental energy I expend
just trying to picture
women naked?
But the thing
you don't realize
is that there's good naked
and bad naked.
Naked hairbrushing, good.
Naked crouching, bad.
Hey, there's Hanke.
All right.
It's grovel time.
Hey, George. Jerry.
Listen,
I just got sober,
so I've been going
through the 12 steps.
Uh-huh.
What are you up to now,
uh, step nine?
Yeah.
Making amends.
Important step.
Maybe the most important.
Anyway, uh...
Jerry, you know,
this may sound dumb,
but, you know,
when we first met,
I thought your name
was Gary.
And I think I may even
have called you Gary
a couple of times.
And I don't know
if you noticed,
but I always felt bad about it,
so I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I did notice...
and I appreciate you
rectifying it.
Great. Great.
Well,
I'll see you guys later.
[♪]
Well, I just got out
of a 27-minute shower.
Made some good cuts,
and I didn't lose
anything I needed.
Yeah, I think what I kept
is even stronger now.
You got some suds over here.
Wha--?
Oh, man!
Jeez!
Look at that.
I'm all lathery.
Jerry, you gotta show me
what I'm doing wrong.
Oh, come on.
No. I mean it, man.
I'm lost.
You promise you'll never
come in here again?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, Jerry, you know I can't do that.
Now, my sense of it is
you're probably wasting time
working piecemeal,
first cleaning one area,
then another.
Well,
that's how cats do it.
But when you have a faucet
instead of a tongue,
you wanna use gravity.
Okay. Let's turn
the water on now.
No. I told you,
it's just a dry run.
Hey.
Well, Hanke's moved on
to step 10.
He was spotted taking
personal inventory.
That's step 10?
All he has to do now
is count his blessings,
say a prayer,
and he's done.
You believe this?
Come on, Jerry. How about a--?
A baggy swimsuit?
No. You're not getting
any skin, Kramer.
Well, this has all been
one big tease!
[♪]
ELAINE:
These proofs look
pretty good.
Oh. Can I move this?
Yep, I think
this will work.
I'm gonna...get
another bottle of water.
Here, take mine.
There's a little left.
Oh, thanks, Walter.
Ahh!
[♪]
Guys, there's no doubt
that the pay is good,
but I just don't know
if I see myself
working with ice cream.
You get pretty buff forearms.
I don't know
if I'm into that.
Oh, hello, Hanke,
others.
George.
You know, Jason, I, uh...
I couldn't help notice I...
I didn't get my apology.
Apology? For what?
A drafty apartment?
A sweaterless friend?
A ball-game giveaway
MetLife windbreaker?
George, come on,
not that neck-hole thing.
Yeah, the neck-hole thing,
and I would appreciate it
if you would say sorry.
No way. You would have
completely stretched it out.
You're an alcoholic!
You have to apologize!
Step nine! Step nine.
All right, George,
all right. I'm sorry.
I'm very, very sorry.
I'm so sorry that I didn't want
your rather bulbous head
struggling
to find its way
through the normal-sized
neck hole
of my finely knit sweater.
[OTHERS SNICKERING]
[♪]
Oh, see,
that's smart.
Constant motion.
MAN:
Hey! Oh, yeah, yeah.
I-- I'm watching you too,
but this guy's
really showing me something.
[♪]
You got a steak?
What happened to you?
People in this city are crazy.
Here you go.
Thanks, buddy.
Oh, yes.
You got any A1?
'Cause I'm cooking a steak.
What?
A different one.
Oh!
Jerry--!
MELISSA:
Okay, Jerry. Fixed that bike.
Oh. That wasn't
really necessary.
I don't ride it.
It's just for show.
I should really clean
those bearings. Hold this.
Look at all that gunk.
Please don't crouch.
Ouch. Caught my skin.
Oh, that's bad,
especially that area.
You got anything
to snack on?
Uh...
Oh, pickles!
[GRUNTING]
It's a tough one. Hngh!
Please stop.
Let me help you with that.
[GRUNTING]
[JAR POPS]
Ooh!
Oh.
That's gonna
leave a welt.
Look at that.
I can't.
I can't look anymore.
I-I've seen too much!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Peggy, we've gotta talk.
What is it about me
that you find so offensive?
[SIGHS]
You seem to be
with a lot of men.
What?
I happen to have
a very steady boyfriend.
You know, I mean, we...
broke up a few times.
And there has been
an occasional guy here...
or there, but I--
Wh--? Why is this
your business?
It's not.
Good day.
Oh. All right.
You think I've got germs?
I'll give you some germs.
How about some
for your keyboard, huh?
How about that?
You like it?
Ooh. How about
for your stapler?
Hm? That's good,
isn't it?
You have a happy
and a healthy.
[COUGHING]
[♪]
JERRY:
Well, technically, he did apologize.
Jerry, I felt like
a straight man
in some
horrible sketch.
He was riffing!
Riffing. On my pain!
So now you want
an apology for the apology
plus the original apology?
That's right.
I'm two in the hole.
Well, I hit the wall
yesterday with Lady Godiva.
She did a full body flex
on a pickle jar.
Did you explain to her
about the good naked
and the bad naked?
Where am I gonna get
a fat guy and a cannonball?
Well...
what if you
showed her bad naked, huh?
You still got
that belt sander?
Yeah.
Well, you on all fours,
that thing vibratin',
kickin' up sawdust.
Ho-ho!
She'll get the picture.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yello?
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry, guess where I'm calling from.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
World War I plane?
No, I'm in my shower.
You know, I'm trying to get out
of the shower sooner,
and then I ask myself, "Why?"
I mean, this is
where I wanna be.
So I got a waterproof phone,
I shaved,
I brushed my teeth,
and I ordered
a pair of chinos from J. Crew.
When are you getting out?
[LAUGHS]
I'm not!
I'll see you later, buddy.
[♪]
PETERMAN:
Bad news, people.
Peggy is home sick.
Oh, please.
She's stuffed up, achy,
and suffering from
intense malaise.
Oh, come on.
We all
have intense malaise.
[LAUGHS]
Right?
I just spoke with her, Elaine.
She's in bed.
Yeah. Let me tell you something.
This is all in her mind.
Okay? She is insane.
She thinks
I made her sick
because I coughed
on her doorknob,
rubbed her stapler
in my armpit,
and put her keyboard
on my butt.
Yeah. She's a wacko.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So you're Jason Hanke's supervisor?
Sponsor.
Whatever. Listen,
I'm very concerned
about this guy.
He's doing very well.
He's already onto step 10.
Yeah, well, when you don't
actually do the steps,
you can go through them
pretty quick.
You can get through
six a day.
Is there some unresolved issue
between you and Jason?
I don't know. A little
something called step nine.
Instead of an apology,
he was beboppin'
and scattin' all over me!
I'm not sure
what you want me to do.
Well, aren't you
the boss of him?
You shouldn't
let him move up.
When I was
in the Cub Scouts,
I got stuck on Webelos
for three years
'cause I kept losing
the Pinewood Derby.
You're quite upset, George.
Well, I think you should
drop him down to step two.
Admit there's
a higher power?
Yeah, let him
chew on that for a while.
You know, George,
I think I can help you.
We're having a meeting tomorrow.
Why don't you just come by?
All right.
That's more like it.
Thank you very much.
By the way, uh...
my uncle was in Alcoholics.
[♪]
Lomez, you're not listening.
Jerry likes the naked.
It's just some of the things
that she does when she's naked.
Will you calm down?
I'm on your side.
Jeez! Hey, hold on a second.
I got a clog.
I'll call you back.
[♪]
What are you doing?
I found a rough spot
on the kitchen floor.
I thought I'd polish it up
with this belt sander
I have here.
No, not that.
Why are you naked?
I thought naked is good.
This isn't good naked.
[♪]
SPONSOR:
George, here, have a seat.
Where's Hanke?
Shh.
Okay,
let's get started.
Welcome to
Rageaholics Anonymous.
What? Rageaholics?
George, this can help you.
Hey, I am not here for rage.
I'm here for revenge!
MAN:
Excuse me.
We have a "no yelling" policy
at these meetings.
Excuse me.
Am I talking to you, pinhead?!
Am I?!
Please don't call me
"pinhead."
I'm losing it!
[♪]
JERRY:
He took you to Rageaholics? Why?
Probably because this whole
universe is against me!
You got a little rage.
I know, and now they
want me to bottle it up.
It makes me so mad!
By the way, my bad-naked demo
didn't quite work.
This bread has nuts in it!
Oh, great. Elaine.
What is wrong with my body?
Chicken-wing
shoulder blades.
That's it?
No, but that's
one problem. Why?
Well, I was walking around naked
in front of Melissa--
Whoa.
Walking around naked?
Uh, that is not
a good look for a man.
Why not? It's a good look
for a woman.
Well, female body is a...
A work of art.
The male body
is utilitarian.
It's for getting around.
It's like a Jeep.
So you don't think
it's attractive.
It's hideous.
The hair, the...
lumpiness.
It's...simian.
Well,
some women like it.
Mm. Sickies.
[♪]
KRAMER:
"Installing your Clarkman garbage disposal.
Dismantle latch hasp
beneath main drainage line."
Oh, come on, Clarkman.
[♪]
[RINGS]
Puddy.
Is David Puddy there?
This is Puddy.
Well, this is Kramer.
I know.
Um, listen,
you're a mechanic.
Could you help me install
a garbage disposal?
Well, it's a big job. You've
gotta dismantle the latch hasp
from the auxiliary
drainage line.
No, it says main line.
It's a misprint.
What do you got, a Clarkman?
Yeah.
I'll call you back.
I'll talk you through it.
Oh, okay.
Well, thanks, buddy.
Hey, Puddy.
Hey, babe,
your boss called.
You owe five bucks
for a balloon bouquet.
He says you can just give it to
him tomorrow when you see him.
Balloon bouquet for who?
Peggy took a turn
for the worse.
Peggy. Ah, great.
I suppose she's still
blaming me?
That's what he said.
Yeah.
I don't believe
this woman.
Talk to me, babe.
She's this crazy woman
who is convinced
that my germs make her sick.
Oh, a germ-a-phobe.
I know what that's about.
Huh?
I'm a recovering
germ-a-phobe.
Ten years.
What is this symbol?
It's a germ.
[♪]
Elaine, it was very nice
of you to bring the man
you're currently sleeping with
here to talk to me,
but I assure you,
I don't have any problem
with germs.
Don't you. Elaine?
[GASPS]
Please!
PUDDY:
I know it looks bleak.
I've been there.
Ten years ago,
waking up in bed
next to a woman like this
would've sent me
running for the pHisoHex.
Really?
I still have trouble
looking at
those disgusting old bedroom
slippers she slobs around in.
Hey, I've had those since
college. They're bunnies.
They're bacteria traps.
So you...just learn
to live with it?
For the most part.
Okay. We're broken up
for the rest of the day.
[♪]
JERRY:
So I'm glad we had a talk and worked this out.
Don't you feel
this is better?
This is nice.
Yes. Clothes.
This is normal.
Hey, what are you
doing tomorrow?
I was thinking
that we could go...
MELISSA:
Jerry?
Jerry, are you
listening to me?
Oh. Yeah.
Uh, what? I'm sorry.
I wanted to know
what you were doing tomorrow.
Ah, maybe a haircut,
and I don't know,
maybe I guess...
[♪]
So you broke up.
We couldn't carry on
a conversation.
I kept trying
to picture her naked.
She kept trying
to not picture me naked.
Hang on.
[WHIRRING]
So, what are you up to?
Oh, just cooking up a little
thank you for Puddy.
Hey, how do you make
those radish roses?
Insert a knife
into the center and twist.
Then, to make it bloom,
soak it in water
for 30 to 40 minutes.
No problem there.
[♪]
HANKE:
George, thanks for coming down to talk to me.
I wanted to see you
right away,
but my hours here
aren't very flexible.
I just started yesterday.
Well, I'm here.
What is it?
Well,
I talked to my sponsor,
and, uh,
I've thought it over,
and, you know, my apology
at the coffee shop
was sarcastic and rude,
and you deserve
much better.
Well...
thank you.
You're welcome.
Can I get
a triple Minuteman Mint?
Waffle
or sugar cone?
Uh, excuse me.
Um, Jason...
[CHUCKLES]
I don't wanna get into
a big thing here, but...
I'm not sure if technically
what you just said
was actually an apology.
What?
Can you get on that cone?
Would you hang on
just a second, son?
George, what are
you talking about?
All you said was,
"You're welcome,"
which is nice,
it's very nice,
but I feel I gotta get
the apology.
Is there anybody
else here but you?
I'm alone.
And it's my second day.
And you know, I don't even think
we have that flavor, so...
George, really,
enough. Okay?
I admitted I was wrong.
What more do you want from me?
I would like an apology.
All right--
BOY: You try it?
No, this guy doesn't
know what he's doing.
Oh, yes, I do.
Yes, I do, okay?
I'm interacting
with someone here,
if you can understand that.
Now, I'm sorry.
Ah, there it is!
You just said it.
That's what I want!
Now say it again
and tell it to me.
I'm not saying anything to you.
I'm not sorry.
I was never sorry.
It was cashmere.
I hate step nine!
Where's that Rum Raisin?
Where is it?
I can't find
anything here.
I need a drink.
Daiquiri Ice,
here we go.
What are you looking at?
Get out! Come on!
Can't you see we're closed?
Get out!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Mmm.
This food
is fantastic, Kramer.
And what a pretty
radish rose, huh?
Well, thank you.
Well,
here's to Peggy
on her first week
of being germ-free free.
Yeah.
And here's to
David Puddy
for helping me
install a much-needed
and much-appreciated
garbage disposal in my bathtub.
ELAINE:
Ah.
KRAMER:
Yeah.
You have a garbage disposal
in your bathtub?
Oh, yeah, and I use it
all the time.
Yeah. I made
this whole meal in there.
This food was in
the shower with you?
Mm-hmm.
I prepared it as I bathed.
[ALL GAGGING & GROANING]
Oh, germs.
Germs. Germs!
[♪]
Excuse me. Is this,
uh, Rageaholics?
No. Germ-a-phobes.
Thanks.
What are
you guys doing here?
Kramer.
Right.
Hi. I'm, uh, Jason.
I'm a Rageaholic.
ALL:
Hi, Jason.
Uh, this is
my first meeting.
GEORGE:
Step skipper!
That man is a step skipper!
He skips step nine!
Please, step nine.
That's right!
He never apologized to me
for saying that I would
stretch out the neck hole
on his sweater.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Wasn't funny.
It was a very nice sweater.
Take a look at his neck,
not to mention the melon
sitting on top of it.
I don't know
if I'd trust him with a V-neck.
He's beboppin' and scattin',
and I'm losing it!