[♪]
WOMAN:
Careful, this plate is extremely hot.
Thank you.
Ow! Ow.
I just told you it was hot.
Why'd you touch it?
I just wanted to know
what your idea of hot is.
Hey, babe, you ready
to hit the ice?
Yep. I am ready
to skate up a--
[LAUGHS]
Why are you wearing that?
It's my winter coat.
A fur?
Is there a problem?
A seemingly infinite supply.
Ow! Ah. Careful, it's hot.
Ah!
[♪]
JERRY:
So Puddy wears a man fur?
He was struttin' around
the coffee shop
like Stein Eriksen.
And, of course, you find fur
morally reprehensible.
Eh, anti-fur.
Who has the energy anymore?
This is more about hanging off
the arm of an idiot.
This is the first
you're seeing of the coat?
Ugh. We never dated
in winter.
You might want to get a look
at that bathing-suit drawer.
Oh,
we walked by Bloomingdale's
the other day,
and I saw that massage chair
we want to get Joe Mayo
as an apartment gift.
An apartment-warming gift?
We got to give presents
to people for moving?
The birthdays, Christmas,
it's enough gifts.
I would like one month off.
Kramer said it's a perfect gift.
That's what we're getting him.
We're not buying it
at Bloomingdale's.
I will buy it,
you pay me back later.
I'll sniff out a deal.
I have a sixth sense. Heh.
Cheapness is not a sense.
ELAINE:
I can't stand Joe Mayo's parties.
You know, the second
you walk in,
he's got you working
for him.
"Hey, can you do me a favor?
Can you keep an eye on the ice,
make sure we have enough?"
Ah.
I had a great time
at the last one.
I was in charge
of the music.
[CHUCKLING]
I turned that mother out.
Hey, you got any pliers?
Hey.
What, has Newman got another
Army man stuck in his ear?
Hilarious.
Newman and I are reversing
the peepholes on our door
so you can see in.
Why?
To prevent an ambush.
Yeah.
So now I can peek in
to see if anyone
is waiting to jack me
with a sock full of pennies.
But then anyone can just
look in and see you.
Our policy is: we're comfortable
with our bodies.
You know, if somebody wants
to help themselves to an eyeful,
well, we say,
"Enjoy the show."
I'm sorry I can't stay
for the second act.
Hey, George,
here's the model number
on that chair, by the way.
Hmm, nice wallet.
Wallet.
What?
Nobody carries wallets
anymore.
I mean, they went out
with powdered wigs.
Here.
See, here's what you need:
just a couple of cards
and your bankroll.
See, keep the big bills
on the outside.
That's a 5.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[♪]
KRAMER:
♪ I'm on the Mexican ♪
♪ Whoa-oh, radio ♪
Uh, what are you doing?
Hey, Silvio.
Yeah, I'm reversing
my peephole.
Hey, you know you gotta
get permission from me.
I'm the super.
Who said you could do that?
Well, who says I can do any
of the things I do in my place?
Like what?
Well, like--
Uh, nothing.
I'll, um--
I'll switch it back.
No, no, no, no.
That's all right.
Oh, yeah,
well, that's good.
Because Newman and I,
we think--
Newman, he did this too?
Well, yeah.
I deal with him.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Hey, look at this.
This is the same massage chair
we're getting for Joe Mayo,
$60 cheaper.
Except the store's
in Delaware.
I'll have 'em overnight it.
Maybe cheapness
is a sense.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, it is better
without this big wallet.
It's more comfortable.
It doesn't matter
if it is,
it's wrong.
Why?
Because important things
go in a case.
You got a skull
for your brain,
a plastic sleeve
for your comb,
and a wallet
for your money.
Look at this thing.
That's-- That's huge.
You got more cow here
than here.
I need everything
in there.
Irish money?
I might go there.
"Show this card
"at any participating
Orlando-area Exxon station
to get your free
Save The Tiger poster."
All right,
just give me that.
And give me some
of those Sweet'N Lows.
[♪]
[OPERA MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Ooh, yeah.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Who is it?
It's Newman.
What do you want?
I'm in the middle of something.
I can't believe
I'm being evicted.
What?
What are you talking about?
The reverse peepholes.
Silvio says I'm an agitator
and I'm out of the building.
No, he can't do that.
I'm homeless.
I'm gonna be out on the street
corner dancing for nickels.
I'll be with the hobos
in the train yard
eating out of a bucket.
We'll go and talk to him
and straighten
this whole thing out.
Uh, you, uh--
You better put something on.
[STAMMERING]
[♪]
JERRY:
George, I am loving this no-wallet thing.
A man carries a wallet.
You know, the very fact
that you oppose this
makes me think
I'm onto something.
Hey, Jerry.
Hey, Joe Mayo.
Nice place.
Thanks. George, can you do me
a favor and stay by the phone
in case anybody calls
and needs directions?
Love to.
Thanks.
Jerry--
Music?
Actually, can you keep an eye
on the aquarium
and make sure nobody
taps on the glass?
But I could do that
and the music.
Oh, no, don't worry about
the music, just have fun.
I was ready
to get jiggy with it.
Hey.
Hey, Elaine.
I think you know
Dr. Zaius.
So, Elaine, notice anything
different about my pants?
So, George,
did you get the chair?
No, I-I don't have it yet.
So we're giving him nothing?
No, I brought a picture
of the chair.
Did you at least
get him a card?
I thought we'd all sign
the picture.
Elaine.
Hey, Joe Mayo.
I need you to be
in charge of coats.
Oh, fantastic.
All right.
[QUIETLY]
There you go.
And, Puddy, can you make sure
nobody puts a drink
on my sound system?
Sure thing, Joe Mayo.
Hi. I'm Jerry.
How do you like my pants?
Nice.
It's working.
[TAPPING]
Don't tap on the glass.
[PHONE RINGS]
Joe Mayo's apartment.
Hey!
Cocktail off the speaker.
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
Goodbye, Dr. Zaius.
[♪]
Why are we in Jerry's
apartment?
Well, I, uh-- I like to think
of this as my conference room.
Yeah, it has
a more formal atmosphere,
you know, with the shelves
and the--
The furniture.
Make it quick,
Kramer.
My wife and I are
about to go bowling.
Oh. Well, um,
Newman thinks that, uh,
you evicted him?
I did.
I don't like Mr. Newman.
He is an agitator.
Look,
I've known Newman all my life,
in the building,
and you're all wrong about him.
He's a model tenant.
Portly, yes,
but smart as a whip.
Okay, on your word,
he can stay.
All right.
But I'm gonna keep
my eye on him.
Well, you won't regret it.
What's wrong?
[SIZZLES]
[♪]
JOE:
Elaine, thanks for coming.
Good working
with you.
All right,
let's hit the bricks.
What?
Hey, I got a coat
just like this.
Oh. Ooh...
[♪]
ELAINE:
So Joe Mayo had the same coat.
And you threw it out the window?
Mm-hm.
God, you're like a rock star.
So now Joe Mayo wants me
to buy him a new coat.
Because you threw it out?
No, because I was in charge
of the coats.
It's insane.
But you did actually throw
his coat out the window.
But he doesn't
know that.
As far as he knows,
someone stole it.
And that's the person who should
be held responsible.
But that's you.
So I guess I'll have
to buy him a new coat,
even though I don't think
I should be held responsible,
which I am anyway.
Well, I'm satisfied.
[GROANS]
My back is killing me.
Of course,
because of that wallet.
You-- You got a filing cabinet
under half of your ass.
This is an organizer,
a secretary,
and a friend.
ELAINE:
Look at you,
you're on a slant.
Here, just give me
a couple of napkins.
There. There, I'm fine.
[CRUNCH]
What was that?
I think I had some
hard candy in there.
[♪]
GEORGE:
No, no, this is supposed to go to Joe Mayo's apartment.
[GRUNTS]
How does this thing work?
[CHAIR WHIRRING]
Ah.
So do you want me
to deliver this chair
to your friend's place
or not?
Ahhh.
[♪]
Ready to go?
All set. I can't believe
we're going dancing.
You don't go that often?
No, because it's so stupid.
Shall we?
Do me a favor.
Can you hold this stuff for me?
Compact, lipstick,
all this?
And can you also carry
my keys?
What are you,
a medieval dungeon master?
And a tin of Altoids.
Man.
[KEYS JANGLING]
Ow. Sharp key.
So you're sleeping
with Silvio's wife?
Well, there's very little
sleeping going on.
Why didn't you tell me
about this?
Uh, frankly, I don't see how
it's any of your business.
Well, it's my business now.
Look,
I stuck up for you.
Man, if he catches you,
we're both out.
Hey, what is that
up that tree?
[EXHALES]
Man, that looks like
a dead bear.
No, that's a fur coat.
Hey, uh, give me a boost.
[GRUNTING]
Where did you learn
to climb trees like that?
The Pacific Northwest.
[♪]
So you had to carry some
of Keri's stuff, big deal.
You don't understand. I went
on a successful pocket diet,
and I want to keep
that weight off.
You know what? We sell
this thing at Peterman
that would be perfect
for you.
Not more of that crap
from the Titanic?
No, no.
It's a small men's carryall.
I'm not carrying
a purse.
It's not a purse.
It's European.
Oh.
Hey,
did George buy Joe Mayo
that chair yet?
I don't know.
If I'm getting him
a new fur,
I'm not chipping in
on a gift too. [RINGING]
GEORGE [GRUNTING]:
Yeah?
Hey, George, did you get
Joe Mayo that chair yet?
Not yet. Oh.
Ho-ho! God!
What?
It's in...
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
transit.
Did he get it?
No.
Mm, good.
Tell him I'm out.
What, she's out?
Well, so what?
You're getting a deal.
We'll split it three ways.
All right!
What is that noise?
That's my toaster.
I gotta go.
[GEORGE GRUNTING]
You know, sometimes
I get the feeling
George isn't being
completely honest with me.
Hey.
Oh, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Here are your pliers back.
Oh, thanks.
Weak hinge.
Well, I guess I'd better go
and price fur coats.
Oh, go down to 88th street.
They're free.
What are you talking about?
Well, they're hanging
from the trees.
You know, Newman found
one there yesterday.
Man, that guy can climb
like a ring-tailed lemur.
88th street?
That's where Joe Mayo lives.
That's the coat!
[CRUNCH]
What was that pop sound?
Well, I had some hard candy
in there!
[♪]
NEWMAN:
So to what do I owe this unusual invitation?
Come in, come in.
Ah.
This is very much
as I imagined it to be...
aside from this rattan piece,
which seems oddly out of place.
Okay.
Please, sit down.
Newman, um,
I wanted to talk to you
about something.
This isn't about
my opening your mail?
What?
I don't. Never have.
Anything I read
was already open.
Uh, no, no, Newman,
ahem,
I heard that you found
a fur coat in a tree?
And I believe that it belongs
to a friend of mine,
and I'd like
to give it back to him.
Sorry. Climber's keepers.
[SIGHS]
You know, Newmie--
[CLEARS THROAT]
--I know how you feel
about me,
and I have to tell you
I'm quite flattered. Heh-heh.
You are?
Oh, yeah. I mean,
of all the men that I know,
you're the only one
who's held down a steady job
for several years.
Well, it's--
It's interesting work.
I don't mind it.
[CHUCKLES]
Don't you have a boyfriend,
a-a burly, athletic type?
Oh, him? Oh, don't worry.
He's cool.
Cool?
Very cool.
So, what do you say?
Can you do me
this one little favor,
Newmie?
Oh, how I've waited
for this moment.
But, alas, my heart belongs
to another man's wife,
and I have given
the coat to her.
All right,
we're done here.
For I am in love
with Svetlana,
and I don't care
if the whole world knows,
except for Silvio, who would
throw me out of the apartment,
where I would be dancing on--
Thank you.
Thank you,
thank you very much.
[♪]
Nice carryall.
It's European.
Do you still have
my lipstick?
Uh, yeah, I think I do.
I can never find anything
in here.
Oh, here it is.
Thanks.
So that Joe Mayo throws
the worst parties, doesn't he?
What was your job?
My job was to keep you away
from the music.
What? He doesn't like
my taste in music?
Guess not.
You should have
been there last year.
I got jiggy with it.
[♪]
Kramer, it's Silvio!
Open up,
I need to talk to you!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I can see you
through the reverse peephole!
Stupid thing.
[CHUCKLING]
Hey, Silvio.
Look at this.
Huh?
Svetlana says she find it
in the laundry room,
but I think it is a gift
from that postman agitator.
Where is he?!
Now, relax, Silvio.
No, that's it.
You're both out of the building!
Oh, come on! Newman didn't
even give her that.
No, it's-- That's not even
a woman's coat.
That's a--
That's a man's.
A man's?
Yeah.
What kind of a man
would wear fur?
Oh, lots of them.
Yeah.
Would you?
No.
Then who?
What about Jerry?
Jerry?
Yeah, sure.
He's a celebrity.
Oh, yeah, they wear
a lot of furs.
They're desperate,
insecure people.
Yes, you are right.
It's all about:
"Me, me, me.
"Please, look at me.
I am so pretty.
Love me! Want me!"
Yeah, something
like that.
[♪]
JERRY:
I have to do what?
All you have to do
is wear the fur
so Silvio thinks it's yours.
I'm not wearing the fur.
Well, then Newman and I, we get
thrown out of the building.
Is that right?
All right, why don't you
just take a good hard look
at what your life will be like
if I'm not around.
Newman too?
Oh, come on, man!
Well, I'll tell you what,
if you do this,
I'll give you that Walkman
you're always asking about.
That's my Walkman.
And you'll get it back.
All right.
All right, good.
Thanks. I owe you one.
Hey.
Oh, hey,
and by the way,
that Walkman was broke
when you gave it to me.
George, did you get
that chair yet?
It gets here when it gets here.
Stop riding me.
You know what? Just call up
and cancel it. I'm out.
Excuse me?
Joe Mayo doesn't like
my taste in music,
he's not getting
a gift from me.
I can't believe
you're dropping out too.
So now Kramer and I have
to pay for the entire gift?
Whoa, whoa.
Now, who's this Joe Mayo
everyone's talking about?
He's the guy we're buying
the chair for, remember?
It was your suggestion.
I think the chair is
a fantastic gift idea,
but I never heard
of this Joe Mayo.
And frankly,
it sounds made-up.
Oh, so now I have to buy
the whole chair by myself?!
No, you don't have
to buy anything.
I already bought it!
I've been lying to you
for three days,
and now you're all screwing me!
I don't understand.
Why didn't you tell us
you had it?
I needed it.
My back is a little tweaked.
Because of your giant wallet.
Just get rid of it.
Never.
It is a part of me.
I will just return the chair,
and it will be easy,
because the receipt
is in my good friend.
Your good friend
is morbidly obese.
Well, at least
I'm not carrying a purse.
It's not a purse!
It's European!
All right,
Silvio's down there.
He's shoveling the walk.
Now, all you got to do
is put this on,
you go down to the corner,
you pick up a paper,
and you come right back.
All right.
There you go.
How do I look?
Odd.
[♪]
"Learn guitar,
first lesson free."
Heh.
Well...
[GRUNTS]
My receipts!
The chair!
My tiger poster!
Hey, Silvio.
Just out for a little stroll
in my favorite fur coat.
That is your coat?
It sure is.
Kramer says you need it
because you're an entertainer
and you're desperate
for attention.
That's true.
Jerry, you forgot
your purse.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, Silvio,
look at Jerry here,
prancing around in his coat
with his purse.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yep, he's a dandy.
He's a real fancy boy.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Maybe this isn't my coat.
All right,
you're not fancy!
No, he's very fancy!
"Want me! Love me!
Shower me with kisses!"
Mwah! Mwah, mwah, mwah!
[LAUGHS]
Jerry,
where'd you get it?
That's his coat.
No, it's not.
It's mine.
I'm a fancy boy.
That's not your coat.
If that is not his coat,
whose coat is it?
It's Joe Mayo's coat.
Who's Joe Mayo?
Uh, he must be the man
that's sleeping with your wife.
Hey!
[GASPS]
Hey! Hey!
Officer!
KRAMER:
There he goes!
Someone took
my European carryall!
Your what?
It's a black leather thing
with a strap.
You mean, a purse?
Yes, a purse!
I carry a purse!
[♪]
So Silvio ambushed
Joe Mayo?
Yeah, he was waiting inside
his apartment for him
with a sock full
of pennies.
He should have had
a reverse peephole.
Hey, babe.
JERRY:
Hello? Hello?
What is that?
It's my new coat.
You ditched the fur?
Yeah, I saw Jerry wearing his.
He looked like a bit of a dandy.
Check it out.
Eight ball.
You got a question,
you ask the eight ball.
You're gonna wear this
all the time?
All signs point to yes!
[♪]
♪ I'm on a Mexican radio ♪