All right,
be careful with the car.
Yeah, yeah.
And don't move the seat.
I've got it
where I like it.
Goodbye.
Two and 10, babe.
Okay.
Don't peel out.
I won't.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
♪ Jesus is one
Jesus is all ♪
♪ Jesus picks me up
When I fall-- ♪
MAN 1 [OVER RADIO]:
And he said unto Abraham--
CHOIR:
♪ Amen, amen ♪
MAN 2:
So we pray--
WOMAN:
Faith--
MAN 3:
Jesus!
Jesus?
[♪]
KRUGER:
According to our latest quarterly...thing,
Kruger Industrial Smoothing
is heading into the red.
Or the black, or--
Whatever the bad one is.
Any thoughts?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Well, I, um--
I know, uh, when I'm
a little strapped, heh,
I sometimes drop off
my rent check
having "forgotten"
to sign it.
That could-- That could
buy us some time.
Works for me.
Good thinking, George.
Good idea.
All right, George.
Way to go, man.
Heh. Or we, uh--
We don't even send
the check,
and then when they call,
we pretend
we're the cleaning service.
[CHUCKLES]
[IN FOREIGN ACCENT]
Hello? I sorry.
No here Kruger.
Are you done?
Silly voices.
Come on, people,
let's get real.
Good one.
Whew.
That was bad.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I had 'em, Jerry.
They loved me.
And then?
I lost 'em.
I can usually come up with one
good comment during a meeting,
but by the end,
it's buried
under a pile
of gaffes and bad puns.
Showmanship, George.
When you hit that high note,
you say good night
and walk off.
I can't just leave.
That's the way
they do it in Vegas.
You never played Vegas.
I hear things.
Here's one.
I borrowed Puddy's car,
and all the presets
on his radio
were Christian
rock stations.
I like
Christian Rock.
It's very positive.
It's not like
those real musicians
who think
they're so cool and hip.
So you think that Puddy
actually believes in something?
I mean, it's--
It's a used car.
He probably never changed
the presets.
Yes, he is lazy.
Probably doesn't know how
to program the buttons.
Yes. He is dumb.
So you prefer dumb and lazy
to religious?
Dumb and lazy
I understand.
Mmm.
Tell you how
you could check.
How?
Reprogram all the buttons,
see if he changes them back.
You know?
The old switcheroo.
No, no, the old switcheroo
is you poison your drink,
and then you switch it
with the other person's.
No, it's doing the same thing
to someone that they did to you.
Yeah, Elaine's gonna do
the same thing to Puddy's radio
that the radio did to her.
Well, that's
the gist of it.
Quiet! Ugh.
So where is
this Sophie?
She's picking me up
in a few minutes.
How long have
you two been together?
I don't know,
since the last one.
Oh, here she is.
You want to meet her?
BOTH: Nah.
By the way, how did Puddy
get back in the picture?
I, uh--
I-- I needed
to move a bureau.
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Jerry,
you got any pepper?
Hey, Jerry.
Hey, Mickey.
Check the pepper shaker.
KRAMER: Yeah.
Hey, Mickey.
[SNIFFS]
[SNEEZES]
See? It should sound
like that.
Something like that.
Ee-ah-choo!
A little wetter.
See, I didn't believe it.
Wh-what's
with the fake sneezing?
We're going down
to Mount Sinai Hospital.
See, they hire actors
to help
the students practice
diagnosing.
They assign you
a specific disease
and you act out the symptoms.
It's an easy gig.
Yeah. Wow!
Do medical schools
actually do this?
Well, the better ones.
All right,
let's practice retching, huh?
Ready?
[BOTH GAG]
[PHONE RINGING]
I think the phone
is ringing. [BOTH GAG]
Would you hold it
a second?!
[PHONE RINGING]
Thank you. Will you get out
of here with that stuff?
Mickey, D.T.'s, huh?
Hello.
Hey, it's me.
Elaine?
No, it's me.
George?
Jerry, it's Sophie.
I can't believe
you don't recognize my voice.
Oh!
I knew it was you.
I was joking.
I'm a comedian.
You got any ipecac?
Ipecac?
Kramer, I really think you guys
are going too far with this.
No. Mickey,
he swallowed 12 aspirin.
Did he overdose?
No, it's just too much.
[♪]
KRUGER:
And it gets worse.
The team working
on the statue
in Lafayette Square
kind of over-smoothed it.
They ground the head down
to about the size
of a softball.
And that spells trouble.
All right, well,
why don't we smooth the head
down to nothing,
stick a pumpkin
under its arm
and change the nameplate
to Ichabod Crane?
[ALL LAUGHING]
All right.
That's it for me.
Be good, everybody.
[LAUGHING]
Ichabod Crane.
[♪]
In your packets
you will find the disease
you have been assigned
and the symptoms
you will need to exhibit.
"Bacterial meningitis."
Jackpot!
"Gonorrhea"?
[EXHALES]
You wanna trade?
Sorry, buddy.
This is the Hamlet
of diseases.
Severe pain, nausea,
delusions.
It's got everything.
How 'bout you?
You wanna trade?
Sure.
Okay, what do you got?
The surgeon left
a sponge inside me.
[EXHALES]
Good luck with that. Heh.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I knew I had hit my high note,
so I, uh...
I thanked the crowd,
and I was gone. Heh.
What'd you do
the rest of the day?
Saw Titanic.
Mmm.
So that old woman...
she's just a liar, right?
And a bit of a tramp
if you ask me.
Hello, boys.
Hey,
so did you give that radio
the old switcheroo?
I did.
And the Christian rock?
Resurrected.
And look what I pried
off of his bumper,
a Jesus fish.
Jerry,
you have any fish sticks?
No.
So you're disappointed
he's a spiritual person?
Well, yeah. I got him because
he seemed so one-dimensional.
I feel misled.
I think it's neat.
You don't hear that much
about God anymore.
I hear things.
Hey, so Sophie gave me the
"it's me" on the phone today.
It's me?
Isn't that
a little premature?
I thought so.
She's not a "me."
I'm a "me."
I'm against
all "it's me's."
So self-absorbed
and egotistical.
It's like those
hip musicians
with their
complicated shoes.
Well...
I got gonorrhea.
That seems about right.
That's what they gave me.
They?
The government?
No. No.
He's pretending
he's got gonorrhea
so med students
can diagnose it.
And it's a waste
of my talent.
It's just
a little burning.
Mickey,
he got bacterial meningitis.
Well, I guess there are
no small diseases,
only small actors.
[ALL LAUGHING]
All right,
that's it for me.
Have a good one, everybody.
What was that?
Showmanship. George is trying
to get out on a high note.
Showmanship.
Maybe that's what
my gonorrhea's missing.
Yes,
step into that spotlight
and belt that gonorrhea
out to the back row.
Yes. Yes, I will.
I'm gonna make people
feel my gonorrhea.
And feel the gonorrhea
in themselves.
[♪]
And are you experiencing
any discomfort?
Just a little burning
during urination.
Okay.
Any other pain?
The haunting memories
of lost love.
May I? Lights.
Our eyes met across
the crowded hat store.
I, a customer...
and she a coquettish
haberdasher.
Ooh, I pursued and...
she withdrew...
and she pursued,
and I withdrew.
And so we danced.
And I burned for her.
Much like the burning
during urination
that I would experience
soon afterwards.
Gonorrhea.
MICKEY:
Yes!
[♪]
JERRY:
One message. I hope it's not from you.
SOPHIE [OVER MACHINE]:
Hey, Jerry, it's me. Call me back.
Sophie.
She's still doing that?
Yep.
All right,
I tell you what you do.
You call her back
and give her the "it's me," huh?
Pull the old switcheroo.
I think that's
a "what's good for the goose
is good for the gander."
What the hell
is a gander anyway?
It's a goose that's had
the old switcheroo pulled on it.
Hi, Sophie, it's me.
Hey, Rafe.
She thinks
it's someone named Rafe.
Good, good. Let her think it.
[DEEP VOICE]
So what's going on?
Not a lot.
Ask about you.
So, uh,
how are things with Jerry?
Oh, I really like him,
but, well...
I still haven't told him
the tractor story.
Right, right,
Are you sick, Rafe?
You sound kind of funny.
I sound funny?
Abort. Abort.
Yeah, I better get
to a doctor, bye.
[NORMAL VOICE]
That was close.
What drives me
to take chances like that?
That was very real.
She said there's
some tractor story
that she hasn't
told me about.
Whoa. Back it up,
back it up.
Beep, beep, beep.
Tractor story?
Beep, beep, beep?
What are you doing?
[♪]
ELAINE:
So where do you wanna eat?
Feels like
an Arby's night.
Arby's.
Beef and cheese and...
do you believe in God?
Yes.
Oh.
So you're pretty religious?
That's right.
So is it a problem
that I'm not really religious?
Not for me.
Why not?
I'm not the one going
to hell.
[♪]
GEORGE:
You know what I think?
I bet she stole
a tractor.
No one's stealing
It's a 5-mile-an-hour
getaway.
We're dancing
around the obvious.
It's gotta be disfigurement.
Does she walk around
holding a pen
she never seems to need?
No, she looks
completely normal.
Oh, okay.
Here it is.
I got it.
She lost her thumbs
in a tractor accident,
and they grafted
her big toes on.
They do it every day.
You think she's got toes
for thumbs?
How's her handshake?
Little firm, isn't it?
Maybe a little too firm?
I don't know.
Hands a little smelly?
Why do I seek
your counsel?
Well, I'm going to hell.
That seems about right.
According to Puddy.
Have you heard the one
about the guy in hell
with the coffee and doughnuts--
I'm not in the mood.
I'll have some coffee
and a doughnut.
What do you care?
You don't believe in hell.
I know, but he does.
So it's more
of a relationship problem
than the final destination
of your soul?
Well, relationships
are very important to me.
Maybe you can have one
with the prince of darkness
as you burn
for all eternity.
And a slice
of devil's food cake.
[♪]
GEORGE [LAUGHING]:
Hey, hey.
Where is, uh, everyone?
They're all
off the project.
They were boring.
George,
you are my main man.
I am?
I don't know what it is.
I can't put my finger on it,
but lately,
you have just seemed on.
And you always leave me
wanting more.
This is a huge project
involving...
lots of numbers
and papers and folders.
I'm not too worried
about it.
Let's get started.
Okay.
George, check it out.
Yeah?
Three times around
with no feet. Hm?
All me.
All me. Heh.
[♪]
All right, and here are
your ailments for this week.
By the way, Mr. Kramer,
you were excellent.
Oh,
thank you.
Cirrhosis of the liver
with jaundice.
All right.
I get to wear makeup.
What did you get?
Gonorrhea.
Uh, excuse me.
I think there's been a mistake.
See, I had gonorrhea
last week.
Oh, it's no mistake.
We loved what you did with it.
Boy, I don't believe this.
I'm being typecast.
[♪]
I move my knight here.
Check.
They should update
these pieces.
Nobody rides horses anymore.
Maybe they should
change it to a tractor.
Jerry, are you embarrassed
that you're losing?
Losing?
You know, yesterday I lost
control of my car,
almost bought the farm.
Bought the farm?
Tractor.
This is an odd side
of you, Jerry.
I feel uncomfortable.
Wait, don't go.
Let's thumb wrestle.
[♪]
GEORGE:
A scar?
A big, long scar,
where her leg would dangle
when she's riding a...
A tractor.
I'm sure she's
a little self-conscious
and doesn't like to talk
about it.
Don't see why she's
more self-conscious
about that
than her toe-thumbs.
She doesn't have
toe-thumbs.
Well, if she keeps horsing
around with those trac--
All right.
How's the two-man operation
at Kruger?
Heh. Two-man. It's all me.
Kruger doesn't do anything.
He disappears
for hours at a time,
gives me fake excuses.
This afternoon, I found him
with sleep creases on his face.
The only reason I got out
to get a bite today
was that he finally promised
to buckle down
and do some actual work.
GEORGE:
Oh, I don't believe this.
This is what I have
to put up with, Jerry.
Mr. Kruger.
Mm?
Who said he was going to do
some actual work today? Who?
I'm not too worried
about it.
Well, I am.
Couldn't you try to go
through some of that stuff
I put in your shoebox?
All right, all right,
I'm going.
Ho-ho!
Have you ever seen anything
like this?
Never.
[♪]
Elaine, they forgot
to deliver your paper today.
Why don't you, uh,
just grab that one?
That belongs to Mr. Potato guy.
That's his.
Come on, get it.
Well, if you want it,
you get it.
Sorry.
Thou shalt not steal.
Oh, but it's okay for me?
What do you care?
You know where you're going.
All right, that is it.
I can't live like this.
Oh, no.
Come on!
All right, what did I do?
David,
I'm going to hell.
The worst place
in the world.
With devils and those--
Those caves and--
And the ragged clothing.
And the heat.
My God, the heat!
I mean, what do you think
about all that?
It's gonna be rough.
Ugh. You should be
trying to save me.
Don't boss me. This is why
you're going to hell.
I am not going to hell.
And if you think
I'm going to hell,
you should care
that I'm going to hell.
Even though I am not.
You stole my Jesus fish,
didn't ya?
Yeah, that's right.
[GROWLING]
[♪]
MICKEY:
Oh, my liver.
Why did I drink
for all those years?
Why did I look for love
in a bottle?
Mr. Kramer, you're up.
I'm here.
Wait a minute.
What?
You are doing gonorrhea,
aren't you?
Yeah, well, we'll see.
So, uh, what seems to be
bothering you today, Mr. Kramer?
Well, I... I guess it started
about 20 years ago
when I got back
from Vietnam.
And this was the only friend
I had left.
MICKEY:
Hey! That's my cirrhosis.
He's stealing
my cirrhosis.
You want to be sick?
I'll make you sick.
Cirrhosis of the liver
and, uh...
PCP addiction?
[YELLING]
[♪]
MAN:
Let me see if I understand this.
You're concerned
that he isn't concerned
that you're going
to hell.
And you feel
that she's too bossy.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, oftentimes, in cases
of interfaith marriages,
couples have difficulty--
ELAINE:
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No one's getting married here.
You aren't?
No.
Oh.
We're just, you know,
having a good time.
Oh.
Well, then it's simple.
You're both going to hell.
No way.
This is bogus, man.
Well, thank you, Father.
Oh, oh, did you hear the one
about the new guy in hell
who's talking to the devil
by the coffee machine?
I'm really not in the mood.
I'm going to hell.
Ah, lighten up.
It'll only feel
like an eternity.
[LAUGHING]
[GROWLING]
[♪]
You know, Jerry,
there's this thing
that I haven't
told you about.
See...
there was this tractor
and...
[SIGHS]
Oh, boy, this is...
This is really difficult.
Sophie, it's me.
I know about
the tractor story.
And I'm fine with it.
How could you know?
Shh. Shh. Shh.
It's not important.
What's important
is I'm not gonna let
a little thing like that
ruin what could be
a very long-term
and meaningful relationship.
KRAMER:
I didn't say that. No.
You gave me gonorrhea.
You didn't even tell me.
Well, I'm sorry.
I gave you gonorrhea
because I thought
you'd have fun with it.
Hey, hey,
I'm with someone.
Oh. Hello.
No, I understand.
This could be
a tough thing to deal with.
The important thing
is that you have a partner
who's supportive.
You know...
she's right.
Unfortunately,
I didn't have a partner.
I got gonorrhea
from a tractor.
You got gonorrhea
from a tractor?
And you call that
the tractor story?
You can't get it
from that.
But I did. My boyfriend
said I got gonorrhea
from riding the tractor
in my bathing suit.
All right,
that's it for me.
You've been great.
Good night, everybody.
[♪]
Would you mind helping me out
with some of this stuff?!
You seem like you got
a pretty good handle on it.
No, I don't!
Don't you even care?
This is your company.
It's your name on the outside
of the building.
Speaking of which,
the R fell off,
and all it says now
is K-uger.
K-uger? That sounds like one of
those old-time car horns, huh?
[IMITATING CAR HORN]
K-uger. K-uger.
Oh-ho. Ho!
You are too much,
Mr. Kruger. Too much.
Thank you, George.
You've been great.
That's it for me.
No, no. You're not going out on
a high note with me, Mr. Kruger.
[IMITATING CAR HORN]
It's K-uger.
No. No!
Good night, everybody.