FRANK:
I got no legroom back here.
Move your seat forward.
It's as far
as it goes.
There's a mechanism.
You just pull it
and throw your body weight.
I pulled it.
It doesn't go.
If you want the legroom,
say you want the legroom!
Don't blame the mechanism!
All right, Dad,
we're five blocks
from the house.
Sit sideways.
Like an animal.
Because of her,
I have to sit here
like an animal.
Serenity now!
What is that?
Doctor gave me
a relaxation cassette.
When my blood pressure
gets too high,
the man on the tape
tells me to say,
serenity now!
Are you supposed
to yell it?
The man on the tape
wasn't specific.
What happened to the screen
door? It blew off again?
I told you
to fix that thing.
Serenity now!
[♪]
So I told Bobby and Lisa
we'd try
that new Chinese/Spanish place,
La Caridad, on Saturday.
I thought we had tickets
to the Knicks' home opener.
I thought this was more fun,
so I gave the tickets away.
What?
All right. Fine.
Are you mad at me?
No. Uh...
I love a good Chinese/Spanish
whatever-it-is.
You know,
I've never seen you mad.
I get peeved.
Mad.
Miffed.
Irked?
I would like to see you
get really mad.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Why does she want you to be mad?
She says I suppress
my emotions.
So, what do you care
what she thinks?
Good body.
She probably gets that
impression because you're cool.
You're under control.
Like me.
Nothing wrong with that.
But I get upset.
I've yelled.
You've heard me yell.
Not really. Your voice
kind of raises
to this comedic pitch.
Hey.
Kramer, I am so sick
of you coming in here
and eating all my food.
Now, shut that door
and get the hell out of here!
[LAUGHS]
What is that,
a new bit?
GEORGE:
I told you.
Hey, any of you guys want
to come out
and help me fix my father's
screen door in Queens?
Sorry, I'm fixing
a screen door in the Bronx.
I'll do it.
Really? You-- You want to come?
Yeah. I love going
to the country.
[LAUGHS]
Where are they going?
Fix a screen door
in Queens.
[LAUGHS]
That's funny.
Hey, listen,
what are you doing Saturday?
Not going to the Knick game.
I need somebody
to go with me
to Mr. Lippman's
son's bar mitzvah.
You know, if you don't bring
a guest, they save on catering.
You should be able
to buy a cheaper gift.
Oh, I don't think
that's possible.
[RATTLES]
[♪]
Now, get a little closer,
'cause I can't see
the screen door.
Yeah...
Perfect.
Dad, the hinges
are all rusted here.
That's why the wind keeps
blowing the door off.
ESTELLE:
I hate that old door.
Throw it out!
Serenity now!
It might be time
to just let her go, Frank.
She's worked hard
for you.
Will you put her to rest for me?
Oh, yeah.
I'll take good care of her.
ESTELLE:
And get George to put those boxes in the garage!
Dad, what is all this?
ESTELLE:
It's junk.
My computers.
I've been selling them
for two months now.
Shut up!
You're selling computers?
Two months ago,
I saw a provocative movie
on cable TV.
It was called The Net,
with that girl from the bus.
I did a little reading,
and I realize
it wasn't that far-fetched.
Dad, do you know
what it takes to compete
with Microsoft and IBM?
Yes, I do.
That's why I've got
a secret weapon.
My son.
[♪]
JERRY:
Damn it, they gave me cream.
I asked for nonfat milk!
I think they have 1 percent
over there.
One percent?
They can kiss 1 percent
of my ass!
Okay, Jerry, enough.
I'm not buying it.
You're damn right
you're not buying it!
You shouldn't have to try.
It's just being open.
I'm open.
There's just nothing in there.
Uh-huh.
Think I'm lying about this?
I think you are.
Well, I'm not.
Yes, you are, liar.
Oh, stop it.
Okay, liar.
That's enough!
Ooh, that was good.
Really? It felt good.
ELAINE:
Congratulations, Mr. Lippman.
Oh, Elaine.
[CHUCKLING]
Hi.
My boy's a man today.
Can you believe it?
Oh,
He's a man.
congratulations, Adam--
[GRUNTING]
I'm a man!
[♪]
JERRY:
Tongue?
Yeah.
Wow.
I didn't try that
till I was 23.
Boy, this kid's not just a man.
He's a man's man.
And I think he's been
telling his friends.
I got invitations
to six more bar mitzvahs.
[RINGS]
Hello?
Yeah, this is
Jerry Seinfeld.
No, no, no,
I do not want to stop over
in Cincinnati!
Well, then you upgrade me.
That's right,
you should thank me!
Goodbye.
Hey, I'm flying first-class.
Where did that
come from?
Patty showed me
how to get mad.
You got a problem
with that?
No.
Good.
All right, relax, tough guy.
I gotta get out
to my father's garage.
Help him sell some computers.
The two of you working
in that little garage
is like a steel-cage
death-match.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
Kramer?
Hey.
What--? What are you doing?
Oh, I'm putting up
Frank's screen door.
Yeah, this beauty's got
a little life in her yet.
What do you need it for?
The cool evening breezes
of Anytown, U.S.A.
Let's see how
this baby closes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[♪]
Morning, Ma.
ESTELLE:
You're late!
Morning, Dad.
I am not Dad
in the workplace.
My professional name
is Mr. Costanza,
and I will refer to you
as Costanza.
FRANK:
Morning, Braun.
Hey, George.
Two cream, no sugar.
What is Lloyd Braun
doing here?
Your mother recommended him.
Yeah, of course she did.
That's all I ever heard
growing up:
"Why can't you be more
like Lloyd Braun?"
You know he was
in a mental institution?
I didn't read his résumé.
[DINGS]
Another sale, Mr. Costanza.
Chalk me up
on the big board.
What is this?
This is your lagging.
Good work, Braun.
ESTELLE:
Good for you, Lloyd!
[♪]
ELAINE:
So, Adam, I just talked to your father
and apology accepted.
I'm not apologizing.
It was great.
I told everyone.
Yeah, I know.
Uh, by the way,
could you do me a favor
and tell Mitchell Tanenbaum
that I will be unable
to attend this Saturday?
Are you free Friday night?
I am, but that is not the point.
You are 13,
and I am in my early...
20s.
But I'm a man.
The rabbi said so.
No. You are not a man.
It takes a long time
to become a man.
I mean, half my friends
aren't even there yet.
Well, if I'm not a man,
then this whole thing
was a sham.
First they said I was gonna
get great gifts,
and then somebody
gives me Boggle.
I renounce my religion!
Who wants cookies?
As of this moment,
I am no longer Jewish!
I quit!
[MOUTHS]
What?
[CHUCKLING]
Mmm.
FRANK:
You're late again, Costanza, so listen up.
Starting tonight, we're having
a little sales contest.
The loser gets fired,
the winner gets
a Waterpik.
ESTELLE:
You're not giving away our Waterpik!
Serenity now!
You know what?
It doesn't matter,
because I quit.
I guess your mother
was right.
You never could compete
with Lloyd Braun!
[DINGS]
All right.
You wanna sell computers?
I will show you
how to sell computers.
[ANGRILY]
Hello, Mr. Finerman,
you wanna buy a computer?
No? Why not?
All right, I see!
Good answer!
Thank you.
[DINGING]
Serenity now!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Adam, you don't become a man overnight.
Look at your father.
It takes time, patience,
experience, uh,
several careers
of varying success.
I mean, these are things
that I look for in a man.
Well, that does me
a lot of good.
"Early 20s."
Well, I'm sorry, sir.
I tried.
So that's the type of guy
you're looking for?
[SIGHING]
Oh, I guess so.
Why?
What is this?
Anytown, U.S.A.
Hello. Is Kramer home?
Oh. Hey.
Hello, neighbor.
Boy, those azaleas
are really coming in nicely.
Oh, you gotta mulch.
You've got to.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
You barbecuing tonight?
Yeah. Right after the fireworks.
[TINKLING]
So where do you want
to eat tonight?
Well, how 'bout going back
to La Caridad?
[ANGRILY]
Again?
How much flan
can a person eat?
Jerry, you've been yelling at me
all afternoon.
Well, I don't think
more flan is the answer!
Maybe I should
just leave.
Maybe?
Goodbye!
Double goodbye.
Hey, buddy.
Hey. Happy New Year.
Y'all come back real--
Did you and Patty
just break up? Yeah.
In fact, she broke up with me.
And I don't wanna talk
about it!
Well, then you're free tonight.
I heard about this great place
called La Caridad.
[DOOR OPENS]
That's the last thing
she said to me.
She wanted to go there also,
but I wasn't in the mood.
Whoa. What is the matter?
It's Patty.
Jerry, you break up
with a girl every week.
What--? What is this
salty discharge?
Oh, my God.
You're crying.
This is horrible.
I care.
[♪]
JERRY:
Patty won't call me back.
I don't know
if I can live without her.
Well, she's really gotten
to you, hasn't she?
I don't know
what's happening to me.
Well, it's simple.
You let out one emotion,
all the rest
will come with it.
It's like Endora's box.
That was the mother
on Bewitched.
You mean Pandora.
Yeah, well, she had one too.
Jerry, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Oh, gee--!
That's it! That's it.
I warned you kids.
I told you not to play
in front of my house.
This time I'm keeping it.
And you're not getting
your rock back either.
Hall urchins.
Are you still
down in the dumps?
Come on.
It's just a chick.
You ever hear of a little thing
called feelings?
Well, I got just the thing
to cheer you up.
A computer. Huh?
Well, you can check porn
and stock quotes.
Porn quotes.
I'm so lucky to have a friend
like you, George.
Well...
Ever tell you
how much I love you?
What?
I love you, George.
Come here.
I-- I'm already here.
I'm here. I'm here.
Uh, you know what? If you want
a computer, call me.
I-- I-- I-- I gotta go.
Go wherever you want.
I'm still gonna love you.
Hey. Look what they did.
Look what they did
to my house.
I turn my back
for two seconds,
and they put shaving cream
all over the door.
Yeah, I see you!
I'll teach these kids
a lesson.
Where's that hose
I put under your sink?
Hose under my sink.
I love you, Kramer.
I love you too, buddy.
And, George--
I don't wanna hear it.
When I give you the signal,
turn this water on full blast.
Signal?
What--? What signal?
I don't know.
I'll yell, uh, "hoochie mama."
All right, if-- If I do it,
will you buy a computer?
On the signal, George,
on the signal.
Only if you buy.
I gotta make a sale.
I love you, Costanza.
All right, will you shut up?!
Now! Now, George!
Turn on the faucet!
George,
turn on the faucet!
Hoochie mama!
[SOBBING]
[♪]
ELAINE:
So now the other Lippman kissed me.
Well, sure. They're Jewish,
and you're a shiksa.
What?
It means non-Jewish woman.
I know what it means,
but what does being a shiksa
have to do with it?
You've got shiks-appeal.
Jewish men love the idea
of meeting a woman
not like their mother.
Oh, that's insane.
I'll tell you what's insane.
The price that I could get you
on a new desktop computer.
I am not buying
a computer from you.
There's porn.
Even so.
Damn it.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Don't get me wrong, Mr. Lippman,
I'm-- I'm very flattered
that you found me
attractive enough
to lunge at me, heh,
but the only reason you like me
is because I'm a shiksa.
That's simply not true.
If you weren't Jewish, you
wouldn't be interested in me.
You are wrong. I'll prove it.
Oh, no. Don't.
I renounce Judaism.
Oy vey.
[♪]
JERRY:
What happened to you, pal?
Joey Zanfino and some
of the neighborhood kids,
they ambushed me
with a box of grade A's.
Are you all right?
Oh, no, no.
I'm fine, fine.
Serenity now.
Serenity now,
serenity now.
So you're using
Frank's relaxation method?
Jerry, the anger,
it just melts right off.
Serenity now.
[STAMMERING]
Pfft. Serenity now.
Oh.
Hey, what happened
to you?
Serenity.
Well...
you are not gonna believe this.
Now Lippman has renounced.
This shiksa thing
is totally out of control.
What is with you people?
What are you looking at?
Sit down, Elaine.
Oh, no, Jerry, I can't take
any more gentle sobbing.
I've been thinking about
what it means to be complete.
Do you have an apple
or anything?
Look at us,
hurtling through space
on this big blue marble...
Or a nectarine?
I'd love a nectarine.
...looking everywhere
for some kind of meaning...
Why am I in such a fruit mood?
Ah! Banana.
...when all the while,
the real secret to happiness
has been right here
in front of us.
What?
Elaine...
Jerry, I found a way
to beat Lloyd Braun!
I buy the computers myself,
I store 'em in your apartment.
Then after I win the contest,
I bring them all back,
I get my money back.
It's brilliant! Ha, ha, ha.
What--? What's wrong
with your leg?
I'm asking Elaine
to marry me.
I'll store these over
at Kramer's apartment, then.
It's all right.
I'll find him.
Elaine?
Um...
Jerry,
I got a lot going on
with, um...
With Lippman right now.
Lippman?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Yeah. And him too.
[SHOUTING]
What?
Oh, yeah.
Um...
I think George
is calling me,
so I'm gonna go
and give him a hand.
And just--
Come on. Come on!
Can I help you?
No. Stay. Stay. Stay.
[♪]
FRANK:
Hey, Braun,
Costanza's kicking your butt!
Watch how it's done.
Oh, hello,
Mr. Vandelay?
Would you like
to buy a computer?
Oh, really?
Two dozen?
[DINGING]
Costanza, you're white-hot!
AUTOMATED OPERATOR:
If you'd like to make a call,
please hang up and--
Hey, Braun, I got good news
and bad news,
and they're both the same:
you're fired.
Costanza,
you've won the Waterpik.
ESTELLE:
You're not gonna give away that Waterpik!
You wanna bet? Serenity now.
Serenity now.
You know,
you should tell your dad
that "serenity now" thing
doesn't work.
Just bottles up the anger,
and then eventually you blow.
What do you know?
You were in the nut house.
What do you think
put me there?
I heard they found a family
in your freezer.
Serenity now...
insanity later.
What happened here, Kramer?
Serenity now,
serenity now.
Kramer!
Oh, gee-- Jerry.
Gee, I didn't hear you
come in.
Yeah, the, uh--
Yeah, the children.
They-- They've--
They've done some redecorating.
Serenity now, serenity now.
You don't look well.
Huh? Oh, well, that's odd,
because I feel perfectly
at peace with the world.
Hey-- Eggs-- You--
Serenity now, serenity now,
serenity now...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Look at me.
I stepped
on your last rose.
[EXHALES]
Jerry, come on, don't get so upset about it.
There's always next spring.
Would you excuse me
for a moment?
[MURMURING]
Serenity now, serenity now.
[SCREAMING]
Serenity now!
GEORGE:
Jerry, I did it! Ah-ha-ha!
I beat Braun!
KRAMER: Serenity now!
Come on, give me a hand
with the computers?
[CRASHING NOISES]
KRAMER [HOWLING]:
Serenity now!
Why couldn't you squeeze
one of those stupid
rubber balls
to get your stress out?!
Why did you have
to destroy 25 computers?!
George, you listen to me.
I owe you one.
All right?
[KRAMER WHISTLING]
He's incorrigible.
You want to talk about it?
Oh, please don't tell me
you love me again, Jerry.
I can't handle it.
George,
letting my emotions out
was the best thing
I've ever done.
Sure,
I'm not funny anymore,
but there's more to life
than making shallow,
fairly obvious observations.
How 'bout you?
All right.
Here goes...
[♪]
Rabbi, is there anything
I can do
to combat this shiks-appeal?
Heh, Elaine, shiks-appeal
is a myth, like the yeti
or his North American cousin,
the Sasquatch.
Well, something's going on here,
because every able-bodied
Israelite in the county
is driving pretty strong
to the hoop.
Elaine, there is much
you don't understand
about the Jewish religion.
For example, did you know
that rabbis are allowed to date?
Well, what does that have
to do--?
You know, a member
of my congregation
has a time-share
in Myrtle Beach.
Uh, perhaps
if you're not too busy,
we could wing on down
after the high holidays.
Elaine?
[DOOR SLAMS]
Laney?
[♪]
GEORGE:
So that's it.
All of my darkest fears
and everything I'm capable of.
That's me.
Yikes.
Well, good luck with all that.
Where are you going? I...
I thought I could count on you
for a little compassion.
I think
you scared me straight.
All right, Jerome,
I'm in.
What?
Maybe we should
get married.
Maybe everything we need
is right here
in front of us.
Jer, let's do it.
I tell you,
I don't see it happening.
What? What happened
to the new Jerry?
He doesn't work here anymore.
Oh, well,
that's just great!
I love you, Jerry.
Right back at you, slick.
[EXHALES]
You know,
all these years...
I've always wanted to see
the two of you
get back together.
Well, that's because
you're an idiot.
[♪]
You single-handedly
brought Costanza and Son
to the brink
of bankruptcy.
Well, what about all
the Lloyd Braun sales?
He was crazy.
His phone wasn't even hooked up.
He just liked ringing
that bell.
I told you
to clean up this garage!
I have to put my car in!
This is a place
of business.
I told you never
to come in here.
Serenity now!
All right.
Dad, you really should lay off
the "serenity now" stuff.
So, what am I supposed to say?
Hoochie mama?
[GARAGE DOOR RATTLING]
ESTELLE:
Move your crap! I'm coming in!
[ENGINE STARTS]
No, you're not!
Hoochie mama!