ALL:
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Elaine, cake?
Uh, no, thanks.
It's Walter's special day.
You know,
there are 200 people
who work in this office.
Every day is somebody's
special day.
Elaine. Where you going?
It's Walter's last day.
We have to celebrate.
It's his birthday
and it's his last day?
This is other Walter,
from Returns.
Hey, what's going on here?
ALL [IN UNISON]:
Surprise!
Oh, guys.
Elaine, it's my last day.
Have a piece.
Uh, all right.
Pile it on.
ALL:
♪ For he's A jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Happy birthday
To you ♪
♪ For he's
A jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday... ♪
[♪]
What is so bad about having
a little piece of cake?
It is the forced socializing.
I mean, just because we work
in the same office,
why do we have
to act like we're friends?
Why aren't you there now?
I had to take a sick day,
I'm so sick of these people.
By the way, I talked to Lisi
and tomorrow night's
good for her.
You know, I shouldn't go out
with a friend of yours.
I foresee messiness.
Yeah, you're better off sitting
around here reading comic books
and eating spaghetti
at 2 in the morning.
Hey, speaking of tomato sauce:
do you wanna come with us
to Mario's Pizza?
Your old
school hangout? Why?
They're closing.
We're going for one last slice.
Hey. All right.
Hi. Check it out, huh?
Official police caution tape.
Look at that.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Step back, son.
There's nothing to see here.
Where did you get this?
Well, I got it
from my cop buddy, Doug.
You have
a lot of friends.
How come I never
see any of these people?
They wanna know
why they never see you.
I'm gonna eat that later.
So they just
gave you this?
Oh, no, no.
I had to fish around
in the evidence room
for it.
You know, they're all
preoccupied, trying to hunt down
this new psycho serial killer,
the Lopper.
All right, I'll see ya.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Who is the Lopper?
No, no, no.
It's no big deal.
Just some guy who's been running
around Riverside Park--
Pffff.
--you know.
Cutting people's heads off.
How come I haven't
read about it?
Well, the police,
they've been having
some internal dissension
about the name.
Really?
What are the other titles?
Uh, Heads-o, uh...
the De-Nogginizer...
Son of Dad.
Son of Dad?
Yeah.
That was my suggestion.
It's sort of a catchall.
Yeah.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Mario's Pizza,
just as she was.
Ha-ha.
Hey, Mario! Remember us?!
No.
We used to come in every day.
So where you been?
We're tanking here.
We'll have two slices
and two grape sodas.
Oh, thanks.
That'll save us.
All right,
make it the large sodas.
Hey, Jerry, remember Frogger?
Ha, I used to be
so into this game.
Gettin' that frog
across the street
was my entire life.
Yeah. And then
you went on to...
Well, it's a good game.
Watch the truck.
Double jump!
[BEEPING]
Eat the fly!
Eat it!
[POWERING DOWN]
Thanks a lot.
Eh, beat it, punk.
Hey, look at
the high score: "G.L.C."
George Louis Costanza.
That's not you, is it?
GEORGE:
Yes.
Eight hundred
and sixty thousand.
I-I can't believe
it's still standing.
No one has beaten me
in, like, 10 years.
I remember that night.
Oh, I was unstoppable.
Perfect combination
of Mountain Dew and mozzarella.
Just the right amount
of grease on the joystick.
Here's your pizza,
pea brains.
I think I remember
why we stopped coming here.
Yeah.
[♪]
ELAINE [THINKING]:
This pen smells really bad.
So why do I keep smelling it?
Is it too late for me
to go to law school?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
What is this?
You were out sick yesterday,
so we got you a get-well cake.
It's carrot.
It's good for you.
♪ Get well, get well soon
We wish you to get well ♪
Stop it!
That's not even a song!
I mean, now we're celebrating
a sick day?
I think it's nice.
ELAINE: What?!
What is nice?!
Trying to fill the void
in your life
with flour and sugar
and egg and vanilla?
I mean,
we are all unhappy.
Do we have
to be fat too?
Not you, Becky.
I know you have
a slow metabolism.
I don't want one more piece
of cake in my office!
♪ Get well
Get well soon-- ♪
It's not happening.
Can we still eat it?
[♪]
I'll tell you, Lisi,
I never expected that movie to--
End under water.
--be that long.
I mean, most action movies are--
So much more violent.
--not as long.
Well, I should probably--
Get going.
Yeah.
Well, it was nice
meeting you.
I'm sure I'll see you--
Eight tomorrow?
Actually, that's--
What you were thinking?
Right.
Oh, here you are. Ha-ha.
You, uh--?
You want to--?
Sure. Uh...
How about this one?
Well, I'm
doing it, Jerry.
I'm buying
the Frogger machine.
Now the torch
will burn forever.
Fabulous. See, now
you're really doing something.
So you wanna come down
to Mario's Pizza with me
and help me pick up the Frogger?
Hey, how you gonna keep
the machine plugged in
while you move it?
What?!
Once you unplug
the machine,
all the scores
will be erased.
You're right.
Why must there
always be a problem?!
You'd think just once
I could get a break!
God knows I earned it
with that score.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Well, more bad news, Jerry.
You know, the police
found another victim
of the Lopper
in Riverside Park.
I saw the photo,
and it looked
a lot like you.
Oh, come on.
There's a lot of people
walking around
that look like me.
Not as many
as there used to be.
No. I-I need a guy
that can rig a Frogger machine
so that I can move it
without losing power,
'cause I have
the high score.
H-hello?
You know, George,
you're not gonna find
an electrician like that
in the Yellow Pages.
Now, I know just the guy
who can do this.
Another friend?
Oh, no, no, no.
This guy is no friend.
In fact,
we don't even get along.
Well, i-is he good, Kramer?
Oh, he's the best.
And the worst.
Kramer, listen to me.
I'm never gonna
have a child.
If I lose this
Frogger high score,
that's it for me.
Believe me, George,
you can count on
Slippery Pete.
Slippery Pete?
Yeah.
I don't care
for the name, either.
In fact, that's one of the
things that we argue about.
All right.
I'm gonna find
a guy with a truck.
G.L.C. must live on!
[PHONE RINGS]
Come on.
Ng-dat-de-dong.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
So how's it going
with my friend?
She's a sentence-finisher.
It's like dating
Mad Libs.
[MUFFLED SINGING]
What is that?
Oh, it's a cake party.
It's the third one today.
[APPLAUSE]
[SIGHS]
I didn't realize
how hooked I got
on that 4:00 sugar rush.
So join in.
I can't.
I denounced them.
[SUCKS TEETH]
Maybe I'll go raid
Peterman's fridge.
He's always got a truffle
or something in there.
Uh-huh...
Hey, wh-wh-what--?
Yeah, I dropped an egg.
Be careful.
[♪]
Anybody here?
Peter-boy?
[GASPS]
It's a cakewalk.
PETERMAN:
♪ Get well Get well soon ♪
♪ We wish you
To get well ♪
[PETERMAN LAUGHS]
Oh, what a stirring
little anthem of wellness.
Elaine!
Mr. Peterman, uh...
We missed you
at the get-well party.
Poor old Walt has a polyp
in the duodenum.
It's benign, but,
ooh, still a bastard.
Oh, Elaine.
Can you keep a secret?
No, sir, I can't.
Inside that small,
college-boy mini fridge
is my latest acquisition.
A slice of cake
from the wedding
of King Edward VIII
to Wallis Simpson,
circa 1937.
The price: $29,000.
[♪]
Well, Lisi,
that was another--
Lovely evening.
--really bad meal.
I was thinking
maybe we should--
Go for a hansom cab ride?
--call it a night.
I'll walk you home.
Where do you live?
Eighty-fourth street
off Riverside Park.
Riverside Park...
I thought we were going--?
Back to my place.
That's right.
[♪]
So you slept with her?
She lives right off
Riverside Park.
I was scared
of the Lopper,
so I let her stay over.
And you automatically
sleep with her?
I just wanted
to make out a little,
but she kind of--
Finished your thought.
Yeah.
Guess what I ate.
An ostrich burger.
No. A $29,000 piece of cake.
Peterman got it at the Duke
and Duchess of Windsor auction.
Ah, it was the most
romantic thing I've ever eaten.
How did it taste?
A little stale.
Yeah.
So, uh...
Are you sleeping
with Peterman? Ha-ha.
No.
He doesn't know I ate it.
In fact,
he almost caught me.
I have to sneak back in
and even it out.
You know, they say
ostrich has less fat,
but you eat more of it.
Hey, so I talked to Lisi...
and she has got
a big surprise for you.
She's planning
a weekend trip
to Pennsylvania
Dutch Country.
Pennsylvania
Dutch Country?
Oh, that's the serious
relationship weekend place.
What is going on with you two?
Well, I think
by sleeping with her,
I may have sent her
the wrong message.
What's that?
Oh, 4:00 sugar fix.
Well, I'm calling
this off right now.
No, no. You are way past
the phone-call breakup stage.
Well, I'm not going over there.
That's where
the Lopper is.
Oh. It's daylight.
It won't take you
that long.
Just make
a clean break.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Just a little off the side...
Perfect.
Well, ha...
No point
in wasting 1200 bucks.
[♪]
ELAINE [THINKING]:
Oh, commander, isn't the wedding marvelous?
More cake?
Oh, I shouldn't.
I mustn't.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Ah, what the hell?
[♪]
GEORGE:
Now, each of you is here
because you're the best
at what you do.
Slippery Pete,
Kramer tells me you are one hell
of a rogue electrician.
And Shlomo, you're
the best truck driver.
I don't know
if I'm the best.
Oh...you're very good.
Let's say, good.
Okay. Good.
And Kramer, you're in charge
of taping off the loading zone.
Lock and load.
You think you can handle that,
numb nuts?
All right, all right,
come on now.
That was my
mail order bride.
Hey, you weren't home,
so I signed for her.
It doesn't give you the right
to make out with her.
You weren't even married yet.
All right, all right!
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
Whatever happened
in the past...is past.
Ha-ha. All right.
Now, ahem, this is the, uh--
The basic layout
for Mario's Pizza.
So what kind of a jail time
are we looking
at if we were caught?
What do you mean?
We're stealing
this thing, right?
No. I-I-I paid for it.
I thought
we were stealing it.
Yeah. It feels like
we're stealing it.
We're not stealing it.
I definitely thought
we're stealing it.
All right, let's--
Let's focus.
Can we get back
to the plan?
Well, I need a battery
for this kind of job.
Can I at least
steal a battery?
Fine. Steal the battery.
Now, all right,
here is the Frogger.
This is the front door--
Mm-hm.
--and this is the outlet.
What's that?
The outlet?
Mm-hm.
That's where
the electricity comes out.
Oh, you mean the holes.
Which one's the bathroom?
Uh, here.
They put the Frogger
with the toilet?
Yecch.
The Frogger is here.
George, I thought
that was the door.
Where are all
the pizza ovens?
I thought
the bathroom was here.
[♪]
All right.
You understand now?
It's not that complicated.
[♪]
ELAINE:
I need to replace an antique piece of cake.
Do you have anything
that's been...
you know,
laying around for a while?
Something prewar
would be just great.
Oh, hey, Elaine.
What, you got the munchies?
No, Kramer, I am
in big, big, big trouble.
I need a cake
that looks like this.
Oh?
Oh, yeah, Sotheby's.
Yeah, they make good cake.
Do any of these look close?
No, no.
But I know I've seen cake
just like that.
Oh?
Oh, Entenmann's. Yeah.
Entenmann's?
From the supermarket?
No. They're not really
in the supermarket.
They got their own case
at the end of the aisle.
[♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi, Lisi.
Hi, honey.
Is that a bat?
Uh, yeah.
I found it
on the street.
It's gotta be
worth something.
So, what do you
want to do, sweetheart?
Well, before we do anything...
Maybe we should talk.
Then this Pennsylvania Dutch
thing comes out of nowhere.
I mean, how am I supposed
to respond to that?
Then may I say something...
without being interrupted?
Well, I'm sorry
if I ruined your life.
That's exactly
what I set out to do.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Mm-hm. Uh-huh.
Are you afraid
to kiss me in public?
Have we even been in public?
LISI:
Now you're gonna tell me what I'm thinking.
Well, go ahead,
'cause I'd really like to know.
You are not dumb.
Don't say that.
These beans
are pretty good.
Mm-hm. Twenty minutes.
JERRY:
Well, I'm sorry I'm not Brad.
I'm me!
Nice to meet ya!
Boy, did your mother
do a number on you.
[CRYING]
Fine. So it's over.
Oh, thank God.
Why is it dark out?
W-What time is it?
Nine-thirty.
We've been breaking up
for 10 hours?
Goodbye, Jerry.
Lopper.
Maybe we should give this a
little more time,
see how it looks
in the light of day.
Out.
[♪]
Lopper.
Lisi, Lisi,
let me in.
We can work this out.
I was wrong. You were right.
I'll do anything.
[DOOR BUZZES]
[♪]
Jerry! You came
for the big moment.
Nah, I'm waiting for...
Ha-ha. Everything's
timed out to perfection.
Slippery Pete's got the Frogger
on battery power.
Truck will be there any minute,
and Kramer taped
the loading zone.
Oh. Sounds great.
Yeah.
You gotta come over tonight.
We can play.
Ah, I can't. I'm busy.
I'm going away
on a long weekend.
Where?
Look what I found.
I got one for you too.
Oh, great.
Uh, you know what?
Why don't you put it in the car
so I don't accidentally toss it
in that Dumpster?
Ha-ha-ha. Okay.
I'll meet thee in front
of your place, 15 minutes.
A long...
long weekend.
I hear thee.
Elaine! Excellent.
I'd like you to meet
a friend of mine,
Irwin Lubeck.
Oh, hello.
Charmed.
Ha, ha, ha.
All right.
Brace yourself, Lubeck.
You are about
to be launched, via pastry,
back to the wedding of one of
the most dashing and romantic
Nazi sympathizers of the entire
British royal family.
I guess I'll just--
PETERMAN: No, Elaine, stay.
Lubeck here...
is the world's foremost
appraiser of vintage pastry.
PETERMAN:
All right, Lubeck.
How much is she worth?
I'd say about 219.
[LAUGHS]
Two hundred
and nineteen thousand dollars!
Lubeck,
you glorious titwillow,
you just made me
a profit of $190,000.
No. Two dollars
and nineteen cents.
It's an Entenmann's.
Do they have
a castle at Windsor?
No. They have a display case
at the end of the aisle.
Oh, good Lord.
You all right, Peterman?
You look ill.
♪ Get well
Get well soon ♪
♪ We want you
To get well ♪
♪ Get well
Get well soon ♪
♪ We want you
To get well ♪
[♪]
[BEEPING]
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Eat the fly.
Got him.
You idiots. You're gonna
wear down the battery.
Oh, the batteries are fine.
We've got...
Oh, God.
Only three minutes left.
Quick. Get this thing back
in the pizzeria.
George, they closed up.
Wh--?
I need an outlet!
A what?
Holes! I need holes!
The pharmacy's still open.
All right. Kramer,
you block off traffic.
You two, go sweet-talk
the pharmacist.
You owe me a quarter.
Slippery Pete.
GEORGE:
Kramer, hurry up!
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
I'm out! No tape left!
Well, come on.
I'll help you push it across.
Wait a minute.
This looks familiar.
This reminds me
of something.
I can do this.
By yourself?
Jerry, I've been preparing
for this moment my entire life.
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
He look like a frog.
So do you.
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
[THUD]
[TRUCK HORN HONKS]
[FROGGER POWERING DOWN]
[EXHALES]
Game over.
[♪]
Mr. Peterman,
you wanted to see me, sir?
Elaine, up until a moment ago,
I was convinced that I was
on the receiving end
of one of the oldest
baker's grift in the books...
the Entenmann's shim-sham...
[SIGHS]
...until I remembered
the videotape
surveillance system,
that I installed
to catch other Walter
using my latrine.
But it also caught...this.
Mr. Peterman, I-I can ex--
Elaine, I have
a question for you.
Is the item still...
with you?
Um... Well, uh...
As far as I know.
Do you know what happens
to a butter-based frosting
after six decades
in a poorly ventilated
English basement?
Uh, I-I guess I hadn't--
Well, I have a feeling
what you are about to go through
is punishment enough.
Dismissed.
[♪]