[♪]
George, you're not really
handicapped, are ya?
I've had my difficulties.
I saw you running down
Amsterdam Avenue,
lifting that 200-pound
motorized cart with one hand.
Mr. Thomassoulo,
during times of great stress,
people are capable
of superhuman strength.
Have you ever seen
The Incredible Hulk, sir?
No.
How 'bout the old, uh,
Spider-Man live-action show?
George, I realize
that we've signed
a one-year contract with you,
but at this point,
I think it's best if we both
go our separate ways.
Uh, I-I don't understand.
We don't like you.
We want you to leave.
Clearer.
[♪]
JERRY:
So you're staying at Play Now?
Why not?
The pay is good.
I got dental.
And private access to one
of the great handicapped
toilets in the city.
But they know
you're not handicapped.
Aren't you ashamed?
They should be ashamed.
They signed me
to a one-year contract.
As long as I show up
for work every day,
they have to pay me.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
[COMICALLY] Hellooo.
[COMICALLY]
Hellooo, Elaine.
What's that?
Oh, it's just a stupid thing.
Well, I'm sure it's stupid.
It's not about me, is it?
Nooo...
Not at allll...
Tell me.
JERRY:
All right.
Know this girl Claire
I'm seeing?
Yeah.
Well, he and I started joking
that when she falls asleep,
her stomach stays awake
all night and talks to me.
How's it talking?
The bellybutton's like a mouth.
[COMICALLY]
I'm booored...
Talk to meeee...
Oh, I gotta start taking
these "stupid warnings"
more seriously.
Hey, look who's here: Puddy.
My Puddy?
But we broke up.
And yet he continues to live.
Hey, Benes. How are you?
I'm doing great.
Great.
See ya.
Well, that's it.
[CHUCKLES]
You two are back together.
What?
The "bump into."
The "bump into" always leads
to the backslide.
David and I will not
be getting back together.
Elaine,
breaking up is like knocking
over a Coke machine,
you can't do it in one push.
You gotta rock it back and forth
a few times,
and then it goes over.
That's beautiful.
ELAINE:
What about you?
You were even engaged,
and you cut it off
just like that.
That's different.
I had no feelings
for those people.
But you, you'll backslide.
You wanna bet?
Stakes?
Fifty.
Dollars?
All right. Witness.
Witness.
Done.
Percentage?
BOTH:
No.
[♪]
CLAIRE: I'll call you tonight?
JERRY: Yeah.
What's wrong with the belt?
At the movies last night,
I went to the bathroom
and I unbuckled a little wildly
and the buckle kinda banged
against the side of the urinal,
so...that's it.
So you're insane?
Oh, yes, quite.
Hello.
Of course,
it's a sliding scale.
See you later.
Hellooo...
♪ La la la ♪
Look at this. They're redoing
the Cloud Club.
The restaurant on top of the
Chrysler Building? Good idea.
Of course it's a good idea.
It's my idea.
I conceived this whole project
two years ago.
Which part, the renovating-the-
restaurant-you-don't-own part,
or spending-the-200-million-
you-don't-have part?
See, I come up
with these things.
I know they're gold,
but nothing happens.
You know why?
No resources, no skill,
no talent,
no ability, no brains, no--
No.
No time.
It's all these menial tasks:
laundry, grocery shopping,
coming in here
and talking to you.
You have any idea how much time
I waste in this apartment?
I could ballpark it.
Hellooo...
Here we go.
Now she comes in.
My whole day is shot.
Hey, I called you last night.
Where were you?
I went out with, uh--
[CLEARS THROAT]
With a friend.
George?
Nope. No. No.
Well, I was here.
That's everyone.
[LAUGHING]
Are those the same shoes
as yesterday's?
Uh, um, you know, I wear
these shoes all the-- The time.
Your hair,
it's somewhat de-poofed.
No. It's-- It's the new look.
You know, heroin chic.
Wait a second.
What's going on here?
What? Nothing. Nothing!
Aah!
You're wearing the same clothes
as yesterday.
You saw Puddy.
Oh, hoochie moochie.
Game over. Pay up.
No!
It was an isolated
sexual incident.
We are not back together.
Then what do you call it?
People don't just bump
into each other and have sex.
This isn't Cinemax.
It was no big deal, okay?
I mean, we fooled around,
then we went out,
we grabbed a little dinner.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Uh, dinner? That's it.
What?
You're all the way back.
[GROANS]
Sex-- That's meaningless.
I can understand that.
But dinner,
that's heavy.
That's like an hour.
KRAMER:
Oh, man.
2.9 percent financing
on a Toyota 1-ton.
That was my idea too!
[♪]
Good morning.
Go to hell.
Hi, Alice.
That's a nice dress.
Don't even look at me.
Hey, Glenn.
Ah, go to hell.
Heard that one already.
[♪]
So that's the bedroom.
Here's the bathroom.
You need to familiarize
yourself with the kitchen.
Yeah. Go ahead and look
through some of the drawers.
And you are?
Oh, hey. I'm Darin.
I'm...new here.
Yeah. That's Jerry. You don't
have to worry about him.
Go across the hall
and get started on that mail.
Right.
Okay. Good.
He's a go-getter.
Who's he?
My intern from NYU.
Well, you remember
my corporation,
Kramerica Industries?
All right.
Yeah, well,
apparently NYU
is very enthusiastic
about their students getting
some real-world
corporate experience.
But you only provide
fantasy-world
corporate experience.
Well, this'll really
free up my time
so I can focus
on more important things,
like my bladder system.
All right, it's time to go.
No. Jerry, it's not for people.
It's for oil tankers.
I know.
See, the idea is a rubber
bladder inside the tanker,
so if it crashes,
the oil won't spill out.
Actually, that is not
a bad idea. Yeah.
Now it's time to go.
Oh.
[PHONE RINGS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
Hello?
GEORGE: Hellooo...
Hellooo...
JERRY:
What's going on?
Siege mentality, Jerry.
[CHUCKLING]
They really want me out of here.
They've downgraded me
to some sort of a bunker.
I'm like Hitler's
last days here.
So you gonna leave?
Oh, no! I'm invigorated.
Ha, ha.
They'll never get me out.
I'm like a weed, Jerry.
I thought you're like Hitler
in the bunker.
I'm a weed in Hitler's bunker.
I'm getting uncomfortable
with the Hitler stuff.
I got another call. See ya.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Hello?
Hi. This is Darin
from Kramer's office.
Mr. Kramer would like
to schedule lunch
at Monk's coffee shop.
Really? When?
Ten minutes.
Do you need directions?
No, I don't.
I'll call back in five minutes
to confirm.
Yeah, five.
Hey.
So where's my money?
No money. I'm Puddy-free.
So are we eatin' or what?
Oh, yeah. Hold on.
[PHONE BEEPS, DIALS, RINGS]
Hello, Darin? This is Jerry
from Jerry's office.
Uh, we're gonna be three
for lunch.
What do you mean,
he's already left?
Elaine's gonna come
with us, all right?
What? When did this happen?
Well, just--
Darin!
[♪]
ELAINE [VOICE-OVER]:
I am not calling Puddy.
Hm. What did I do
with my gloves?
Oh, I bet I left 'em
over at Puddy's.
I should call him.
I need those gloves.
No, I better not.
I'll call.
Oh, ha,
look at that.
There are the gloves.
I was just about to call.
Ha, and there they are.
That's funny.
Heh, that's really funny.
[CHUCKLING]
That is really, really funny.
You know who loves
funny stories?
David Puddy.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Well, Play Now's through playing.
They turned the heat
way up in my office.
Tried to sweat me out.
Do you have to write
all this stuff down?
Well, Mr. Kramer's
in a meeting with Mr. Lomez,
but he didn't want
to miss anything.
So how hot did it get?
I don't know,
a hundred and twenty,
130.
Then they sent some guys in
to sandblast for six hours.
Tomorrow, they're
putting in asbestos.
I guess you could take anything
but actual work.
Bring it on!
[COMICALLY]
Hellooo, Kramer.
Welcome.
♪ La la la ♪
Heh. I'm sorry.
I couldn't get out of there.
What did I miss, huh?
Well, after ordering,
Mr. Seinfeld
and Mr. Costanza debated
on whether or not
Iron Man wore some sort of
undergarment between his skin
and his iron suit.
KRAMER: Uh-huh.
And I still say
he's naked under there.
Oh, that makes a lot
of sense.
Aw, shut up.
Then Mr. Seinfeld went
to the restroom, at which point,
Mr. Costanza scooped ice
out of Mr. Seinfeld's drink
with his bare hand
and used it to wash up.
And then Mr. Costanza
then remarked to me,
"This never happened."
[♪]
[JERRY CHUCKLES]
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing.
[CHUCKLES]
What are you laughing about?
Tell me.
All right, but this is--
This is really dumb,
really stupid.
[LAUGHING]
We've been doing this silly kind of voice.
So is it fun humiliating me?
No, it's not you.
It's your stomach.
He's talking with this funny,
booming, jovial voice--
Hellooo.
So you think I'm fat?
No. It--
Mr. Kramer says,
"Hey, buddy."
We're in the middle
of something.
Would you mind
coming back later?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Should we set something up?
Get out!
I'm leaving too.
Nobody said you're fat.
He's a lovable character.
He's like-- Like--
Like the Kool-Aid guy.
He is fat!
No. He's just a little bloated.
CLAIRE:
Goodbye!
It's mostly water weight!
KRAMER:
Boysenberry.
Kid's still learning.
DARIN:
Mr. Kramer,
the dean of my internship's
on Line 2.
She wants to set a meeting.
Yeah, well, nothing before noon.
Line 2?
Yeah. Your phone is Line 1.
Oh.
[♪]
So the gloves were
right by the phone?
That is pretty funny.
You see? I mean, this is what
Jerry doesn't understand.
We can see each other. We can
see each other every day,
but it doesn't mean
we're back together.
No. I mean, I love just
seeing you and having sex.
Yeah. Ha, ha.
Not having to do all that, uh...
You know, work.
Well, either way...
All that calling you
and buying you stuff.
David.
Hearing about how everyone
at work isn't as smart as you.
It's brutal.
All right, that's it.
We're back together.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Look, Elaine, be reasonable.
Get those clothes off.
You're spending the night,
and we're gonna cuddle.
What?!
You heard me. Strip!
[♪]
[GEORGE WHISTLING]
[LAUGHING]
All right.
Okay.
[THUMPING]
[GRUNTING]
[EXHALES]
[SNIFFS]
[NUMBER DIALS]
[LINE RINGS]
Hello, Marjorie?
George Costanza.
How are you, sweetheart?
Listen, could you give
Mr. Thomassoulo
a message for me?
Yes. If he needs me,
tell him
[SHOUTING]
I'm in my office!
[NORMAL VOICE]
Thanks.
KRAMER:
Uh, Dean Jones, you wanted to talk to me?
I've been reviewing
Darin's internship journal.
Doing laundry?
Ah.
Mending chicken wire?
High tea with a Mr. Newman.
I know it all sounds
pretty glamorous,
but it's business as usual
at Kramerica.
Far as I can tell, your entire
enterprise is little more
than a solitary man
with a messy apartment,
which may or may not
contain a chicken.
And with Darin's help,
we'll get that chicken.
I'm sorry,
but we can't allow Darin
to continue working with you.
Well, I have to say,
this seems capricious
and arbitrary.
Your fly's open.
So you sure you're not still
angry about last night?
No. I'm fine.
Just as long as you don't
ever do that voice again.
Never?
Never.
What about if you're not around?
No.
So I have to choose between
seeing you and doing the voice?
That's right.
I can do that.
What's your decision?
I don't know.
[LIONEL RICHIE'S "HELLO"
PLAYING]
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Is it me
You're Looking for? ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ I can see it
In your smile... ♪
Hellooo.
♪ La la la ♪
♪ I love you ♪
[PANTING]
Jerry. Hi.
Hellooo...
♪ La la la ♪
[♪]
GEORGE:
You broke up with her?
Why?
So we could do the voice.
♪ La la la ♪
What's the matter?
I think I'm getting tired of it.
I mean, is that all it does,
"hello" and "la la la"?
I-it could do anything.
It could be Spanish.
Holaaaa.
Helloooo.
I think I like the girl
better than the voice.
Really?
Hellooo.
Still?
I told you.
All right, here you go.
Choke on it.
See? Never bet
against the backslide.
I knew you two
would get back together.
Yeah, well not for long.
I'm breaking up with him.
I don't think so.
I've seen you two together.
You make each other miserable.
It's kismet.
Double or nothing.
Done.
GEORGE:
Witness.
You're in there again?
I think Play Now is putting
something in my food.
All right, I'm out of here.
[EXHALES]
Yeah...
What is this?
I don't know.
I found' em in your closet.
Ever since Darin left, I haven't
been able to find anything.
He took all my clothes
to some cleaners.
I'm clueless.
Is that clock right?
Yeah. 9:00.
I was supposed to pick up Newman
at the zoo 12 hours ago.
[COMICALLY]
Goodbyyyye, Kramer.
Jerry, buddy, I gotta
tell you something.
That voice is played.
Really?
So played.
GEORGE:
I told you.
[♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Darin. What are you
doing here?
You know, the college canceled
the internship.
I don't care
about the internship.
I care about Kramerica.
No, no, no,
Kramerica is no more.
What about the oil-tanker
bladder system?
We were gonna put an end
to maritime oil spills.
[EXHALES]
Probably.
Darin, you go home.
Forget about Kramerica.
Well, you're still here?
I haven't had time to leave.
Well, I haven't changed
my mind.
Boy, you are a tenacious
little monkey.
All right, I'll do it.
Ha. Yes!
Kramerica Industries lives!
Let's get to work.
Okay.
Let's see what Jerry's
got to eat.
[♪]
THOMASSOULO:
You win, George.
We've had it.
[CHUCKLES]
You leave right now,
and Play Now
will give you
six months' pay.
That's half
of your entire contract.
Please. Just-- Just--
J-j-just-- Just go.
See, if I stay the whole year,
I get it all.
Wanna play hardball, huh?
Fine.
[INTERCOM BEEPING]
[ECHOING OVER P.A.]
Attention, Play Now employees:
George Costanza's
handicapped bathroom
on the 16th floor
is now open to all employees
and their families.
Well played.
I'll see you in hell,
Costanza.
JERRY:
Claire,
thanks for giving me
a second chance.
Our relationship
is certainly worth more
than some silly, stupid voice.
Hold on one second.
So we definitely don't wanna
do the voice anymore?
I don't think so.
All right, we're back
together again. Great. Bye-bye.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[HEAVY THUD]
Hey.
JERRY:
Trouble down at the plant?
That's a drum of oil.
Darin and I are finally
gonna test my bladder system.
You have to drink
that whole thing?
No, no, no, no.
It's for oil tankers.
All I need to do is fill
some sort of rubber container
with oil and then drop it to see
whether or not
it can withstand the impact.
I understand.
Would a, uh,
giant rubber ball work?
Conceivably.
Well, Play Now has all kinds
of different rubber balls.
Why don't we test your bladder
system at my office?
You're not?
Oh, yes, I am.
Mr. Thomassoulo likes
to play dirty.
Well, there's nothing dirtier...
than a giant ball of oil.
Hey, you want to split
a Reuben?
I don't think so, David.
We're through.
Oh.
That's a nice sweater.
[♪]
Whoo. That was a doozy.
[EXHALES]
Go again?
Book it.
GEORGE:
Witness.
David, I know this hurts,
but it's the way it has to be.
[LAUGHING]
I'm gonna go get
some popcorn.
So how did it end?
They got away.
Huh.
Listen, David,
I've gotta run.
Can you lend me 50 bucks?
Hey.
Jerry, did you bring
the video camera?
Yeah. I put a six-hour tape in.
That should cover
the experiment, the arrest
and most of your trial.
All right, I'll see you.
KRAMER: Yeah.
GEORGE: Oh, uh,
you might want to stick around,
Jerry.
Mr. Thomassoulo picked
the wrong man
to hire
'cause he was fake handicapped.
I can't.
I gotta meet Claire.
You gave up the voice?
Yeah. That was stupid.
Unless you guys
are liking it again?
KRAMER & GEORGE:
No, no.
Darin?
Sorry, Mr. Seinfeld.
Uh, bathroom?
GEORGE: Hey,
use mine. I'll let you in.
I thought it was open
to the public.
I, uh... I took care of that.
[LOCK CLATTERING]
Huh?
Wow.
Xanadu.
No wonder you're putting
in so many hours.
May I?
I insist.
I'll fix us a drink.
[PHONE RINGS]
I got it.
Whew.
You know, Darin, if you had
told me 25 years ago
that someday
I'd be standing here
about to solve
the world's energy problems,
I would've said you're crazy.
[LAUGHS]
Now let's push this giant ball
of oil out the window.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
So check out my view.
Wow.
JERRY:
Hey, there's Claire. I better go down.
Hey, there's Kramer and Darin.
Hey, there's
the giant ball of oil.
Claire's right
underneath that thing.
Claire!
Hellooo!
JERRY:
Hellooo.
Helloooo!
I don't believe this.
[SHOUTING]
I'm not looking up
if you're going
to do that voice.
Bombs away.
This is going to be a shame.
[SCREAM AND SPLASH]
Oh!
Hellooo.
Well, that didn't work.
[EXHALES]
Hey, how 'bout this:
Ketchup and mustard
in the same bottle?
Oh, that sounds
interesting, sir.
Yeah.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[♪]
JERRY:
Claire won her lawsuit against Play Now.
Gee, Play Now's filing
for bankruptcy.
I guess you're not
going in anymore. No.
So they're not paying you--
No.
So you're pretty much--
Yeah.
Whatever happened to Darin?
Darin's going away
for a long, long time.
Well, Claire sure
looked pretty funny
all covered in oil like that.
[COMICALLY]
Hellooo. I got beaned
with a giant ball of oooil.
[COMICALLY]
I'm slippery as an eel.
♪ La la la ♪
I'm just so glad it's back.
See? This is good.
This is the way
it should be.
You know, uh--
Why were we fooling ourselves?
We belong together.
Elaine, I want to break up.
Tsk. Ah, nuts.
[♪]