So-- So you're saying
UNICEF is a scam?
It's the perfect cover for
a money-laundering operation.
No one can keep track
of all those kids
with those little
orange boxes of change.
Oh, no, it's Sally Weaver.
Oh, yeah, your old
college roommate, huh?
No, it's Susan Ross'
old college roommate.
She moved to New York
a few years ago.
She's trying to become
an actress.
Ah, dramatic or comedic?
Untalented.
She's always inviting me
to see her in some bad play
in a tiny room
without ventilation.
It's really depressing.
You know, we don't go
to enough theater.
She should just give up.
Hey...
Hey, Mr. Too-Big-
To-Come-To-My-Shows.
I just came from tap.
I'm all: whoo!
[CHUCKLES]
I'm on my way
to an audition.
I'm still looking
for that big break.
Why don't you just give up?
Kramer...
Well, that's
what Jerry says.
Well, now, face it. If it hasn't
happened, it's not gonna happen.
All right. Okay, I'll go grab us
a booth, huh?
Yeah. Join us?
So...Susan's dead.
[♪]
Well, I think she was happy
someone finally said it.
Why did you have
to say anything to her?
Well, I thought
the conversation was lagging.
Why can't you ever just
keep your big mouth shut?
Well, I come in here
to have a pleasant meal,
and if we're not gonna have one,
I'll grab a bite at your place.
Ge-- Ge-- Get out.
You know,
maybe Kramer was right.
Some people should
just give up. I have.
What did you want to be?
I don't remember.
But it certainly wasn't this.
Look at this cartoon
in The New Yorker.
I don't get this.
Me neither.
And you're on the fringe
of the humor business.
Hey.
Hey, George,
look at this.
That's cute.
You get it?
No, never mind.
Come on. We're two
intelligent people here.
We can figure this out.
Now, we got a dog
and a cat in an office.
It looks like
my accountant's office.
But there's no pets
working there.
And the cat is saying,
"I've enjoyed reading
your e-mail."
It's-- It's got something to do
with that 42 in the corner.
That's a page number.
Well, I can't crack
this one.
Oh, this has gotta be
a mistake.
Well, try shaking it.
Well, Janet, uh,
should be here any minute.
You've been hiding her from us.
You must really like her.
Oh, Jerry, the minute I saw
this girl, we just clicked.
She's got such a nice face,
you know?
Her eyes, her mouth,
nose...
We know what a face
consists of.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Jerry, Elaine,
I give you Janet.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
JANET: Hi.
Do we still have time
to make the movie?
Oh, uh, yeah. We just can't go
to the supermarket
to get some candy.
[WHISTLES]
Jerry, she looks
exactly like you.
She does not.
Yeah, maybe she doesn't.
I don't care.
[♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
JERRY: Hey, Kramer.
Oh, hey.
You got some messages.
Yeah, uh, George, George,
Elaine, George again, Elaine,
Newman-- But that
was a crank call.
Yeah, and, uh,
some Sally woman called.
Says, "Thanks a lot."
Yeah, she's quitting
the business.
You ruined her life.
What? You're the one
who ruined her life.
Well, that's not how
she remembers it.
Well, I gotta
talk her out of this.
I thought you said
she stinks.
She does stink,
and she should quit.
But I don't want it to be
because of me.
It should be
the traditional route:
Years of rejection
and failure
until she's spit out the bottom
of the porn industry.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Yeah?
GEORGE: Hey, George and Janet.
Oh, who's Janet, huh?
George's girlfriend.
Elaine thinks she looks like me,
but I think it's,
as you would say, kooky talk.
You know what woman I always
thought you looked like?
Lena Horne.
Hey.
Hey, George.
And you must--
Look exactly like Jerry.
You don't see this?
Oh, you're like twins.
Whoo! This is eerie.
Kramer, what--?
What are you talking about?
Janet doesn't look anything
like Jerry.
Well, maybe we do look
a little like each other.
No. What do you know
about what you look like?
Come on, George,
relax.
Just because
they look alike,
it doesn't mean you're
secretly in love with Jerry.
All right, we're--
We're going now. Bye-bye.
We just got here,
George.
Well, it's getting dark.
Yeah, she's a nice girl.
Kind of quiet, though.
What are you doing?!
Don't tell a woman
she looks like a man.
And George doesn't want to hear
his girlfriend looks like me.
Frankly, neither do I.
Well, how should I have
broached the subject?
You don't broach.
You keep your mouth shut.
Well, it sounds like
someone's having a bad day.
Yeah, because of you.
Well, then I think
one of us should leave.
[♪]
JERRY:
Sally, you can't quit the business.
This is all
because of me?
Mm-hm.
You can't give up.
You don't think
people tell me I stink?
When I'm on stage,
that's all I hear.
"You stink. You suck.
We like magic."
Really?
Of course.
I stink, you stink.
It's show biz.
Everybody stinks.
Yeah. You've been stinking
since the '80s.
All right, I think
we've covered my act.
Now, you get out there and
stink it up with everybody else.
All right, yes!
Thank you,
I'm gonna do it.
[CHUCKLES]
Now!
[♪]
ELAINE:
Well, I've asked everyone at work,
and no one gets
this cartoon.
I don't understand why
no one can explain it.
But I am going
to get to the bottom of this.
Oh, I think
we're at the bottom.
Hey, George.
Janet seems really nice.
And she's quite a...
Tsk. A handsome woman.
What does that mean?
Yeah, what does that mean?
What do you mean by that?
Enjoy.
Elaine, huh?
She's completely--
Oh, I know.
Because you don't think Janet--
No.
Why would I--?
It's ludicrous.
Yes.
And neither one of us--
No.
So--
Exactly.
I'm not gay.
Neither am I.
Kramer, get in here!
Kramer! Hey!
Where's the crazy man?
Come on out!
Come on in here!
Hey! Get in here!
What are you doing? Come in.
Right over here.
What's happening?
What are you doing?
Come and talk to us.
I made an important
life decision.
Let's talk about that.
Don't leave.
Uh, all right. I, uh--
I know I've been kind
of shooting off
at the mouth lately.
Uh, first, with that girl whose
life you destroyed, and, uh...
and then about George
dating a-- A lady Jerry.
What's the decision?
I know you want me
to keep my big mouth shut.
Well, that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
I'm never gonna talk again.
Yeah, right.
What do I need
to talk for, huh?
What, to blab
to the neighbors
about how George has
a new fem-Jerry friend?
Or to tell everybody
at the coffee shop
how George is all mixed up
in a perverse sexual amalgam
of some girl
and his best friend?
See, now, I've done all that.
Now it's time for silence.
Silence? Yes!
Kramer, you're never
gonna be able
to completely
stop talking.
Jerry, 94 percent
of communication is nonverbal.
Here, watch.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
[MOUTHS]
What are you talking about?
Wha--? Wha--?
What does this mean?
Well, it's Frank
and Estelle's reaction
to hearing about George's
man love for a she-Jerry.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
That's the idea!
Kramer, there's no way
you stick to this.
You're gonna start now?
That's right-- Ooh!
Right...now.
Ow! That hurts!
Now.
[♪]
So, uh, J. Peterman wants
to hire some of our cartoonists
to, uh, illustrate
your catalog.
Well, we're hoping
that if perhaps
the catalog is
a little funnier,
people won't be so quick
to return the clothes.
[LAUGHS]
Uh, for example, I--
You know, I really do...
Well, I love this one.
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
that's a rather clever jab
at interoffice politics,
don't you think?
Uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah.
Uh, but why is it
that the--?
That the animals enjoy
reading the e-mail?
Well, Miss Benes, uh,
cartoons are like gossamer,
and, uh, one doesn't
dissect gossamer.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, you don't have
to dissect it,
if you could just tell me why
this is supposed to be funny.
Oh, it's merely a commentary
on contemporary mores.
But what is the comment?
It's a slice of life.
No, it isn't.
A pun?
I don't think so.
Vorshtein?
That's not a word.
You have no idea
what this means, do you?
No.
Then why did you print it?
I like the kitty.
You know what?
You people should be ashamed
of yourselves.
You know, you doodle a couple
of bears at a cocktail party
talking about the stock market,
you think
you're doing comedy.
Actually, that's not bad.
Oh, really? Heh. Yes.
Well, you know, I--
I have others.
[♪]
JERRY:
Sally, I can't believe
you're already doing
a one-woman show.
Oh, no, it's just a little
performance piece I wrote.
But you know what?
You really inspired me, okay?
A tear?
Hey, there you are.
Oh, right,
code of silence.
How's that going?
Ah...
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you. Heh.
Hi, everybody. Um, I think
you're really gonna like this,
'cause it's about me.
Well, all right,
it's not just about me.
It's about me and this guy,
Jerry Seinfeld,
who I like to call
the devil.
Okay, okay,
so I run into this Jerry
on the street,
and then he says to me,
"Hey, Sally, you stink.
You should give up acting."
Oh, I'm doing Jerry now, okay?
So you have to imagine
I have horns, a tail
and hooves instead of feet.
[LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGH]
You know what I mean, that guy?
Oh, shut up.
[♪]
ELAINE:
She does a full hour
about how you're the devil?
I gotta go see this thing.
Good luck. It's sold out
for the next three weeks.
Well, I bet I can get in
once I mention
I'm from The New Yorker.
The New Yorker?
Yes, The New Yorker.
I met with their cartoon editor,
and I got him to admit
that that cartoon
made no sense.
Wow! Good work,
Nancy Drew.
[CHUCKLES]
Then we ended up
going out to lunch,
and he had some great gossip
about James Thurber.
Nodding off.
And he said I could submit
some of my own cartoons.
Wow, that's incredible.
But you don't draw.
I do too.
What, your sad little horsies?
The house with the little curl
of smoke?
The sunflower
with the smiley face?
The transparent cube?
That's better than your drawings
of naked Lois Lane.
Where did you see that?
Those are private!
[♪]
SALLY:
Jerry, sorry I'm late.
Channel Nine is doing
a piece on my show.
Isn't that great? Heh.
Do you hate me?
No, no. I thought
the show was terrific.
I was just wondering
if you have to keep saying,
"Jerry Seinfeld
is the devil"?
Well, that is the title.
I know, but I thought maybe you
could mention how I apologized
and encouraged you
to stick with it.
You know, I workshopped that
and, uh, snoozers.
[LAUGHS]
But, ahem, I'll tell you what,
I'll tinker.
It's all a journey.
Thanks.
You got a little, uh,
schmutz there.
Excuse me, Miss Weaver?
Oh, my God, it is you.
I-- I-- I've seen
your show six times.
What a surprise.
Oh, you're great.
It's great.
It's so great to see a show
that's about something.
Where to?
[♪]
GEORGE:
My friends are idiots.
She doesn't look like Jerry.
She doesn't look
like anybody.
And so what if she does
look like Jerry?
What does that mean?
That I could have everything
I have with Jerry,
but because it's a woman,
I could also have sex with her?
[CHUCKLES, SNORTS]
And that somehow that would be
exactly what I always wanted?
She doesn't even look
like Jerry.
You know, I really look a lot
like your friend Jerry.
I know.
[♪]
MAN [OVER TV]:
Thanks for watching Nine News.
We leave you tonight
with a scene
from Sally Weaver's
one-woman show.
Okay, so I go
to meet Jerry Seinfeld
at this horrible coffee shop,
right?
And he's like, "Hey, stop doing
your show."
And I'm like, "Hello!
It's a free country."
So then he goes,
"Okay, schmutzie."
And he starts pawing
at my sweater, right,
and getting all, you know,
Hands Across America.
There really was schmutz.
I-- I didn't try and grab her.
And this is what he looks like
when he is eating.
You know? Right--
Get out of my house!
Well, boys, I did it.
I had to stay up
all night,
but I finally came up
with a great New Yorker cartoon.
I've stayed up all night.
I fix myself up a little
before I go out.
That is not the point.
Some mouthwash, a hat,
something.
Just read it.
Pretty good.
Pretty good?
Wha--? This is a gem.
Kramer, lookit.
What? It's funny.
It's a pig
in a complaint department.
Yeah, and he's saying,
"I wish I was taller."
[LAUGHS]
See? That--
That's his complaint.
I get it.
Do you? Because that's not
a normal complaint.
Well, how about if
it was something like,
"I can't find my receipt.
My place is a sty."
You know, everything with you
has to be so jokey.
I'm a comedian.
"I wish I was taller."
That's-- That's--
That's nice.
That's-- That's real.
Yeah, well, I got a complaint.
This cartoon stinks.
Well, I'll tell you
who doesn't think it stinks:
The New Yorker.
That's right.
They're publishing it
in their next issue.
Oh, you know what?
I just ran into Newman
in the hall.
He said you tried to grope
Sally Weaver?
Oh, well, that's it.
I'm gonna put an end
to this.
Wha--?
[PHONE BEEPING]
The pig says,
"My wife is a slut"?
Now, that's a complaint.
Hello, Sally?
Yeah, this is Jerry.
I just wanted
to leave you a message
and let you know I caught
your little piece on TV...
...and I'm getting
a little tired of hearing
how horrible I am, and I would
really appreciate it
if you would just leave me out
of your act altogether.
[ALL LAUGH]
Well, that's it.
I'm calling in
the big guns.
"...to cease and desist
on behalf of my client,
Jerry Seinfeld."
Signed, crybaby
Jerry Seinfeld's lawyer.
Okay, well, I've got two words
for you, Jerry Seinfeld:
[TV BLEEPS]
...you!
How could she say that on TV?
And how did she get
a cable special?
I've never gotten
a cable special.
Well, that's it. I'm not
giving her any more material.
We are incommunicado.
Exactly.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Check it out.
From the new issue
of The New Yorker.
It's funny, isn't it?
Uh...
Lookit. The pig wants
to be taller.
And what's this guy
gonna say, huh?
Ha-ha. Nothing.
[LAUGHS]
Elaine, I'm afraid I have
incurred yet another flat tire.
Can I fix that
after lunch, sir?
Oh, no, right away.
Chop, chop.
Oh, a new cartoon.
"I wish I was taller."
[LAUGHS]
I'd like to see that complaint
get rectified.
[LAUGHS]
You see? See?
Smart people
think this is funny.
And you want to know why?
'Cause I wrote it.
You shouldn't
make fun of pigs.
Flash of lightning,
Elaine.
I just realized why I like
this cartoon so much.
Oh, do tell, sir.
It's a "Ziggy."
A "Ziggy"?
That irreverence, that wit.
I'd recognize it anywhere.
Some charlatan
has stolen a "Ziggy"
and passed it off
as his own.
And I can prove it.
Quick, Elaine,
to my archives.
[♪]
Do you--?
You know what--?
You know what's great
about our relationship?
It's not about looks.
It's not?
No.
It can't be.
Okay.
For instance, I remember
when we first met,
we had a great conversation,
huh?
I remember you said I was
the prettiest girl at the party.
But then after that
we really talked, didn't we?
Well, you told me
how familiar I looked
and that you must have seen me
somewhere before, and--
No, no. Look...
This relationship has-- Has--
Has got to be about something.
And fast or I am in very serious
and weird trouble.
Um...
what else happened?
You asked for a piece of gum
because you thought your breath
smelled like hummus.
All right! Yes!
Gum, good enough.
I'll take it.
I like gum.
I do too.
You see, that's what
we're about.
You don't remind me of anyone
and we love gum.
I have gum in my hair.
I'm losing it.
[♪]
Hey, you're Jerry's friend.
You're kooky. Mind if I sit?
My show is going really well.
Have you seen it yet?
You should.
Everybody else in town has.
Oh, you know what?
I got recognized the other day.
How weird is that?
I know.
At first,
I liked the attention,
then after a while, it's like,
take three steps back.
Get a life, okay?
But there wouldn't be
a Sally Weaver
without the fans,
you know what I mean?
But who am I anyway?
There's Sally Weaver the woman,
Sally Weaver the artist,
Sally Weaver the person--
You know, you gotta shut up.
I'm sorry. I--
I haven't spoken in days.
Well, lay it on me,
string bean.
JANET:
Let me get this gum out of my hair
and then I'll be ready
for bed.
Okay, look, the gum
isn't cutting it for me.
We need to be
about something else.
Anything, please.
[DOOR OPENS]
JANET:
George...
Your hair.
Well, I had to cut
the gum out,
and I had a little trouble
getting it even.
So why don't you
get undressed, George?
George is in weird trouble!
[♪]
JERRY:
You ripped off a "Ziggy"?
It must have seeped
into my subconscious.
Puddy has
"Ziggy" bed sheets.
Did you read
the comics today?
Oh, I see Ziggy's back
at the complaint department.
The New Yorker is
stealing my ideas.
[LAUGHS]
See, that's funny...
'cause it's real.
ELAINE:
Hey, lookit,
Sally's cable show is on.
Hey-- Hey, Kramer, come on in.
You're gonna watch this.
This will be funny.
Now she's got nothing.
Master of evil,
Jerry Seinfeld,
broke off all contact with me.
That's right, sister.
Why don't you just give up?
Why are you yelling
at the TV?
Okay, get this.
I heard he makes
his best friend date women
who look just like him.
Hello! Issues!
Elaine, have you
been talking to her?
Hey, I'm just a fan.
Oh, and speaking of issues,
guess who got
a no-polish manicure
and begged his neighbor
not to tell anyone?
I thought
you stopped talking.
All right, starting now.
You broke up with her
because she cut her hair?
How short?
Like that.
You mean, like--?
That.
So she--
Yes.
And you don't--
No.
So--
Exactly.
Hm.
We must never
ever speak of this again.
No, no.
Hey, you--? You want
to go see a movie?
Actually, I think
I'm gonna take a few days off.
I think
that's for the best.
Yes.