I'm doing a set tonight.
You hanging out?
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
[♪]
[SMOKE ALARM BLARING]
[RINGS]
Hello?
You're bad, huh?
I'd like to see you come up here
and say that to my face!
[POUNDING]
So what's the deal
with politics?
I don't get it.
Am I right, people?
[MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[SIGHS]
I don't believe this.
[♪]
I read somewhere
that this Brentano's
is the place to meet girls
in New York.
First it was
the health club,
then the supermarket,
now the bookstore.
They could put it
anywhere they want.
No one's meeting anybody.
Hey, Jerry, look at all
of these pagodas, huh?
I gotta get over to Hong Kong
before it all goes back
to China.
You better hurry.
I'm gonna hit the head.
Oh, boy, look at this.
Hong Kong's outlawed
the ricksha.
See, I always thought those
would be perfect for New York.
Yes. The city needs more
slow-moving wicker vehicles.
Hm, Elaine's been to Hong Kong.
I should give her a call.
She's at that annual
Peterman party tonight.
You know, the one
she danced at last year.
No, that wasn't dancing.
Hey, there's Leo.
Oh, who's Leo?
Uncle Leo.
Oh, yeah, right.
Forgot his first name.
Yeah.
Did I just see that?
Well,
that ought to keep you busy
for a couple of days, huh?
[♪]
So, Elaine,
are you gonna dance
this year?
Maybe.
All over your face.
WOMAN:
If you do dance,
the cooks wanna know
so they can be
brought out of the kitchen.
They missed it last year.
[TAPPING]
My friends, a toast.
As the woolly-haired Melanesians
of Papua New Guinea once said:
[CLICKING AND POPPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
All right!
Who's dancing?
PETERMAN:
No one.
All right, I'll just have
to get things started.
ALL:
Ooh!
[ALL CLAMORING]
[APPLAUSE]
Hi. I'm Zach.
Hi.
I'm miserable.
[LAUGHTER]
[♪]
♪ Ba, ba
Ba-da, ba-dum ♪
Excuse me, sir.
What are you doing?
I'm all set.
Did you take that book with you
into the bathroom?
What do you want to hear?
[♪]
GEORGE:
They made me buy it.
A hundred bucks
this thing cost me!
How dare they?
I got news for you,
if it wasn't for the toilet,
there would be no books.
Yeah, I understand
Gutenberg used to spend
a fair amount of time
in there.
They're selling coffee,
bran muffins,
you're surrounded by
reading material...
It's entrapment!
"French Impressionist
Paintings"?
I find the soothing pastoral
images very conducive--
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm gonna go back there
later and return it
when there's
different people working.
You wanna catch a movie?
I can't.
I'm meeting Uncle Leo.
I saw him shoplifting
at the bookstore.
All right, Leo.
Stickin' it to the man.
Sleeping in the car again?
Cocktail flu.
Oh, right. The big party.
You, uh...
didn't dance again,
did you?
No.
I found a better way
to humiliate myself.
[SIGHS]
There was this guy,
and we had a few too many.
You went home
with him?
ELAINE:
Worse.
We made out at the table
like our plane was going down.
Oh, the drunken make-out.
An office classic.
Did you end up
Xeroxing anything?
Do you know
how embarrassing this is
to someone
in my position?
What is your position?
I am an associate.
Hey. Me too.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, God.
Why did I do this?
Now, I'm the office skank.
Well, unless you tell everybody
you're dating.
ELAINE:
Oh.
Right.
'Cause if we're dating,
what everyone saw was just...
a beautiful moment
between two lovers.
As opposed to a spirited bout
of skanko-Roman wrestling.
Oh, bravo.
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, hey.
Can I fix you fellas
some drinks and sandwiches?
No, no.
We've already eaten.
But you can clear some
of this stuff out of the way.
Jerry,
check this out.
Remember my idea
about rickshas in New York?
Well, we're gonna
make it happen.
No, you're not.
Well, Newman, he knows a guy
in the Hong Kong post office.
No, he doesn't.
He's shipping us a ricksha.
It can't miss.
Yes, it can.
We'll start out with one,
and then when it catches on,
we're gonna have
a whole fleet.
It's the romance
of the hansom cab
without the guilt or dander
of the equine.
That's right.
So who's gonna pull this thing?
I just assumed
that you would.
Yeah, but I thought--
[GIBBERS] No.
My, isn't this
an awkward moment?
Wait a minute.
What about the homeless?
Can't we worry about them later?
To pull the ricksha.
They do have an intimate
knowledge of the street.
They're always
walking around the city.
Why not just
strap something to them?
Now, that's the first sensible
idea I've heard all day.
[♪]
LEO:
Jerry, hello!
So, Leo, how's everything?
You doing okay?
I still have the ringing
in the ears.
It sounds like the phone.
Yeah, yeah.
But what about money?
Are you strapped?
Do you need a little?
Are you kidding?
I should be loaning you money!
But I'm not.
Leo, I saw you
in Brentano's yesterday.
Why didn't you say hello?
Because you were too busy
stealing a book.
You still say hello.
Leo, I saw you steal.
Oh, they don't care.
We all do it.
Who? Criminals?
Senior citizens.
No big deal.
You could get arrested.
Arrested? Come on!
I'm an old man. I'm confused.
I thought I paid for it.
What's my name?
Could you take me home?
Leo.
All right, all right,
Mr. Goody-Two-Shoes.
You made your point.
Thank you.
Will somebody answer
that damn phone?
[♪]
Of course Zach and I
have been dating.
What did you think,
I was the office skank?
Well...
Well?
We've been dating
for 3 months,
between you and me
and anyone else
you want to tell.
Ha-ha.
Oh, man. Ugh!
Isn't that Zach?
Yeah.
Aren't you upset?
Yes!
Oh, man!
[WAILING]
All right, listen up.
Now, you three
have been handpicked
out of possibly dozens
who applied.
Now, what we're looking for
are motivated, hard-working,
homeless, uh, gentlemen,
like yourselves,
to pull rickshas.
Now, I don't care
where you're from,
or how you got here,
or what happened to your homes.
But you will have to be
physically fit.
[CLINKS]
The government!
Because to pull rickshas
requires more
than just strong legs.
You're also gonna need
a well-toned upper body.
Or a shirt.
Right.
Who's first?
Name, please.
Rusty.
You know, I once knew
a horse named Rusty.
No offense.
All right now. Take it down
the end of the block,
make a controlled turn,
and bring 'er back.
Let's see
what you've got.
Okay, ready and go!
Giddyup.
Good form.
All right, pace yourself.
You're gonna have to do this
all day for very little money.
KRAMER:
Hey, what's he doing?
I think he's stealing
our ricksha!
Well, then, he's out.
I'll take the job.
Potato salad!
[♪]
Yes, I, uh--
I need to return this book.
[BEEP, BUZZER]
I'm sorry.
We can't take this book back.
Why not?
It's been flagged.
Flagged?
It's been in the bathroom.
It says that
on the computer?
Please take it home.
We don't want it
near the other books.
Well, you just lost
a lot of business.
Because I love to read!
Oh, I don't believe this.
Excuse me, I wonder
if you could do me a favor?
My uncle's having a problem
with shoplifting.
Mm-hm.
Where's your uncle?
He's over there
in the overcoat.
If you could just kind of
put a scare into him,
you know,
set him straight.
We have a 51-50
in paperbacks.
All units respond.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Roger, 10-4.
51-50. That--
That's just a scare, right?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to stand out of the way
and let us handle this.
Swarm! Swarm!
What?
I'm an old man! I'm confused!
You're under arrest.
I just wanted you
to scare him.
Jerry, you ratted me out!
Hello?
Hello.
[♪]
JERRY:
Mom, I didn't rat out Uncle Leo.
I just wanted the guard
to scare him straight.
Jerry, he won't last a day
in prison.
Prison?
I'm sure it's just a fine.
He's got priors.
Prior convictions?
Leo?
It was a crime of passion.
Leave it alone.
Besides,
it's not stealing
if it's something you need.
What does that mean?
Nobody pays
for everything.
You're stealing too?
JERRY:
What are you stealing?
Nothing.
Uh, batteries.
Well, they wear out so quick.
Mom, you too?
Sometimes your father forgets,
so I have to steal them.
All right,
I'll talk to you later.
Well, the ricksha's gone.
We strapped it
to a homeless guy and he--
[HIGH-PITCHED BUZZ]
He bolted.
Well, you know,
85 percent of all
homeless ricksha businesses fail
within the first three months.
I tell you, we should have
got some collateral from him.
Like his bag of cans
or his...
other bag of cans.
We gotta find that ricksha.
You check the sewers
and dumpsters.
I'll hit the soup kitchens,
bakeries and smorgasbords.
To the idiot-mobile.
[♪]
So even though you're not really
going out with this guy,
he's cheating on you.
That is correct.
But here's the beauty part.
Now, I stand up for myself
by telling everybody
I'm dumping his sorry ass,
and I'm the...office...
Tina Turner?
All right.
Well, I've been
to every Brentano's.
This thing is flagged
in every database in town.
Is it so horrible
to have to keep a book?
I don't understand
what the big deal is.
They let you try on pants.
Not underpants.
Hey, that's your Uncle Leo.
Uncle Leo. Hello!
Jerry.
Uncle Leo...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know about your...
past.
You mean my crime of passion?
If anyone betrays me,
I never forget.
Uncle Leo, wait!
Hello!
French impressionism.
Ohh, I love this!
Now, what is the problem
with this book?
Nothing.
How much do you want for it?
You know, I could let it go
for, uh, say, 125.
Leo's furious.
What is that
doing on the table?
Jerry, simmer down.
I'm not eating anything
in the vicinity of that book.
What is wrong with this book?
Simmer!
That book has been
on a wild ride.
George took it
into the bathroom at--
All right!
Everyone clear!
Biohazard! Coming through!
Clear!
May I ask,
what do you read
in the bathroom?
I don't read in the bathroom.
Well, aren't you something?
[♪]
PETERMAN:
Elaine, do you have a moment?
It's about your lover.
Oh, yes.
I know all about
his little performance
in the break room.
Elaine,
who among us hasn't snuck
into the break room
to nibble on a love newton?
Love newton?
I'm afraid the problem with Zach
is more serious.
He's back on the horse, Elaine.
Smack.
White palace.
The Chinaman's nightcap.
An addict.
Well, it just keeps
getting better.
And in a tiny way,
I almost feel responsible.
I'm the one
who sent him to Thailand
in search of low-cost whistles.
Filled his head
with pseudo-erotic tales
of my own opium excursions.
Plus I gave him
some phone numbers
of places he could score
near the hotel.
Look, uh, Mr. Peterman,
the fact is,
is that I was planning on
breaking up with Zach anyway.
He was cheating on me.
Damn it, Elaine,
that wasn't Zach.
That was the yam-yam.
Now, he is going cold turkey,
and you will be at his side.
Oh. Well, you know, I--
I had planned to--
No buts, Elaine,
or I will strip you
of your associate status.
Uh, P.S.,
the first 24 hours
are the worst.
Better bring a poncho.
[♪]
HELEN:
It was a crime of passion.
UNCLE LEO:
If anyone betrays me, I never forget.
HELEN:
He won't last a day in prison.
[♪]
Jerry.
Hello!
Jerry!
[PHONE RINGS]
Answer the damn phone!
[GASPS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello!
Hey. It's me.
Uncle Leo?
Oh, that's nice.
What are you up to?
Nightmares. You?
My fake boyfriend is going
through real withdrawals.
ZACH:
I'm burning up!
Eat your soup!
You're not feeding him, are you?
Why?
[GAGS]
I told you,
away from the curtains.
Away.
Use your bucket.
[RETCHES]
There you go. That's it.
You know what? I gotta go.
[DIAL TONE]
Hey, buddy.
Oh!
Kramer.
I thought I heard you.
Get out of here.
Hey, Kramer,
there you are.
Will everybody please leave?
I heard that a postman
spotted a ricksha
down in Battery Park.
Our ricksha?
It's entirely possible.
I want everyone out!
Ok, let's talk
in Jerry's kitchen.
Ah.
I'll make some cocoa.
Good night...Jerry.
Good night...Newman.
[♪]
NEWMAN:
There it is.
KRAMER:
Rusty.
Oh, there you are.
Oh, do I get the job?
Yeah, yeah.
We'll get back to you.
Come on,
let's get this baby home.
[GRUNTS]
What?
You know,
when you think about it,
it's kind of silly for us both
to pull this thing
all the way back uptown.
I mean, after all,
it is a conveyance.
I guess, that's true.
So which one of us
is gonna pull?
Well, there's only one way
to settle this.
One spot, two spot,
zigzag, tear,
pop-dye, penny got,
tennyum, tear,
harum-scarum,
rip 'em, tear 'em,
te, ta...
toe.
Yeah.
Best two out of three.
One spot, two spot...
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
Hey, boy!
Smooth it out up there!
Too much jostling!
[♪]
So you wanna donate this
to charity?
Well, I assume
there's some sort of write-off.
What's the value of the book?
A-about $200, Miss DeMooney.
It's DeMornay.
Rebecca DeMornay.
Oh.
Oh. Wait a second.
This book has been
in a bathroom.
Wh-what are you talking about?
That's-- That's ridiculous.
It's been flagged.
I know.
I used to work
in a Brentano's.
Mister, we're trying to help
the homeless here.
It's bad enough
that we have some nut out there
trying to strap 'em
to a ricksha!
All right, I--
I'll just take 50.
D-do we have a deal?
Yeah.
And here it is.
You get your toilet book
out of here,
and I won't jump over
this counter
and punch you in the brain.
I could take it in merchandise.
Here I come.
[♪]
So this book will tell me
how to get puke out of cashmere?
Yeah.
Great.
So the worst is over?
Yeah.
Now I can break up
with him.
He's clean
and I'm the office hero.
Seems like you're better at fake
relationships than real ones.
Yeah. Huh.
I even got an idea
out of it.
The detox poncho.
See ya.
I'd like to speak
with the manager, please.
Mind your pace, boy!
Chop chop!
I've hit the wall!
I gotta take a break!
Well, don't tarry.
I'm behind schedule as it is.
Yah!
Boy?
Boy!
Kramer!
Whoa!
Wait!
[SCREAMING]
Well,
this is the first day
of the rest of my life.
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
George,
what are you doing here?
I can't sell the book.
It's been marked.
It certainly has.
So I'm going to steal
another one,
and then I'm going
to return it.
That way, everything is even.
You defile one book,
steal another,
ask for your money back,
and to you that's even.
I'm going in.
Did you want to speak
to the manager?
Yes. My uncle Leo was caught
shoplifting here the other day.
Yes. Uncle Leo.
I remember him.
I'm sorry. Our policy is
we prosecute all shoplifters.
Oh, come on.
He's just a lonely old man.
All old people steal.
That's right.
That's why we stopped
carrying batteries.
Look, I'll be honest with you,
We've had a lot of trouble
with theft lately,
and my boss said I have
to make an example of someone.
So it could be anyone?
Mm, I guess.
As long as we catch him
in the act.
That guy!
Swarm!
JERRY:
No! Jerry!
[♪]