[♪]
Ahem. Maura, I, uh--
I want you to know
I've given this
a lot of thought.
I'm sorry, but, we, uh--
We have to break up.
No.
What's that?
We're not breaking up.
W-we're not?
No.
All right.
[♪]
JERRY:
She said no?
She said no.
What did you do?
What could I do?
We fooled around
and went to a movie.
George, both parties don't
have to consent to a breakup.
It's not like you're launching
missiles from a submarine
and you both have
to turn your keys.
Obviously, you didn't
make a convincing case.
Let me hear
your arguments.
Well, I don't
really like her.
That's good.
I don't find her attractive.
Solid.
I'd like to sleep with
a lot of other women.
Always popular.
Sometimes at restaurants
she talks to her food.
[MIMICKING]
Ooh, Mr. Mashed Potatoes, you are so good.
You have
an airtight case.
And in bed--
I'm afraid we're out of time.
Hey.
What?
Check these out.
These are Jerry Lewis'
old cuff links
that he actually wore in
the movie Cinderfella.
I got 'em at an auction.
I got some cuff links
I could've loaned you.
No. Jerry Lewis
is gonna be at this
Friar's Club roast
I'm going to.
Now I have an in to strike up
a conversation with him.
You already have an in.
You have
the same first name:
Jerry.
Oh, that'll
intrigue him.
Well, it worked when I met
George Peppard last week.
George Peppard
has been dead for years.
Well, whoever he was,
he knew a lot about
The A-Team.
[♪]
So you would choose
your last meal
based on the method
of execution?
Right. Right. I mean,
if I was getting the chair,
I'd go for something
hot and spicy.
You know, Thai,
maybe Mexican.
Lethal injection
feels like pasta, you know?
It's painless.
Don't want anything too heavy.
So, um, why don't we
get together some time?
Oh, sure. Why don't you
give me your number?
I think it'd be better
if I called you.
Oh. Okay. Maybe we could
grab some lunch sometime...
Do--? Do you work
around here, or--?
Mm-mm. No.
Not really.
So is there anything
you can tell me about yourself?
I think you're
very beautiful.
Oh. Ha, ha.
That'll do.
[LAUGHS]
[♪]
JERRY:
What about Puddy?
I haven't talked to him
in like three weeks.
I think
it might be over.
So, what's
this guy about?
I don't know.
Wouldn't tell me
his phone number,
where he worked...
I'll bet he's
in a relationship.
Or he's
a crime fighter
safeguarding his
secret identity.
Elaine, you could be
dating the Green Lantern!
Which one is he?
Green suit,
power ring.
I don't care
for jewelry on men.
Hey.
It happened again.
Another robbery
in the building.
So you bought
a cooler?
It's a strongbox
to protect my irreplaceables.
And what
would those be?
Some taxidermy that's been
in my family for generations.
My Tony,
my military discharge.
You were
in the Army?
Eh...briefly.
Now I gotta find a good
place to hide this key,
because if
somebody finds this,
they hold the key
to all my possessions.
Literally.
Literally?
What's that
supposed to mean?
You mind if
I hide this somewhere?
No. Go ahead.
[SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
A little privacy, huh?
Oh, come on!
Oh.
Come on, Jerry.
This is a security issue.
Boy, you wouldn't last
a day in the Army.
How long did
you last?
That's classified.
Hey, what if
he's married?
Kramer?
No, the Green Lantern.
KRAMER:
Okay!
So you would date
a married guy?
That's
so hacky.
Well, I don't know.
I may never marry.
This might be
the closest I get.
[UTENSILS CLINKING IN DRAWER]
You peeked!
This is your
hiding place?
It was
under a spoon!
[♪]
GEORGE:
And so, for all these reasons,
we are officially
broken up.
Thank you...
and good night.
No, George, we're not.
But I proved it!
I refuse to give up
on this relationship.
It's like launching missiles
from a submarine.
Both of us have
to turn our keys.
Well, then, I am gonna have
to ask you to turn your key.
I'm sorry, George.
I can't do that.
Turn your key, Maura!
Turn your key!
[♪]
So how is a guy like you
not involved?
I might ask you
the same thing.
ELAINE [THINKING]:
That's true. Maybe he's not married.
Oh, that is so sweet.
How long do I
have to hold this?
Oh, no.
Who is it?
Uh...
Uh, no one. No one.
Here. Uh, let me show you
a shortcut. Come on.
Married. That's it.
I'm chuckin' the flower.
[♪]
Jerry!
Elaine, what are you
doing down there?
You didn't hear me buzzing?
Oh, I guess it's broken.
Well, throw down
your key.
It's liable to bounce
and go into a sewer!
I'll catch it!
You'll chicken out
at the last second.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, will you at least
keep me company until
somebody comes out?
[ANNOYED]
All right.
Hey, you know
what's weird?!
Huh?
I used to be able
to have a huge meal,
go right to sleep,
but I can't anymore.
Nodding off!
Well, I was right.
He's an adulterer.
And he's cheating
on his wife with me!
We haven't
done anything yet.
I'm hungry! Can you
throw something down?
All right!
Here! I'm gonna try
and fix the buzzer.
ELAINE:
It went in the sewer!
Hey!
What are you doing?
You jammed
your key in here?
You shorted out
my intercom!
You just had to go
lookin' for it, didn't you?
See, you hate it that
I have a little secret.
Anything I do: ooh, ooh!
You gotta know all about it!
You're so
obsessed with me!
I'm gonna
go let Elaine in.
What are you
doing with her?
[BANGING]
Kramer!
KRAMER:
Security issue!
Oh, hey, you got in.
Yeah.
Flirted with
the menu guy. Here.
Oh. Thanks.
KRAMER [BANGING]:
That wasn't me!
So he's definitely
married, huh?
Ugh.
Boy, would have
loved to have been there
when you told him off.
[CLEARS THROAT NERVOUSLY]
Oh, come on.
Well, he could be
a superhero!
You should've
seen him run.
KRAMER:
Okay!
All right,
Jerry.
Let's see if you can
get it in your head
that this is not
an Easter egg hunt
for your childish
amusement.
Jerry!
[TRYING TO WHISTLE]
George, the buzzer's
broken. I'll come down!
I believe
this belongs to you.
[YELLS]
[♪]
Where did you
get that?
I bought it.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I--
I don't know you.
What?
There's been some robberies
in the building.
I-- I can't
let you in.
But I live here. I ran out
to buy some birdseed,
and-- And I
forgot my key.
Sounds like
a scam.
I'm very sorry.
So I broke up
with Maura.
It's done.
I'm out.
Great. You're lonely
and miserable again.
Feels right.
Is that guy
still there?
He's staring
at us.
Don't look at him.
[KNOCKING]
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
We don't hear that.
Want a bite?
No, I don't.
[♪]
GEORGE [THINKING]:
I think that ginger ale at the coffee shop
is just Coke and Sprite
mixed together.
How can I prove it?
Ah! I can't! Damn it!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi, honey.
What?
M-Maura, what are
you doin' here?
I ended this
relationship twice.
George, you didn't mean that.
That was just a fight.
Why does it
always seem like
I'm the only one
working at this breakup?
George, I listened
to your arguments,
and they were rambling
and flimsy.
I'm not convinced.
Come on. Get dressed,
and let's get some dinner.
All right.
[BABY-TALK VOICE]
Ew, Mr. Apple! You have a brown spot!
[♪]
ELAINE:
So this is your little... love nest?
It's nothing special,
just a little place I keep.
Oh.
Uh, shall I light a fire?
Oh. That sounds...
romantic.
I'm having a little
problem with the heat.
Um, I got some
cardboard out here.
ELAINE [THINKING]:
This is wrong! I should go!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Can you
get that, please?
ELAINE:
Oh, sure!
[GASPS]
Where's Glenn?
You're the woman
from the street,
and I am so sorry.
You know, I'm not
really a homewrecker.
I-I-I-I thought
he was a superhero.
I swear!
Lady, I'm not his wife.
I'm his welfare caseworker.
Is he home?
This is his home?
Yes.
So he's...
Poor.
[BANGING]
I think this
will burn!
[♪]
So you do
live here.
Yeah.
You live
on this floor?
Yeah.
So you live right...
there.
Yeah.
So I guess I'll s--
[SLAMS]
[♪]
ELAINE:
He wouldn't give me his number,
because he doesn't
have a phone.
He's not married.
He's poor.
Is he wretchedly poor?
Does he wear one of those
barrels with the straps?
He probably busted it up
and burned it for heat.
So when are you givin'
Boxcar Willie
his walkin' papers?
How can I end it
over money?
I feel bad.
Well, let's think.
Have you ever dealt with
the poor in any other situation?
Yes. There was
this homeless guy
who used to urinate
on our garbage cans.
Good. How did
you handle that?
Well, we gave him
a few bucks,
and now he goes in
the alley across the street.
Same situation.
Pay him off,
and you're clean.
Well, I am not
paying Glenn off
to get out of
this relationship.
Wh--? What am I
supposed to do,
just walk into his hovel
and hand him...?
Well, how much do you
think it would be?
Hey.
Hey, where have
you been?
Seeing Maura.
Apparently, I was
unable to break up
beyond a reasonable doubt.
If only he could have been
cheating on his wife.
You know, things would have
been so much simpler.
Who is this,
Blue Arrow?
Green Lantern.
We found out his super-power
was lack of money.
All right.
He's invulnerable
to creditors.
We get it.
He's the
Got-No-Green Lantern.
Thank you.
Hey, Elaine.
Maybe his
girlfriend
is Lois Loan.
Well-crafted.
Hey, maybe this
cheating thing
is what I could use
to ditch Maura.
Sure. Just tell Maura
you're having an affair.
She's like a
district attorney.
If it's not the truth,
I'll break under the cross.
I actually
have to do it.
Could you move
over there?
Hey, you know,
there's this secretary at work
that always had
a crush on me.
Really? How come you
never pursued her before?
She's too tanned.
It's the middle of the winter.
She's like a carrot.
Did I leave
my glasses here?
He could wipe out his
checking account
in a single bounce!
Keep 'em.
[♪]
[DOOR OPENING]
[PARROT SQUAWKS]
[CHUCKLES]
There's a giant parrot
in the hallway.
It's Phil's.
Who?
Our neighbor that
you turned against.
Anyway, I told him
it would be fine with us
if he wanted to let it stretch
its wings out in the hallway.
What'd you
tell him that for?
Because since you've been
playing God with the front door,
I've been tryin' to
smooth things out, Jerry.
In fact, I was just
hangin' out at his place.
Really? What's it like?
Is it nicer than mine?
Where does he have the couch?
Well, I don't know,
but the key problem is solved.
I hid it at Phil's.
He let you?
No. He doesn't know.
See, I hid it
without telling him.
So, uh, Phil won't be
compulsively looking for it,
like some people.
You.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[PARROT SCREECHING]
[BANGING, YELLING]
[♪]
So you-- You say you've been
in the city all winter?
I was in Maine
for a couple days.
Well...
here we are.
[CHUCKLES]
George...
I've always fantasized about
jumping into bed with you.
Ho-ho!
But...
I don't want
to spoil things
by sleeping
with you too soon.
Are you sure?
'Cause it could really
help me out of a jam.
I wanna build something
with you, George.
Oh, not more building.
And I won't take "no"
for an answer.
No?
No.
All right.
[♪]
Eh, what are we doing
in this alley, anyway?
It's a surprise.
[GIGGLING]
Oh.
What are you doing?
What is that?
It's a bag
of doughnuts.
It's garbage.
No, no, no, no.
When they make
the new ones,
the old ones
come out right here.
All right. That's it.
How do you spell
your last name?
It's a bear claw!
You have no idea
how rare this is.
I'll make it out
to cash.
How about 200 bucks?
Two-fifty?
Mm!
Make it 300.
You know, Elaine,
you're the bear claw
in the garbage bag
of my life.
Aw, Glenn...
[♪]
Hi. Is Phil here?
Yeah, I'm here.
[PARROT SQUAWKS]
Phil, hi.
I-I know we got off
to kind of a bad start,
but your bird--
Which is lovely,
by the way.
--made a mess
on my door.
And?
I thought maybe
you'd clean it up,
or your maid there.
That's my wife.
All right.
I think we're done here.
[♪]
JERRY:
So you're in a relationship with a woman you don't like,
and you're having
an affair with a woman
that won't
have sex with you.
This isn't going well.
I cannot find my
Jerry Lewis cuff links.
Without 'em,
I have no in!
You don't need
the cuff links!
You have the same name!
Jerry!
Where you goin'?
Help me look!
It's a big night.
I'm, uh...
ice-skating with one,
and going to a staged reading
of Godspell with the other.
Which is with who?
It doesn't matter.
Whoo! Boy.
Yeah, you
clean up nice.
I can't go until
I find my cuff links.
Yeah, see? I knew
you would lose 'em.
That's why I took 'em
outta your dresser drawer
and put 'em
in my strongbox.
[FLATLY]
You're a lifesaver.
Would you get them, please?
Yeah. We'll stop by Phil's.
We'll pick up the key.
[WOMAN SOBBING]
Hey, what's
goin' on?
Fredo is dead.
That strange
Portuguese guy
that lives next door
to the incinerator?
No! My bird.
We just got back
from the pet cemetery.
Oh...Phil.
Mrs. Phil.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I'll bet you are!
They told us
he was poisoned!
Something in his food.
But I--
I didn't-- I--
[DOOR SLAMS]
Kramer, they think
I killed Fredo!
And who buries
a bird?
Yeah. Just give it
to the Portuguese guy,
and he puts it
in the incinerator.
Just get the key,
and let's get outta here.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, it's a--
It's a funny thing
about that bird dying.
I hid the key
in Fredo's food dish.
Whew! That's a weird
coincidence, huh?
Kramer.
What?
You killed Fredo!
Well, Fredo was
weak and stupid.
He shouldn't have
eaten that key.
Kramer, I need
those cuff links,
but now they're in the box,
and the key is in the bird.
What are we gonna do?
You just answered
your own question.
Oh, no.
I'll get the shovel.
[♪]
The, uh, actor
that played Jesus
made some odd choices.
What?
I mean, uh,
I had fun ice-skating.
George?
Maura.
Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
You told me
to meet you here for lunch.
Oh! I'm caught
in my own web of lies!
I'm Maura.
I'm Loretta.
You wanna join us?
Oh! This is all
blowing up in my face!
My-- My serious girlfriend
and my torrid love affair
have accidentally
crossed paths.
I have ruined
three lives!
Well, I understand if you
never wanna see me again.
So...
George, what we have
is too important.
We can work
through this.
So can we.
What?
So this is still
not over?
No.
You?
All right.
[♪]
GLENN:
Elaine, wow.
A TV, a stereo.
Yeah, and I got you
a cord of wood
so you won't
have to burn 'em.
Oh, my God. Alison.
You're home early.
Who is this?
His wife.
You're poor and married?
Looks like it.
Who the hell are you?
I guess I'm Lois Loan.
[♪]
Kramer, I can't believe
we're graverobbers.
"Man's best friend."
Jerry, I want something
like that on my tombstone.
Oh, my God.
Here he is.
I don't wanna
dig him up.
All right.
Then you're the one
getting the key
out of him.
I'll dig.
Listen, I heard that
Lassie number three's
buried around here.
I'm gonna go
check it out.
[CLINK]
Well, that was easy.
[♪]
All right, honey.
One last look.
Then you have to let Fredo
rest in peace.
Hey, Kramer,
I dug Fredo up.
Now let's
cut him open.
Oh, my God!
[MUFFLED YELL]
Hey, neighbor.
[♪]
All right.
I'm gonna try
giving them $55 each.
What do you think?
Give me 40,
you'll never see me again.
[SUCKS TEETH]
So what're you gonna do?
You gonna live here,
are you gonna move out,
or what?
I'll just take
the fire escape
to get in and out
of the building.
So, what's in
the cooler?
[GASPS]
Well, will you
look at that.
I guess I forgot
to lock it.
You mean
it was open?
We desecrated
a pet cemetery for nothing?!
Well,
this is one for the books,
huh, Jerry?
[♪]
KRAMER:
Really one for the books.