When are they gonna learn
that any news about China
is an instant page-turner?
What's that?
It's a Wizard electronic
organizer for my dad.
I'm goin' to Florida
for his birthday.
How much was it?
Two hundred.
But I'll tell him it's 50.
He doesn't care about the gift,
he gets excited about the deal.
Where are you gettin'
a Wizard for $50?
Ah, I'll tell him I got it
on the street
and maybe it's hot.
That's his favorite.
I got a message
from the Rosses at work today.
Susan's parents?
When's the last time you talked?
At the funeral, give or take.
You know,
deep down I always kinda felt
that they blamed me
for Susan's death.
Why? Because you picked out
the poisoned envelopes?
That's silly.
Oh. Um...
Darryl, these are...
people I know.
Jerry, George.
Nice meeting you.
I gotta run, Elaine.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Still no Puddy?
Ah, I think his
answering machine's broken,
so I just gave up.
What do you think?
What, about you datin'
a black guy?
What's the big deal?
What black guy?
Darryl.
He's black, isn't he?
He is?
No, he isn't.
Isn't he, Elaine?
You think?
I thought he looked Irish.
What's his last name?
Nelson.
That's not Irish.
I think he's black.
Should we be talkin'
about this?
I think it's okay.
No, it isn't.
Why not?
Well, it would be okay
if Darryl was here.
If he's black.
Is he black?
Does it matter?
No, of course not.
I mean, I'd just like to know.
So you need to know.
No, I don't need to know.
I just think
it would be nice if I knew.
Shall I take that?
Uh, one second.
Oh, here.
Uh, yeah. Hang on.
Just...yeah.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Uh, Mrs. Ross, it's--
It's George.
Who?
George Costanza,
Susan's, uh...friend?
GEORGE:
Long time no speak.
We're all out of lime juice.
Told that woman to buy more.
George,
the Susan Ross Foundation
is having an event
this weekend.
Ohh, I just, uh, leased
a house out in the Hamptons,
and I have got to get out there
this weekend
and sign the papers.
I'm goin' back to bed.
Thank you for calling George.
Oh, sure.
I mean, after all,
you were almost my, uh...
Okay, I gotta go.
House in the Hamptons.
Well, I been lying about
my income for a few years.
I figured I could afford
a fake house in the Hamptons.
Well.
Hey.
Well,
grab a cigar, boys.
Yeah.
It's time to celebrate.
Oh, what are we celebrating?
Uh, you remember
my coffee table book?
With the little legs?
That's the one.
A big Hollywood so-and-so
optioned it
for a movie.
How are they gonna make
that book into a movie?
Remember that photo book
on toy ray guns?
Yeah?
Independence Day?
How much are they payin' you?
Let's just say that I don't
have to worry about working
for a while, a long while.
That's funny because
I haven't seen you working
for a while,
a long while.
And you're not going to.
Because I'm hanging it up.
Boys, I'm retiring.
From what?
From the grind.
I mean, who needs it?
I've accomplished everything
I've set out to do.
What's that?
Oh, I bought myself
a little retirement gift.
Gold watch.
Ooh!
[WHISPERING]
Well, it's not really gold.
Ohhh.
[♪]
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY]
Hey.
Great music.
Oh, it's my neighbor.
They blast that stuff
24 hours a day. I hate it.
Yo, yo! Turn it down!
Oh, wow.
These are nice.
Do they have any
cultural significance?
They're...African.
Right.
[LAUGHS]
African.
Well, not "Africa."
Actually, South Africa.
South Africa.
My family used to live there,
but we got out years ago,
for obvious reasons.
You know how it is.
Maybe.
You must hate
hot dogs, huh?
Or else you, uh--
You really like 'em
and that's why you--
You do this.
I tell ya, if I had
one of these things,
I'd be eatin' hot dogs
all the time.
Are you gonna buy
a hot dog or not?
No.
[♪]
[BLENDER WHIRRING]
Rise and shine, sleepyhead!
Ha, ha.
It's 5:30 in the morning.
We let you sleep in.
Well, as long as I'm up,
Dad, I got you
a birthday present.
Here. Happy birthday.
Aw, Jerry.
I should be
buying you presents.
What does that mean?
Leave your father alone.
It's his birthday.
Ooh!
[CHUCKLES]
It's a radar detector!
Radar detector.
I've never seen you go over
20 miles an hour.
You're like the grand marshal
of the Rose Bowl parade.
It's a Wizard organizer!
This looks like too much money.
Nah, I got it
from a guy on the street.
It was like 50 bucks.
You think it's hot?
Could be.
Attaboy!
Helen! Jerry got me
a hot Wizard computer!
I'm right here.
And you can do everything
with it.
You can get e-mail, fax.
There's a calculator.
So I can use it in a restaurant
to figure out the tip?
Yeah, I guess.
But the really cool thing
is the daily planner.
Helen,
we can go into restaurants
and figure out the tips!
Jerry, you're getting
your father too excited.
Hey, buddy.
When did you get in?
Kramer, what are you doing here?
I told you I was retiring.
I moved in next door.
Mr. Cornstein died,
and it's a beautiful apartment.
Yeah, your folks said
it was for rent,
so I jumped on it.
Kramer, you can't live
down here,
this is where people
come to die!
Not you.
Older people.
Don't eat cookies
for breakfast!
I'll fix you
something.
How about a feta cheese omelet?
Mmm. That sounds great, Mom.
If you feed him,
he'll never leave.
I don't have any feta.
How about cottage cheese
and Egg Beaters?
I guess.
I don't believe this.
I know. I know.
Don't I look more relaxed?
[♪]
Wow!
Yeah!
Whoo!
[SIREN WAILS]
ELAINE:
So, George, do you have any thoughts
on this Darryl situation?
Actually,
I did have a thought.
Oh.
Why don't you just ask him?
Because if I ask him,
then it's like
I really want to know.
Maybe he's, um...
mixed.
Is that the right word?
I don't think we're supposed
to be talkin' about this.
I'm just, uh, gonna go
to the bathroom.
You know what? I'm leavin'.
I'll just talk to Jerry
when he gets back.
Oh!
Mrs. Ross, Mr. Ross.
Oh, you're George's friend.
We saw him in the city
this weekend.
What happened to his place
in the Hamptons?
The Hamptons?
[LAUGHS]
George Costanza?
Uh, I--
[LAUGHS]
I don't think so.
Have a good one.
[LAUGHING]
Rosses.
George.
We were just talking about you.
GEORGE:
Oh.
Well, sorry I missed that,
uh, charity thing,
but this was one of those
truly glorious Hampton weekends
that you always
hear about.
Really.
Yeah, I may move out there.
I mean it. I'll do it.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Keep it real!
[♪]
MORTY:
Another fine meal.
And now for my Wizard
tip calculator.
Dad, it's got lots
of other functions.
Don't worry. I'll get
to the other functions.
I can't get it open.
Yay! Jerry got it open.
The service was slow,
and God forbid
they should refill the water.
How does, uh,
12.4 percent sound?
Well, your tip is $4
and 36.6666 cents.
We'll round down.
Jerry, it was so nice of you
to come down here
on your father's birthday.
You've helped take his mind
off the condo election.
Oh, right. You can't run
for condo president
because you were impeached
at the other condo.
I was never impeached.
I resigned!
Even so,
the press would bury him.
What press?
The condo newsletter.
The Boca Breeze.
Pinko commie rag.
Hey, Morty,
your boy here,
he just got a date with
that young aquacise instructor.
She's 50.
You know
what he's got?
He's got charisma.
That's my man.
All right,
I'll see you guys. Yeah.
Yeah.
Morty,
what are you lookin' at?
I'll tell you
what I'm looking at.
The next condo board president
of Del Boca Vista,
phase three.
[♪]
DARRYL:
Elaine, thank you for the Wizard!
[LAUGHS]
Wow, it's got
so many functions.
Yeah, yeah.
Forget about all that.
First thing is first.
Warranty information.
Name. We know that.
Uh, hobbies.
Skiing, racquetball--
I don't do that stuff.
It doesn't matter.
Um...
Oh! Here's one.
Race.
Isn't that optional?
It certainly should be.
It's nobody's damn business!
But they really
would like to know.
All right. Asian.
What?
Just to mess with 'em.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh, right.
Good one.
"Average income."
Uh...
over 100,000.
Really?
Does that matter?
No.
But it is very nice to know.
[LAUGHS]
[♪]
JERRY:
So did you figure out
Darryl's...
You know.
Ah, I've given up.
So now we're going to a bunch
of Spanish restaurants.
Figure that'll cover us
either way.
You're a master
of race relations.
Hey, so Kramer's running
for president of the condo?
Yeah, it's all
my father's doing.
[GIBBERS]
He wants to install Kramer
in a puppet regime
and then wield power
from behind the scenes,
preferably from the sauna
in the clubhouse.
[ELAINE LAUGHS]
Who are they running against?
Common sense
and a guy in a wheelchair.
Jerry?
He's still down
with his folks.
What are you doin' here?
Elaine, Elaine--
I'm gettin' his mail.
Oh, no.
He asked you
to get the mail?
Mm-hm.
Jerry, why is Elaine
getting your mail?
George, listen to me.
I have a very important job
for you.
I want you to come by
twice a day
and flush the toilet
so the gaskets
don't dry out and leak.
What?
Well, what about the mail?
This is far more important.
You must exercise the gaskets,
George.
All right, Jerry.
I'll do it.
See ya.
So, I ran into
the Rosses again.
Oh, right,
at the coffee shop.
Where did they get the idea
that you have a place
in the Hamptons?
From me.
What did you say?
I told them I have a place
in the Hamptons.
What did you say?
I told them you didn't.
And I laughed,
and I laughed.
[LAUGHS]
So they knew?
Those liars!
But you lied first.
Yeah, but they let me
go on and on,
all about the Hamptons!
They never said a thing!
You don't let somebody lie
when you know they're lying.
You call them a liar!
Like you're a liar!
Yes, thank you!
Was that so hard?
So this is over?
Not over?
I'm bettin'...not over.
Not by a long shot.
I'm callin' up the Rosses
and inviting them out
to my nonexistent place
in the Hamptons.
Then we'll see
who blinks first!
Haven't you done enough
to these people?
This is not about them.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to exercise
Jerry's gaskets.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Vote for Kramer.
Cosmo Kramer,
running for condo president.
Like your vote.
Thanks.
Remember, ma'am, a vote for me
is a vote for Kramer.
Can you cut my meat?
Gladly.
[♪]
Coffee?
Sure.
Are you black?
Or should I bring some cream?
I'm black. Oh, you know what?
Bring a little cream.
Look at that.
Did you hear that?
What?
There are still people
who have trouble
with an interracial couple.
Interracial? Us?
I mean, isn't--
Isn't that unbelievable?
Yes, it's awful!
They're upset because
we're an interracial couple?
Ha, that is racism!
I don't feel like eating.
Agh, me neither.
Well, maybe this turkey club.
So,
here I am
ready to take you
to the Hamptons.
Sounds grand.
Do you have
your bathing suits?
It's March.
Speak now, or we are headed
to the Hamptons.
It's a two-hour drive.
Once you get in that car,
we are going all the way...
to the Hamptons.
All right.
You want to get nuts?
Come on.
Let's get nuts!
[♪]
JERRY:
Hey, Dad?
You can program
this thing to beep
every time you need
to take a vitamin!
Dad, you look so different.
No, we're campaigning, Jerry.
To rule the people,
one must walk among them.
This is the homestretch.
Tomorrow's the election!
Right. Yeah.
Polls close after dinner, 3:00,
but then when we win,
the celebration goes all night
until the break of 8 p.m.
[LAUGHS]
You know, you can put
that whole schedule
right in your daily planner.
Daily what?
Have you read
today's Boca Breeze?
Hey, look at that
picture of me, huh? Yeah.
"Candidate Cosmo Kramer
caught barefoot in clubhouse."
What?
Barefoot
in the clubhouse?
Kramer, don't you realize
this is against the rules?
Well, I couldn't find my shoes.
Kramer, these people work
and wait their whole lives
to move down here,
sit in the heat,
pretend it's not hot,
and enforce these rules.
Who wants
hot chocolate?
This is
a huge scandal!
We need damage control.
All right, look.
People seem to like
those tip calculators.
Wizards!
How about if we give one out
to every member
on the condo board?
Kramer...
There are 20 people
on the board.
Thank God
you can get that deal.
Payoffs.
Now we're playin' politics!
All right, what do we do next,
Morty, huh?
Wire taps? Slush funds?
First I need a nap.
Ooh, I'll get
your electric blanket.
Kramer, I can't get
that many Wizards.
What about your deal?
I didn't have a deal!
They're $200 a pop.
What do I do?
Don't worry about it.
I know a guy.
Down here?
Yeah,
Bob Sacamano's father.
[♪]
And that leads into
the master bedroom.
Tell us more.
You want to hear more?
The master bedroom opens
into the solarium--
Another solarium?
Yes, two solariums.
Quite a find.
And I have horses too.
What are their names?
Snoopy and Prickly Pete.
Should I keep driving?
Oh, look, an antique stand.
Pull over. We'll buy you
a housewarming gift.
[CHUCKLING]
Housewarming gift.
All right,
we're taking it up a notch!
[♪]
Here you go.
Long day?
Yeah. I just worked
a triple shift.
I hear ya, sister.
Sister?
Yeah. It's okay.
My boyfriend's black.
Here he is. See?
Hi, Elaine.
Hey.
He's black?
Yeah.
I'm black?
Aren't you?
I'll give you
a couple minutes to decide.
What are you talking about?
You're black.
You said we were
an interracial couple.
We are because you're Hispanic.
I am?
Aren't you?
No. Why would you think that?
Your name's Benes.
Your hair.
And you kept taking me
to those Spanish restaurants.
That's because I thought
you were black.
Why would you take me
to a Spanish restaurant
because I'm black?
I don't think we should
be talking about this.
So what are you?
I'm white.
So we're just a...
couple of white people?
I guess.
Oh.
Yeah.
So do you want to go
to the Gap?
Sure.
[♪]
Oh, well.
I handed out
all the Wizards.
The polls close
in one hour.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
I think we got this baby
all sewn up, huh?
Yeah. Oh, uh--
There was an extra one.
Norman Bergerman.
He won't be leavin'
any tips where he is. Aw.
Congratulations,
Mr. President.
Mr. Puppet Master.
Ha-ha.
Hey, Morty.
What's wrong with these
tip calculators?
What are you
talking about?
It's overtipping.
I just left 5 bucks
for a BLT.
Let me see that.
This isn't a Wizard,
it's a Willard.
A Willard?
Sacamano Sr. screwed me!
Mine doesn't have a seven.
I'm ruined!
Jerry,
why didn't you get them Wizards?
Because
a real Wizard's $200!
You didn't have a deal?
No deal, not hot.
Morty, you and Kramer,
you're finished.
What?
SID:
Everyone vote for the guy in the wheelchair.
The people have spoken.
Well, that's it for me. I'm--
I'm headin' back to New York.
Dad, I'm sorry.
You should be!
How could you spend $200
on a tip calculator?!
It does other things!
[♪]
Where are we, George?
Almost there.
This is the end
of Long Island.
Where's your house?
We, uh, go on foot from here.
All right.
There's no house!
It's a lie!
There's no solarium.
There's no Prickly Pete.
There's no other solarium.
We know.
Then why?
Why did you make me
drive all the way out here?!
Why didn't you say something?
Why? Why? Why?!
We don't like you, George.
And we always blamed you
for what happened to Susan.
Oh.
All right.
Let's head back.
[♪]