[♪]
JERRY:
Yeah. Yeah.
All right.
Uh-huh.
[KNOCKS]
[MUFFLED]
Chinese food.
Oh. There's
my Chinese food.
I gotta run.
All you.
Who was it?
I did a show for
a car dealership,
and they're getting me
a new Saab.
What about your old car?
Couldn't get the blood out?
Nah. The engine
clotted.
You know who set
this whole thing up for me?
Frank Merman.
Fragile Frankie Merman?
Never liked that guy.
Why? He's harmless.
Every summer,
you guys went to
camp together.
I was jealous.
It felt like
he was the summer me.
He was not the summer you.
Eh.
Besides, you had a summer me.
Whitey Fisk,
the guy who snuck you
into Last Tango in Paris.
I made him up.
So you never saw
Last Tango in Paris?
No.
Too bad.
It was erotic.
[DOOR OPENS]
Well...
I've had it with
these jackbooted
thugs.
Pottery Barn?
I got three Pottery Barn
catalogs in one day.
That makes eight
this month.
Hm. Mira Sorvino.
Think she'd go out with me?
Why don't you just
throw 'em out?
Oh, no.
I've been saving 'em up
here in your apartment.
And now...
it's payback time.
Pottery Barn is in
for a world of hurt.
Can I have one?
I need one of those
old-looking phones.
[SIGHS]
So you want to grab a bite?
I can't.
I gotta make
the weekly call to the folks.
So call now.
Gotta prep.
I need a couple anecdotes,
a few you-were-right-abouts.
It's a whole procedure.
Wasn't Fragile Frankie
the one that used to
run into the woods
every time he got upset?
That's him.
Hm.
Is he still nuts?
What do you think?
They gave me a new car
for 30 minutes of
"So, who's from
out of town?"
[♪]
PUDDY:
Seriously,
is this the best okra
you've ever had, or what?
Mmm.
Delish.
Delish?
You know,
short for delicious.
Oh. Like scrump.
Yeah.
I'm gonna be late.
I'll see you later.
Excuse me. Can I
borrow your ketchup?
Oh, sure.
[MAGICAL HARP PLAYS]
Thanks.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
ESTELLE:
Hello?
Hey, it's Georgie.
Let me put your father
on the phone.
GEORGE:
Ma--
Who's this?
Dad, it's me.
Hey, uh, listen. I was at, uh,
Fortunoff's the other day,
and you know what?
You were right.
[KNOCKING]
[MUFFLED VOICE THROUGH PHONE]
Chinese food.
FRANK:
Sorry, George, our Chinese food just came.
Talk to you later.
Chinese food?
[DIAL TONE]
[♪]
Hey, you like
sending out catalogs!
How do you like
getting 'em back?!
[♪]
JERRY:
So? Maybe they had Chinese food.
After dark?
Please.
At their age, that's like
swallowing stun grenades.
Well, there's
one way to check.
Where there's
Chinese food...
there's leftovers.
Well, gentlemen...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
...Laney is...
in love.
[CLAPS HANDS]
That's dynamite.
Yeah, I'll look for
the leftovers.
Yeah.
Hey. Hey, hey.
I met this guy.
And it was
like this...
totally unreal
fairy-tale moment.
Wasn't Whitey Fisk,
was it?
Oh, George's friend.
Whatever happened to him?
Nothing. I don't--
I don't know.
I-- I got
to go.
So this is
beautiful.
You and Puddy
and this new guy
in a big pot
of love stew.
Oh, yeah.
Puddy.
Well, I won't fire him
until I see if this
new guy can, uh...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
...handle the workload.
Will you look
at this?
More catalogs.
Omaha Steaks,
Mac Warehouse,
Newsweek?
I can't stop
all these companies,
so I'm gonna attack
this problem
at the choke point.
[CLICKS]
Stop the mail?
[SNAPS]
That's even better.
[♪]
Jerry.
Hey, Frankie.
So where's
the car?
This is it.
Inside the van?
It is the van.
Don't you
remember?
We always talked about
how cool it would be
to have a van
and just drive.
We were 10.
Come on. Let's
take it for a spin.
I don't want
a van. [DOOR OPENS]
Well, just tell him
you want the Saab.
You don't
understand.
This is Fragile
Frankie Merman.
When we were in camp,
if you upset him,
he'd run into the woods,
dig a hole and sit in it.
Well, I have an idea.
Keep the van,
and just get a bumper sticker
that says,
"If this van's a-rockin',
don't come a-knockin'."
Always helpful.
[♪]
ESTELLE:
Oh, Georgie. [GEORGE CHUCKLES]
What are you
doing here?
Just dropped in
for a visit.
You, uh...
You never
called me back.
Uh, the phone broke.
Well, we gotta get moving.
What? Where are
you going?
We have
a catered affair.
You're going
like that?
It's creative
black tie.
Move, woman.
No Chinese
leftovers.
George is getting
suspicious.
[♪]
Elaine.
Sorry I'm late.
[MAGICAL HARP PLAYS]
I'm gonna be in the can.
Okay, Jack.
Oh, can I use
your phone?
Sure.
Puddy? It's Elaine.
We're through.
Yeah. That's right.
Again.
Thanks.
[♪]
FRANKIE:
Nice captain's chairs, huh?
Aye, aye.
Oh, there's a spot.
Just back up.
[BEEPING]
Oh, hold on. There must be
a truck backing up.
No. That's us.
Great.
You know, Frankie...
I was wondering.
What if I decided
that it's...
silly to have
a van because,
you know...
I live in New York City.
Is there maybe some way
I could exchange it?
You don't like the van.
No. No, no.
It's just hypothetically.
I gotta go to the park.
No. No,
you don't.
No woods.
I love the van.
I'm a van guy.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Check it out.
Rain and sleet
may not stop them.
But let's see them
get by...
these bricks.
Where'd you get
the bricks?
Jerry, the whole
building is brick.
So you want to take a ride
with me out to Jersey?
I'm gonna try and sell
the van to a lot.
A dealer? Are you
insane?
No. Take out
an ad.
Sell it privately.
I don't wanna
meet the people
that are in the market
for a used van.
[♪]
Come on, Jerry, just
let me help you.
Okay.
All right. Okay.
Here we go. Yeah.
So, uh,
for sale, huh?
For sale.
A big...
juicy...
van.
And, ooh...
we gotta put down,
"interesting trades...
considered."
I don't want
a trade.
No, no, no, no.
You don't have to.
See, it's all about tickling
their buying bone.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Hey, you know what?
This is all your mail.
They're putting it
in my box now.
Let me see that.
Oh. That's it.
They have gone too far.
They keep pushing me
and pushing me!
Now I got no choice
but to go down there...
and talk to them.
Hey, Jerry.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I'd like you
to meet someone.
This is Jack.
[MAGICAL HARP PLAYING]
[♪]
WOMAN:
May I help you?
Yeah. I'd like to
cancel my mail.
Certainly. How long
would you like us to hold it?
Oh, no, no.
I don't think you get me.
I want out.
Permanently.
I'll handle this,
Violet.
Why don't you take
your three-hour break?
Oh, calm down,
everyone.
No one's canceling
any mail.
Oh, yes, I am.
Well, what about your bills?
The bank can pay 'em.
The bank.
Mm.
What about
your cards and letters?
E-mail, telephones,
fax machines,
FedEx, Telex,
telegrams,
holograms--
[WHISPERS]
All right, it's true!
Of course nobody needs mail.
What--? What do you think
you're so clever,
figuring that one out?
[WHISPERS]
But you don't know the half of what goes on here.
So just walk away, Kramer.
I beg of you.
Is everything
all right here,
postal employee
Newman?
Yes, sir.
I believe everything
is all squared away.
Isn't it...
Mr. Kramer?
Oh, yeah.
As long as I stop
getting mail.
[LAUGHS]
[♪]
Welcome back.
[GASPS]
Pretty quick for a, uh...
catered affair.
I don't know
what you mean.
You ditched me.
That's twice.
Now I demand to know
what's going on!
George, we've had it
with you.
Understand?
We love you
like a son...
but even parents
have limits.
ESTELLE:
The breakups,
the firings,
and every Sunday
with the calls.
What my wife is
trying to say
is this is supposed
to be our time.
I'm not following.
I'm sorry, George.
We're cutting you loose.
You're cutting me loose?
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
I'm gonna make love
to your mother.
[♪]
GEORGE:
They don't want to see me anymore.
But this is what
you've always wanted.
It is.
Just not
ready yet.
Ah, that's kind of sweet.
Ah, shut up, Jerry.
My parents think
they can ignore me.
Heh-heh.
Well, they better
think again.
Oh, no.
George, please.
What are you gonna do?
You remember
my cousin, Rhisa?
I'm gonna date her.
Mother of God.
One little wink.
She'll freak out,
tell my parents.
They'll be all over me.
Hah.
What is this tape?
That guy Elaine's dating
seems really familiar to me.
I think he might be
a comedian
I worked with one time.
Wait a second.
Wha--?
What-- What is this?
ANNOUNCER:
This weekend, Nobody Beats The Wiz
is slashing prices
on our entire stock.
Nobody beats me
because I'm the Wiz.
Yes. I'm the Wiz.
I'm the Wiz.
That is the guy.
Elaine's in love
with the Wiz guy?
No. She thinks
she's in love with him,
but she's just remembering
this old commercial.
That's pretty
pathetic.
I know. They're
not even related.
Hey.
Uh, hey.
[SLAPS THIGH]
I'm gonna
get going.
Hey, have fun
at the family reunion.
[LAUGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
So...
what do you know
about this Jack fella?
Isn't he the best?
Yeah. Nobody
beats him.
Yeah.
[GIGGLES]
What kind of work
does he do?
Oh. Right now
he's a fact-checker
for New York magazine.
It's not much,
but it has a certain kind
of quiet dignity.
[REFRESHED SIGH]
Right.
Quiet dignity.
As opposed to, say...
this?
Nobody beats me,
because I'm the Wiz.
Yes, I'm the Wiz.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[MAGICAL HARP PLAYING]
Hello.
Yeah, the van is
still for sale.
Sure, come on by.
Yeah, I called
about the van.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Some more merlot?
Yeah, thanks.
Sure.
You know, Rhisa,
I, uh--
[SLURPING]
I've always found you
very attractive.
What?
I know it may sound...
shocking...
but, uh, I just can't
stop myself from...
wanting you.
You want to borrow
money, right?
No. No. I--
I just want us to be...
together.
All right.
All right?
Let's go for it.
Well...
we could dance
around it a little first.
Nah.
Let's be bad, George.
Let's be really...bad.
Whoa. Whoa. Easy.
So how come
you're selling it?
You know why
I'm selling it.
I hate it.
How many miles?
Two.
City or highway?
Look, do you really want to
buy this thing or what?
Hey, hey, hey,
take it easy.
I'm not gonna be
pressured.
I'll walk away
right now.
Is this thing bent?
I'm not paying
for that.
All right. Just
get out of here.
All right, look. Look,
I'm gonna be honest.
I'm very interested
in the van.
Okay, fine.
What do I have to do
to put you
in this van today?
Well, I don't have
any money,
but it, uh,
says right here:
"Interesting trades
considered."
You put that in!
Glad I did.
Here.
You want to trade me
an undershirt.
No, I want to trade you
screen legend Anthony Quinn's
undershirt.
He took this off to do
sit-ups in the park,
and I nabbed it.
[TAPS SHOULDER]
That's disgusting.
Well, that's
my final offer.
[♪]
You dumped me for some
idiotic TV pitchman?
Look, I'm sorry, Puddy.
It-- It was a mistake.
So let's just--
Let's just put it behind us,
and we can continue
as if this never happened.
Jeez, I don't know.
What if we're out somewhere,
and you see
the Maytag repairman?
[LAUGHS]
You're not taking me back?
That's right.
He's not idiotic.
He's the Wiz.
And nobody beats him.
[SADLY]
Nobody.
Here you go.
Mail is evil.
Pass it on.
Hey, mail blows.
Fax it to a friend.
Why does this dummy
have a bucket on its head?
Because we're blind
to their tyranny.
Then shouldn't you
be wearing the bucket?
Yeah.
Move along, Betty.
Is this, uh,
Jerry Seinfeld's van?
Well, not anymore.
He traded it to me for
some Hollywood memorabilia.
I'm, so--
I'm so stupid.
What?
Uh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
Yeah, nice to
meet you.
[♪]
JERRY:
She's into it?
She's leaving me
dirty messages
on my answering
machine.
So have your parents
found out about it?
She wants to
keep it quiet.
She thinks we have
a real future together.
It's a brave
new world, all right.
Hey, guys.
Hey, uh. Huh?
Hey, how's the anti-mail
campaign going? Oh.
It's fantastic.
We were out in front
of the post office today...
and not one person
went in.
It's Sunday.
Why is the mailman
wearing a bucket?
Huh?
Well, it symbolizes
our persecution.
Then shouldn't you
be wearing the bucket?
Oh.
Hey, I want
my van keys back.
Uh...well, I, uh--
I thought we made a deal
for Quinn's T-shirt.
Are you insane?
Give 'em.
No, I can't. I can't.
See, I-- I told Frank
he could borrow it.
Yeah, he wants to move
some of George's stuff
into storage.
Wait a minute.
He's picking up
the van tonight?
This is perfect.
I'll drive Rhisa
to someplace romantic,
then when my father
slides the door open...
I'm in the van
kissing his brother's
daughter.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, listen, Jerry. One of
your friends came by.
And he was very upset
that I had your wheels.
Oh, no. Not Frankie.
I didn't catch
his name.
But then he went running
into the park.
Oh, no. The woods.
The hole.
[BUCKET CLATTERS]
Hey.
Kramer. What the hell
are you doing?
I know. I'm gonna switch
the bucket to something else.
Not that.
What?
You're in trouble, Kramer.
I shouldn't be talking to you,
but I'm telling you as a friend.
Here's how it's gonna happen:
You may be walking,
maybe on a crisp autumn day
just like today,
when a mail truck
will slow beside you.
And the door will open.
And a mailman you know,
maybe even trust,
will offer to
give you a lift.
Are you through?
No! And no one
will ever see you again!
Are you through?
Yes.
No, wait.
Okay, yes.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Quick. Get in.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's exactly how you said
it was going down.
There's another way,
and it's going down now.
No, you said
a mailman I know,
and you're
a mailman I know.
I know you know, but you
don't know what I know!
Hey!
Hey.
JERRY:
Frankie!
Frankie.
Frankie,
is that you?
My name is Edgar.
Have a nice night.
Thank you.
Stupid.
So stupid.
[VEHICLE
APPROACHING]
Jerry?
[ENGINE STOPS]
RHISA:
All right, George.
I'm ready.
Yeah, hold on.
I'm, uh--
I'm just trying to get a reading
on my dashboard compass.
[MUTTERS]
Where are my parents?
♪ Georgie ♪
[THUMP]
Is this Seinfeld's van?
Seinfeld's van!
Wait. What's he saying?
I think he's saying
"Son of Sam." Oh, my God!
No, they caught him.
I knew it wasn't
Berkowitz!
[WHINES]
[♪]
ELAINE:
So I told him,
"Hit the road.
I'm going back
with Jack."
[BOTH GIGGLE]
That's the second
good piece of news
I've gotten today.
Really? What was
the first?
They're
bringing me back.
Yeah.
I'm the Wiz again.
What?
[LAUGHING]
I'm the Wiz!
Well, what-- What about
your fact-checking job?
Oh. Here's a fact.
Uh, I'm the Wiz.
I'm the Wiz, and
nobody beats me.
[♪]
Frankie. Come on
out of there.
You hate the van.
But I'm keeping it.
As much as I
hate the idea
of being a van guy...
it's a lot better
than hanging out here
with the nocturnal
dirt people.
So can we go for a ride?
Yeah, let's just...
get the hell
out of here. Okay.
Are you done with that?
Good.
He left the door
unlocked.
Why did Kramer
have to park the van
in the woods?
Isn't it obvious?
There are no parking
meters out here.
Wow.
Hey. Look at this.
Hoochie mama.
[♪]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Oh, my goodness. What have
they done to you here?
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
Who are you?
Well...
you can just call me Henry.
Henry Atkins?
The postmaster general?
Last time I checked.
Henry...
can I get
out of here now?
Oh, oh, oh.
Sit a bit.
I mean, after all, I drove
all the way up here from D.C.
just to talk to you.
Oh.
I even had to cancel
a round of golf
with the Secretary
of State.
Do you like golf, Mr. Kramer?
[FEARFULLY]
Yeah.
Mr. Kramer, I've been, uh...
reading some of
your material here.
I gotta be
honest with you.
You make a pretty
strong case. Uh-huh.
I mean, just imagine.
An army of men
in wool pants
running through
the neighborhood
handing out pottery catalogs
door to door.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, it's my job.
And I'm pretty damn
serious about it.
In addition to
being a postmaster...
I'm a general.
And we both know
it's the job of
a general to,
by God,
get things done.
So maybe
you can understand...
why I get
a little irritated
when somebody calls me
away from my golf.
I'm sorry.
I'm very, very sorry.
Sure you're sorry.
I think we got
a stack of mail
out there at the desk
that belongs to you.
Now, you want that mail,
don't you, Mr. Kramer?
Sure do.
Good. Now,
that's better.
All right.
Jeez!
Newman?
Tell the world
my story.
[WHIMPERS]
[WHIMPERING]
[♪]
Hey, George.
Jerry.
Hey, that's the guy.
What? George
Costanza,
Frankie Merman.
Oh.
The summer me.
The winter me.
You must be
George's cousin.
Girlfriend.
All right.
Hey, what is that?
That van's
a-rockin'.
Don't go
a-knockin'.
ESTELLE:
Oh, my God!
Oh, you gotta
sell this van.
Oh, yeah.
[♪]
What you saw
in that van
was a natural expression
of a man's love for his lady.
[GROANS]
Your father's right.
It's beautiful.
And it was safe.
Oh, God.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
once again...
your mother and I--
Oh.
Make it stop.
[♪]