If you borrow my blender,
you should return it.
Oh, what's
the difference?
Come on, we're like
Cain and Abel.
Yeah, you know,
Cain slew Abel.
No, he didn't. They were
in business together.
Dry wall or something.
Oh, no.
All right,
then what was it?
Well, I think Abel
worked hard all summer
harvesting his crops,
while Cain just
played in the field.
Then when winter came,
Abel had all the nuts.
Cain had no nuts,
so he killed him.
The way I remember it,
Cain, he was
a successful doctor.
But when he took this
special formula,
he became Mr. Abel.
You broke my blender,
didn't you?
Yeah. Well, I was trying
to make gravel and it just--
Just didn't work out.
Oh, I knew it.
[♪]
Why were you
making gravel?
Well, I like the sound it makes
when you walk on it.
Ah, this...looks
familiar.
Of course, it's garbage.
No, no, no, no.
These brown things.
The chairs.
Jerry,
this is the set
from the old Merv Griffin Show.
[GRUNTS]:
They must be throwing it out.
This stuff
belongs in the Smithsonian.
Or at least in the dumpster
behind the Smithsonian.
[SIGHS]:
Boy, one minute Elliott Gould is sitting on you
[LAUGHS]:
and the next thing you're yesterday's trash.
Come on, Kramer,
get out of there.
Oh, no, no, you go ahead.
I'm not finished taking this in.
[GASPS]:
Oh.
Jerry, look.
Merv Griffin's cigar.
Oh.
[♪]
You know, I, uh,
spilled a yogurt smoothie
in here two days ago.
[CHUCKLES]
Can't smell anything,
can you?
Banana?
Right.
George, watch out
for those pigeons.
They'll get outta the way.
Really smell banana?
[FLUTTERING]
[GASPING]
Oh, my God!
So, uh...
...where we eating?
...and it was his idea
to put a sprig of parsley
on the plate.
[LAUGHING]:
Making this up.
There was never
a Joseph Garnish.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
The toys.
Where did you
get all these?
My dad was
a collector.
I inherited them
after he died from
a long painful bout with--
Super-Ball.
Hey,
an original G.I. Joe...
...with the full
frogman suit.
Jerry,
what are you doing?
I'm putting this on him
and we're going
to the sink.
[LAUGHS]:
No, Jerry.
They're priceless.
They've never
been played with.
I just wanna
touch them a little.
I said no.
Now, come here.
[♪]
Hi.
[GRUNTS]
I'm Lou Filerman.
I'm new here.
Hey, Walter.
What is the deal
with that guy?
Uh, he's Lou Filerman.
He's new here.
[SIGHS]
Hey, your coffee stain
looks like Fidel Castro.
You've been
an enormous help.
[♪]
JERRY:
You ran over some pigeons?
How many?
Whatever they had.
Miranda
thinks I'm a butcher.
[STAMMERS]:
But it's not my fault, is it?
Don't we have a deal
with the pigeons?
Of course we have a deal.
They get out of
the way of our cars,
we look the other way
on the statue defecation.
Right, and these pigeons
broke the deal.
I will not accept
the blame for this!
So Miranda's cooled
on you?
I'm getting nothing.
Yeah, me neither.
I thought you
were sleeping together.
Oh, the sex is wild.
But she's got this
incredible toy collection
and she won't let me near it.
I don't
understand women.
Here comes one.
Hey.
What's going on?
Art Garfunkel?
No, Castro.
Right.
All because of this
creepy new guy at work.
He just-- He just
comes out of nowhere
and he's right
next to you.
So he just sidles up?
That's right.
He's
a real sidler.
Maybe you didn't see him.
W--
You never see him.
He sidled me again
in my office.
I was sitting there
making Cup-a-Soups
singing that song
from The Lion King.
"Hakuna Matata"?
I thought
I was alone.
That doesn't make it right.
[♪]
See, to me the Hakuna Matata
is not nearly as embarrassing
as the Cup-a-Soup.
Would you just...
...let it go?
KRAMER:
Hey, Jerry. Come here a sec.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
It's the
Merv Griffin set.
How did you
get this in here?
Oh, you just bring it in
sideways and...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
...hook it.
So where are you
gonna sleep?
Yeah, backstage.
Hm...
...this chair
smells like garbage.
Oh, well a lot of
the stars from the '70s,
they were not as hygienic
as they appeared on TV.
[LAUGHS]:
Now, you take Mannix, for example.
[PHONE RINGING]
I'm gonna get that.
All right, well, Jerry,
we'd love to
have you back any time.
Well,
Elaine Benes.
Well, it's great
to have you.
Boy, is it possible that
you're even more beautiful
than the last time
I saw you?
[LAUGHING]
[PIGEONS COOING]
[YELLS AND GRUNTS]
We had a deal!
ELAINE:
Mr. Peterman, here are these pages that you w--
One moment.
I'm reading
the most fascinating article
on the most fascinating people
of the year.
And...
...done.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry
I needed this so quickly.
It must have been
an awful lot of work.
Thank you very much,
you two.
What?
[♪]
JERRY:
So three dates and she still won't let me play with the toys.
Hm, that's interesting.
You know,
someone mentioned,
you were not very happy
with your toys, growing up.
Yeah, that was me.
That's right.
Right, right.
And, uh, you mentioned that,
uh, you didn't get a G.I. Joe.
You had--
An Army Pete.
Right.
He was made of wood and
in the rain he would swell up
and then split.
Ooh, and we all know
how painful that can be.
[DOOR SLAMS]
ELAINE:
Jerry?
Oh, there you are.
Elaine Benes.
Well, this is
quite a thrill.
Yes, come--
Yes, sit down.
Yeah.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Well, I'll tell you,
this sidler guy
is really chapping my hide.
Now--
Excuse me?
[SIGHS]:
Yeah, we're... talking this way.
Well, he's getting credit
for work that I did.
He's gonna sidle me
right out of a job.
Uh, now, for those of us
who don't know,
uh, sidling is what?
Kramer, what
is wrong with you?
What do you mean?
Well, for starters,
you're looking at note cards.
I'm gonna give that guy
a taste of his own medicine.
So I am going to
sidle the sidler.
You sidle?
Y-You stomp around
like a Clydesdale.
Not with these honeys.
[LAUGHS]:
Wrestling shoes.
Only in New York.
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Jerry?
KRAMER:
Oh...
[UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING]
...hey!
Well,
ladies and gentlemen,
it's our good friend,
George Costanza.
What a surprise.
[LAUGHS]
MAN:
Turn music off.
Yeah, sit, sit.
[LAUGHS]
Well,
it happened again.
What happened?
Hey, hey.
I'll ask the questions.
What happened?
Well, I just stomped
some pigeons in the park.
They--
They didn't move.
All right. Let's, uh,
change the subject.
Now, uh, you and, uh, Jerry
dated for a while.
Tell us, uh...
...what was that like?
Wrong card.
I-I don't
get these birds.
They're breaking
the deal.
It's-- It's like the pigeons
decided to ignore me.
So they're
like everyone else.
[LAUGHS]
All right, let's take
a short break.
[BURPS AND GRUNTS]
Okay, uh...
...we're back.
[♪]
Boy, that-- That bank clock is--
Is 8 minutes off.
Then why don't you just
run it over too?
Zing.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
George,
what are you doing?
[STAMMERS]:
Did you see that? That pigeon didn't move.
I had to swerve out of the way.
I saved that pigeon's life.
[CHUCKLES]
What pigeon?
You drove right
into that squirrel.
Squirrel?
Well, we have
no deal with them.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC
PLAYING ON TV]
[JERRY IMITATES GUNSHOTS]
Jerry, those hands.
They never stop.
I'm sorry.
Got any booze?
What say you and I get ripped.
No, thanks.
I have a headache.
[SIGHS]:
Can you just get me an aspirin?
All right.
Hm,
"Will not cause drowsiness."
"May cause...drowsiness."
[♪]
FILERMAN:
Here's the new copy you wanted.
[SIGHS]:
Oh, yes.
Well, this certainly
looks like a lot of words...
...in record time.
I'm very impressed...
...with both of you.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHS]:
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
I am also disgusted.
This is incoherent drivel.
This is a total redo.
And I'm assuming
I need it right away.
Well, I guess
we'll just have--
Oh, just give me that.
[JERRY HUMMING]
[IMITATES
ANIMAL GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS]
Mission accomplished.
Back to base, Joe.
[HUMS]
[♪]
MIRANDA:
Doctor, is the squirrel going to live?
There's been
massive trauma.
We could, of course,
try to save him, but...
[SIGHS]:
...it would be costly, difficult,
and we'd have to send away
for some special,
really tiny instruments.
Well, uh, are there
any other options?
We could put him to sleep.
What might that
cost?
Well, it's by the pound,
so...about 80 cents.
Well.
[WHISPERS]: George.
[WHISPERS AND LAUGHS]:
I was just-- I was curious, that's all.
We, uh--
We'd like you to
do everything possible.
He, um--
He's not gonna be the same,
you know.
Yeah, yeah.
I, uh-- I know.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So they're flying the tiny instruments
in from El Paso.
[SIGHS]:
El Paso.
I spent a month there
one night.
[LAUGHING]
El Paso.
What's he here for?
[SIGHS]:
Well, he takes some of the pressure off of me.
So, Jerry, uh,
what's going on with you?
I understand there's
a young lady in your life, hm?
Well, actually,
it's kind of a funny story,
because she has this
amazing toy collection
and last night
I got to play with them.
Ooh.
Well, sounds like
things
are progressing.
Do I hear
wedding bells?
Are you married
right now?
Newman.
She doesn't even
know about the toys.
I gave her the
wrong kind of medicine
and I...guess
she passed out.
What do you mean,
wrong kind of medicine?
She's even got that
football game
that we loved.
Oh, come on.
Gotta get me
over there.
Wait,
wait a minute,
you mean to say that you
drugged a woman
so you could take advantage
of her toys?
Let's pause a moment.
[UPBEAT JAZZ SONG PLAYING]
Jerry,
now, what you do
with your personal life
is your business.
But when you're on my set
you clean it up, mister.
I told you
he was a risk.
Oh, like he's not just
carrying you.
And has been for years.
Yeah,
well, you bombed.
That story stunk
worse than these chairs.
Shh. Smile, everyone.
We're back.
[GRUNTS]
[♪]
You wanted to see me, Elaine?
Yes, Lou.
[SIGHS]:
You've got a lot going for you.
[LAUGHS]:
You're, um-- You're...spontaneous.
You're...symmetrical.
Youre, uh--
[LAUGHS]
--You're very quick,
aren't you?
[SIGHS]:
Um...
...it's just that your...
My dead tooth?
No...
...your...
...blegh.
What, my breath?
Ugh.
What can I do?
Well, you should never,
ever go anywhere...
[MINTS RATTLING]
...without these.
Thanks, Elaine.
You're such a super lady.
[RATTLING]
[♪]
More wine
and turkey?
Hm.
So when I saw George
on the street
with an
18 pound turkey
and a giant box of wine,
I thought,
"What a coincidence,
we're just about to eat."
What is that stuff in turkey
that makes you sleepy?
Tryptophan...
Tryptophan.
...I think.
Have
some more wine.
What video did you get?
Oh,
Oh...
George brought home movies
of his boyhood trip
to Michigan.
Four hours.
More
heavy gravy?
[♪]
[GRUNTS]:
Ah, yes. Touchdown.
Your turn, Jerry.
[GAME BEEPING]
Lately though,
I've been, uh--
I've been buying
the generic brand of wax beans.
You know,
I rip off the label...
...I can hardly
tell the difference.
We've officially
bottomed out.
Who's our next guest?
We got no one.
[SIGHS]
We need a new format.
We should shut down
and retool.
[SIGHS]
What about a guest host?
I'll pretend
I didn't hear that.
[♪]
MIRANDA:
Doctor, how's the squirrel?
Is he dead?
No, fortunately
the special tiny instruments
arrived just in time.
Would you like to visit him?
Yes, he would.
You, um--
You have 30 minutes.
So, uh...
...squirrel...
One more thing, Mr. Costanza.
We just need to know
what time
you'll be picking him up
tomorrow.
[SIGHS]
What's that?
Oh, we're discharging
the squirrel.
We think he'll be
better off at home.
He has no home.
He's a squirrel.
[CHUCKLES]
Your home, Mr. Costanza.
Just make sure he gets
his medicine six times a day
and keep his tail elevated.
[♪]
JERRY:
Maybe it'll be fun having a pet.
It's not a pet.
It's a wild invalid.
And it knows that
I tried to kill it.
As soon as it gets better,
it's gonna gnaw my brain out
in my sleep!
Jerry. Hey-yeah.
What are you doing
tomorrow?
Want you to come by
the set.
What about my
questionable material?
No, we got
a whole new format.
Edgy, youthful.
Plus, we got Jim Fowler.
Jim Fowler? The animal guy
from Wild Kingdom
is coming
to your apartment?
Well, I practically
raised his kids.
Perfect, he's a zoo guy.
He takes care of animals.
Can--Can I
bring the squirrel by?
Oh, two animal acts
on the same show?
[LAUGHS]:
What is this, amateur hour?
Look, George,
I'm sorry.
Maybe another time,
all right?
I gotta get to Fowler.
I know that he would take
this squirrel off my hands.
It's practically bionic.
ELAINE:
Hey.
[LAUGHS]
Nice sidle, huh?
Speaking of which,
I think I've got
that problem solved.
Tic Tacs work?
He's a human maraca.
Boy, my knuckles are still
cramped from that football game.
You took him over to Celia's?
What?
It's a victimless crime.
What about the woman
who's been drugged
and taken advantage of?
Okay, one victim.
I think it's
unconscionable.
Hey, last night, I found
a whole Weeble village
right behind
the Easy-Bake Oven.
Easy-Bake Oven?
[OVEN DINGS]
Who wants cupcake?
Ooh, me, me, me, me, me.
You know that batter is
like 30 years old.
FRANK [ON TV]:
You step on it and it flushes.
Why is your father
giving a tour of a rest stop?
ESTELLE:
Stop squirming. Oh, don't look.
Thi-- This is the part
where they change me.
You're 8 years old.
ESTELLE: Georgie.
I was 7 and a half.
[♪]
[TIC TACS RATTLE]
That noise.
That's the noise!
What?
That infernal rattling sound
that has plagued me
these past two days,
and I could not find
the source.
In my office, in the hallway...
...even in the men's room.
Shame on you, Elaine.
No, no,
[LAUGHS]:
Mr. Peterman, that wasn't me.
That reminds me of
the Haitian voodoo
rattle torture.
You haven't gone over
to their side, have you?
No, Mr. Peterman.
Because if I hear
one more rattle--
just...one
--you're out on your can.
And if you are undead...
I'll find out about that too.
[RATTLING]
[RATTLING STOPS]
Lou. In here.
We have to talk.
Oh, right.
[GASPS]: Stop it.
Bad voodoo.
You gotta stop using these.
Why?
Because they're turning
your teeth green?
I only buy the white ones.
Okay, well
then your teeth are green
for a different reason.
You gotta stop
carrying these, okay?
Just use mouthwash.
I can't.
It burns my cankers.
Binaca.
Again.
Right, right. Cankers.
Um, I got it. Chew gum.
I hate gum.
The only gum I liked
came with
the Mickey Mouse
gumball machine.
They stopped making that
20 years ago.
Well, stinky,
this is your lucky day.
[♪]
Okay, a little later
we're gonna be
talking with animal expert,
Jim Fowler.
Where are the cameras?
But first,
we're talking with...Jerry.
Okay, Jerry, uh...
...you, uh--
You drugged a woman
in order to play with
her toy collection.
How do you feel about that?
It was great.
I've done it
a few more times since then.
And she doesn't
know anything about this?
Not a thing.
[NEWMAN LAUGHS]
Well, Jerry, we have
a little surprise for you.
Come on out, Celia.
What kind of sick,
twisted creep are you?
Whoa.
Hey.
What-- What is this?
What is she doing here?
It's
the new format.
Scandals
and animals.
Eh, eh, eh.
If you think you can drug me
and play with my toys,
you've got another thing
coming, buddy.
Go, girl.
Ooh.
W-What kind of woman
drinks an entire box of wine?
KRAMER AND NEWMAN:
Ooh.
Mr. Fowler,
I-I have a squirrel here
that is a miracle of
modern science.
[LAUGHS]
George, I told you we're booked.
Careful. Hawks and squirrels
don't get along together.
Ooh, another interesting
confrontation.
This could be spicy.
George,
bring him over.
Uh--
No, you idiot.
Hawks eat squirrels.
[KRAMER LAUGHS]
[SQUAWKING]
[SCREAMING]
[♪]
KRAMER:
Are we getting this?
So the whole set
was destroyed?
The squirrel
kept scurrying
and the hawk
kept clawing.
Well, at least we know that
prosthetic squirrel hips work.
Sorry about the set.
[SIGHS]:
I'll tell you,
it was a grind having to
fill 10 hours a day.
I'm not sure
I was ready
to have my own
talk show set.
I got the nut bread, George.
Let's go.
[SIGHS]
So the squirrel's
gonna make it?
Yeah, he's in my bed.
I'm...
...sleeping on the couch.
On the couch?
So you're--
Still getting nothing.
[PIGEONS COOING]
GEORGE:
Go ahead, pigeons.
[LAUGHS]
Laugh it up.
I'm getting in my car now,
and the last I heard...
...we have no deal!
[♪]
I'm glad you called,
Elaine.
I really needed
to talk to someone.
Oh, well, hey,
I dated Jerry too.
I-- I know what a monster
he can be.
More wine and turkey?
Who's he?
Oh,
he's nobody.
Hey, listen,
let me top that off for you.
[♪]