[♪]
Hey.
Morning.
This is crazy.
You know, I-- I, uh...
I can't go on like this.
But why?
I need some space.
Does that mean
I have to go too?
Well, you don't think
she's just talking to me.
Hey, shut up.
You shut up.
Oh, I hate this.
You'll get used to it.
It's like a rugby scrum.
No, no,
I don't want this anymore.
We're going to work with you.
And on your dates.
And shopping.
And to the bathroom.
Elaine.
Elaine. Elaine.
I can't breathe.
I'm suffocating.
Elaine. Elaine.
I can't breathe.
You're all killing me!
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
Turn your alarm off!
[SIGHS]
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
Your background is impressive,
George, but, uh,
how does it apply
to what we do here
at Kruger Industrial Smoothing?
Well, at the Yankees,
it was, uh--
It was all about
smoothing things over.
You know, chiseling away,
grinding down.
In fact, heh, we, uh--
We used to call it
"the grind."
It says here you worked
at Play Now for four days?
That-- That should be a 14.
Let me just...
Well, George, I'll be honest.
I could go either way on you.
But what the hell?
We need someone, huh?
You, uh--
you won't regret this, sir.
I don't care.
Let's...find you
an office, huh? Ahem.
[GEORGE CHUCKLES]
[♪]
GEORGE:
Then when I saw the photo I remembered where I'd seem him.
The boom box incident.
The boom box incident?
Summer of '89,
I'm at the beach.
This family sets up
next to me.
I go into the surf.
When I come out, my clothes,
my towel, my umbrella,
they're all gone.
GEORGE:
I am furious.
I start screaming
at these kids,
demanding my stuff back,
and then finally,
I lose it.
I grab their boom box
and I chuck it
into the ocean.
KRAMER:
Yeah?
Seems reasonable.
Then I see my clothes
floating out there.
The tide took them out,
not the kids.
Even more reasonable.
So now the father
is screaming at me.
He's demanding that I pay
for the boom box.
So, heh...
finally I gave him
a fake address
and got the hell
out of there.
And that guy
is your new boss?
Mm-hm, until that
stupid photo jogs his memory.
Kruger.
That's not Kruger
Industrial Smoothing, is it?
Yeah.
Yeah, grinders,
sanders, whetstones.
They're the ones who botched
the Statue of Liberty job.
Right. They couldn't get
the green stuff off.
It is a horrible company.
There is no management
whatsoever.
I could go hog-wild in there.
You know what you do?
You sneak that photo
out of there
for a couple of days
and get it airbrushed.
Like retouched?
Remember that photo of me
and Gerald Ford,
and I took it in--
Brrrr.
Got that Ford
right out of there.
Ohh, this is good.
This Kruger guy is clueless.
Hee-hee.
I can't wait
to work for him.
KRAMER:
Yeah.
Jeez.
Look at this.
This sandwich is terrible.
Everywhere you go
they always give you
these misshaped,
shoddy meats.
Look, look, look.
I haven't had a decent sandwich
in 13 years.
Neither have I.
[♪]
Hey.
Well, our meat problems
are solved.
Where'd you get this thing?
I traded in
my sausage press.
I mean,
look how thin that is.
See, that's all surface area.
The taste
has nowhere to hide.
[EXHALES]
Hey.
Hey. Slice?
Welcome
to flavor country.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Hey, I got a date
with that doctor you met.
Sara Sitarides?
Mm-hm.
Hm.
What's with you?
You remember that
next-door neighbor of mine,
the apartment
that always smells
like, uh, potatoes?
Your whole building
smells like potatoes.
This jackass goes to Paris,
leaves her alarm on.
[SIGHS]
It's been beeping
since 3:30 this morning.
You know,
that happened to Lomez,
so he blew
his neighbor's circuit.
How did he do that?
Yeah, well, it's easy.
Just let me finish
this mile-high
and I'll be right with you.
Oh, Jerry, we're gonna need
a case of Kaiser Rolls.
I think we might have one left
in the stockroom.
[♪]
[SNIFFS]
My, this hallway smells like potatoes.
I know, I know.
This is it. Okay.
Oh, you see.
This socket--
It's probably connected
to her apartment.
Oh.
So what we'll do...
Come on.
We'll take
this paper clip
and we'll bend it,
so it'll short out
the entire circuit.
There you go.
Can you do it?
Oh, I think
I'll let you do it.
No, no, no. It's easy.
Just...do it quickly.
No, I really don't want to.
Well, I don't want to, either.
I thought
you've done this before.
Yeah, well, I have.
It's just...
It's no picnic.
Well, then,
how are we gonna do it?
All right, all right,
fine, fine. I'll do it.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES]
Oh, mama.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna lose that nail.
[♪]
SARA:
I enjoy the challenge of medicine.
Naturally, you would have
no idea what it's like
to have someone's life
depending on you.
Well,
I have this neighbor...
A joke.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you have any idea
what it feels like
to save someone's life?
Is it anything like
hitting a homer in softball?
No.
'Cause I hit a whopper
last week.
[♪]
CLERK:
Here you go.
Airbrushed you
into sand and sky.
[CACKLES]
GEORGE:
What did you do here?
You took out the wrong guy.
I thought you said
you wanted to be out.
But I'm still here.
You took out the other guy.
You've really lost
a lot of hair.
I am aware.
[♪]
Hmm.
ELAINE:
"The world's best pizza cutter...
seventy-six bucks."
How often do I make...?
[GROANS]
I've gotta buy a book.
[CAT MEOWING LOUDLY]
The cat.
[♪]
JERRY:
He took out Kruger?
I just pray Kruger
doesn't realize it's gone
until this guy can
fix it up.
This slicer is indomitable.
Where'd you get
that butcher's coat?
You buy enough meat,
they'll give you anything.
Kramer.
Huh?
My neighbor has a cat.
When you blew the power,
we must have shut off
the automatic feeder.
See, that's the same thing
that happened to Lomez.
Well, what did he do about it?
Well, he, uh, moved
into a motel,
and the cat
eventually died.
Well, this meowing is
absolutely worse than the alarm.
Oh, well,
that's a prickly one, huh?
Ugh.
How was the doctor date?
Ah, it died
on the table.
She spent an hour and a half
making me feel
like if I don't save lives,
I'm worthless.
Well, you know,
she's very focused.
Dermatology is her life.
Dermatology?
Yes. She's a dermatologist.
Saving lives?
The whole profession is,
"Eh, just put some aloe on it."
The slicer.
Elaine, let's go.
Where are we going?
The cat.
Just grab that meat
and let's ride.
When are you going on
your next date with her?
Oh, what's the point?
What, you're gonna pass up
a wonderful opportunity
to put that aloe-pusher
in her place?
A revenge date?
That-- That sounds
more like you than me.
This could be so sweet, Jerry.
Saving lives?
She's one step above working
at the Clinique counter.
Dermatologist.
Skin doesn't need a doctor.
Of course not.
Wash it, dry it, move on.
You're right,
I'm gonna call her up right now
and tell her off.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
This has to be
carefully orchestrated.
You go to a fancy dinner.
Flowers.
Flowers?
Yeah, you got to do it classy.
So you've done this?
Almost.
Couldn't get the girl
to go out with me
a second time.
[♪]
I think we're looking
at half a millimeter.
Can it cut that thin?
Oh, I've cut slices so thin,
I couldn't even see them.
[CHUCKLES]
How did you know
you cut it?
[CAT MEOWS]
Well, I guess I just assumed.
Don't worry, kitty,
dinner's coming.
Look at that, huh?
That's a hall-of-famer.
All right,
let's do it.
All right, here we go.
Yeah.
Watch this baby slide.
Okay.
Come on.
Go, kitty. Come on.
Aah,
ha, ha, ha, ha.
How about that?
It works. Wow.
Can I borrow that thing
for a while?
Oh, I don't think so.
Why not?
Well, you're not
checked out on it.
What do I have to know?
Well, where the meat goes.
Right there.
Where do you turn it on?
But where does the meat go?
[♪]
SARA:
The restaurant, the flowers, this is so nice.
Well, I'm a classy guy.
[CHUCKLES]
How's the life-saving business?
It's fine.
It must take
a really, really big zit
to kill a man.
What is with you?
You call yourself lifesaver?
I call you
Pimple Popper, M.D.
Dr. Sitarides?
Mr. Parry.
How are you?
I just want
to thank you again
for saving my life.
She saved your life?
I had skin cancer.
Skin cancer.
Damn.
ELAINE:
You were right, Kramer.
This slicer
is absolutely amazing.
[BLOWS]
[SLICER WHIRRING SOFTLY]
Yeah.
Yeah. No, no, no.
I'll bring it by tonight.
Okay. Bye.
[WHIRRING STOPS]
Ugh.
These heels are so uneven.
[♪]
CLERK:
Here you go, Mr. Costanza.
[CHUCKLES]
What is this? This--
This is a drawing.
Looks real, doesn't it?
This is a cartoon.
Hey, I had to draw that guy
from memory.
Considering,
I think that's damn good.
But it's not a photograph.
I need a photograph!
Then you better get a camera.
[♪]
JERRY:
He looks like a Peanuts' character.
I know.
The only way to fix it now
is to get a whole new photo
of Kruger.
Well, you can do that.
Without his shirt on?
You can't do that.
Well, maybe Kruger
wasn't the place for you.
They seem so disorganized.
I understand.
What about
the Coast Guard?
Seems like
a lot of pride there,
a lot of tradition.
True.
You mean, for you?
You think?
What about your seasickness?
Maybe I could be a land guy.
I don't know
if they have land guys.
Someone's gotta unhook the boat
before it leaves...
the place.
Pliers?
Drawer.
Got it.
What are they for?
I, uh...
got a piece of my heel
stuck in the slicer.
Come again?
Okay, I got
a little slicer happy,
but listen,
don't tell Kramer, okay?
He has very...
strong feelings for it.
I almost forgot to ask you.
How did the revenge date go?
Uh, it went okay.
Did you dress nice?
Did you do it classy?
Yeah, I started out
real classy.
Yeah, you did.
You classed it up, huh?
But then I found out
about the skin cancer.
Oh, so it backfired.
Yes.
So I guess I'm lucky
I never tried that myself.
Of course
she treats skin cancer.
That's how I met her.
She was doing a skin-cancer
screening at Peterman.
This is what dermatologists do.
Sadly, that knowledge
could have helped me.
Wait a second.
She did a skin-cancer
screening at Peterman?
Uh-huh.
Could she do that at Kruger?
I don't know. I guess.
So I set up a screening,
everyone takes
their shirt off...
and click.
I snap me a shot
of a bare-chested Kruger.
You got a little thing
for this fella?
Jerry, you got to talk
to Sitarides.
Y-yesterday you told me I had
to take my revenge on her.
And that was wrong, Jerry.
You simply must apologize.
Must I?
Yes.
Because it is the mature,
adult thing to do.
How does that affect me?
Hey. Ooh.
Elaine.
All right,
where's the SP 2000?
'Cause I gotta slice.
Uh...I forgot it.
Huh?
Mm, I gotta get home.
Oh, okay, well,
I'll go with you.
Uh...
I'm not actually
going straight home.
I have to first stop off
at the, uh...
circus.
You know,
with all the...
clowns.
[GRUNTS]
Elaine, you--
You have fun.
Oh, no clowns.
I don't like clowns.
The clowns.
[♪]
JERRY:
So, again, I'm sorry.
I had no right to yell at you.
You're a lifesaving doctor,
and I'm just a comedian--
Jerry, enough.
I'll do your friend's screening
because I believe in that,
but as far as you
and I are concerned,
it's off.
Was it Pimple Popper, M.D.?
That's the one.
Still got it.
[♪]
Out, damn heel.
[GRUNTS]
Ugh.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Elaine?
Kramer?
Yeah, listen,
I need my slicer back.
Just hold on.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[POUNDING, GRUNTING]
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing, K--
Hah.
Here.
Here you go.
Wh--
Ahh.
Okay?
Yeah.
I'm on the phone,
all right?
I'm on the phone
with someone.
My blade is all dinged up.
Oh, come on.
Elaine.
Phone call.
I've got a big phone call.
Oh, come on,
this is important.
MAN [IRISH ACCENT]:
Hey! Get the hell out of here!
Whoa, that's a lot of potatoes.
[♪]
KRAMER:
So George took my slicer down to Kruger,
and they're smoothing it out
for me.
What the hell is this?
Oh, boy, that looks
like an allergic reaction.
Have you been wearing
a fake beard?
No.
What have you been doing?
Nothing. I got up,
I ran some errands,
I went down to Sara's office
and apologized--
Whoa, back up.
Dr. Sitarides, yeah?
What happened there?
Well, I tried to apologize.
It didn't go over too well.
Th--
There's your hives.
What, she gave me hives?
Jerry, as the Bible says,
Thou who cureth
can maketh ill.
She did kind
of touch my face.
Now, you listen to me.
You gotta find this woman
and tell her you're not
a test-tube pincushion.
It does itch.
Maybe I will go down to Kruger
and talk to her.
All right, great.
I gotta go down there
and pick up my blade.
Oh, hey, and I couldn't find
that stockroom.
[♪]
[CAT MEOWING]
Oh, that's fantastic.
[♪]
GEORGE:
I just, uh, talked to Mr. Kruger.
He'll be down in a minute.
He wanted me to take
a photograph for the record.
What record?
His personal file. I--
Heh, I don't ask, I--
Jerry!
What brings you here?
I don't know.
This?
Looks like hives.
Where do you suppose
that could have come from?
Jerry,
what are you doing?
Setting the record straight.
Come on, Sitarides,
cop to it.
What brand of perverted science
do you practice?
Are you suggesting I somehow
infected you on purpose?
I want the antidote,
pimple popper.
That's it.
I'm outta here.
You're insane.
Uh--
Am I?
You touched my face.
I didn't imagine that.
But, eh--
Dr. Sitarides, don't go.
Oh, thanks, Jerry!
Hey, George.
Hey, doc.
We doing, uh,
screening in here?
Uh...yeah. Yeah.
Why don't you head on in?
We'll-- We'll be in
in a second.
Be right with you.
Doc, huh?
Oh, Kramer, this is perfect.
I need you to go in there,
pretend you're a doctor,
and check this guy
for moles.
Moles. Yes...
Freckle's ugly cousin.
And just, uh,
get a picture of him
with his shirt off.
You're really cooking up
a little scheme here.
Come on,
let's get in there quick.
Quick, quick, quick.
[♪]
[CAT MEOWING LOUDLY]
That is it.
I can't take this anymore.
[FOGHAT'S "SLOW RIDE" PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
♪ Slow ride ♪
♪ Take it easy ♪
Male mammal...
Approximately
30 to 60 years of age.
Uh, weight...
Ohh, indeterminate.
Okay, uh,
Mr. Kruger, uh,
we're gonna take a photo now
for the records,
so if you'll, uh,
stand up, please,
give me a,
uh, big smile.
Uh, no, no, no. Not that--
That big.
Yeah, that--
That's nice, yes.
Okay.
Yes, let's have
a look-see, hm?
Okay, uh, so, uh...
Ooh, fiber from shirt
on left shoulder.
I'm gonna have
to keep my eye on that.
How long have you been
doing this, Dr. Van Nostrand?
Oh, long, long time.
Yes, I've seen moles so big,
they have their own moles.
Freckles that cover two men.
So how am I looking?
Oh, so far so good--
Wh-- ?
Y-you...
[PANTS]
Here.
I really owe you one.
We got a problem.
What?
Well, he's got a mole
on his shoulder.
Very suspicious.
Tell him you're
concerned about it,
he should see
somebody else.
George,
why would I,
a Julliard trained
dermatologist,
send him to another doctor?
Because you're not
a dermatologist.
No, but he thinks I am,
and I'm not gonna
betray that trust.
Now, here's what I wanna do.
I think I can get a section.
Then I'll go down--
Whoa, whoa. A section?
Yeah, if I can grab my slicer,
and if he holds still--
No, no, you're not taking
a deli slicer to my boss.
It'll be ultrathin.
He'll barely feel it.
No! Absolutely not!
All right. Shh.
Well...
it's my medical opinion
that you're making
a big mistake,
and it's going...
in my chart.
[IRON BUTTERFLY'S "IN-A-GADDA-
DA-VIDA" PLAYING ON RADIO]
Yeah, hello,
is this Allied Locksmith?
Oh, finally.
Okay, listen,
I need somebody
to come over here right away.
NEIGHBOR:
Turn that off! Turn it off!
I am getting a locksmith,
all right?
Relax!
NEIGHBOR:
All right, that's it.
Yeah. The address is 78 west--
[MUSIC STOPS]
NEIGHBOR:
Oh, oh, mama, ah, ah.
ELAINE:
Hello?
[♪]
JERRY:
So Kramer pulled it off?
Yep, and the photo
is all fixed
and back on his desk,
no thanks to you.
Well, that woman had it
coming to her.
L-look at my neck.
I look like I had
a beard of bees.
Why don't you see somebody
about it?
I-I called everyone.
You know how hard it is
to get a dermatologist?
A real dermatologist?
Hm? Squamous cell carcinoma.
You know, you're not a doctor.
You shouldn't even have books--
That's what he has
and I gotta give him a call.
We gotta come clean.
You can't tell him the truth.
You'll blow the whole thing.
I don't want this
on my conscience.
I will get him to see
a real doctor.
You just stay away
from him.
Yeah. All right.
Yeah, yeah, well.
Hey, I wonder if they have
a picture of my rash in here?
Yeah, they got
everything, Jerry.
I underlined
the best parts.
Hey, this looks
like what I have.
"Caused by exposure
to benzene,
a common ingredient
in metal cleaners."
Huh, well, that's weird.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm
cleaning my slicer.
That's my hand towel.
I use that on my face,
neck and chest.
That's where the hives
are coming from.
It's not Dr. Sitarides.
It was Dr. Van Nostrand.
So somehow
the Bronze-O is reacting
to the poison
she's giving you.
All right, get out.
And take your Bronze-O with you.
Whoa.
Ah--
That's toxic.
That's--
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
KRUGER:
George. Come on in.
I'm just going over
our annual report.
Boy, did we take it
on the chin last year.
Uh, listen, Mr. Kruger,
I got a message
from Dr. Van Nostrand,
and he says, uh,
it might be wise for you
to see another doctor
about that mole.
I'm not too worried about it.
Well, he said
it could be cancerous.
Maybe you should
have it checked out.
George,
take a look
at this photo.
[CLEARS THROAT]
This was taken 10 years ago.
Now, that mole looks exactly
as it does today.
So there's no cause
for concern, huh?
Whatever.
And, actually,
funny thing
about this photo,
we were at the beach,
and there was
this dumb-looking guy nearby.
When he went in for a swim,
my sons and I
took all his stuff
and threw it
in the ocean, heh.
What a pear-shaped loser.
Well, that pear-shaped loser
was me!
And I was in that photo
until I broke in here,
stole the photograph,
and airbrushed myself
out of it.
Well, I'll be.
You have lost
a lot of hair.
That's what they tell me!
[♪]
So you want
more pastrami?
ELAINE:
Um, what was that last thing you gave me?
That was pretty good.
Yeah, it was olive loaf.
ELAINE:
Oh.
You want that?
I can't believe
Kruger didn't fire you
after all you did.
He said he didn't care.
Heh-heh, God,
I love that place.
Did you ever see
another dermatologist?
Yeah, I finally got in
to see Dr. Kazarian.
He said it was really bad.
What he give you for it?
Aloe.
So where's that locksmith?
Mm, tough to get them out
at this hour.
ELAINE:
Can I have a sip?
Uh, yeah. Coming up.
[SLURPING]
[♪]