[♪]
When are they gonna have
the flying cars, already?
They have been promising
that for a while.
Years. When we
were kids,
they made it seem like
it was around the corner.
I think Ed Begley Jr.
has one.
No, that's--
That's just electric.
What about
Harrison Ford?
He had one in, uh,
Blade Runner.
That was a cool one.
What's the competition?
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang?
What do you think
the big holdup is?
The government
is very touchy
about us being
in the air.
Let us run around on the ground
as much as we want.
Anything in the air
is a big production.
Yeah. Right.
And what about
the floating cities?
And the underwater
bubble cities?
It's like we're living
in the '50s here.
[♪]
It's good
suspension.
Would you stop it?
You'll have plenty of time
to destroy it after I get it.
Hey, George.
I'm buying this car.
Shh!
What is wrong with you?
You never tell 'em
you like the car.
You're not sure
what you want.
You don't even know
why you're here.
That vein again.
I'm starving.
We should have had
lunch first.
It'll be 20 minutes.
I told you, Puddy's
getting me an insider deal.
Since when is Elaine's
boyfriend selling cars?
I thought
he was a mechanic.
I guess he graduated.
That's an easy move:
go from screwing you
behind your back
to screwing you
right to your face.
[HONKS]
Thank you.
Puddy's just gonna
give you the car, huh?
You'll see. They stick you
with the undercoating,
rustproofing,
dealer prep.
Suddenly you're on your back,
like a turtle.
All right,
calm down.
My father had
a car salesman buddy.
He was gonna
fix him up real nice.
Next thing I know,
I'm getting dropped off
in a Le Car
with a fabric sunroof.
All the kids
are shouting:
"Hey, Le George!
Bonjour, Le George!
Let's stuff Le George
in Le Locker!"
Jerry, I don't think
this thing is hooked up right.
All right,
we're going in.
[KRAMER THUMPING]
You've got
a good eye there.
I see you've noticed
the unibody construction.
I'm Rick.
Are you looking to buy
or to lease?
Uh, borrow.
From my friend.
Yeah, he'll be
buying.
Maybe I should
talk to him.
Oh, I don't
think so.
No, he's
an entertainer.
You know, all over
the place? Brrp.
That's where
I come in.
I see. So you're
his mana--?
Uh, neighbor.
That's right. Yeah.
[CLAPS HANDS]
Well...
Why don't we take this boiler
out for a shakedown, huh?
[♪]
Look at
these salesmen.
The only thing
these guys fear
is the walkout.
No matter what
they say, you say:
"I'll walk out
of here right now."
Can I help?
Hold it.
One more step,
and we're walking!
George. Sorry.
We're just waiting
for David Puddy.
He is. You don't know
what I'm doing.
Hey.
Sorry
I'm late.
My new salesman
boyfriend took me out
to celebrate
his promotion.
Oh. Where'd you go?
Uh...to
a restaurant--
Arby's.
I had
the roast beef.
So, Puddy, I decided
I'm gonna go with
another
900 convertible.
All right. Classic.
High-five.
David, can you
tell me
where the Xerox
machine is?
Oh, sure, babe.
Salesmen-only copy room
right there.
Oh.
Hey, come on, guys.
I'll show you the 900.
[BELLIGERENTLY]
Yeah, you show us the 900.
[♪]
And look at
these features, Mr. Kramer.
Antilock brakes,
automatic climate control--
Uh, make a right
at this corner, please
--an adjustable
steering wheel and--
Oh, Mr. Kramer,
you missed the turn.
No. No. No, I didn't.
That's okay. We'll
make this next right
and swing around
to get back.
Well, it's a test drive, right?
I never drive around here.
If I'm gonna
recommend this car,
I need to see that
it'll handle my daily routine.
So where are we going?
Just a little place
I like to call
"You'll See."
[POPS LIPS]
[♪]
I'm starving.
Got any of those
free doughnuts
you use to soften
people up?
By the Service Department.
All right, remember.
No rustproofing.
Commit to nothing.
If you have
to speak, mumble.
Au revoir, Le George.
Don't think
it can't happen!
So, Puddy,
this is
a pretty good
move for you, huh?
No more grease monkey.
I don't care for that term.
Oh. Sorry.
I didn't know.
I don't know too many monkeys
who could take apart
a fuel injector.
I saw one once that
could do sign language.
Yeah, I saw
that one. Uh...
Koko.
Yeah, Koko.
Right, Koko.
That chimp's all right.
High-five.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on here?
You didn't agree
to anything, did you?
No. We both just saw
the same monkey.
Well, I got screwed
on the doughnuts.
There were
none left. Heh.
Well, there's
a vending machine.
I can show you where it is.
Hey, gimme
a dollar.
Where's your money?
I'm here
helping you.
Hey. Where's
Puddy?
The copy machine
is broken. [SNICKERS]
That's what they
want you to think.
Have you noticed
your boyfriend has developed
an annoying little habit?
The squinting?
No.
The staring?
He keeps asking me
to give him a high-five.
I thought
all guys do that.
Slapping hands
is the lowest form
of male primate ritual.
Even some of them
have moved on.
They're doing
sign language now.
It's that bad?
What do you think
the Nazis were doing?
That was the heil-five.
Tsk.
Isn't that from your act,
like, 10 years ago?
It was a good bit
in the 80s,
and it's still
relatable today.
Good news. We got
a 900 in black.
That's the hot color.
High-five.
Um, David,
you know what?
Can you
come help me
fix the copy
machine? Come.
You owe me
five.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Twix.
[MAKES ASCENDING
HIGH-PITCHED NOISE]
B5.
Ah, come on!
[SIGHS]
Uh...
excuse me.
Do you have, uh,
change of a dollar?
No.
Could I, uh--
Could I trade you
for another one?
Don't have one.
Uh, excuse me.
When your, uh--
When your wallet was open,
I-- I glanced inside,
and I...
couldn't help but notice
that you have several
crisp dollar bills.
You're incorrect.
Perhaps you could
look again, please?
I'm very hungry.
We had doughnuts
earlier.
I guess everyone here enjoys
giving the old scroogie, huh?
You're all doing
a hell of a job!
[CHUCKLES ANGRILY]
What I would do with you.
[♪]
Mr. Kramer, we're
really not allowed
to use the cars to run errands.
Now, look,
Rick.
I'm very close to
giving this car,
that my celebrity friend
is considering,
my full endorsement.
Ooh. Let's see if
I can get a smile
from
these femininas.
Hey, ladies!
It's a Saab 900!
What do you think?
Can I interest you in a little
supplemental restraint?
[LAUGHS]
Jeez.
[♪]
I think the candy
comes out over there.
People drop change
down here, Jerry.
And they're too lazy
to pick it up.
Either that, or they've got
a weird little hang-up
about lying facedown
in filth.
Why don't you just
go to the cashier?
The cashier is at lunch,
which is where
I'd like to be.
How much was under there?
I think something bit me.
I just need another nickel.
Puddy thinks I should
go for the CD player.
What do you think?
[CHUCKLES]
He's got a live one.
He's just reeling
his big fish in.
Hey, can I have
my dollar back?
It's wrinkled.
It's worthless.
[CACKLES
TRIUMPHANTLY]
Come on.
Jump!
They just put out
some more doughnuts.
They did?
Last one.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Okay, just one more errand, and we can head back.
Actually, it looks like
we're gonna need some gas.
Oh? Well,
how much gas you think
is in there
right now?
Well, it's on E.
You know, Rick, oftentimes
Jerry, he lends me his car,
and I find myself
in a situation
where the car is
almost out of gas.
But...for a variety
of reasons,
I don't want to be
the one responsible
for purchasing
costly gasoline. Mm.
So you wanna know
how far you can drive
your friend's car
for free.
Well, I make it up to him
in other ways.
[♪]
As you will see,
the candy bar is paid for,
and yet
remains dangling
in the machine.
Hey, it's gone.
Where is my Twix?
What? That guy's
eating it!
Well, how do you know
that one's yours?
Yeah, I-- It was
dangling.
There were
only two left.
He must have bought one
and gotten both.
Sir, are you gonna
buy a car?
No!
Hey. Hey.
I see you!
That is my Twix!
Oh-ho-ho!
Ho-ho!
Paper jam.
Got it.
Yay.
High-five.
On the flip side.
Eh, uh--
David, um, I--
Don't leave me hanging.
You're a salesman now.
And the high-five is...
It's very grease monkey.
What did I say
about that?
I-- I'm sorry,
but the high-five
is just so stupid.
Oh, yeah? I'll tell you
what's stupid.
You, stupid.
Oh, that is
really mature.
Yeah? So are you.
You're the grease monkey.
Uh-- That--
That doesn't make
any sense.
[GROANS]
I am leaving.
If you leave,
we're through.
Fine. We're through.
Oh, so you're leaving.
That's right.
High-five.
On the flip side.
Taking me
to Arby's.
Hey. Wh--
Where are you--
Let's finish
this up.
Did you two break up?
That chick's whacked.
[TYPING ON ADDING
MACHINE]
We're history.
Just left out
a couple of things.
Uh, rustproofing.
Rustproofing?
Transport charge.
Storage surcharge.
Additional overcharge.
Finder's fee.
Finder's fee?
It was on the lot.
Yeah, that's right.
And, uh, floor mats...
keys...
Keys?
How you gonna
start it?
[♪]
Excuse me.
I believe you
just ate my Twix bar.
It was
dangling.
And when you purchased
your Twix bar,
you got a little freebie.
And you never
bothered to ask why
or seek out
its rightful owner.
First of all,
it wasn't a Twix.
It was a 5th Avenue bar.
[SCOFFS]
You must think
I'm pretty stupid.
That was
no 5th Avenue bar.
I can see
the crumb there
in the corner
of your lip.
Now, tha--
That is a cookie.
And we all know that Twix
is the only candy bar
with the cookie crunch.
That's a-- It's
a little nougat.
Nougat? Please.
I think I've reached
the point in my life
where I can tell the difference
between nougat and cookie.
So let's not
just say things
that we both know
are obvious fabrications!
You know you're getting
a little vein there?
I know about
the vein!
Believe this guy?
Hey, George.
Hey.
I'm starving.
No. Last one.
Listen. You gotta
help me out.
Elaine and Puddy broke up.
He's treating me like
a regular customer.
I tried to tell you,
but you wouldn't listen.
No-ho-ho. You were
gonna get a deal, huh?
There's no laws in
this place. Anything goes.
It's Thunderdome!
Is someone
helping you?
Stay back!
[♪]
RICK:
Where is it now?
Still some overlap
between the needle
and the slash
below the E.
How low
are you gonna go?
Oh, I've been in
the slash many times.
This is nothing.
You'll get used to it.
Just...
[POPS LIPS]
...put it out of
your mind.
Have you...
ever been
completely below...
the slash?
Well, I almost did once.
And I blacked out.
When I came to,
the car was in a ditch,
and the tank was full.
I don't know who did it...
and I never got to
thank them.
Mr. Kramer, the road!
Whoa! Whoa!
[HORN HONKING]
Listen, Puddy. When we
first started this deal,
I thought things
would be different.
Now, if you wanna
play hardball,
I got my friend
George here,
and he can play
pretty hard...ball.
George...
vein it up.
All right, Puddy,
listen and listen good.
I need to know the name
of that mechanic
that walks around
here.
Big guy, a liar,
short name.
Sam? Mo? Sol?
George.
Can we focus
on the car here?
I'm starving.
I can feel my stomach
sucking up against my spine.
Jerry, I just need
your signature here,
and we'll get you
that yellow car ready to go.
Yellow? I wanted black.
I can't give you black
at that price.
George, would you
help me, please?
Yes. This is
wrong!
Sing it, sister!
Just because
a candy bar
fails to fall
from its perch... Oh, God.
...does not imply
transfer of ownership.
Mo, Sol or Lem
is not gonna
get away with this!
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hey. George.
[♪]
RICK:
Is it just the angle I'm looking at?
No, sir. We are
down there.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh. This is amazing.
Oh, I never
felt so alive.
All right,
I'm satisfied.
We better get
some gas.
What? Well,
we can't stop now.
What do you mean?
We have to keep going,
back to the dealership.
That was the plan.
There was no plan.
Well, let's make it the plan!
Let's just go for it,
like Thelma and Louise.
They drove to
a dealership?
No. They drove off a cliff.
Oh, you are
one sick mama.
I like it.
Mr. Kramer, the road!
Yup! Yup!
[HORN HONKING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Elaine, you gotta
get back here.
Puddy is screwing me
on this car,
which is yellow now.
Who is this?
[FRUSTRATED GROAN]
What?
You gotta get back
with Puddy
so I can make this deal.
You know, just that
you cared enough to call
means so much, Jerry.
You're gonna get back
together anyway.
It's thousands
of dollars.
I don't know.
Come on. You don't
have to see him
till my 15,000-mile
check.
Well, will you pay
my cab fare out there?
Fine.
And I didn't like
that roast beef.
How about some lunch?
No. No lunch.
I'll hang this phone up
right now.
All right.
Lunch.
I'll see you.
Bye.
Everybody's
ripping me off.
[♪]
Yes, I'd like to
report a problem
with one of
your mechanics.
When did you bring
your car in?
Yeah, right.
I'm gonna get my car
repaired at a dealership.
[LAUGHS]
Why don't I just flush my money down the toilet?
Sir...
what exactly
is the problem?
One of your guys,
Kip or Ned--
short name
--stole my Twix
candy bar.
Are you saying he grabbed
your candy bar away from you?
He might as well have.
I caught him, and
his face was covered
in chocolate
and cookie crumbs.
Thought you said
it was a Twix.
Oh, it was.
But he claimed it was
a 5th Avenue bar.
Maybe it was.
Oh, no. No.
Twix is the only candy
with the cookie crunch.
What about
the $100,000 bar?
Nope. Rice and caramel.
Nougat?
No.
Positive?
Please.
You know they changed
the name from $100,000 bar
to 100 Grand?
All I want is
my 75 cents back,
an apology,
and for him
to be fired.
I remember when you
used to be able
to get a Hershey
for a nickel.
What's the one with
the swirling chocolate
in the commercial?
They all have swirling
chocolate in the commercial.
Not Skittles.
Dad, I told you
you could sit here
only if you
don't talk.
You make your father
sit here all day?
He likes it.
All right. Do you mind?
I have the window.
Now what are you
gonna do about my Twix?
Twix has
too much coconut.
No! There's
no coconut!
I'm allergic
to coconut.
I'm not.
A nickel.
[♪]
Cab receipt.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hey, Puddy.
I'm with a customer.
[SCOFFS]
No, no. No, E--
Elaine.
The-- The car
can wait.
What's important is you two
getting back together.
Uh, then we'll talk
about the car.
I don't wanna get back
with her. Too bossy.
David.
Okay...
now, I know this is
an important decision.
Why don't we all just sit down
and talk about it?
[GROANS]
Come on.
Now, look...
you both find each other
attractive, right?
[SIGHS]
[SCOFFS]
[IN UNISON]
Right.
Clearly, no one else
can stand to be
with either one of you.
[CHUCKLES]
I guess. Good point.
All right.
Now what do I have to do
to put you two
in a relationship today?
[♪]
Uh. Cars can
go on empty,
but not us humans,
huh, fella?
I'll get us a couple
of Twix bars.
No. No coconut
for me.
All right. I'll get you
a Mounds bar.
Keep the engine running.
[YELLS]
No, man. Not the gas.
But it needs it, Kramer.
It needs it bad.
You think that this will
make you happy?
'Cause it won't!
Oh, you should just
go on without me.
Listen to me.
When that car rolls
into that dealership
and that tank
is bone-dry,
I want you to be there with me,
when everyone says,
"Kramer and that other guy,
"oh, they went farther
to the left of the slash
than anyone ever dreamed."
[ENGINE KNOCKING]
Maybe we'd better
get moving.
It's good to have
you back, Stan.
It's Rick, by the way.
No time!
[♪]
Mr. Costanza,
I really don't
have time for this.
Now, if this mechanic guy
was, in fact,
eating a 5th Avenue bar,
as he claims...
wouldn't you agree
he would have no problem
picking one out
from a candy lineup?
Candy lineup?
I've spent the last hour
preparing 10 candy bars,
with no wrappers or
identification of any kind,
for him to select from.
Took you an hour?
Only I hold the answer key
to their true
candy identities.
And so, without
further ado...
I give you...
the candy lineup.
Hey, Willie,
check it out.
Free candy!
That's my candy
lineup!
Where are
all my cards? They're--
They're all
on the floor.
And you!
How many Twix does that
make for you today?
Like, eight Twix?
No.
Hey, this Clark bar
is good.
It's a Twix.
They're all Twix!
It was a setup!
A setup, I tell you!
And you've ruined it!
You've all
screwed me again!
Now gimme one.
Gimme a Twix.
They're all gone.
[LONG SCREAM]
Twix!
What was
that?
There's a mental hospital
right near here.
All right.
Elaine, David,
I believe we have a deal
here in principle.
Arby's no more
than once a month.
And in exchange, Elaine
comes to your softball game
and doesn't read
a book.
Hm.
Well, that's not bad.
I can live with that.
So you're back
together?
Yeah.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
All right. All right,
all right. That's enough.
Now, let's get back
to my deal.
That undercoating. That's
a rip-off, isn't it?
Oh. We don't even
know what it is.
So I'm getting
the insider's deal.
Insider's deal.
High-five.
[♪]
Rick:
There's the dealer!
Hey!
[GIGGLING]
We did it. We
pulled it off.
I can't believe it.
Where's the needle?
Oh, it broke off,
baby.
[CHEERS]
Oh, Mr. Kramer,
I gotta thank you. Huh?
I-- I learned a lot.
Things are gonna be
different for me now.
Well, that's
a weird thing to say.
I wonder how much longer
we could have lasted.
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder. Hm.
Hm.
[BOTH SCREAMING, CHEERING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[♪]
This is nice.
What kind of car is this?
Caprice
Classic.
You couldn't just give him
one high-five?
And where does it end?
Then everyone's
doing it.
It's like the wave
at ball games,
air quotes, the phrase
"Don't go there."
Someone's gotta
take a stand.
This Arby's is good.
So, George...
I still
don't understand.
How was that a setup?
And who were you trying
to set up anyway,
the mechanic
or the manager?
I don't know.
All of them.
They're all crooks.
Besides,
I couldn't get
all different
candy bars anyway.
[KRAMER AND RICK
LAUGHING, SCREAMING]
What was that?
I think there's
a mental hospital
near here.
Yeah.
Very near.
[KRAMER AND RICK
CHEERING, LAUGHING]
Yahoo!
Yahoo.
[SIGHS]
Well, I think
we stopped.
[SIGHS]
Mm, you can probably
let go of my hand now.
Mm. Yeah, yeah.
[SIGHS]
Well, I'll think
about it.
[CAR DOOR
CLOSES]
Do you have my card?
[♪]
DAD:
A nickel.