[♪]
So Whatley's
still Jewish, huh?
Oh, sure. Without the parents,
it's a breeze.
[GIGGLES]
Hey. Happy Hanukkah.
Hey, Tim.
Great party.
Yeah.
Huh?
Uh.
Ah...
Hey, George, thanks again
for getting me
those Yankee tickets.
Oh, yeah, still in good
with the ground crew. Heh.
That's good.
Look, I'd better circulate.
Happy Hanukkah,
Tiffany.
This place is like
Studio 54 with a menorah.
I'm gonna get some more of
these kosher cocktail franks.
Ooh, I got Denim Vest
checking me out.
[CHUCKLES]
Fake phone number's
coming out tonight.
Oh, you have
a standard fake?
Mm-hm.
It spells out,
"No Elaine."
Isn't that eight letters?
The extra E is for:
"Ecchh."
That's neat.
Hm, Jerry, no, please.
Denim Vest.
He's smoothing it.
Jerry. God!
Hi.
Hi, I'm Jerry.
You might not know it
to look at me,
but I can run really,
really fast.
Nice vest.
Oh.
I like the...
big metal buttons.
They're snaps.
Listen,
maybe we should, uh...
go out sometime.
Why don't I give you
my phone number?
[♪]
GEORGE:
How'd it go with that girl?
Great. I'm going out
with her tomorrow night.
How'd it go
with the cocktail franks?
Great!
I ate the entire platter.
Had to call in sick today.
Didn't you call
in sick yesterday?
Hey, I work for Kruger
Industrial Smoothing.
"We don't care,
and it shows."
You're gonna open
your mail here?
Hey, at least I'm bringing
something to this.
"Have you seen me?"
Nope.
Ooh.
Something from Whatley.
See? You give, and you get.
This is what I'm trying
to teach you.
"This holiday season, a donation
has been made in your name
to the Children's Alliance"?
Oh, that's nice.
I got him Yankee tickets, he got
me a piece of paper saying,
"I've given your gift
to someone else."
To a children's charity.
Don't you see
how wrong that is?
Where's your Christmas spirit?
An eye for an eye!
Do me a favor, don't give me
anything this year.
Hey.
Oh, nothing for me.
I'm going
to Atomic Sub later.
Atomic Sub?
Why are you eating there?
I got a card, and they stamp it
every time I buy a sub.
Twenty-four stamps,
and I become
a submarine captain.
What does that mean?
Free sub.
[GROANS]
What?
Nothing.
It's a card from my dad.
What is it?
Elaine!
"Dear son,
Happy Festivus."
What is Festivus?
It's nothing.
When George was growing up,
Jerry, no!
his father hated
No!
all the commercial and religious
aspects of Christmas,
so he made up
his own holiday.
Oh. And another piece
of the puzzle falls into place.
All right.
And instead of a tree,
didn't your father put up
an aluminum pole?
Jerry, stop it!
Weren't there feats
of strength that always ended up
with you crying?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to work!
You happy now?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
KRAMER:
Hey, neighbor.
Are you reading
my VCR manual?
Well, we can't all
be reading the classics,
Professor Highbrow.
Oh, I can't believe it!
I've lost
my Atomic Sub card.
Oh, no.
I bet I wrote that fake number
on the back of it
when I gave it
to Denim Vest. So?
I've eaten 23 bad subs.
I just need one more.
It's like a long,
bad movie,
but you want to see
the end of it.
No. You walk out.
All right.
Then it's like
a boring book,
but you gotta finish it.
No. You wait for the movie.
I want that free sub.
You don't need the card.
High-end hoagie outfit
like that,
it's all computerized.
Technology.
They're cloning sheep now.
KRAMER:
No, no, no. They're not cloning sheep.
It's the same sheep.
I saw Harry Blackstone
do that trick
with two goats
and a handkerchief
on the old
Dean Martin Show.
Oh, I gotta get ahold
of Denim Vest.
So why don't you try
your blowoff number
and see if he's called it?
That's a good idea.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah, go.
What?
Really?
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Bye.
Great news. Yeah.
The strike's been settled.
I'm going back to work.
What strike?
Yeah, H & H Bagels.
That's where I worked.
You?
Worked?
Bagels?
Yeah, look, see? I still have
my business card.
Yeah, we've been on strike
for 12 years, huh?
Oh, I remember seeing
those guys picketing out there.
But I haven't seen them
in a long time.
Yeah, well, H & H wouldn't
let us use their bathroom
while we were picketing.
Kind of put a cramp
on our solidarity.
What were your demands?
Yeah, 5.35 an hour, and that's
what they're paying now.
I believe that's
the new minimum wage.
And now you know
who to thank for that.
All right,
I gotta go.
Why didn't you
ever mention this?
[SIGHS]
Well, Jerry,
I didn't want you to know
I was out of work.
It's embarrassing.
[♪]
KRAMER:
All right, everybody!
I'm back!
Who are you?
Cosmo Kramer. Strike's over.
Oh, yeah. Kramer.
Uh, what? Didn't any
of the other guys come back?
No. I'm sure they all got
other jobs, like, 10 years ago.
Oh, man.
Well, it kind of makes you
wonder what it was all for.
I could use someone
for the holidays.
All right. Toss me an apron!
Let's bagel!
What are those?
Those are raisin bagels.
I never thought
I'd live to see that.
[♪]
ELAINE:
So, anyway, I've been giving out
your phone number
as my standard fake.
So you're Elaine Benes.
We've been getting calls
for you for five years.
So, listen,
when this guy calls,
if you could just give him
my real number.
Hey, Charlie,
guess who's here.
Elaine Benes.
Elaine Benes!
ALL:
Elaine Benes?
MAN 1:
You make a lot of man friends.
You know who's a man?
Charlie here.
He's a man.
You know who else? Me.
I'm a man.
Oh, my.
I'll have this Vest guy
call your real number.
You just,
uh, give it to me,
and that way,
I'll have it.
My number? Uh...
Okay, uh...
There you go.
And, uh--
Tell you what, put a sawbuck
on Captain Nemo
in the third at Belmont.
TIM:
Hey, Jerry.
Hey, Tim.
What's up?
Actually, I'm having dinner
with a girl I met at your party.
Mazel tov.
Jerry.
Hi.
Gwen?
Yeah.
Really?
Come on.
Our table's ready.
Tsk.
[♪]
GEORGE:
So attractive one day,
not attractive the next?
Have you come
across this?
Yes, I am familiar
with this syndrome.
She's a two-face.
Like the Batman villain?
If that helps you.
So if I ask her out again,
I don't know
who's showing up:
the good, the bad,
or the ugly.
Clint Eastwood!
Yeah.
Hey, check this out.
I got to give Christmas presents
to everyone down at Kruger,
so I'm pulling a Whatley.
"A donation has
been made in your name
to the Human Fund."
What is that?
Made it up.
"The Human Fund.
Money for people."
What do you think?
It has a certain
understated stupidity.
The Outlaw Josey Wales!
Yeah.
Ah.
Bagels on the house.
Hey!
Ha-ha!
How was your first day?
Oh, fantastic.
It felt so good
to get my hands back
in that dough.
Your hands were
in the dough?
No. I didn't
make these bagels.
No, they're day-olds.
The homeless
won't even touch 'em.
Oh, we try to fool 'em by
putting a few fresh ones on top,
but they dig. They--
They test.
All right, uh--
Ah, I'm outta here.
Happy Festivus.
What's Festivus?
When George was growing up
No!
his father--
Stop it!
It's nothing!
It's a stupid holiday
my father invented.
I-it doesn't exist!
Happy Festivus,
Georgie.
God!
Frank invented a holiday?
He's so prolific.
Kramer, listen, I got
a little phone relay going,
so if a guy calls H & H
and he's looking for me,
you take a message.
You're still trying
to get that free sub?
Hey, I have spent
a lot of time,
and I have eaten a lot of crap
to get to where I am today,
and I am not
throwing it all away now.
Is there a captain's hat
involved in this?
Maybe.
[♪]
FRANK:
Kramer, I got your message.
I haven't celebrated
Festivus in years.
What is your interest?
Well, just tell me
everything, huh?
Many Christmases ago,
I went to buy a doll
for my son.
I reach for
the last one they had,
but so did another man.
As I rained blows
upon him,
I realized there had
to be another way.
What happened to the doll?
It was destroyed.
But out of that,
a new holiday was born,
a Festivus
for the rest of us!
That must have been
some kind of doll.
She was.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas!
Oh, Sandy.
Here is a little
something for you.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh.
Thanks.
Phil, I loved those cigars.
Incoming.
PHIL: Ow.
Aw, Mr. Kruger, sir,
Merry Christmas.
Not if you could
see our books.
What is this?
The Human Fund.
Whatever.
Exactly.
Erica!
And at the Festivus dinner,
you gather your family around
and tell them all the ways
they have disappointed you
over the past year.
And is there a tree?
No. Instead, there's a pole.
Requires no decoration.
I find tinsel distracting.
Frank, this new holiday
of yours
is scratching me
right where I itch.
Let's do it, then.
All right.
Festivus is back!
I'll get the pole
out of the crawl space.
All right.
Hello, Frank.
Hello, woman.
Kramer, Kramer,
any word from the Vest?
Uh, no, no.
Oh.
Uh, listen, Harry,
I need the 23rd off.
Hey, I hired you to work
during the holidays.
This is the holidays.
But it's Festivus.
What?
You know you're infringing
on my right to celebrate
new holidays.
That's not a right.
Well, it's going to be
'cause I'm going back
on strike.
Come on, Elaine.
Yeah, it's a walkout!
No, I gotta stay here
and wait for the call.
You're siding with management?
No, I'm just--
Scab! Scab!
Scab!
Hey.
Boy, am I glad
to see you.
You were expecting
someone else?
You never know.
You know, you might want
to take the tunnel.
So, uh, what do you feel
like eating, Chinese or Italian?
[GASPS]
I could go either way.
You're telling me.
[♪]
So she was switching
back and forth?
The whole time.
She was like
a 3-D baseball card
that changes,
depending on the angle.
So one minute she's pretty
and at the plate,
and the next, she's ugly
and advancing the runners.
So, what happened next?
Well, we stopped by here,
and--
Actually, the only place
she always looked good
was in that back booth
over there.
Well, so?
Just bring her here.
This is all
you really need.
I can't just keep bringing her
to the coffee shop.
I mean, what if things,
you know, progress?
Lights out.
All right,
I'll give it a shot.
I do really like
this coffee shop.
Nice cuff links,
by the way.
Office Christmas gift.
I tell you, this Human Fund
is a gold mine.
That's not a French cuff shirt,
you know?
I know. I cut the button off
and poked a hole
with a letter opener.
Oh, that's classy.
[POLE SCRAPING FLOOR]
Well, happy Festivus.
What is that?
Is that the pole?
George, Festivus is
your heritage.
It is part
of who you are.
That's why I hate it.
It's a big dinner Tuesday night
at Frank's house.
Everyone's invited.
George,
you're forgetting how much
Festivus has meant to us all.
I brought one
of the cassette tapes.
FRANK [ON TAPE]:
Read that poem.
GEORGE:
I can't read it. I need my glasses.
You don't need glasses!
You're just weak!
You're weak!
ESTELLE:
Leave him alone!
All right, George.
It's time for the Festivus
feats of strength.
No! No! Turn it off!
No feats of strength!
I hate Festivus!
Come on.
We had some good times.
Hey.
Hi...there.
This is, uh, Kramer and Frank.
Hi.
[STAMMERING]
Hello.
So you ready to go?
Uh, why don't
we stay here?
The, uh, back booth
just opened up.
Now, this is
a good-looking both.
[♪]
Protect Festivus.
Hey. No bagels.
No bagels. No bagels.
Hey! No bagels.
No bagels. No bagels...
MAN:
Lady, if you want a sandwich,
I'll make you a sandwich.
I want the one
that I earned.
[RINGS]
I'll get it.
H & H and Elaine.
Elaine, you should get
out of there.
I sabotaged the bagel machine
last night. It's going down.
What did you do?
You've been warned.
Oh, hi.
Hey, the steam valve
broke.
Can we still make bagels?
Sure. It's just
a little steamy.
How do you like
your bagels now?
George, I got
something for you.
I'm supposed to, uh,
find a charity
and throw some
of the company's money at it.
They all seem
the same to me,
so, what's the difference, hm?
Twenty thousand dollars?
Made out to the Human Fund.
Gee.
Oh, damn.
I've locked myself
out of my office again.
All right.
I'm going home.
[♪]
GWEN:
Jerry,
how many times do we have
to come to this...place?
Why? It's our place.
I just round a rubber band
in my soup.
Oh, I know
who's cookin' today.
Hey, hey!
Surprise, surprise.
Hey, Georgie.
I think I'm just gonna go.
I'll be here.
GEORGE: Hey, soup.
She didn't touch it.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Paco.
Whoo.
Hey, look, take a look at this.
Twenty thousand dollars
from Kruger?
You're not keeping this?
I don't know.
Excuse me?
I've been doing
a lot of thinking,
and this might be my chance
to start giving something back.
You want to give something back,
start with the $20,000.
I'm serious.
You're gonna start
your own charity?
I think I could be
a philanthropist,
a kick-ass philanthropist.
I would have all this money,
and people would love me.
Then they would come
to me and beg,
and if I felt like it,
I would help them out,
and then they would
owe me big time!
The first thing
I'm gonna need is a driver.
No bagels, no bagels,
no bagels, no bagels. Yow!
Kramer, the Vest just called.
Yamahama,
it's fright night.
Oh, yeah,
I got a little steam bath,
but, listen, in 10 minutes,
I'm gonna have my hands
on that Atomic Sub card.
And?
Free sub.
I'll see you.
Yeah.
Oh.
Kramer, hi.
Oh, hello.
It's Gwen. We met
at the coffee shop.
Uh-huh.
I'm dating your friend Jerry.
I don't know
who you really are,
but I've seen
Jerry's girlfriend,
and she's not you.
You're much better-looking
and like a foot taller.
That's why we're always
hiding in that coffee shop.
He's afraid of getting caught.
Oh, he's a tomcat.
Steve.
Hmm?
It's Elaine.
From Tim Whatley's party?
Yeah.
You look--
Different.
Huh. I see you're still sticking
with the denim.
So do you have that card
that I gave you?
Well, I had it
back at my place,
but I can't go there now.
I'll give it to you later
or something.
No, no, no, no.
You give me your number.
Okay.
Sure.
Do you have the mumps?
No.
Typhoid?
Yamahama!
A fake number.
Blimey!
[♪]
KRUGER:
George, we've got a problem.
There's a memo here
from Accounting
telling me there's no such thing
as the Human Fund.
Well, there could be.
But there isn't.
Well, I-I could, uh--
I could give
the money back. Here.
George, I don't get it.
If there's no Human Fund,
those donation cards
were fake.
You better have
a damn good reason
why you gave me
a fake Christmas gift.
Well, sir, I--
I gave out the fake card
because, um--
I don't really celebrate
Christmas. I, uh--
I celebrate Festivus.
Feminist?
Festivus, sir.
And, uh, I was afraid
that I would be persecuted
for my beliefs.
They drove my family
out of Bayside, sir!
Are you making
all this up too?
Oh, no, sir.
Festivus is all too real
and...I could prove it,
if I have to.
Yeah, you probably should.
[♪]
GEORGE:
Happy Festivus!
FRANK:
George, this is a surprise.
Who's the suit?
Oh, Dad, this is my boss,
Mr. Kruger.
Have you seen
the pole, Kruger?
No, he doesn't need
to see the pole.
He's gonna see it.
Happy Festivus.
Yamahama.
I didn't have time
to go home.
What are you doing here?
Embracing my roots.
They nailed you
on the 20 G's?
Busted cold.
It's made from aluminum.
Very high
strength-to-weight ratio.
I find your belief system
fascinating.
[LAUGHING]
Hey! Happy Festivus, everyone!
[GIGGLES]
Hello again, Miss Benes.
What are you doing here?
Damnedest thing, uh,
me and Charlie were calling
to ask you out, and, uh,
we got this bagel place.
I told them
I was just about to see you.
It's a Festivus miracle!
Dinner's ready.
Let's begin.
KRUGER:
Oh.
Dr. Van Nostrand.
Huh?
Oh, uh, that's right.
FRANK:
Welcome, newcomers.
The tradition
of Festivus begins
with the airing
of grievances.
I got a lot of problems
with you people!
And now,
you're gonna hear about it.
You, Kruger,
my son tells me
your company stinks!
Oh, God.
Quiet. You'll get yours
in a minute.
Kruger,
you couldn't smooth
a silk sheet
if you had a hot date
with a babe--
I lost my train of thought.
[DOOR OPENS]
Jerry.
Gwen, how did you know
I was here?
Kramer told me.
Another Festivus miracle!
I guess this is the ugly girl
I've been hearing about.
Hey, I was in
a shvitz for six hours.
Give me a break.
[GWEN GRUNTS]
Gwen! Gwen, wait!
[JERRY YELPS]
Bad lighting on the porch.
Hey, how did my horse do?
He had to be shot.
[MOUTHS]
Yeah.
And now as Festivus
rolls on,
we come to the feats
of strength.
Not the feats
This year,
the honor goes to Mr. Kramer.
Uh-oh.
Oh, gee, Frank,
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
I have to work
a double shift at H & H.
I thought
you were on strike.
Yeah, well, I caved.
I mean, I really had
to use their bathroom.
Frank, no offense,
but this holiday's a little--
[TOOTING]
--out there.
Kramer, you-- You can't go!
Who's gonna do
the feats of strength?
How 'bout George?
[DOOR OPENS]
Good thinking, Kruger.
Until you pin me,
George,
Festivus is not over.
Oh, please.
Somebody stop this.
Let's rumble!
ESTELLE:
I think you can take him, Georgie.
GEORGE:
Hey, come on! Be sensible.
FRANK:
Stop crying, and fight your father!
GEORGE:
Ow, ow! I give, I give!
This is the best
Festivus ever!
Uncle! Uncle!
[♪]
All right, that's enough.
You're fired.
Thank you.
[♪]