[♪]
You sure you can't
stay longer?
No. We just came up
for the funeral.
Poor Marvin Kessler.
He went too early.
He was 96 years old.
That had nothing
to do with it.
The man was
out of shape.
That's why we joined
a program.
We walk once around the block
three times a week.
And every morning,
I eat a plum.
Well, whatever you're doing,
you're wearing me out.
What about you?
Yeah. Looks like
you're getting
a little spare tire
there, tiger.
Really?
Hey, Seinfelds.
Hey, Mr. Kramer.
Hi.
How long
you staying?
We just came to town
for a funeral.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I heard.
Yeah, Marvin Kessler.
Boy, that makes
you think.
If he could go...
[CLICKS TONGUE, WHINES]
See you downstairs
at the car. Oh, hey.
Hey, you sure you don't
need a hand with that?
No, no. The luggage
is on the program.
I got a brick in here.
[KRAMER CHUCKLES,
TAPS CASE]
[WINCES]
Did you give blood?
No, no, no.
Not giving. Hoarding.
I'm storing it at
the blood bank.
Just in case.
In case of what?
Jerry...I know myself.
If I'm out on the street,
and it starts to go down,
I don't back off
until it's finished.
Are we finished?
Done.
VIVIAN:
Elaine, I'm so glad you came out.
Yeah.
Now, you haven't seen Jimmy for years.
I know. Well, I'm glad I got to
see him before he hit puberty
and got, you know, all...
lurchy and awkward.
[GIGGLES]
Yeah.
Actually, uh,
I'm gonna need someone
to look after him
tomorrow evening.
Tomorrow evening? Sure.
Do you know anyone
responsible?
Do I know anyone?
Well, if you think of
anybody, give me a call.
[♪]
GEORGE:
What are you doing?
Oh, incense.
For the mood.
Oh, yes. By
all means. The mood.
[CHUCKLES]
Let me know if there's
anything I can do
to lend support
to the mood.
[CHUCKLES]
Mm.
Mm. Cream soda?
Vanilla.
Oh.
Hm.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Can you believe that?
Vivian doesn't think
I'm responsible.
Who wants to be
responsible?
Whenever anything
goes wrong,
the first thing they ask is
"Who's responsible for this?"
I couldn't raise a kid?
Come on. I love
bossing people around.
Hey.
What happened? I thought
you were with Tara.
I was. I had to leave.
She lit this
vanilla incense.
The smell
drove me nuts.
I-- All I could
think about was food.
I had to
get out of there.
Gonna need some
pudding here. Pudding!
You just left?
What did you tell her?
I told her I had
a bus transfer
that was only good
for another hour.
What?
I don't know.
I was starving, Jerry.
Oh, pudding.
Ha-ha.
Ah, you want some?
Hey, do you guys
think
I'm getting
a little...chunky?
What, are you kidding?
We look great.
Mm. You know what
this pudding needs?
The skin on the top.
Like when your mother used to
make it on the stove.
Elaine, what do
you think?
I think you're getting a little
pudding under the skin yourself.
[♪]
KRAMER:
My service rates went up?
You banks are
all the same,
with your hidden fees
and your service charges.
Well, maybe I'll just
take my blood elsewhere. Yeah.
Well, we could transfer it
to another bank for you.
Oh, no, no.
No more banks.
I'm keeping my blood
in my freezer
with my money!
[♪]
GEORGE:
So, uh...
what do you say?
I guess we could use
some food in
our lovemaking.
Okay. We got your, uh...
Got your strawberries.
Your chocolate
sauce.
Your pastrami on rye
with mustard.
Your honey--
Wait, wait, wait.
Pastrami on rye
with mustard?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Don't you remember?
They used pastrami in
that movie Nine 1/2 Weeks.
Remember the, uh,
pastrami scene?
No.
Well, maybe it was
Ghost Busters.
Whatever it was,
it worked.
Come on.
Oh, God. Ah!
[♪]
JERRY:
Didn't go for it, huh?
No.
So she didn't appreciate
the erotic qualities
of the salted,
cured meats?
She tolerated
the strawberries
and the chocolate
sauce,
but, uh...
it's not a meal,
you know?
Food and sex. Those
are my two passions.
It's only natural
to combine them.
Natural? S-sex is about love
between a man and a woman,
not a man and a sandwich.
Jerry, I'm not suggesting
getting rid of the girl.
She's integral.
Maybe instead of trying to
satisfy two of your needs,
how about satisfying
one of somebody else's?
Hey, speaking of which,
I found a great way
to separate the skin
from the top
of the pudding
without leaving any
around the edges--
X-ACTO knife.
[GIGGLES]
I told you, George,
no more pudding.
I'm starting
a purification program. Mm-hm.
Keep all that kind of
food away from me.
Well...
then, I guess these...
would be out of
the question.
What the hell is that?
Pudding-skin singles.
[♪]
KRAMER:
Hey, buddy.
Hey, I'm borrowing
all your Tupperware.
Oh?
Why?
Well, I closed my account
at the blood bank.
What? It-- It-- It's here?
It's in the building?
Right across the hall.
What, you want to go see it?
No, I don't.
In fact, if even one
corpuscle of that blood
should find its way
across that hall,
I will freak out
on you, Kramer.
Freak...out.
You know, for a fat guy,
you're not very jolly.
Hey. Working out?
You know it. And I ditched
all my junk food.
What the heck is
going on here?
Sorry, buddy. Cleaned house.
It's all health food.
Well, I may have to
take it,
but I don't have to
like it.
Vivian left me
a message.
I guess a certain someone
changed her mind
about whether someone
was responsible enough
to watch a certain
other someone.
Is this about me?
No.
Well, then,
I've lost interest.
Vivian.
Hi, it's Elaine.
Yeah, I'm over at Jerry's.
I got your message.
What?
Yeah. He's right here.
Hold-- Hold on.
For me, hm?
Go.
Yeah. W-- What--?
Yeah. Tonight?
Yeah. Yeah,
I'll be there.
Yeah, later.
Well, somebody's
babysitting.
You?! I'm more responsible
than you are.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go fill my freezer
with my own blood.
[♪]
[TARA GIGGLING]
TARA:
Oh! Huh.
[MOANING]
GEORGE [WITH FULL MOUTH]:
Oh, Tara!
[♪]
[KNOCKS]
Hello? Vivian!
Oh, boy, this is
a nice screen.
[WHISPERS]
Kramer.
Ye-- Ah! Don't
take my money.
It is me,
you idiot.
Hey-- What--?
Yeah.
Hi. All right. You gotta
get out of here.
I'm gonna babysit the hell
out of that kid.
Wait, I'm the babysitter.
No, no, no, no.
You're out. I'm in.
Now, hit the road.
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
[SQUEALS]
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
Elaine.
Eh--
What are you
doing here?
Um, ahem, Kramer is actually
sleeping one off,
so I thought that I would...
[KRAMER MOANS]
...help out--
Oh, you got some
raccoons or something.
[KRAMER YELPS]
Well. I guess this will
be all right.
Jimmy. You
remember Elaine. Mm.
She's gonna
watch you tonight.
Hi, Jimmy.
Ooh!
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
JERRY:
Hey, what are you doing here?
Thought you were
babysitting.
Well...there was an incident.
Oh, no.
Where's the blood?
It's in here,
isn't it?
Will you stop it?
What is this?
It's Jell-O.
What about this?
This is blood, isn't it?
Come on. This is
tomato juice. Look.
Oh, you're sick!
You're sick!
Will you calm down?
I took all my blood
down to Newman's.
He let me put it
in his meat freezer.
Hey, what's
going on?
Who made pudding?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. George--
He came by and made some more
of those pudding-skin
singles.
They're delicious.
Damn that George.
I told him I didn't want
this stuff around anymore.
Heads up!
[GASPS]
[GUN CLICKING]
You're dead,
President Lincoln!
You're dead!
I wish I was dead.
Can I have your juice?
As long as
you don't p--
Thanks for the refill.
[YELLS, CACKLES]
[ CHUCKLES]
Hey.
Hey, Elaine.
Hi.
How did it go?
Oh, he's a--
He's a joy.
Really?
Some sitters have told me
he's a bit of a handful.
Oh. Handful of sunshine.
I wish I could do this
every day.
Oh. Elaine,
that's so good to hear. Mm.
I've been having a few
health problems lately.
It's not serious, is it?
Well, it might be.
Well, you know, just in case
anything does happen,
it's nice to know there's
somebody like you around.
Oh, yeah.
That, uh...
That is nice
to know.
[♪]
Hee-hee.
Ah!
Hey, Jerry, it's okay.
I'm right here.
I can see that.
What happened?
Oh, well, that--
That knife--
It...nicked your jugular.
You know, Jerry...
when somebody yells
"heads up,"
you're not supposed to
actually look up.
I'll remember that.
Anyway, you're lucky
I was there.
You lost a lot of blood.
What?
Oh, yeah.
You got three pints of Kramer
in you, buddy.
[POPS MOUTH]
[SCREAMING]
[HOWLING]
[♪]
GEORGE:
Three pints of Kramer's blood?
I can feel his blood
inside of me...
borrowing things
from my blood.
Well, so much for
purification week.
So how's the, uh,
fornicating gourmet?
Doing quite well,
thank you.
Yesterday, I had
a soft-boiled egg
and a quickie.
You know what?
If I could add TV
to the equation,
that would really
be the ultimate.
George, we're trying to
have a civilization here.
Hey.
Hey, how was babysitting?
Oh, just great.
I found out that Vivian's got
some sort of a medical problem,
and if the worst
happens,
she wants me to
take care of Jimmy.
Oh, well, I'm sure
it won't be the worst.
It doesn't matter. I mean,
if anything happens to her,
I'm on deck.
Scissors mishap,
air show disaster...
Chinese organ thieves.
It's a dangerous world.
She's right. I heard
Kramer got mugged
out in the suburbs
on a babysitting gig.
Really?
[♪]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
KRAMER:
Look at this.
Look at the hair
on the back of my neck.
It's all brambly. See?
It's like a thicket
back there.
Look, I need somebody
to shave it for me, huh?
Huh? I'm-- I'm not
touching that thing.
Well, I have to say,
I'm very surprised...
and disappointed,
blood brother.
Oh, no.
What?
Jerry, I gave you
my blood.
Listen to your pulse.
"Hey, buddy.
Hey, buddy."
Kramer, I'm not
shaving your neck.
Oh, so my blood's
not enough?
Would you like
a kidney too?
Because I'll give it
to you.
I'll rip it out
right here
and smack it
on the table.
All right, all right.
I'll do it.
Sit down.
No, no, no. I don't
have time right now.
I'll catch you
tonight.
We'll do sort of an all-over
kind of thing, all right?
[PHONE RINGS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hello?
Kramer called. He told us
you were in the hospital.
Kramer called you?
He calls every week.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
He says he's fine.
Tell him
to eat a plum.
Jerry, you really have to
take better care of yourself.
We bought you some sessions
with a personal trainer.
I don't need
a personal trainer.
All right, I--
I gotta go.
We'll talk
about this later.
MORTY: Plum!
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
Why are you calling
my parents?
Well, maybe if you
called more often,
I wouldn't have to.
Listen, is it
all right
if I watch a tape in here?
Why here?
Well, I'm taping
Canadian parliament
you know, on C-SPAN.
Okay.
Is it all right if I
watch it in your bedroom,
'cause your bed
is really nice.
Fine.
Okay.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
No, no. I do not
want that in here.
Blood.
All right.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hello, doughboy.
Mr. Mandelbaum.
You're the personal trainer?
I'm here to whip you
into shape.
So grab your jock...
if you need one.
It's go time.
[♪]
VIVIAN:
Elaine?
Oh, hi.
Oh, God.
I didn't hear you
come in.
Where's Jimmy?
Mm. I don't know.
I don't know.
We had Ho-Ho's
for dinner,
and then, uh--
And then he put this
plastic bag over his head
and started running around
till he got tired.
And he-- He laid down
somewhere. I--
I'll tell you, I'm no good
at watching that kid.
Ha. Sleeping
like an angel.
Elaine...you're the best.
No. I'm a scatterbrain.
That's probably
why I can't
hold a job or keep a man.
You're a riot.
So you're gonna
watch Jimmy tomorrow?
All right.
But I'm...
running out of
purses here.
[♪]
JERRY:
Okay, Mr. Mandelbaum,
what do you want me
to do?
Drop your purse,
honey...
and pick up
that medicine ball.
Is this a gym or some kind
of fitness museum?
Not funny. Over
your head with it.
Now, you ready?
For what?
All aboard
the pain train.
How many sessions
did my parents pay for?
Not enough to make a man
of you, daffodil.
[♪]
[TARA GIGGLING]
[GEORGE SNICKERING]
GEORGE:
Spicy mustard.
[GIGGLING]
[GEORGE HOWLS]
You are hot tonight.
TARA [GIGGLING]:
Oh, George!
Now for the trifecta.
[TARA LAUGHING]
GEORGE: Mm.
TARA: George?
Hm?
George?
[MOANS]
What are you
doing?
Pleasuring you?
[SAMBA MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
What is this?
Oh, we're making sausages.
[CLICKS OFF]
I thought you were
gonna watch a video.
Well, yeah.
An instructional video
on how to make
your own sausages.
Kramer, I'm not
in the mood for this.
All right. Nemwan, let's go
grab some mail sacks
and haul these beauties
out of here.
[SAMBA MUSIC RESUMES]
Blood over there,
sausage over here.
I'm living in
a slaughterhouse.
Tonight, I want you
to sleep on this.
Toughens
the vertebrae.
Oh, what in
holy hell?
Sausages.
Is this your diet?
No. They're not mine,
Mr. Mandelbaum--
Don't lie to me,
butter bean.
We're taking it up a notch.
[♪]
JERRY:
So the free-love buffet is over?
I got greedy.
Flew too close to the sun
on wings of pastrami.
Yeah. That's what you did.
I can't believe I got another
session with Izzy Mandelbaum.
He's probably gonna
make me box a kangaroo.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Sandwich is
making me flush.
Oh, no. I'll tell you
what you did, Caligula.
You've combined food and sex
into one disgusting,
uncontrollable urge.
Think you're right.
You gonna eat that?
No, but please tell me that's
all you're gonna do with it.
[MOANING
PLEASURABLY]
Jerry.
I tell you...
if this woman dies,
it is gonna be
a major inconvenience.
[TAPS TABLE]
These fries are really,
really good.
All right. That's
enough of that. Mm.
I mean, I can't shake
this woman, you know?
Now I gotta go to
Jimmy's birthday party.
Whew!
Sleepy.
I mean, no matter
what I do,
I cannot weasel out
of raising this kid.
Well, sleepy here's
quite a weasel.
Maybe he can
bat for you.
Yeah. That's
what I need.
A pinch weasel.
Why'd you get rid of
that sausage?
It wasn't me.
It was Mr. Mandelbaum.
Yeah? Well,
Newman's not happy.
He booted me
out of his freezer.
Look...
I gotta take my blood
back to the bank.
Can I borrow
your car?
What's wrong with yours?
Well, I got no a.c.
And I gotta keep the blood
cold, or it'll go bad.
All right, but this is it.
This is the last favor.
We're even.
All right.
Even-steven, okay?
Oh. Uh, by the way, uh,
when you get back to
your apartment, um,
try to keep it down,
because Newman's taking
a nap in your bed.
[♪]
[SAMBA MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
[HUMS]
Oh, man.
What's that?
[EXHALES]
What is...?
What is that?
[EXHALES]
Oh.
"If the engine
begins to overheat...
turn off air conditioner"?
Never. I can't
do that.
Oh, mama.
Ah--
[GASPS]
Jeez! Come on.
Man, this thing
is bone-dry.
[EXHALES]
Vivian.
Elaine.
Hi.
Um, this is my friend, George.
[CHUCKLES]
Hi.
I'm gonna go
say hi to Jimmy.
Okay.
[WHISPERS] You're up.
[SIGHS]
Oh.
Isn't Elaine fantastic?
Yes, she is.
It's a-- It's a pity
we won't be
seeing much more
of her.
Really? Why?
Oh, you haven't heard?
No, she's going to live
with her grandparents
in Reading,
Pennsylvania.
Her grandparents passed away
five years ago.
Yes, they did.
I was covering. Hm.
Elaine has been deported
back to Scotland.
She's an American citizen.
I've seen her passport.
All right, no more lies.
Elaine has been chosen to
represent the Upper West Side
in the next
Biosphere project.
What? I haven't heard anything
about another Biosphere.
That's because
it's underwater.
This is insane.
Is it?
Yes, it is.
Well, it's all
for charity,
so, what's
the difference?
[TIMER DINGS]
You. Very knowledgeable.
Well. I'm, uh...
I'm also an architect.
Is that pastrami?
Yes, it is.
I find the pastrami
to be the most sensual
of all the salted,
cured meats.
Hungry?
Very.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
VIVIAN:
Oh. Wait.
[GRUNTS]
[CLICKS ON]
Oh!
[BOTH MOANING]
GEORGE:
Ah! Vivian!
Is this really
necessary?
If you want to live
in a butcher shop,
I'm gonna treat you
like a piece of meat.
What if I can't
keep up?
You lag, you drag.
Fire it up, son.
Right, Dad.
[STARTS CAR]
Mandelbaum.
BOTH:
Mandelbaum. Mandelbaum.
Move it. Move it.
Move it. Get
those knees up.
Come on. Kick it.
Kick it.
[CAR REVVING UNEVENLY,
ENGINE KNOCKING]
What's going on?
There's something wrong
with your car.
It's dripping something
on my feet.
Yeah. Some kind of red liquid.
Oh, my God, the blood.
Blood?
Uh-oh.
[GROANS]
[JERRY
SCREAMS]
Get up, boy.
Get up.
We got a problem here.
Tough it out.
This is for real.
Ow.
Ow! Ow!
You got to want it.
So how far
did they drag you?
For the first quarter mile,
they thought I was just dogging it.
Hi, George.
Hi, Jimmy.
Yeah, Jimmy.
Why don't you, uh...
go wait outside?
You know,
play with something.
Ow!
What's the kid doing here?
I'm babysitting!
Vivian asked me to raise him
if she doesn't make it.
Oh, that's a drag.
Kid.
GEORGE: Yeah.
You put blood in the car?
Jerry, it was overheating.
You should take better care
of that thing.
Well, they told me
I got more blood,
so I guess
I owe you again.
You didn't get
the blood from me.
Then who?
What?
Hello, Jerry.
[SCREAMING]
[HOWLING]
[♪]