Cup of tea
with lemon.
What happened
to your voice?
I was screaming
at hecklers all night.
Last time
I open for a rodeo.
Well, Jerry...
I've been thinking.
I've gone as far as
I can go with...
George Costanza.
Is this the suicide talk
or the nickname talk?
The nickname.
"George."
What is that?
It-- It's nothing.
It's got no snap,
no zip.
I need a nickname that
makes people light up.
You mean like
"Liza."
But I was thinking...
T-bone.
But there's no T
in your name.
What about
G-bone?
There's no
G-bone.
There's
a G-spot.
That's a myth.
T-bone, the ladies
are gonna love you.
[♪]
ELAINE:
Why did they hire you for a rodeo?
They heard I opened
for Kenny Rogers once.
Didn't he throw you
off a bus
in the middle
of Alabama?
Oh, I had that
coming to me.
You know,
Kenny Rogers has a--
[WHISPERS]
Why did you get a maid?
You don't have to whisper.
She knows
she's a maid.
[WHISPERS]
Where did you get her?
[NORMAL VOICE]
I hired her from a service.
All done.
Thank you.
Nice job.
Is this mine?
Yeah.
[DOOR CLOSES]
What?
Come on, Jerry.
You didn't notice?
Notice what?
She's not really
even a maid.
Oh.
She wants to be
an actress... Mm-hm.
...or a,
uh, model... Mm.
...or a dancer.
Or a...
BOTH:
newswoman, uh-huh.
Hey. Hi.
Well, bad news,
boys.
Yeah, my life
is over.
My girlfriend's
moving away.
You have
a girlfriend?
Jerry, where
have you been?
At a rodeo.
Where's
she moving?
Downtown.
Downtown
New York?
Yeah.
I don't know
if I can handle
one of these
long-distance
relationships.
It's, like
ten minutes by subway.
Uh, I don't know.
Oh, jeez.
Well, you got
a maid.
Come on, it's a whole
different world downtown.
Different Gap,
different Tower Records.
And she's a 646.
What?
What is that?
That's the new
area code.
They've run out
of 212s,
so all the new
phone numbers are 646.
Huh. I was a 718 when
I first moved here.
I cried
every night.
Listen.
Heads up, Elaine.
I'm gonna have to stop by
later and pick up a fax.
At work?
No. At your apartment.
I don't have
a fax machine.
Here we go.
Well, now what
are we gonna do?
See? This is why you should get
a fax and a Xerox.
And a deadbolt.
Are you sure
you don't have one?
Because there's a lot of stuff
in my apartment I've never seen.
Then maybe
you have a fax machine.
You just
blew my mind.
[♪]
KRUGER:
Let's order lunch.
Mary, I will have
a chef's salad.
Turkey
sandwich.
T-bone steak.
For lunch?
Well, I am just
a T-bone kind of guy.
[SNICKERS]
Love that T-bone.
In fact, you might
as well call me--
That sounds good.
I'll have one too.
Watkins,
you're having a T-bone?
I love 'em.
Well, then we should
call you T-bone.
Uh...no, no--
No, we shouldn't.
T-bone!
ALL:
T-bone! T-bone!
T-bone!
[RINGS]
Hello?
[FAX BEEPS]
What?
MACHINE:
You have 57 messages.
Message one...
[FAX BEEPS]
Message two...
Message three...
Hey, it's George.
Listen, I--
MACHINE:
Message four...
[FAX BEEPS]
Kramer.
[RINGS]
Hello?
[FAX BEEPS]
Aah!
[♪]
JERRY:
Well, Cindy, the place looks great.
Thanks, Jerry.
Gotta run.
Okay, I'll
see you.
Hi,
Elaine.
[GROANS]
All right!
Fooling around
with your maid.
That is
a wise decision.
Elaine. Do you think
I would go willy-nilly
into a situation
so obviously fraught
with potential
complications?
Tsk. You are paying a woman
to come to your house
and sleep with you.
No.
I pay her to clean.
The rest is--
What?
A health plan?
I was going to say,
"being a good host."
Oh-ho-ho.
Oh.
But the point is we have
our personal relationship,
and we have our work
relationship.
They're separate,
and, I think,
somewhat sophisticated.
So you consider this
a relationship?
Yes, I do.
Oh. Have you
been out?
Yes, we have.
Where did you go?
The store.
Mm.
To get what?
Stuff.
Cleaning supplies?
And gum.
Oh.
Well, there's nothing
more sophisticated
than diddling the maid
and then chewing some gum.
She's not a maid.
She might be a newswoman!
Hey, uh--
Well, I just
saw Madeline off.
Yeah, she's
in a cab and--
ung-ung-ung
--on her way.
I miss her
already.
Hey, Kramer.
What was it
you were having faxed
to my house
every 30 seconds?
Well, I-- I signed up for
a food-delivery service.
Yeah, "Now We're Cooking."
It's a...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
...play on words.
You know, they're
faxing me the menus
from
some restaurants.
Which ones?
Well, all of them.
Yeah, it's the deluxe package.
So this is never
gonna stop?
Well,
it better not.
Paid for
the whole year.
So should I pick
those up later?
You can pick 'em up
right now.
[IMITATES
FAX BEEPING]
Ah!
[♪]
ELAINE [THINKING]:
I wonder if anyone knows he's here.
If he just
disappeared...
...would anybody notice?
All right,
Miss Benes...
all finished.
Here's
your new number.
Ahem.
Six-four-six?
What is this?
That's your new
area code.
I thought 646 was
just for new numbers.
This is
a new number.
No. No, no, no.
It's not
a new number.
It's-- It's-- It's
just a changed number.
See, it's--
It's not different.
It's the same, just...
changed.
Look...I work for
the phone company.
I've had a lot of experience
with semantics,
so don't try to lure me into
some maze of circular logic.
You know,
I could've killed you,
and no one
would've known.
I could've killed you,
and no one would've known.
Hm.
[♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
JERRY:
Kramer, you're still on the phone?
Madeline and I are
watching Quincy together.
Jerry, you know
this comes on
at the same time here
as it does there?
Really? It's Tuesday here.
What day is it there?
Jerry's teasing.
Oh-oh!
Commercial.
Oh, you going to
the bathroom?
Yeah,
I'll go too.
Madeline
stays here.
Hey,
T-bone.
No.
No T-bone.
No T-bone?
KRAMER:
Hey, is that T-bone?!
No! There's
no T-bone!
KRAMER:
Well, why no T-bone?!
Why no T-bone?
'Cause Neil Watkins
from Accounting is T-bone!
Oh, yeah.
I'm back.
Hey, you wanna play cards
over the phone?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, hey, uh,
listen, Jerry.
Uh...laundry's
piling up there.
You might want to
tell your girlfriend.
Mm. Yeah.
Your girlfriend
is doing your laundry?
KRAMER:
He's sleeping with his maid!
Sleeping with
the maid?
Yes.
I've done that.
Did you ever eat
an ostrich burger?
No.
[♪]
You're probably
one of those women
who doesn't like to
give out her number.
No, I'm not.
Here you go.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Six-four-six?
It's a new
area code.
What area?
N-- New Jersey?
No, no. It's right here
in the city.
It's the same as 212.
They just multiplied
it by three...
and then
they added one
to the middle number.
It's the same.
Do I have to
dial a 1 first?
I'm really kind of
seeing somebody.
Yeah?
Well,
so am I!
[♪]
GEORGE:
Excuse me.
Can I, uh, talk to you,
Watkins?
It's T-bone.
The thing is...
I'm supposed to be
T-bone.
Heh-heh. You're
not a T-bone.
Uh, you're a perfect
George.
What?
Now, you listen
to me!
Boy, look at
George.
He's giving it
to T-bone.
He's...
He's jumping
up and down
like some kind
of monkey.
Hey, what was
the name of that--
Th-that monkey
that could
read sign language?
All right. You can
have T-bone.
Stop crying.
[SNIFFLING]
I'm not crying.
And I...
shouldn't have said that
about your wife.
Please accept
my apologies.
Okay, everybody,
uh...
I have an announcement
to make.
From now on...
I will be
known as--
Koko, the monkey.
What?
ALL:
Koko! Koko!
Koko!
Thank you both
for being here.
Um,
excuse me.
I live in
the building.
Did something happen
to Mrs. Krantz?
She passed.
Oh,
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
A quick
question.
Did she by any chance
have a 212 phone number?
[♪]
CINDY:
I can't find my earring.
Oh. Here
it is.
Hey.
Listen, can I
borrow your suitcases?
Yeah, it's
in your closet.
No, no, no.
I looked.
They're behind my skis
and my tennis racket.
Thanks, buddy.
Where you going?
Huh? Well, I'm-- I'm
getting out of town.
I'm gonna visit Madeline
for the weekend.
You know, this place
is looking kind of messy.
What happened
to Cindy?
Oh, she's here. She just
didn't get around to it. Oh.
Hi, Kramer.
Thanks, Jerry.
Bye.
Oh.
Well, what's
the matter?
What did I
just pay for?
Uh-oh.
You're a john.
[♪]
JERRY:
Koko?
Koko.
Well, it's probably the most
intelligent ape there is.
Yeah.
So...
how's Cindy
the maid?
Everything's
going great,
except, basically,
I'm paying for sex.
Tell me about it.
I went out with
this girl last week.
First, I had to pay
for dinner. Then--
No, George. She's coming over
and not cleaning.
It's like
I'm seeing a prostitute.
How much you pay
this maid?
Forty.
Forty? I'm paying 60
to my maid.
She doesn't do laundry.
And I'm getting nothing.
All right.
Once, she pinched
my ass, but...
I don't know
what that was.
what this is.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look at that.
Huh?
Ooh.
Jerry, you wouldn't believe
what it's like down there.
Taxicab drivers
are insane.
You know, everybody
is in a hurry.
Look, I-- I can't eat with you
leaning over like this.
Just look
straight forward.
Yeah, well, now
I can't see Jerry.
I look
about the same.
What?
I was talking to him.
Uh, what?
Never mind.
Come on,
what'd he say?
Never mind.
Jerry.
Come on,
what'd you say?
What?
Come on.
Where'd you go?
Go back.
Eh.
Come on,
what'd you say?
I said,
never mind.
Yeah,
I know that.
I hate
the counter.
Hey.
Oh. I hate
the counter.
Yeah, who's that?
Well, I got
a 212 number
from this little old lady
in my building, Mrs. Krantz.
Oh, she didn't
mind?
No. She died.
Hey, that's
great.
What happened
to Mrs. Krantz?
Elaine got a new number
because she died.
Newman died?
What did he say?
Some new
kind of pie.
I'll try
a piece.
All right,
who's down there?
Hey, there's
a booth. Well--
Hey. Elaine.
Oh, hi.
Did you hear
about Newman?
What?
[WHIMPERS]
[♪]
GEORGE:
Hey.
So how's it going
at work?
They get tired
of it?
Oh, yeah.
Double zero?
It's "ooh."
As in "ooh-ooh,
ah-ah."
Your nickname's
Koko?
One of the girls down at
the maid service is named Coco.
Really? Coco?
Yeah. Coco.
That girl's
all right.
You know, if I could get
this Coco woman down to Kruger,
then they wouldn't be able to
call me Koko anymore,
because Kruger would
never allow two Kokos.
Sounds like he runs
a real tight ship.
Say goodbye
to Koko.
Goodbye,
Koko.
Goodbye, Koko.
Phew! Jerry.
This relationship
is killing me.
The distance, the longing,
the distance, the--
you know, I didn't realize it,
but I'm a needy person.
Kramer, maybe this relationship
isn't for you.
Oh, yeah? So what am I
supposed to do,
be more like you?
All sealed up in here,
emotionally unavailable.
Paying scrubwomen
for sexual favors.
No! Jerry!
I won't be like you!
Never! I'll never
be like you!
What was that?
I didn't
hear anything.
All right,
I'm taking off. Okay.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Oh, right.
Hey, it was great seeing
you again. I love your outfit.
No. My money.
For what?
For my maid services.
You booked me for today.
But you didn't
really do any work.
I made the bed.
But you took
a nap in it.
So?
I thought that was
kind of...
girlfriend bed-making.
No, that was
the maid.
Who took the nap?
The girlfriend.
Forty dollars seems
kind of steep for a nap.
So, what are you saying?
That I'm a-- A bad maid or--
Or some kind of
a prostitute?
Ho, ho. Ho!
Hold on.
Let's keep this
sophisticated.
You know, I don't think
I want to be your girlfriend
or your maid.
So is this
a breakup/quitting?
Yeah. Don't ever call me
or hire me again.
Oh, yeah?
Well, then,
were through!
And you're fired.
[♪]
TELEPHONE SERVICEMAN:
Sign here.
ELAINE:
Yes! Two-one-two.
Hey, what happened to
the guy I had last time?
Oh, you know,
it's an odd thing.
He went out on a job,
never came back.
Nobody knows
what happened.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
All right. I am
back in the game.
Hello?
Gammy.
No. You got
the wrong number, kid.
Gammy Krantz.
It's your grandson, Bobby.
Why haven't
you called?
Oh, nuts.
Do you hate me
'cause of my lazy eye?
No. It's just that
I've been
kind of buried over here.
[♪]
JERRY:
So the kid doesn't know his grandmother is dead?
G-5.
Hit.
No, I guess his parents
didn't want to tell him.
B-2
Miss.
He called
six times yesterday.
[SCOFFS]
What a nightmare
it must be to have
a real family.
I wouldn't
worry about it.
B-6?
Hit. Uh.
You sank my submarine.
Elaine...
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
COMPUTER VOICE:
you have a collect call from--
KRAMER:
Hey, buddy, don't say no!
I accept.
I went down
to Madeline's.
I told her, "You gotta move,
or it's over."
Well, what happened?
I think it's over.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
We had a big fight,
she threw me out,
I started walking,
And now
I'm lost downtown!
I don't have any money.
I don't recognize anybody.
[SOBBING]
I miss home. I don't even know how to get there.
What's around you?
Uh. I'm looking
at Ray's Pizza.
You know
where that is?
Is it Famous Ray's?
No, it's
Original Ray's.
Famous Original Ray's?
It's just Original,
Jerry!
Well, what street
are you on?
Okay, I'm on 1st
and 1st.
How can the same street
intersect with itself?
I must be at the nexus
of the universe.
Just wait there.
I'll pick you up.
And, Kramer...
stay alive.
No matter
what occurs,
I will find you!
Aah!
[♪]
You Steinfeld?
Yeah.
My name is Maxwell.
I'm from Maid to Order.
It's a pun.
I sent one of my girls
over to your place.
Cindy.
She says she had a little
problem with you.
You didn't pay.
She didn't really do what
she was supposed to do.
Oh, yeah? She told me
what you like.
You're a little sickie,
aren't you?
Disinfectant on the blinds,
vacuuming the couch--
Hey, hey, come on.
Come on.
I gotta
live around here.
You know what I do to people
who stiff me on a job?
What?
Well, it kind of
depends on the situation.
But if I don't get
my money from you,
I'm gonna
get it from her.
I-- I don't want
any trouble.
You want the money?
Here. No-- Hey!
Wait, wait! Whoa!
Give it to the girl.
I'm an independent
contractor.
Tax purposes.
[♪]
Bobby, you gotta stop
calling your Gammy.
Why?
Because sometimes you call
very early in the morning
when Gammy has been out late
the night before.
And sometimes
when Gammy's not alone.
Your parents still haven't
said anything to you
about your Gammy?
[SIGHS]
All right.
Here we go.
[COUGHING]
Gammy doesn't
feel so good.
I think Gammy
might be dying.
Yep. Yep.
Okay.
Goodbye, Bobby.
Don't call anymore.
I'm dead now.
Gotta go.
[♪]
BOBBY:
Nine-one-one.
Nexus of
the universe.
Hey.
Cindy. Cindy.
What do you want?
Here. I got
your money.
I don't want
any money from you.
Come on. Take it.
It's money.
Let me give it
to you.
[OVER LOUDSPEAKER]
Looking for a good time, sir?
You wanna step out
of the car...
sickie?
Well, this is all...
very sophisticated.
[POUNDING]
All right!
Hang on, Gammy!
You're gonna make it!
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
Hey, you look
a little lost.
You from
around here?
Uh, no.
You know where
you're going?
Uh, not really. My friend
was supposed to pick me up,
but I don't know
where he is.
Doesn't sound like
much of a friend.
You got any money?
Uh, no.
You wanna make some?
Okay.
Do you know how to
use a mop wringer?
Yeah. Yeah.
Why don't you
get in the car?
[DOOR BEEPING]
Hi.
These are
soft seats.
[♪]
KRUGER:
Hey, Koko.
Who's this?
Uh, this is our new
vice president of
acquisitions, sir.
So you're just hiring
new people now?
That's your job?
To hire people?
Yes?
Okay. Good enough
for me, Koko.
Ahem.
Now, what's
your name?
My name is Coco.
Coco Higgins.
Wha--
Coco?
We can't have
two Cocos.
So I guess you're back
to being George.
Well, it was a hell
of a ride.
All right.
The Grace Building.
There's a big stain
on the front.
How do we
get it off?
When I was a little girl
in Jamaica,
my Gammy taught me to take
a wet rag, and in a cir--
Ah, uh-- Uh, excuse me, uh,
Vice President Coco...
No-- No one cares
about your Gammy.
What did you say
about my Gammy?
Forget Gammy.
Who's Gammy?
There--
There's no Gammy.
Maybe there should be
a Gammy.
Oh, no.
George.
Gammy.
ALL:
Gammy! Gammy!
Gammy's
getting upset!
Gammy! Gammy!
[♪]